You see me do it like a hundred times
It you can't dodge them all
He's like he's turning oh shit. He's turning he just growled at us
He's just turning growled
Okay, I need to get my berry
Okay
Okay, I'm gonna be a best
I can't laugh at you aren't
I think I did it of course. I know the horse has a dodge. I've flicked I pressed it probably
Five thousand times in the course of the last two weeks
Ha ha ha
That was really funny. I would like to continue to play the game. That would be swell
Everyone do you growl that us?
Oh
I need to see it I have to see it
I need to see it
Is it it?
Hold on we need to watch this. I need to examine this because I don't know what the fuck I don't know what the fuck happened
Oh my god, I look like I'm weirdo.
Oh my god, dude.
What?
Why does it sound so weird?
What is it that sounds so weird?
What's wrong with this?
Why do I sound like a-is that what it sound like?
Why do I sound like a fucking cave troll?
Oh, it have a-
Doesn't sound much better.
He's like he's turning.
Oh shit, he's turning.
He just growled at us.
Oh my god, dude.
Dude, he said, Tim, the tool man.
But honestly, man, when somebody asks you, when somebody says, hey dude, you know there's a dodge in the game?
It's not bro.
Yes!
They're a fundamental part of the whole game.
Oh.
All right.
You see me do it like a hundred times
It you can't dodge them all
He's like he's turning oh shit. He's turning he just growled at us
He's just turning growled
Okay, I need to get my berry
Okay
Okay, I'm gonna be a best
I can't laugh at you aren't
I think I did it of course. I know the horse has a dodge. I've flicked I pressed it probably
Five thousand times in the course of the last two weeks
Ha ha ha
That was really funny. I would like to continue to play the game. That would be swell
Everyone do you growl that us?
If
I need to see it. I have to see it
I need to see it
Is this it? Hold on we need to watch this I need to examine this because I don't know what the fuck I don't know what the fuck happened
Oh my god, I look like I'm weirdo.
Oh my god, dude.
What?
Why does it sound so weird?
What is it that sounds so weird?
What's wrong with this?
Why do I sound like a-is that what it sound like?
Why do I sound like a fucking cave troll?
Oh, it have a-
Doesn't sound much better.
He's like he's turning.
Oh shit, he's turning.
He just growled at us.
Oh my god, dude.
Dude, he said, Tim, the tool man.
But honestly, man, when somebody asks you, when somebody says, hey dude, you know there's a dodge in the game?
It's not bro.
Yes!
They're a fundamental part of the whole game.
Oh.
All right.