Hi!
Hello, everyone. German 985 here.
Hello, everyone. German 985.
Oh, well, you can't lie to him like that.
What's up, guys?
Did anyone believe it?
No one's even here to hear it, so.
Yeah, there are like 15-20 people already here.
Oh, you're on Twitch, mother.
I am on the Twitch-itch.
Anyways, happy Saturday.
Happy Sunday if you're from a different country.
And let me show this out to people's.
Actually, I got to write, uh, app.
And they'll see.
Oh, come on.
Well, how come I can't bring up Brett, as I can app mentioned?
Maybe he blew up his Twitter.
MLC stealth.
Like, I'm not even doing you either.
What's going on here, Twitter?
Twitter, what is going on?
Why are you being like this?
I'm going to tweet, too.
You could just retweet what I tweet.
You can all tweet.
You can pick your dog.
You can tweet, I tweet, but you can't.
We all tweet for germistry.
And there we go.
With at MLs.
Okay, why that was weird.
I don't know why it didn't work before.
I wonder who that is.
And tweet.
No, no, no, tweet.
Come to it yet.
Because I need to, uh, write it.
I already tweeted.
Oh, no, it is.
Oh, no, no, no, I was talking to myself, not to you.
Like, as I was telling myself, because I was going to hit the Twitter button.
And I didn't even put like the link.
So I was like, no, no.
It has been Twittered.
And yes, it has.
And there's Twitter.
Now go to YouTube.
And post that.
And then get out of there, because it's not necessary.
And set it stream.
Which means you're going to find, okay.
Good evening.
I'm going to play some team fortress too.
And then if you guys don't know, they just put out a huge, huge CS go update.
So that should be interesting to check out for sure.
It's probably one of the big, they've added like five maps.
I would love to express my enthusiasm for that.
But the last.
I cannot.
You don't have it.
I don't have it.
No.
I'm not going to go out.
Yeah, I think they're going to release us coming soon.
I think it's coming soon.
Otherwise did the update today was pretty huge.
You know, Val, though, it's going to be months, probably.
Yeah, yeah, true.
Very true.
Good evening, everyone.
I'll give that a saying.
I bid you go tomorrow and go tidings.
So let's get rolling.
I'm else he stealth is here, but he's currently, he's currently in the bathroom.
And that's all we're going to say about that.
So let's find a server that is an empty.
Do we need to wait for him before we join a server so that he can play?
Yeah, he's going to have to deal with it.
Oh, there you go.
There he is.
Perfect timing, sir.
Thank you.
I was waiting for the right moment to enter.
And I want to see pretty good.
No, I was watching clips from the on to generous show.
Why are you doing that?
She's funny.
Sorry, I'm late.
You're supposed to be in the stream.
Now let's get into the server.
Let's try to find a 32.
Here we go.
CPU badlands.
I don't know.
I want to do CPU badlands.
This is 28.
That's two fours.
It's trading.
Oh, here we go.
This is two out of 24.
All right, you guys ready?
Not quite yet.
Oh, you better hurry up.
I'm launching it.
It's already on that screen.
It's already on screen.
I've already got Xbox connected.
My console ready to go.
Wait a couple seconds.
By the way, if you guys may,
they never will know who's stealth is,
but some people may not know who you are.
Alex got to give an introduction.
Hey guys, my name is italics.
And I make YouTube videos.
And my channel name is gamers descent,
which you may know me by instead of italics.
That is where I hail from.
Yeah, you come from the the monitoring top of gamers descent.
What time is it right now?
It is 15 after six.
If people ever just saying that.
All right, I'm ready.
What we going to say is Alex before I cut you off?
I don't.
Woo.
I don't know.
I guess to further introduce myself,
I'm a machinima realm director.
So I'm on the other side of the chasm between the two machinima mountains.
I come in peace.
Here we go.
People have already started joining.
Let's do it.
68.177.101.
It's steht et et et et et, Fen
4,
haul in 270-16.
oh I can't film me.
16, I won.
Well you better get in there.
Put TF2 Moa hunting.
TF2 Moa hunting. All you're going to do is get 25 kills in a row. That's very difficult to do in this game.
That is not an easy thing to do in Team Fortress to get more than I'd say more than 15 kills in a row. 10 kills in a row is even like a pretty big field strength.
The only one who could do it is a engineer.
Yeah, how heavy to have you can get a lot of engineer if nobody is like smart and going dimmer manner.
Oh, over medic.
I went on zero red team.
How does the game audio? Let's take a look.
That's all right.
How's the game audio guys? Good.
You're good.
I cannot tell.
Are you going to tell them what's your name is?
I think people will probably figure it out by now.
Dick Simmons, the dump champion.
Oh, where's this scout going?
It's pretty nice fire gun, dude.
Oh, I thought it was you.
Oh, watch it. Watch it.
Look up the still.
Oh, forgot fire kills me.
It's going up pretty well here.
What do I have for a melee right now?
Actually, I got the postal pommel.
Let's try and get some postal pommel.
Yeah, you know, you're not spying.
I need a medic.
Oh, that's.
Oh, yeah, we did it game over.
Did a job team.
So we can do it again.
Very cool.
Oh, we changed.
I wanted to play on upwards.
Oh, I love upward.
I love it too.
Upward is one of my favorites.
Upward.
What do we know?
My most kills is only 25 as a sniper.
I've only gotten one moeab.
I have no idea.
Oh, I thought I'm out.
Good. I love Thunderbomb.
I like the first two stages.
Thunder Mountain.
Jerma, can I be has in a hug?
If you ask him for a hug, get ready.
Internet hug.
There we are.
He, he, he, be has him in your hug.
Here we go.
He has been in.
Here comes the internet hug.
You can do it.
You just received the internet hug.
Look, worth $15.
You got hugs.
That's actually pretty good.
You've got mail.
Oh, I have a new item.
Oh, I got a new item.
I'm giving away my backpack.
I finally got some new stuff.
Why am I even running?
Waiting for players.
What are we going?
You guys, no one's got to give me stuff.
I mean, items are one thing.
I have a, a nice plan.
As you probably saw in my latest video, if you haven't,
I'm going to do a crate unboxing video.
Whatever I get in those crates,
if I get an unusual or something,
it's going to be given away.
So any unusual I get in the boxes,
is going to be given away.
And if I get strangers, they might.
I'm keeping them.
We got, we got a full server.
I will prop the 24.
Yeah, there's five spectators.
Make sure some people are kind of stuck in the spectator right now.
But the unboxing video will probably be next week, how to zoom.
I do, you share.
Take seven, the dump champion.
Yeah, that's me.
Dick Simmons, the dump champion.
Wait, did you put end quotes on that?
I think this is the parrots parentheses.
That's all, I know.
It should be on this screen.
I don't think so.
I've been wrong before though.
All right, I close my door there.
Should be as not on this stream.
Not in the chat anyway.
No, I'm not that I can see.
High five.
Frank.
Can I just kill somebody already?
We got away.
Is that a time, man?
I want to blow them underneath the fence.
Well, I ever played Don of War II.
Oh, man, I was a huge Don of War I fan.
I don't really like what they did with Don of War II.
I'm not going to lie.
Wasn't a big Don of War II person.
Oh, my God.
Oh, I forgot another shotgun.
Still pretty good.
Oh, thanks.
Covered in the G.A. Verody.
I'm going to puke as I get.
Derody makes me puke.
Oh, my God.
Derody. Get out of here.
Conqueror.
Contrary.
No.
I can't believe how many no points I got right there.
Oh, no.
Damn it.
I thought I had more rockets loaded.
SHIT.
What does that spell shoot?
Gosh darn it.
Oh, good.
That's what that spells.
Boom.
Who am I streaming with?
MLC stealth and italics.
Two pros.
We play games.
Sometimes we are special.
Sometimes we play video games.
Occasionally.
Sometimes we laugh.
Sometimes we cry.
Sometimes we share valuable moments together that make us better.
Oh, he's going to get away.
I refuse to let him get away.
He's going to get behind everybody.
He's going to get behind us all.
I think he already is.
Oh, he's gone.
Nine health and I'm jumping off of high surfaces.
Oh, hi.
I survived.
Give me that health.
Can you donate an unusual...
I thought you were about to say can you dig at the sucker?
I would rather you hang onto that.
I don't need anything.
You know, you don't have to give me stuff.
Booker tea.
Best surely an unusual.
Because an unusual is worth a lot.
And I don't want to take stuff like that from people.
So.
Oh, did I make it?
Oh, my God.
That was a good shot.
That guy caught me right when I was coming down.
Oh, I got to take off the conqueror.
Conqueror is...
Oh, man.
I'm not feeling the conqueror.
I'm not right now.
Oh, damn.
That was in the face.
Oh.
What's it?
I'm taking this off.
I'm going to put on...
What am I going to put on?
I'm going to put on the shotgun.
The strange shotgun I still have to give these away.
I have given my third...
I've given 33% of the back pack away so far.
Two more people I have to get in contact with.
And then after that, it is start all over again.
All right, I'm going medic.
Yeah, we could use...
We only got one.
Oh, actually, you are the one.
You just switched.
Actually, there's two, I think.
Are he's medicing?
Oh, we...
Oh, okay, okay, I got to see.
So, which one is Java?
I swear, it's not Dixim and the Dump Champion.
That is a spy.
Oh, no.
If I see...
Is it Uba, a charge?
What classes are you guys playing us right now?
I'm soldier.
Oh, no.
Oh, so little hell.
I am the same time.
What are my video settings on here?
I'll show you.
Video 1280 by 720, because I'm running in a window right now.
I'm going to be able to stream it.
But I play on high, high, high, simple, medium, disabled, color correction,
and then all these other things.
I don't play with anti-aliasing on.
I feel like the amount of resources it takes to the amount of gain you get is not really that noticeable.
At least in my opinion.
Is it at least for a game like this?
Oh, thank you for putting me out of fire, Tyro.
I always play with B-Sync God.
Always.
I'm changing.
I'm changing to engineer.
Do I play any commonly hated games?
Oh, backstab. Turn around, spy.
Do you guys play any commonly hated games?
Is outside our door?
Any commonly hated-cated?
I call it duty.
What would fall under that?
That's fine.
Number one right there.
Yes, stealth.
Answer it, yes.
Stealth does play commonly hated games.
Call it duty.
But like actually hated like literally bad games, I don't know.
Yeah, I don't think I play any really hated games.
Oh, there's the sniper again.
We still got a level 1 up.
Oh, I think I've had a score.
Oh, come on.
Is this guy hacking?
Come on, let me see.
I see a spy on their team running around in his taunts.
And he looks like a wax figure just moving around.
Skating around.
It's probably a glitch or something.
Yeah, I saw that earlier too.
I think it is just a glitch.
But even when he was disguised, it was just walking around.
It's like not moving.
Like arms in the air.
Oh, I got a change this.
I don't got a change that one.
You got to change it.
Oh, I got to hurry the hell up.
Oh, boy.
Do you engineer?
I was a second behind.
I threw my games off-road off now.
What is this?
Like an RTS?
I've got to catch up.
My actions permitted is only a hundred.
Let's go.
A genuine hood.
What's the best scattergun for the scout?
They're all good.
It depends on how you play stylons.
Mid-range, too long-range, use the shortstop.
Close-range, meat shots, force nature, and everything else kind of in between.
The regular scatterguns are probably the best.
At least that's kind of how I see it.
I like that one the best.
No, I got to go over here.
What am I doing?
Oh, god.
I've already spurted this up.
And I salvage this is the real question.
That's the real question.
Can I salvage this?
What am I doing?
I don't know where I want to put it.
I don't know what I want to do.
I'm so torn right now.
This guy's right here.
No, I'm putting it right here.
The limb of the limb of the limb.
That was so torn.
My brain couldn't not handle what I was just doing right here.
Oh, lord.
Oh, this is going down in two seconds.
I have absolutely...
Oh, lag.
Oh, yeah, I got that too.
Super lag.
Is that the real emulsie stealth?
I hope so.
Oh, I'm getting a lot of lag.
Thank you, Engineer, for helping me build this.
Appreciate it.
And let's reload.
Is that the real emulsie stealth?
Oh, yeah.
All right, I got some catching up to doing points.
This is kind of getting embarrassing.
Oh, my gosh.
Here comes...
Oh, there goes the dispenser.
Oh, my God.
Oh, he's up top.
Oh.
That just ruined my life.
Oh, there's that flag in.
Unmoving.
Yeah, I got him.
Or maybe you did ring too much.
We're going this.
I like this better.
I don't feel as bad when I lose all my stuff.
Oh, spy.
Doing his thing.
I think that...
Oh, my word.
He is doing his thing, isn't he?
Get away, Romani.
He's not dead.
Oh, he is not dead.
I didn't get the...
I'm going to duel with him right now.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, so I didn't get the...
I don't know, everyone.
Find him on the cart.
Oh, my God.
You're all right, Doc.
Oh, run away.
I want it up here.
They're about to get to the point.
They almost say...
Oh, crap thing.
Oh, no, no, no, where's he?
Oh, no.
Give it up.
Oh, my God, Roy.
Oh, this guy's still going to get me.
Oh, no.
Oh, I can't believe I'm still alive.
Oh, they got it.
No, I was dead.
I was toast right here.
I was toast.
Oh, I love butter toast.
What's name tag?
I think the chat...
The chat frees for anybody else.
I think the chat is for me.
Somebody has found a name tag.
What's that mean?
I don't think the chat froze.
I was looking at it and I was like, wait, no, nothing.
Oh, they're going to...
They got a heavy medic right here.
Get rid of that medic.
Oh, my God.
When all else fails, just duck and cover.
Well, I'll just fry it.
I didn't know you found that stuff though.
Didn't know you found the name tags.
I thought you had a biome.
You can find it.
No, I think.
He's in the front door.
Frasier, you can find it.
Oh, there's spies surfing around in the base.
There's two spies.
I think sitting outside our doors.
Oh, God, he's over here.
No, wait, that's not even mine.
That's not my century.
I'm really losing it here, guys.
My brain can't even handle what I'm doing.
Oh, get out of my way.
No, no, no, no.
Oh, I just barely saved that.
So many people.
So much death.
Try to get this dispenser up.
Oh, I was primed.
I know you're not dead.
He could.
Wow.
Oh, okay.
I'm going out there.
Someone's going to get toasted out there.
Oh, it's probably going to be me.
Is that you, Dick?
Was that you?
Is it just who walked right next to me?
Was that the spy?
Is that you, Richard?
Yeah, that's me.
Hello.
What are you doing, Richard?
Yeah.
Oh, get the medic.
Oh, yeah.
I went from like last place, like fourth place in one line.
Oh, my God.
What's ringing out?
That's it.
I'm just as fond.
I am.
Wow.
Hi.
What happened?
Hold on, hold on.
That's going to be cool.
Sorry, I was talking to my man.
I'm going to get back to that.
That's a spy.
No.
Oh.
Well, shoot.
God.
Oh, God.
There we go.
This is what I'm talking about.
Ow.
What the fuck?
I'm on the scoreboard, boys.
I have faith in your German.
I wonder if I will play, you think, uh, I read it.
I wonder if German is nice.
What the hell was that?
Just give a nice gun in place, but at the end of that hallway right there.
Yeah, I'm trying to, I can turn it.
I keep destroying it.
I got some people that know what they're doing.
I probably will play zombie fortress at some point.
Probably not tonight, though.
What?
Zombie fortress.
I'm just going into punches.
I don't even care.
Room my knockin' out with one punch.
I'm just going to get a punch.
You're getting knocked out, run up, oh!
Oh, come on, feel the pain.
Feel it.
I would've killed them, too.
Oh, fuck, let's try, let's get one shot.
Uh, just set the next level to where we're going.
We're changing server after this, anyway, so.
Oh.
Alright.
Well, that answers that question.
We're changing server.
Just to...
People want to know, Jerma, what is zombie fortress?
I, uh, I don't know.
I think it's like kind of like...
Oh my god.
Everybody plays as...
Oh, I think everyone has melee except for a small group of people.
Somebody explain it.
Oh, so it's like infection on Halo.
Hey, you're not me.
Or whatever that game mode's called.
I think I know what you're talking about.
Yeah, it's like...
It's kind of like a zombie mode where everyone runs around with melee except for the small group of people that don't have...
They're like the not zombies.
If I'm wrong, somebody please correct me in the chat because I know it's something like that though.
That's probably right.
Somebody said it's like Halo infection.
Watch out for spies.
Oh, they got taken out everything.
I got to be a little bit sneakier with these centers.
And that's going to blow up and kill me.
And that's going to die.
I said, alright.
I'm going, I'm going to go.
I'm going to S.
How are you playing S. Heavy?
I am playing S. Heavy.
See, Scout is what I rage quit as.
I like to run around.
I start his scout and then I'm like, okay, I suck.
Moving on to the heavy where I can actually kill people.
I like this setup.
I'll stick with this.
Whoa, I heard it backstabbed.
I'm standing in the corner.
Oh, God.
Oh, I don't think he's dead.
Maybe he is.
Man, we don't have any engineers do we?
Oh, my.
Wait, what just happened to me?
What just even happened?
I got headshot from across the map.
Oh, my God.
Oh, no, I just struck this.
We're about to lose.
Yeah, there's two spies on the point.
Oh, the car.
We lost.
What are you guys going to get like a second spies?
How many spies are on that damn team?
All right, new new server.
Not GG.
New S EV, RVV RV.
Let's go to.
Actually, hold on.
I'm going to screen's going to go black for one second.
Because I'm going to change.
Then it's changed something real quick.
Well, you do that.
I'll be RV for about 10 seconds.
I'm going to see what my parents want.
Well, because for some reason, when I was doing exploit in the game mode,
it was lagging my game a lot.
I don't know why.
Sometimes I guess it does that.
Yeah, are you using like the screen area or the other one?
I was doing the game source.
That was like lagging my game sort of.
All right, try screen area.
I just did not change it over.
I'm going to be like the release.
All right, let's go to.
You got to be some fun too.
You got a dust fall.
High tower.
Hopefully stealth gets back soon.
Otherwise, he's going to be in trouble.
To delay for him when we were doing the test streaming,
I was using game source and it was working fine.
So it just seems like on again, off again.
Very hit or miss.
That's all I got still.
That's all I got.
That's your only, uh, that's my only delay.
All right.
That's better.
Oh, it's so Joe.
How things going over here today?
Here we go.
I'm from pasting it.
Video and a stream.
Just ballin' like a YouTuber does.
Ballin' straight ballin'.
All right, stealth really, that's all I got.
Now, now we're never man.
All right, 68.
Dot 232.
Dot 177.
Dot 105.
Callin' 27015.
Sorry, stealth, you weren't here.
But you missed out.
That's the IP.
Those of you are wondering.
I hear somebody like here talking.
Oh, is it?
No, he's not making it.
There's no way he makes it.
Hey, there's no way you make it.
I was gonna say, ask some bad news, bears.
Dinner is ready with my parents.
I was gonna probably go eat that with all my stuff.
Dinner?
Well, it on like throw me out as a son.
All right, well, yeah, see you later, dude.
Thanks for coming.
Do you have no problem?
I'm gonna miss you, buddy.
Make sure you signify to this frame.
Is that gonna miss you?
Oh, by screen.
Thanks for having me.
See you guys later.
All right, I missed you guys.
Oh, I'm the host of the call.
I'll just mute myself.
Oh, are you really?
Just mute your...
Yeah, now who should have hosted?
Burbe?
Yeah, I know.
Well, the good thing I missed that,
so I can do it again and miss it again.
I will play until you decide that you wanna play a CSGO.
Then I will bow out as well.
Yeah, thanks for sticking around it.
Oh!
Tell my wife or is it hello?
Hello, wife.
On the stream?
Was that a stream comment?
Yeah, I guess.
Why, stealth, why?
Stealth, how could you be so inconsiderate?
Wow.
Oh, there's a lot of spice.
I just wanna fly a hundred feet in the air.
That's off to the spryme.
He doesn't mess around.
I'm running away.
I'm running into spawn.
You can't get me a spawn.
Sorry.
Text message.
Do you ever have a problem where like you hit Am or something
to change your loadout and then it opens like the options menu?
It does that sometimes, you know.
Just curious.
That is an issue and now I'm gonna die right here.
That is an issue so I should get a tissue.
You know what?
I'm gonna go straight up.
It's my fault.
No.
Yes.
I'm trying, Piro, but I'm not having a great luck right now.
Oh my god.
What is going on with the avatars?
What the hell is going on?
Why is everybody like a pony?
Wait, what?
Hold down tab for a second here.
Yeah.
Is every single avatar a pony for you?
No.
I can keep mine in yours.
Why?
What?
That's all I can see.
Well, that's a...
I have no idea.
Oh my god.
Everyone else in the street can see yours though.
I guess that's good.
Man, no one has pushed our cart past the like spawn area here.
I cannot even hit this person.
There we go.
We are getting absolutely dominated.
They are already going up the track.
Where is this pyrrole?
Oh my god, I'm doing so awful.
Oh my goodness.
No.
Medic stay alive.
Stay alive.
Well,
Medic.
Alright, let's get on this cart.
Let's do this.
Alright, for some reason no one ever wants to go heavy.
I guess we'll get back stabbed all the time.
Does that cart really all the way over there?
Oh my god.
Come on, come at me.
Do you have the cart all the way at that last point?
Are you kidding me?
Holy crap.
Yeah, that was kind of what I was thinking.
How the hell did they get that there?
How the hell did they get there?
Oh, I'm hearing my scream.
Oh, I have to turn this off.
Whoops.
Yeah, that's, wow.
Blue team.
Bravo.
My god.
Look at this insanity going on here.
What is?
Wow.
There was a spy idling in a corner.
And we were sitting there pummeling him for about 10 seconds.
They're going to must have two scouts on the cart.
Get them.
Oh, come on.
That's it.
We lost.
That is game over right there.
I can't.
I can't get them.
Oh, no.
Nope.
That's not game over.
What do I do?
Let's push the car people.
Get on that, god.
All right.
I am as paranoid as you could possibly be right now.
And you know what?
I was literally turning around to check first by behind me and he got me.
Like, my brain was telling my mouse to do that.
And like, I got back.
That's why I went pyro.
I'm just like spraying everywhere.
I was just watching you do that.
All right.
Paranoid.
What's up, guys?
You know, I'm standing up with you.
And again, with the spy.
Even though I'm a pyro, I've got back to have again.
Oh, my god.
People are just everywhere.
I love their message.
They're going to get it.
All right.
I'm playing that right now.
You're playing as a heavy.
Heavy.
Oh, where are we?
Six shot.
Wherever that was.
That got that scout off.
German.
Do you love me?
Now that I can't dance.
That's a song, right?
Yeah.
I would sing it in the shower.
Let's do it.
I'm not going to do the uncrading tonight.
I'm going to be doing.
That's going to be in a live calm, just a straight-up video.
Probably next week.
You.
Get out of here.
You're not dead.
I know you're not dead.
I'm jumping away.
Yeah.
Get away from me.
I need help.
Oh, do I get help?
Or do I spy-check everybody in my team?
Whatever works.
I see you up here, spy.
You little sniper.
You crazy little sniper.
Yep.
Nice try on your stair step, but it didn't work.
Did it?
No, that was not spy.
That got-
Oh, God.
Where's the other guy?
Oh, my God.
Where is the other guy?
No more heavy.
I'm going to go heavy.
I'm staying heavy.
Up there all on the-
They're all on the carto-
Oh, this is me, Robo.
Oh, my God.
Did that pyro?
I just went to a side pyro on them.
I got at least one, I think.
I got to eat this so I can run fast.
Oh, they're going.
They're almost there.
They're going to get it.
So that means I can run away, because I just took this-
There's three people on it?
Oh, they're definitely going to get it.
Yeah.
See how fast I'm running?
You won't get the satisfaction of killing me.
Actually, he kind of did.
He kind of did get the satisfaction of killing me.
Too late.
I am good.
No, I have to-
Oh, do I go medic?
I'm going to wreck sniper.
I'm still too paranoid, man.
I'm just like-
I'm spraying inside the spawn area.
That's how paranoid I am.
Now that's paranoid for you.
Oh, they all blew up.
You are RS5.
No, you're not.
Apparently I am dueling.
Bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum.
Damn.
Oh, what?
I don't even know what just happened.
I was like checking around too.
I'm going medic.
It's the best thing to do right now.
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow.
Spy?
I'm just going to go kill bot medic.
And I can make sure everyone stays alive.
I'm going to have my back turn the entire time.
Do it, man.
The entire time.
We have like-
Oh, we have two pirates on the team right now.
We have like three earlier.
People were just so paranoid.
Oh, you get caught up here.
Oh, god.
And there's another spy.
God, run away.
Help me. Somebody help me.
Stay safe.
Stay close to the blue red.
I can't live it and hit him.
Oh, he's going to kill me.
Oh, my god.
I'm a lucky son of a bitch.
I'm-
I got to run away.
I am on.
What do you say?
Oh, shit.
I didn't want to do that.
Oh, god.
I just like traded with somebody.
Dude, no one is pushing our cart, including myself.
Oh, I'm going to love a god.
It's still like right there.
He's still right there.
Right there, it's fun, man.
Actually, to be quite honest with you, that was the most success I've had all game.
It's with that medic.
And I healed like two people.
Medic.
All right, I'll get another medic.
Ah!
Ah, still a side medic.
Oh, this guy is toast.
Oh, what would be the guy behind me?
Switch.
Oh, you'll see how much spies are on their team.
Just account.
It's got to be at least three.
It's got to be.
If it's not, then I'm wrong.
I need to do it.
I need to take up the grid screen.
Quick fix.
No trades.
I don't take the trades right now.
That was a terrible scar.
That was supposed to be a Scottish accent, guys.
How terrible was that?
That's a spy.
I am certain of this.
No, I guess I'm wrong.
Oh, barely got me.
And I'm like getting people killed because I'm checking for this fucker.
Did I just heal this fight?
No, I didn't.
No way.
Dude, we've got four pyros on our team now.
The people they are listening, they're like,
enough of this nonsense.
We have like getting shot from.
I don't even know where they're coming from.
It's almost like they're coming out of our spawn.
I'm going pyro on easy mode right here.
I've got like the back burner, so I don't even have to think.
I'm just like, spray.
I'm trying to use the, uh, the quick fix.
You know, I'm going to heal you.
We're just going to run like the dickens.
Uh-oh, run away.
Look at all the, what?
Those are all spies.
At least, oh my god, this is the worst thing ever.
Oh my god, chaos.
Run.
Oh my god.
Dude, you run against like the same heavy.
I'm put, I got a, I'm playing spy.
We are trapped in this spawn area right now.
Where are you coming out from?
Left, right or center?
I keep going out because I'm a medic, so I'm trying to go out of the middle.
God, somebody just killed me so I can just get a back stab and feel good about myself.
Look at this.
Look at this K-Goth.
You got to be S.
I can't even say it.
I'm so upset.
Alright, let's make, let's make some statues.
Oh my god, I'm on like your team.
Oh great, now he knows I'm a spy.
Oh jeez.
Oh my god, I'm, I'm, I can't get out of spawn either, man.
This is using the Infos or the kill people.
As soon as I said there were four pyros, everyone switched back on our team.
Look at all those, oh man, I got blasted right there.
Alright, after this we're going to another server.
Because we need to scramble these teams.
They've got a Century gun right next to our cart.
Really?
That's not cool.
Hey, you know what's the note I got?
What do you have?
What you got?
No.
And they're already winning again.
Oh god, no, no please no.
All these ponies.
You know what, when all else fails, you just go.
What do you choose at least two people idling?
Well, at least when all else fails, you go straight up them on night.
And if that don't work, I just speaking of the good night.
More gone.
That's what I just went.
Oh my god, I'm just doing good.
I just charged out of spawn and I flew like 5,000 people.
Come on, last, get them, get them, get them, get them up to you.
And he did it.
He's a champion.
Alright, this is going to be a spire right here.
Get out of town.
I got one of the spots.
Oh my god, no.
Server change.
It's time to change service.
Let's go to, I want to go two weeks.
A server we can win on.
Well, I'm just kidding.
I want to go to my server.
I want to go to a board rush.
Are you ready?
Yes.
So, what's going on here?
It's going to be on my server.
1, 4, 6,
1, 8.
Call on 2, 7, 0, 1, 5.
Go!
You almost lost me on the colon, but I think I got it.
Goal then, 2, 7, 0, 1, 5.
1, 2, 7, 0, 5, 7.
to
the
allows
to
the
Yeah, but still.
There's somebody out there with this ridiculous internet speeds.
Yeah, and I can just, I can just come right in.
Pipeline payload.
Yes, Strangeloves, that this is a talix plane.
You are correct.
Hey guys, hey Strangeloves, how's it going?
So this is the server?
Wait, did that, what? Wait, hold on a second.
Did that already fill up?
We already full.
I didn't, oh, somebody else put it in.
Okay, thank you to whoever put that in.
Thank you. I appreciate it.
I thought you didn't join.
That's what I thought at first.
Oh God, this is like a jellyfish server.
What?
Like the screen is motor like a jellyfish for me right now.
Look at how laggy everybody is.
Look at this.
I feel like it's like, oh my god, look at this claymation server.
Look at that.
Hey, let me see.
Well, oh, look at that pings.
My goodness gracious.
Everyone except for me and you is like 100 plus.
It really looks like a stop motion animation.
Like, video.
I feel like.
I feel like I'm playing at 20 frames per second.
But I'm not.
Oh, I'm sorry guys.
Look, we got to change again because this is just bad.
All right, this is not this is not against the people who are here.
This is one of the people who didn't get in.
Yeah, it's right.
It tells you you can look at the stream and see what I see right now.
It is like.
It is pretty much like I'm watching a cartoon on drugs.
All right, well, yeah, looks like nobody could even get into this one.
There was only seven on eight.
I apologize.
I sorry.
New server.
Take three.
Yeah, third time's a charm.
Third time.
How one?
Two.
Three.
Crunch.
So wait till I get my third time.
I'm probably going to go 32 person server.
I'm going to hope I can.
But wait till I get that server.
We'll be okay.
I want to server all the cool kids have one.
All right, here we go.
66.55.154.
Don't two, three, four.
Call in 27015.
And we paste this in.
And a second once we get in.
I do apologize that we have to do this twice.
That was the third time.
Hopefully this one is going to be the good one.
They pasted it in already.
Did it really?
It told you it was like literally two seconds after you said it.
I saw it pop up in the chat.
You guys are fast.
Lighting fast, even.
You might say.
You can say that.
Bam.
Oh, oh.
I am going demo night.
I actually found.
Oh, sorry.
What?
I said demo.
I was just re-language.
I actually found a salt and ceremonial the other day.
Oh.
I was very happy about that.
Very cool.
So now I can have a legit demo night if I wanted to give up my grenade launcher.
It's a tough call for the booties.
Yeah.
Booties.
And then we got Stimidae here.
With this wicked sick hat.
So I have to do this right now.
Because somebody keeps sending me a very inappropriate message.
And hopefully that stops that from happening.
I don't think it will, but I at least tried.
Oh.
Okay.
All right.
We got a full serving now.
Good to go.
Come back.
Just in time.
But it's on the real way.
Like everyone.
Oh, so over at the same time.
Oh, my God.
You just totally predicted.
Where I was going to shoot.
Shotguns, soldier.
Oh, my God.
Did you see that?
Yeah, yeah.
I've loved it one night.
Yeah, I've only so far given one third.
I'm still waiting on two people.
So eventually I will be giving 100%.
But I have to wait for the other two people to get back to me.
I'm going to get back to the other two people.
Oh, that hurt.
Oh, dear.
I made quite a mess.
Someone on the team was announcing how many spies they have.
They have four, apparently.
I want a good trader.
He is.
How ironic is that?
So he's a double spy.
Yeah, so he's telling us about spies.
So he's spying on the spies for his own spies.
As someone in the comments will end up in the comments.
He's spying on the spies.
Yeah, that is absolutely what it is.
Oh, no, Paul, this may be his wife.
Maybe he's a triple spy.
He said, I serve no one.
The CIA, don't trust anyone.
I like your attitude.
And that's his wife and he's stired.
He's going to get ugly.
He's going to try and stare stabbing.
I already know this.
I know this.
I already know this. I already know this. I've been around the block a few times.
You know what? You, oh no, I'm gonna stand right here. You're gonna have to go that way.
Oh god. Oh no.
Oh!
Let's see where...
On the oldened time. Oh, we got, we got the bluebird pyro going down here. Oh my god.
Well you just die your pyro. What am I doing?
Well they're almost there man. They're right at the edge with seven minutes and 40 seconds to go. We can do this.
Oh come on I would have had it. I would have had it.
I would have had it. I would have been sarcastic by the way. I had no faith.
I don't even know if that's how you spell it but that's what I'm doing.
I love how the highest score scoring player on our team is four points and was like a four-way tie for four.
Me included.
Yeah, yeah, four, four, four, four, four, three.
Boom!
I don't scramble in the teams. Well that's one way to do it.
Whoa! All right so this is, oh goodbye. Wait.
Are you changing your name? Yeah I did.
Did you guess who I am?
Well I...
Yeah it's not hard. Yes because I can see your icon.
Henderson in corporate.
We sell carpets and we do floor finishing.
Where do you come up with your name? You just look at something and say okay I'm gonna take that.
Kind of. It's just whatever is in my brain at that particular second is what it is.
Oh I tried to high five.
So this is gonna be the last round of TF2 and then I'm gonna move on to CS. Go for a little bit.
I gotta make a count then. Oh then you have it right?
I don't have CS go. Oh damn.
That's what I was saying. I'm gonna have to bow out when you switch games.
Let's go. I mean we've been playing for about an hour or something.
Still, still has it but he... Yeah he's... I mean if you need the eat I mean
he's eating macaroni and cheese and like dog food and whatever he eats.
Dude I don't... You're making me hungry man.
macaroni and cheese and dog food. Come on.
Oh that's delicacy. Watch out Uber. I don't think I'm right up the door.
Oh my god that guy just killed every single person in here.
So stealth must be watching the stream.
Why is he responding?
I don't know. Scrains left your cities here. He's in here.
Oh my god. He's eating cheese. Watch the nit at the tape.
It's his parents. Imagine he just has like his laptop out.
I should have done the buff banner. I really should have.
I gotta kill that medic.
Ah.
Oh man.
I can't talk about...
Oh that would have been cool if I had that go off.
Just get the teleport and the telecaribot.
You should be on the winning team now maybe.
Oh don't hit my medic you bastards.
I can't believe they haven't turned around.
How? I just did two crits and I'm hitting my own teammate.
What the hell is going on?
Dude I just planted like six hits into this guy.
Holy crap.
That was ridiculous. I've never seen that happen before.
Both hammering on the same guy.
Oh guys.
Are we got a crit screen now?
We got a crit screen now.
Oh man.
Oh there's four demo man.
I'm demo man.
I think no wonder.
I just like save that demo man's life.
But not really.
Alright push it push it.
Oh push it.
No.
This is a really bad idea.
I just ran around and spawned.
Maybe not.
Come on.
Oh come on.
No.
Oh that is a sad face indeed.
That is a sad face indeed.
Could have had an explosion kill.
Could have what a shudder.
What it didn't have.
I'm trying my hand.
Oh you guys are about to win.
You got like three pyros back here.
Just camping our spawn hard core.
Really?
Oh man never run.
Yeah.
Cool.
Let's do some crazy rocket jumps.
Here we come.
Rocket jump.
I think I got like one kill.
Dude I've been doing I've been doing jump maps.
See we go.
I did some jump maps.
I know what I'm doing.
Alright.
Somebody in the street said
germa plays play tribes of sinned.
That's what they said.
I'm not making that up.
Um I see I see people say that.
Um what
CSGO just had a big huge crazy update.
I want to check that out.
Five.
But to answer your questions in the comments
tribes of sin is free to play.
So it is.
And it's now totally open.
It's not in beta anymore.
It is out now.
Yeah it's out.
It's been released.
It is fun.
So that's uh I'm going to move on from TF2 now.
Played upon an hour of TF2.
So before I go I have to do something good.
I have to do something just stupid.
And just TF2.
Here we go.
Let's go uh place 5.
And I'm going to just.
This is this is the goal here guys.
The goal is to try and blend in with the other team.
So it's going to be hard to people are watching the stream.
But this could be interesting.
I want to try doing this at least once.
Why is there a floating scout stuff here?
Oh no I'm just the high five.
So the goal here is to try and blend in.
Let's see how well I do.
Let's see how well I do here.
All right we're going to stop them.
Come on get them.
Oh my god they're coming the car is upside down.
What the hell is going on with that car?
It is a thing.
Come on we must get them.
All right.
Oh no here they come they're coming out of the right door now.
Blue team.
That's.
No I'm gonna oh you figure me out.
That guy no he didn't see me.
Okay I just got to build my stuff right here.
Just got to build some stuff.
I'm trying to build my uh my teleporter.
My century adds all good stuff.
Let me just uh build that up.
Thank you for the overhealed by the way.
Oh I'm a fake.
It's got you.
I got you.
Oh my god.
Oh I'm gonna get back to my post.
These bastards they ruined everything.
No please don't get me.
Oh my god I gotta get back to my century.
We're gonna if I gotta build my century.
Oh that is that's me right there.
Okay cool.
Uh sniper.
And there we go.
I'm gonna snipe.
All right let me get back to my sniping post.
All right here we go.
Just sniping.
Now the enemy team is coming out here.
Watch out guys.
Be careful.
Now let me snipe with you.
Oh god who's the real one?
We're standing right next to each other.
Oh you got me.
Shit.
Oh you ruined my fun.
That's what I get angry.
And die.
Oh all right that's uh that's gonna be actually out of run via the roundout.
I can't stop.
Why not?
It's disguised as an enemy sniper.
That's the best way to do it.
And then just sit in the corner and be like oh sniper.
Oh I was trying to get the three hits uh
crit with the gun slinger.
Almost got it.
Uh it's really satisfying.
Oh damn it.
Oh he didn't get me.
Uh huh uh huh.
Oh come on come on.
No no okay good good good.
All right let me get my sniping skills.
I found an ambassador.
I still don't have an unfortunate.
Really difficult.
Oh come on.
I'm just trying to snipe.
All right if you guys don't sub spam and chat about or blocking some people.
No they got it.
They found me out again.
Oh we get the wrath of the mod coming down.
Uh huh.
All right this is my last life.
Then I'm moving on to uh counter
Stephenson.
Great opportunity.
Backstab.
I'm gonna tell you how yeah I'm taking the teleporter as a spy.
At level two I'm a real bad bastard.
I'm a real bastard.
Look at this.
Level two teleporter and I'm taking it as a spy.
What a jerk.
I wonder if I can uh just kill people up from up here.
Oh for the love of god.
I just can't get the melee.
Oh well that's the last one.
Like the worst engineer ever.
How come I can't spray my spray?
That's not cool.
Yeah I don't have a spray.
I need to I need a cool one.
I am going to change to saw CS go.
After I swing it this guy over and over again.
So always one more life.
Yeah this is really the last life.
I'm not this is not a joke.
No more no jokes.
This is the last one.
Yeah.
I have to backstab at least one person and that's not the guy apparently.
And that's not the guy either.
It's going to be not that guy.
It's what's what's what's.
Now I can't backstab anybody.
Oh minus will pretend.
Oh let me do that pretender I am.
Come on get that knife.
Oh my god.
Well that's the end for me.
Oh thanks for playing guys.
Tf2.
I'm going to move on to some stuff.
Yep it's a go go.
You're full of fun losing every round.
I'm the only comment denominator here so I take full responsibility for that.
I've been on every losing team so far.
My bad guys.
My bad.
Well at least at least you got
play on the crazy teams that were getting beat.
Oh my goodness.
That was uh you were reaching for that one.
That really was actually I was doing two things at once and my brain was kind of like wait where am I?
Oh yeah I'm streaming I forgot.
So I'll probably play like maybe three two or three rounds of csgo just to check out the new update
because I wanted to check it out.
So screen is going to go black in a second here.
And yeah thank you for coming if you just came for the Tf2.
If you're sticking around with the csgo then it's going to happen in like four seconds.
Well not really but you get the idea.
The screen is going to go black in second.
Screen is totally not black bro.
Oh no there goes.
No it's black.
No it's not.
No it's no oh no that's wrong because I did screen region.
I pulled up the screen region.
Now it should be all screwed up.
Probably hear the sound though.
Get it into window mode.
Jeez okay anyways guys it's been fun.
Thanks for owning me time and time again.
How I get my kicks.
Well I'm just kidding it was a lot of fun.
And enjoy csgo.
I will catch you guys later.
Thanks for coming to me.
Always a pleasure.
Let's get the screen region that.
And huh okay let's play a couple rounds.
Let's see what they did.
Huge updates.
Let's find out exactly what they did in this update.
Have I ever I've I've watched South Park?
I used to love South Park back in the day.
It was one of my favorite shows.
That's right they did add a server bracket.
I gotta check that out.
If I can even get in here.
Still searching huh.
Let's try this again.
Find the game.
There we go.
Retreating data.
Yeah probably only gonna play maybe two or three rounds.
Maybe 10-20 minutes or so.
I just want to check out the new update in the honest.
Okay so this is the new map.
No maybe this is not one of the new maps.
Is it?
I think I've already seen I've already seen.
No maybe not.
Maybe it is a different map.
We'll find out.
Oh wait.
Oh try to pick up a headshot.
Damn.
So this is one of the new maps safehouse.
There are already is another one like this.
Isn't there?
This game is not free to play.
It is in beta right now.
It's in closed beta.
All right I gotta stay alive next time.
The most screwing around.
And the terror is one.
Will they be punched in pie?
You know what?
I can't we can't buy.
Why can we not buy items?
I thought that's what it said you could do.
I'm gonna go around this way.
Let's see if I can pull something off here.
No I don't want to climb up there.
That's a bad idea.
No I just saw somebody.
There we go.
Oh I'm dead.
Nope.
Oh god.
Behind me.
He's behind me.
He's down.
Bomb's down here.
What you got?
It's only one of them left.
No that's a teammate.
There he is.
Henderson incorporated but most eliminations.
I forgot my name was Henderson incorporated.
The clickety-clack.
Now this game will do that.
You'll get a big clickety-clack.
I'm gonna somebody pop there.
I have any grades.
No nobody nobody.
Oh my god I'm getting stuck.
Get stuck.
This is right here.
Whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa.
Let's move uh.
You guys hanging out of a window.
What a creep.
That guy was legit like floating out of the window.
I want to do a different gun.
I don't like this gun.
Auto is upstairs right now.
He is uh.
I think he's created in the kitchen to be honest.
Because he's uh he's a wild dog.
Somebody kill somebody.
Who's auto?
Auto is my uh my little doxan chihuahua
double-man-pinter breed thing.
He's a real cutie.
I don't play League of Legends.
It's too much for my brain to handle.
I feel the same way about League as I do about Starcraft.
And that is this already damn it.
Oh no I got to sit here forever.
I feel the same way about League as I do Starcraft.
The Starcraft is
everyone's just really really good.
And to be able to play that game you have to also be really really good.
Yeah I probably won't be playing that game anytime soon.
Well this is I don't want to just sit here.
I'm going to play a gun game after next round.
Because gun game is more action.
And I can actually pretty good at gun game.
See this game won't I'm not that good at.
Like the general CS go.
I'm not that good at you know what we're going to go play gun game right now.
It's a tomato.
Find a game.
Arms race.
You don't matter which one that's going to play it.
It's not gun game.
It sure is.
Gun game.
Oh I mean arms race is the technical term for it.
I love this map.
It's so interesting.
You heard I like it.
Oh I love the girl is man.
Favorite bands.
Not far.
From behind.
Ah.
He's right here.
Finally moving on moving on in the world.
Now where is he?
Oh there's too many of them.
Damn it.
Yeah keep in mind I'm playing this in a window like half the size of my computer screen.
So it can be kind of difficult to play this game.
How many?
Bolks doesn't take.
No I don't want to do that.
Oh.
Wait I got it.
Oh damn.
Yeah.
Yeah I wish my computer was good enough to play games in full screen and stream them.
But it is almost impossible to do that.
And I am getting destroyed.
My god.
The whole team is like 18 and 14 and.
I'm going this way.
I'm going to get out of town.
Damn it.
Hmm.
Give me that headshot.
God damn.
Yeah it's not my internet.
It's my computer just probably would not be able to handle it.
And I guess internet too.
To stream at like 1080 or 720 it takes a lot of bandwidth so.
Oh.
Oh what was I doing?
This potentially is the worst time like the worst game I've ever had in this entire game.
Like ever.
Haha.
It's making me look embarrassed.
No I don't care.
I'm just playing for fun.
I just want to check out the new stuff.
My favorite guerrillas song is probably Stylo.
I love Stylo.
Where is he?
I don't even know what that guy even was.
Ow.
Oh.
Okay let's get a string of people together here.
Let's get a string of people together.
Now it's over to God.
Oh.
715.
Flip that score around and you got a great score.
All right this time it's going to be different.
The standard will be different.
You need to pray to the Bruins.
All powerful Bruins gods.
Please shine upon me your strength.
Let's see I got this.
My sensitivity might be wrong.
No it's not.
That's an excuse.
There we go.
Let's keep the ball rolling here.
We got Mersey.
Up top.
Oh boy.
Now get away.
Get away.
Oh damn wow.
When did he come from?
I don't know.
Where did that do would come from?
Ah going for the headshots.
Not getting them.
There we go.
Ah.
PP90M1.
I think that's what I just had.
This is the shoot guns.
Oh now I can't go that way.
I'm going to wrap around this way.
Oh how does he not die?
Look at his health.
What did I even hit him with?
Like a sock?
I don't know.
I don't understand.
That guy had like 80% health.
And I hit him with like a wet sock apparently.
Geez my god.
That's insta death every single time.
No, no that guy's that guy was invincible.
How is that guy just invincible?
Somebody explained that to me.
No that's not you.
There we go.
Get out of it.
Oh no.
I'm going to die.
Invincible.
Unpredictable.
Somebody up top?
See buddy where they spawn.
Where the hell are you guys?
I just puke in my mouth.
Pue, pu, pu.
No.
How come I'm going to go across the map?
They just spawned over here.
Get my face in your face.
Get out of here.
Oh come on.
This guy's 20 and 9 right now.
My god.
What?
Man.
That's too many of them.
I at least want to be number one on the team.
Ow.
Get out.
Stop puking.
That's a compile.
Ow.
I at least want to go positive.
That's all I care about.
It's going positive.
Oh god.
I'm being freaking out right now.
Ah.
This guy's going to get a 9-level in two seconds.
To me, it's gold.
Ah.
Oh it hurts to die in this game.
Where is everybody?
That did not kill that guy?
Oh my god.
Spawning right next to me.
Ah.
Spawns are wacky in this game.
People just appear next to you.
Look at that.
Hmm.
Light machine guns.
Now come on.
No, somebody lost.