Do do do do do do do do do do do do do do?!"
Do do do do do do do do do do do do!
Oh, I can hear myself!
Gotta change that.
Oh, I can hear myself.
What's going on, guys?
Uh-uh.
How is your Saturday going?
Or potentially Sunday if you're from a different country?
Oh, I got it.
I'll save that for a second here. Hold on.
Okay, okay.
This is a little smaller on the right, are you?
So I'm trying something a little different.
And I am trying a...
I bought X-plit.
So I have X-plit here and I'm trying a few things.
I'm doing the capture source.
I'm not doing the screen region.
So it's probably going to be a little different or at least on your end it'll look the same on mine.
And it's going to be a little bit different.
All right.
Let me shot this out.
Twitter already had a pre-done.
Don't worry. It's all pre-done.
And is that?
And close that window.
I got to do the YouTube one.
Over the hack that is.
There it is.
Try and just hand-mood.
Post.
Okay.
Close that window.
And then I got this to do.
All right.
We're in business.
Let's get in here now.
So for those of you wondering.
I'm going to...
This is going to be uploaded to YouTube after this.
Probably what I'm going to start doing until YouTube gets its act together.
Because the last time I shot this,
I was like,
I'm going to be like,
because the last time I streamed on YouTube,
last couple times I streamed on YouTube,
it was...
wasn't pretty.
There's a lot of problems, so...
maybe I'll try doing YouTube next week or something like that.
I'm not sure,
but this will be up on YouTube.
This whole thing.
All right.
Refresh again,
because I didn't check that.
Where from Massachusetts am I from?
I am from Boston.
I guess I'm not really from Boston.
I'm kind of from a suburb of Boston,
but I'm close enough where I can say I'm from Boston, I guess.
Let's get a zero out of...
let's try 24.
Any zero out of 32?
There is.
All right.
How about this one?
Here's the IP.
I know what Reading is.
I have family members in Reading.
That's pretty cool.
All right.
The IP is going in the chat right now.
Make sure I get in there first, and there you go.
What's going on, guys?
Bad water basin.
Let's fill this server up, huh?
Come on.
Let's go.
I don't got a whole day.
Who am I kidding?
I got plenty of time.
I get all the time in the world.
That's not really that true, but...
Zero out of zero.
Where is everybody?
I'm the only person that gives a right server.
I think I did, didn't I?
Hope I did.
I hope I came to the right server.
Make sure I did.
This is the one, right?
Yeah, okay.
Copy.
Yeah, I'm going to put it in there again, just in case.
Just in case.
All right.
It looks like that was the right server.
Who's the hope so?
I'll let you one fire.
Okay.
Cool.
I like your hat.
Nimbly, you get a cool hat.
First time in my stream, because you have six hours ahead.
It is late for you.
You are late, dweller.
Oh, that guy's lagging.
I don't want to kill him.
I feel bad.
That guy was like slow-botion.
Got my lemonade over here on the left.
It has been really nice out.
I don't know what it's been like for you guys.
But my goodness, it has been so beautiful out here lately.
It's been 75 degrees, 80 degrees, every single day.
And I've been going outside a lot.
I've been taking my new dog for walks.
You know that, Dale.
Oh, I actually killed him.
Oh, that's a, that's why.
Oh, nice shot, dude.
Nice shooting text.
Funny spots.
Alright, let me go out here.
Yo, boy.
Ooh, good dodging.
Jump into it.
Damn.
How long is streaming going?
I just started.
Literally just started like five minutes ago.
Oh, boy, that's dead.
Oh, come on.
Piro versus piro.
Oh, I didn't kill him.
Oh, I thought he was going to go to the...
I'm going to die.
He knows how much health I have.
Oh, run away.
Dead.
Aqua fire 102.
What's up, dude?
No demo man, no, I'll change this stuff.
Oh, by the way, if anybody has noticed,
I'm not sure if you've noticed.
Oh, God, that's great again.
But my, I changed my FOV.
I made it bigger.
I'll show you what I did.
I didn't make it too huge, but here's my FOV now.
I changed it to like...
Like 30% more, and I made my weapon view model like 30% more.
So if you've noticed that, I know a lot of people are saying,
please change that.
So I did.
It actually is a little bit better.
Easier to see things.
I got a healer now, alright.
Okay, he's got a buff.
Oh, I didn't kill him.
He walks right over and too.
What did he come from?
What did he even come from?
Was he the medic?
No, the medic was healing me.
Like, the medic behind me was healing me.
He just came out of legit nowhere.
Dear ENGY, I saft your centuries.
See you again soon, walled spy.
Spray over.
That's a nice spray though.
That's how he gets in here.
He's the light still alive.
Don't let him get me.
Oh, he's got nowhere to go now.
How did he get that?
He's gonna get me.
He's doing a side stab.
I'm not gonna move.
Yeah.
There we go.
Dear ENGY, I saft your century.
Oh, and I'll move that.
That's me.
Yeah.
Now we got to...
We're getting rolled right now.
Oh my god, I haven't done anything.
I wonder why I would have one kill?
Oh, you're making me waste my stuff scout.
Oh, come on.
How did I not hit him?
That's...
Get him out of here.
He's not dead.
He is not dead.
He is definitely still alive.
Alright, let's go for a super spam shot here, dude.
Come on, walk over that.
Oh my god.
Oh god.
Chaos.
Why am I...
What am I...
I got...
What am I waste?
Let me get the medic at least.
Oh, thank goodness.
If I didn't kill that medic, I would have been so upset with myself.
Oh, I can't...
Do I like Twitch or do I like YouTube better?
I mean, YouTube has a lot of problems right now.
There's a lot of glitches with YouTube.
There's a lot of bugs and stuff.
That's in beta, I can understand that.
But it's...
I would definitely say the process is much easier on Twitch.
That's what I'll just say at least.
The YouTube stream is better quality though, because I'm partnered on YouTube and I'm partnered through Mishinema.
So the YouTube stream will look better.
But, I don't know.
Hopefully they fix up some of their bugs.
I'm confident they will.
Oh, scout.
There he is.
Whoa!
It's really walked through there.
Medic!
Yeah, I'll go combat in Junex.
Absolute.
Look at all these people.
Like goodness.
Oh, don't use that. Don't use that.
Oh, man.
Oh, no.
Oh, come on.
Kill somebody.
Oh, my God.
Come on now.
Oh, I got the medic.
Good.
Oh, keep coming.
Oh, no! Come on, give me the help.
What?
Uber!
Escape.
Escape!
Damn.
But I didn't.
Boom.
Yeah, after this round, I'm gonna go combat, Angie.
Oh, there's a crit dude right there.
Oh, no, give me a way.
Where's the spy?
He's up top there.
He's going up this way.
Get up.
Why am I stuck in the staircase?
Is that another spy?
Yeah, there he is.
I love how it's just like everyone's running frantically around chasing this spy.
Oh, walk over that, please.
Somebody go to the left side.
Come on.
There you go.
I double-dogged there.
Can we go up there?
I'll leave that there.
That can be the defense.
Spam.
Oh, God.
Can we run the car?
No, I'm not yet.
Get away from me.
Yeah, come on, get on the car now.
Come step on that car.
You know you want to.
Ah, come on, get him.
Somebody get on that car.
I want to blow it up.
I need to get healed.
There's a spy up.
It's fun, isn't there?
I might have to go deal with that.
Hold on.
Oh, I just launched myself into nowhere.
What is going on?
Why?
Why are they bouncing?
Oh, well, because...
Where's this spy?
He's freaking me out.
Is that a sniper?
No.
I've been to the police.
The IP I linked it a little while ago.
I'm going to be changing servers after this anyways.
And get more people into the game.
There's a lot of people in this room.
Oh, this is definitely a lot of people still in here.
All crits.
Oh, I didn't get anybody.
Oh, damn.
Oh, man.
Soldier.
Hold on.
I got to deal with this.
That's a spy.
That's definitely a spy.
No way.
Maybe not.
No, it's not a spy.
Wow.
Oh, my God.
I was not ready for this, but I'm going to do it anyways.
Let's do it.
Come on.
Oh, you bastard.
Germa is a wizard.
Official.
Let's go.
Oh, man.
Look at all those people.
How am I doing?
I'm not that bad.
No, no 720 here.
I am not part of it on Twitch.
It's over.
I owe gaming.
Register today.
Oh, I killed myself.
Damn.
I want to start live streaming soon.
Any advice on how to get started?
Oh, yeah.
Most important thing is your internet needs to be able to handle it.
That's, I'd say, the number one thing is go to speedtest.net and run a speed test.
And I'd say if your upload speed is less than 1,
like 1.0, 1 megabit per second up, I'd say it might be difficult for you to stream in good quality.
But if you're higher than 1 or 2 megs up, you should be fine to stream.
But I mean, you guys have been here before when I've had problem streaming.
I have 10 up connection.
And, oh my god.
Oh my god, somebody run over that.
Here we go.
Yes, yes, yes, that's what I wanted to run.
But you guys have been to streams before where it's been unwatchable from lag.
And I have a 10 up connection.
It's just weird.
The internet is a weird place.
And also, I'd also say you need a pretty good processor and video card.
Because essentially your computer is doing kind of like double work.
Oh, no, I got crit rocket.
Oh, I got two cats, man. I love cats.
I love any animal.
The only animal that I could probably say I don't like is, I don't know, maybe like,
this is a hard question.
The only animal that I don't think I would like to, oh my god, another Uber student.
I like the Uber machine tonight.
Oh my god.
Oh, it's crazy.
Anyways, probably an animal big enough that will like literally kill me if I go near it.
So, probably something like that.
Oh, yeah, 4 up is fine.
You'll be fine with 4 up.
Here we go.
Oh my god, I feel like,
I feel like the other team is getting neglected.
Spread the Uber's around.
I don't need them all.
No, I'm just kidding.
We're going up top here.
Or I can just apparently not detonate the mine.
What's going on here?
So many people.
So many people to spam.
This is chaos.
Oh, this is absolute chaos.
Oh my god.
This is ridiculous.
There are two player servers in sanity.
Yeah, this, oh my god.
Yeah, this is a full group in here, man.
Right after this round ends, I'm going to hop in a new server.
I'm going to hop in a new server.
Oh, that's a double.
That's a double.
It's going up here.
Hey, hey you.
Oh, you're real.
I was going high five.
Oh, you want high five?
Oh, sure, I five.
And then just explode myself.
Wow, that was pretty unintelligent, dumpy.
But yeah, that's what I do.
All right, new server.
I'm going to say, you server.
Wait.
Oh, you want to see my brain.
A lot of you guys already know this.
Sometimes I just don't think.
It happens quite often actually.
All right, let's see.
Let's see here.
I would say let's play a randomizer server.
But for my streams, I like to get a lot of people into the games.
As many people as I possibly can that are watching.
So I don't want to just, you know, because most of the randomizer and arena mod tech servers, they're always full.
They always have, you know, 23 out of 24.
So I would be the only one that would be able to get in.
So I like to have people from the stream get priority and come in and play and stuff like that.
Let's find another server.
What is fun with 32?
All right, oh my god, there's so many loading.
Looking for 32.
Hi, tower.
We're going to bunch of bots.
Well, I ever do a workout video.
I've thrown it around.
I was going to do it a long time ago.
But it's just, I don't know if people would even watch it.
I know that there would be a very small group of people that would probably watch it.
But I don't know if like how it would be received.
I think a lot of people would be like, what the hell are you doing?
Why are you like a Whiston Wates?
24 or 20?
You're 32.
Okay.
No, here we go.
Good old fashioned Dustball.
Here is the IP.
Oh, everyone's always asking about Enlighten.
The new Enlighten.
I'm working on it right now.
So there will be a new Enlighten in the next couple days.
Working on it right now.
Yeah, I'll probably do another one of those videos where I give advice.
And I'll probably do like maybe a one or two minute vlog type thing where I show you some stuff.
But I'm not sure I would do like a 20 minute workout video.
Like, okay, then up, then down, then up, then left.
I think that would just be odd.
I mean, I think there would be very weird.
Let's go blue.
I was red last time.
Oh, boom.
What do I want to use?
Oh, the new PDA.
What's going to be, oh my god.
He might not.
And oh, and down, and left, and egg.
And egg.
Alright, let me say this.
Would you guys watch an egg workout video?
Like if it was the egg.
What do I want to even play with?
Oh, I'll stay with this.
I'll stick with this.
Why not?
Buh, buh, buh, buh, buh, buh, buh, buh, buh, buh.
This server is like, is this server like weird?
And it's like, I'm like lagging.
Oh, I'm trying to, I tried to have an iPhone.
Oh, wait, you can just hold your hand like that?
Oh, yeah.
High five, baby.
Alright, and I don't know if it's like the server enough.
Is everybody like all jumpy?
Because they are on my screen.
Does anybody else see that?
I don't want to, we'll go for one or two rounds like this.
Oh, high five, here we go.
Shloping.
Yeah, I mean.
I thought everyone's like jumping all over the place for me.
Oh!
Centred down.
Hey, hey, hey.
What do you think you're doing?
Oh, but I forgot I was going to answer that question.
The reason why I don't do auto reload is because it's somebody in here?
Like the ghost of the pyro just in that room with me.
Oh no.
Alright, well, here we are.
I'll block you way out.
You can't get out. You're a dead ringer.
I got you blocked in.
Hey.
That is a tip right there.
If you shoot a dead ringer and you know he's a dead ringer,
just stand in the middle of the hallway.
And he can't get by you.
Oh, just rats are going up up here.
I don't know why I decided to put him here.
It's a bad idea.
Oh, yeah.
Where is my mini-century?
Why is it still alive?
Oh my god.
Getting distracted.
I have ADD, man.
Wow, we already won.
My goodness.
FG Spidey, Betia, I can say your name.
I bet you a dollar, I can say your name.
32-man Dust Bowl is chaos.
I'm going to go Huntsman Schneipack.
If you want to throw me a duel, I'll absolutely do it.
Ah.
Oh, now I go, let me say, I'm going to sign a Gosa.
I think that's what you say.
Sign a Gosa.
Oh, by the way, if you're watching this on YouTube,
because I'm going to upload this to YouTube afterwards,
yes, I am responding to people in the chat.
So don't just think I have some kind of weird disorder where I just say,
we're random words.
I guess I have that last time too.
Oh, come on, this guy is going to get head shot right now.
Right now, here we go, ready?
I don't think you know, I don't think you understand.
I don't think you understand, here it comes.
Oh, my god, he killed me.
Oh, no, a different guy did.
Eggs.
Look at this like egg.
Man, this server is lagging from me.
I'll tell you right now, oh, look at this double spy collateral.
Oh, no, run away.
Oh, tack!
Oh, I can't even aim at people.
My screen is like, did it take a jellyfish.
Oh, he got me.
He got me.
Oh, whoa, whoa.
Oh, look at the server.
I don't think the server was designed that, but it's pretty people in it.
Oh, wait, you want to get covered in jirati?
Is that what you're saying?
You want me to come smash you?
Is that what you just said?
I'm a fan of Kid Icarus.
I never played it.
Not even the original.
And I'm an old bastard.
And I didn't even play the original.
Oh, that would have been sick.
I heard somebody.
I thought I'd love to kill somebody.
Finally.
I got my first kill, but whoa.
That's because you see where I shot.
If you're watching this like on YouTube, please rewind that and look at where I shot.
I shot like five feet over that guy's head.
I still killed him.
Oh.
Oh, god.
Let's just, all right, let's do it.
Oh.
Oh, there's no way I was going to get out of there.
A good affordable graphics card.
That's a good one.
Hmm.
I'd say probably like the GTX 550 or the 560.
I think those are both under 200 bucks.
I think, under 100.
I think the 550 is, I don't know, the 550 Ti, I think it's called.
I don't even remember.
Go.
I missed him.
I'm going to go.
I think it's called.
I don't even remember.
Go.
Oh, I missed him.
I think Ag should be a weapon.
I don't know how well they work.
Oh, it's SimSass.
You got the 550?
How much is the 550?
And follow up, is it a good graphics card?
There we go.
Did you get it?
Oh, my God.
Hey, let's go on.
Just hiding over here.
Away from you.
No, no, please don't give me, please.
Did you buy the 550 or did it come with your computer?
No, I'm not.
No, I'm thinking.
I didn't get him.
Oh, crap.
Okay, yeah.
So the 550 is only like $130.
I'd say that's a good graphics card to be able to save a little bit of money.
Because the 580 is, geez, what, like $500?
Something like that?
I know it's up there.
And they're already working on the 600, aren't they?
The 600 series?
Oh.
Is that?
Okay, you're real.
You're the real deal.
I got you.
Oh, cover them all.
Okay, okay. Did I even get...
No!
Get this one guy!
Come on.
The 680 is out now.
Oh, dear Lord, what is that?
Like $900?
You can only imagine.
Woo!
I don't think we're going to win this.
Oh god, these people over there too.
All right, I'm going this way.
Is anybody up here?
We almost just got it.
Oh, he's still alive.
He's still alive.
Hey, he's turning on your...
Oh my god.
You guys like crushed that guy.
Geez.
Oh, forget that.
I'm going this way.
Oh my god.
That's my favorite movie?
Hmm.
I don't know.
Probably Ghostbusters or Memento or The Dark Knight or one of the Muppet movies or
there's a lot of movies I've watched that I like.
I'm not a big movie watcher though.
I'm not even a big TV watcher either.
Oh my god, I just missed his head.
Oh, this guy could be toast.
Oh my god.
You know what I have for me?
Oh, this guy doesn't even know I'm here.
Damn it!
Fight Club is also a good one, Ari.
Fight Club is a good one.
I'm over the first time I watched Fight Club.
I was so confused.
I think I was like 16 or like 17.
When did that movie come up?
Somebody do a quick research and find out when did Fight Club releasing?
When did it come up with the others?
Is somebody right in the foot?
Ready?
Oh my god, hide.
I want to see if like, rampuck and beatbox?
I don't think you can.
I would assume rampuck could not beatbox.
1999, okay.
Oh!
So that means I was.
So 10 years ago was 2009.
So 10, 11, 12.
So that was 13 years ago.
I was...
Hmm.
So I'm 26.
16.
15, 14, 13.
I definitely didn't watch it when I was 13.
I don't think my parents would have let me do that.
Yeah, I mean, once I watched it,
I think the first time I watched it when I was like 15 or 16, something like that.
And I was confused.
I was absolutely confused.
Office space is a good movie too.
The thing is, I've seen a lot of movies, but I don't watch a lot of movies.
If that makes any sense to anybody, then, oh my god, I accidentally got that guy.
Greetings from Chile.
Well, greetings from East Coast USA, dude.
It's either very early or very late for you.
I'm not sure. Actually, no, I think we're in the same time zone.
We're close, the same time zone.
Oh my god.
All right, time to play.
Scout.
My real name is Jeremy.
It's Jeremy.
J-E-R-E-M-Y.
Look at all these people he's blowing out.
Look at this good Pyro right here.
Just running around blowing all the teammates out.
You get a gold star.
No, it's not Jeremiah.
It's just Jeremy.
Oh, there's a lot of people right there.
Hmm, much, much, much.
Okay, all right, Scout's not going to work.
I'll go medic.
Do I like Irish people?
I do. I am Irish.
I am Irish.
I am Irish, so.
Look at this server.
All right, after a...
I'm going to change servers after I die next.
Just because this server is very laggy.
Look at this guy.
Looks like he's probably like a claymation.
Look at this like claymation server.
We're on.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Oh, this is why I like the quick fix.
Because you can just do this and it like makes sense.
Oh, my God.
That was the guy I had to steal.
New server.
Yeah, new server.
Oh, yeah.
He defeated me.
Probably helping one more server.
And try some tribes to send.
Because that game is really cool.
Let's go zero out of 24 this time just to keep the lag factor down a little.
Can you give the health sawmill?
Can you give the health nucleus?
That could be good.
Yeah.
Can you give the health sawmill?
Hi, tower.
I'm torn guys.
I don't know where to go.
You are garbage germ.
Why?
What did I do?
Oh, bad water.
Mountain lab.
A day in the life of germa.
Where I just eat like Cheetos and take a bath.
We're going to go here.
We're going to go to buy a duck.
Cautt buy it up.
There's the IP.
I put the IP right in chat.
Should say a little camera next to my name.
Let's go.
Let's go spy.
This is a very weird load up.
I don't know what I was trying to do here.
I got the strange dead ring.
The service full.
What am I talking about?
If you can't get in or trying to get in,
I'm going to apologize.
I think I do have a strange name.
Oh, it's a depth.
It's going to belong to somebody else pretty soon.
Might as well rack up as many kills on it as I can.
I'm an engineer walking out of you from the other side.
Oh, you got me.
Damn.
How dare you kill me like that.
If I could go pro at any sport, baseball.
I've always wanted to be a baseball player.
I'm not sure why, but I just have.
I used to play baseball when I was younger.
I didn't tell high school, and I stopped in high school.
Oh, now they're going to all know that I'm dead wrong.
Dead wrong.
Is that anything like a word?
All right.
I'm going.
I'm a pyro.
I do that the best.
Now it's just a scared chaos stab right there.
What do you hear?
The other team is still trickling in.
Look, I'm just coming out of spawn in myself.
Hey, let's get out of spawn together.
What?
Oh, German, I'm cheating.
I'm watching you stream.
Is my name even German right now?
Oh, scrumple down.
Harvey Hanberger.
George Bumberson.
I go by a lot of different titles.
I'm going to get out of my way.
Oh, you son of a b.
Oh, that's like five million deaths in a row.
It's by time to change up enough.
Low FPS.
Oh, what am I even using?
Okay, I'll rock with this.
I'll roll with this.
I'm cool with that.
Thought that was a spy.
Oh.
What just happened?
Oh, my brain.
There was a soldier right there.
I just killed that medic.
I'm sorry, dude.
I don't think I've ever had a embarrassing name.
Oh, my preferred breakfast food.
Oh, you kidding me?
Eggs.
I had to say.
What have we got here?
All right.
No more fooling around.
Let's get some kills.
Let's kill some bastards.
Get on this point.
Boys and girls.
Where is he?
You are a spade.
Yep, he's here.
It's invisible now.
Oh, that was a total not good idea.
Oh, what was...
Did I jump in the air?
Did I...
What just happened to me?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
What just happened to me?
I...
I don't even understand how that happened.
Maybe I did jump.
That was weird.
Kill Jerma.
Nice name.
Oh, three, two, one.
Well, at least I got one kill.
Tat around.
Boy.
How do you open console?
It's the till day key.
Thing under escape.
Oh, I got some...
I got some expert rocket jumping, guys.
Here we go.
Expert.
Rocket jumper.
Check me out.
I'll be on...
I don't even know what the name of the site is.
So wait, why would I give up TF2?
I thought I made this explicitly clear that I never was.
TF2 is a huge part of my existence.
I don't know what it is.
Oh, I don't know.
I don't know.
Where is auto?
It's a good question.
That's just my brain.
He's gonna know he's not.
What is that?
Oh, that was awful.
There we go.
Oh, can I get like a string or two or three or a row here?
Oh, come on.
And you.
All right.
At least I'm killing people now.
Oh, come on.
And you.
All right.
At least I'm killing people now.
Oh, my Liberty Launcher is now a new rank.
Yeah, I understand that phenomenal.
But to be honest, the items that I have in my backpack right now,
I mean, I know I can understand like, oh, he's giving away his whole backpack.
He's gonna quit.
I mean, I have a lot of friends in Team Fortress.
And a lot of people that, oh, God, hold on.
Oh, God.
I'm totally ruined that much.
Oh, my God.
But I've got a lot of friends in Team Fortress.
And I have a lot of people that have, they support me with this channel.
So any item that I ever want to use, I can just get it back.
It might not be strange.
It might not be genuine.
Like I said in the video, I started with Team Fortress 2.
And I got all the support from you guys from Team Fortress.
A lot of you guys are Team Fortress guys.
And that was a decent shot.
And that's why I felt like doing it, you know,
something I felt like doing.
And mine's made up.
There's no going back now.
So it's gonna happen.
And it looks to you if I can...
No, there's a mini sector.
All right, after this round,
go to one more server, and then I'm gonna hop and try to send.
Boing, boing.
No, that was laggy.
Oh, I didn't want to do that.
Oh, my God.
What is it going on with that guy?
The guy was just skydiving right there.
Oh, I'm dead.
I am so dead.
Oh, you lagged out?
Yeah.
Oh, I'm dead.
I am so dead.
Oh, you lagged out?
Yeah.
Oh, I'm dead.
I am so dead.
Oh, you lagged out?
Oh.
Mission ends in 60 seconds.
Oh, how did I not hit him?
Many centuries.
Get out of here.
Oh, there's this sniper.
Good to know.
Oh.
This is where we get the trouble.
So, but it's snipers.
He's still alive.
Watch this spawn.
Optimus Prime is on the loose.
No, you're real.
Where could he be?
He's going to get on that point.
Get on it.
There we go.
Everyone just stop on here right now.
Ah, missed.
All right, one minute, 40 seconds.
We got this.
Oh.
Hmm.
You got a backup.
Damn, every time I shoot a crit rocket, it just goes right five.
Track.
Oh, bow.
Oh, no, no, no.
No, no, no.
No, I just ruined this again.
Oh, I'm sorry, medic.
I'm an idiot.
Oh.
Yeah, tribes is a free to play game right now.
I would suggest everyone to go get it.
If you play team fortress, you probably like tribes.
It's just another one of those kind of fast paced, you know, projectile based crazy fun games.
FPS is the first version shooter.
All right, so let's set on New Sir.
New Sir, have a...
All right, one more server here.
Then I'm going to hop into tribes for probably like a half an hour or so.
Okay.
So you have 32.
Okay, let's go to...
We got this one is open and it's dust bowl.
We just did we already did dust bowl.
Well, busy town.
That was busy town.
This one's well.
We can do well.
I'm actually known and I know that server might not be able to.
All right, we'll go to this one.
CTF well.
And there you are.
Everyone join it.
Empty randomizer.
Um...
I mean, randomizer...
Is it really empty?
So those servers are like legit empty right now?
No, okay.
Next week we'll do randomizer.
We'll do some randomizer next week.
Let's get...
I'm going to use...
The shortstop.
And the... I'm going to put on the whole set.
Why not, right?
Why not?
Go, go, go, go.
Oh, the runs have not even started.
I'm going to get a kill.
No, I'm not. Too bad.
Woohoo!
No, I'm going to sneeze.
I got a sneeze and there's nothing I can do about it.
Oh, I'm going to sneeze.
There I come.
No. No, I'm false alarm.
No.
Oh, man.
Sorry.
I'm just a mute me.
Are we getting spawn traps?
What's going on?
Thank you.
Manak!
Get me in here.
Oh, it's dead.
They got to get crits.
Oh, damn.
It's the Vizzi spider.
One of the water spouts.
Down came the rain.
And wiped out that goddamn spider.
I just bumped into a spider, but I don't care.
Oh, it didn't wake me.
Oh, man.
I did help.
Oh, you are not.
You are a real bowl.
He's still alive.
No, he's not.
Wait, what?
How was that?
Unless I actually really just killed him.
Go, top.
There's the health.
That's what I wanted.
Oh, god no.
This just bounced off the door and gave me the face.
Oh, no.
I'm gonna die.
Give me my milk.
Oh.
All right, several levels.
Thanks for coming, man.
Well, I ever do more dual commentary.
Oh, hell yeah.
I just took one the other night.
On CSGO with MLC stealth.
Oh, just jump over everybody trying to get around.
Oh, I was gonna get by the train.
Give me out of here.
Give me the stupid intelligence.
D-A-M-M damn damn.
Oh, what just fell?
I got backstabbed.
Gang it.
Special delivery.
All right.
Did it did did did did did did did.
Was this in low right?
German sucks in TF2.
We got a troll.
All right.
One more round of this.
I'm gonna go Pyro this time.
Hmm.
I always do not, I don't put on it.
Let's go.
Yeah.
All right.
Last round.
I'm gonna hop over to tribes.
I'll send.
Damn.
No.
All right.
I got to clear offline.
We can't have any spam coming at me.
I'm gonna go to the other side.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Somebody behind us still?
No, I turned it.
Oh, I don't think I even have the half of the degreaser said to be honest.
No, I don't have the half.
You know, I saw I thought I could get by and then I turned and skid the crap out of myself.
Oh my god, they have crits.
Shoot at me.
Come on.
All right.
Don't get it by the train again.
I almost got hit by the train again.
No, I'm gonna make it.
Oh, damn it.
Where's Burger Boy?
Where is Burger Boy?
How am I not letting him on fire?
Oh, is that mean we're gonna play tribes ascent with Burger Boy?
Special guest appearance from Burger Boy?
God damn it, Burger Boy.
Reveal yourself.
He has.
Burger Boy, Burger Boy's been in videos.
Oh, I'm out of ammo.
Oh, god.
Oh, my power jack.
Would I get one kill with it?
And me versus you.
What do you say, buddy? Let's do this.
I uh, I lost.
Oh, we got crits.
Yes.
I just want to crit fire somebody.
Feels good to crit fire.
It feels good to crit fire.
All right, we're going sniper.
No, we're not. I'm going heavy.
Run, run, run, run, run, run, run.
Get away.
Oh, come on.
B-U-L-L-S-H-I-T with six exclamation points after that.
Wait, why do I have to toss it, Equip?
Okay, whatever.
I'm so scared of.
All right, I killed this five from like 5,000 feet away.
Where is this guy? Oh, my god.
He's on the roof. I thought I was to the right.
All right, take this stupid thing off.
Give me the regular gun.
B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-B-.
All right, I got to like really watch my back now.
I'm playing heavy. Probably the worst idea I could have ever done.
I'm gonna be on fire.
Oh, thank you so much.
Oh, no, here comes another dude.
How are you still alive?
What? I can't find the train again.
Of course I can hit by the train again.
That would absolutely happen.
Oh, full of god.
Hey, we're gonna get Chris, I think.
I hope we get Chris right now.
Oh my god, of course, we get Chris and I die, and I'm dead.
Oh, take this out.
Take this out.
How are you still alive?
I knew it. I knew it was a guy behind us.
Oh, my god.
You got a 32 person server that's not just like ridiculous. They are like insane.
Insanity.
It's like you walk out the door and it's just like, oh, please.
Where is this guy?
I'm so scared of the spy just back.
It's definitely gonna happen right now.
Oh, I'll get it by the train again.
Oh, we won. How do we win?
How am I in the number two right now?
All right, well, good night if you leave it, man.
Thanks for coming.
So now I'm gonna head on to tribes.
I'm gonna head on to tribes.
And I'm gonna head on to tribes.
And do that.
Thanks for playing, everybody.
I gotta change this to save.
I'm gonna tell you that in a minute.
Let me open up tribes.
The screen might go black for a second, guys.
So I apologize.
The screen is going to go black.
So bear with me for one second.
While I load up tribes, I send.
Oh, I have ADHD.
Crazy bad.
I have really bad ADHD.
I'm sure my is dead.
I'm still here.
Talkness, it's all I see.
I already did a setup video, Hannibal.
Go to my 4000 subscriber video.
It should be there.
Don't go into the light.
Now my children.
Let me tell you something.
I am God.
Coming to you from the black screen.
Let me tell you all you need to do to have a good, fun, interesting life.
Is to crash.
Because that's what I think I just did.
Oh, no, no, I'm here.
Okay, okay, hold on.
I thought it was hard crash right there.
That would have been bad.
Alright, let me get into the game.
The screen should come back in about 10 seconds, guys.
Settings.
Audio.
Yeah, that's fine.
Video.
Window.
Come on, let's go window.
Windowed.
Change the resolution.
Alright, let me just add this game as a source into the exploit.
Should be good to go.
Game. Hello.
Is that gonna fit?
Is that work? Let's see.
I think that fits.
Pretty sure at least.
Get that out of the way.
What's with the double screen?
That's weird.
Hmm.
Hold on a second, guys.
I'm gonna change this.
This is a little glitchy.
I'm just gonna add the screen region.
That should be better.
Okay, yeah, there we go.
Alright, so that should be better.
Alright, so I think we're gonna get some people in here to talk while we play.
Those of you that have never played this game, please, my goodness, please go, please go download it.
It is an unbelievable game, and it's free.
What other reason do you need?
Move this.
It's not in the way.
To the left, to the right, to the right.
I need to be moved a little bit.
Alright.
It looks like it's centered, at least on my screen.
Alright, so we're gonna get anybody in this call.
Maybe.
Might happen to the audio.
Audio is still here.
Yeah, it's here, I can hear it.
Alright, somebody call me on Skype so we can start a call.
Boo or stealth or burger boy.
Whichever one of you guys wants to do this thing,
and then just join up.
They might have already been calling.
Yeah, they are.
What's up, burger boy?
Oh, burger boy.
Now burger boys call me.
Get out of here.
I'm inviting them this one.
Is that his door?
I was first.
Where's the talix?
It was offline.
He might be doing a band thing.
Oh, what's up, burger boy?
Make sure you guys are turning off.
Alright, if somebody else wants to join,
can you guys monitor or stealth can you monitor just in case I'm in the game?
Yeah, do it.
What's up, I think?
When I alt tab in a window, it explodes.
I can't really alt tab anymore.
But I want to pull the door.
You could play the game just every 10 seconds.
So if you want, it's going to be difficult to join the game off me right now,
because the way this game works is you have to have like,
I don't know how many friends you can have, to be honest, I really don't know.
But I'm going to go pathfinder.
Turn this up.
Stream is under control.
I'm going to stand and get.
Stream is under control, and I'm going to turn this up.
Can't hear it.
Alright, I think we can go with sound on the stream.
Should be.
Hey, burger boy, do you have drugs or something?
Oh, he's got it.
He's absolutely got it.
So this game, if you don't know what this is, if you're like, what the hell are you doing right now?
This game is pretty much a think of team fortress meets quake,
meets skiing, meets ski free, meets windows 95, meets windows 98.
I'm not sure if that made any sense, but this game is just, look at this, just chaos.
Pretty much think of this game as your, you play as a soldier,
like a Liberty Launcher soldier, and that's pretty much what everyone is using.
Then you ski around like a hundred miles per hour, it's all about momentum,
and we just really want the game.
Yeah, that's a good way to put it.
This game is Halo with Speedhacks and cooler mechanics in my opinion.
The music is cool.
I agree.
One gem of soda.
No, it's changed.
It's changed. You're going to do map.
But it's not really Halo. It's like a, it's cool in Halo in my opinion.
Just because I never really played Halo.
I guess you've never had an Xbox.
You've never could play.
I've never played Halo.
I had an Xbox, I had a 360.
One.
Two or three years ago was the last time I had one.
What's going on? Why am I stuck here?
I'm stuck in this lobby area.
There we go.
So it was lagging right there.
Scream was lagging.
You kidding me?
Let me know if it keeps happening, guys.
Let me try this again.
If it keeps happening, I might restart it.
Just change a couple settings.
This game is so satisfying.
I'm going bloody eagle.
You can get some real satisfying kills within this game.
Especially because it's all about a long range.
It's a long range and people.
It's awesome.
Did you quit and join a different game?
I did. Just join off me.
Oh, it's got one.
It like kicks me out.
Oh, sure.
I don't know.
It's so long.
It's too long.
It's a long queue up.
Bergerboy is not a loud play.
How did I not kill that guy?
Here we go.
This is a beta.
Oh.
It's another chill.
It's free though. It's open beta.
Is it free?
It's free.
You get three shots.
Pretty much the pathfinder is like the scout.
You move around really fast.
Soldiers like the soldier, I guess.
There's like nine classes in this game.
I'm pretty sure there is.
This is just team deathmatch.
Essentially, why do we split the L?
We keep winning.
I'm going on.
I do not quit this one.
Keep staying in this one.
General.
You see this up here.
This is 2700xp.
Pretty much if you don't want to buy the game.
The game doesn't cost any money.
You can buy items if you don't want to wait and unlock them.
It's kind of like that.
If you want to spend money, you can.
If you don't, it takes a long time to get all the items and all the classes and everything.
It looks like it's exaggerated a long time.
Yeah.
Why do the hours of game time unlock a new class?
You start with three classes when you just get the game free.
You can spend 10-20 bucks and you'll unlock everything pretty much.
I'm going to go in-derma.
I'm going to go blood eagle.
Pathfinder again.
I'm going to turn the graphics down a tiny bit because I think people were saying it was lagging.
I'm going to boy you one on the other team.
Oh, we're a good boy.
I like switch teams in this game.
You're just first of the same.
You can just get them in switch teams.
Oh, this guy's toast down here.
This guy's toast guys.
Oh, get him.
I'm going to do my shot.
Finish this dude off.
There it is.
As you can see, I got a shotgun.
You pretty much only have two weapons.
I have grenades too, but I don't really use them.
I know I should, but...
...and see the top, the middle top, 97-92.
This is Team Deathmatch and essentially how this works is when you die,
one point gets taken off your side of the team.
But if your team has the flag or if their team has the flag, kills count is two.
I have the flag right now, so anytime we kill somebody on their team,
it's going to count as two points taken down from their score.
Oh, I just got nailed.
So it's lagging, huh?
Let me see if the hell is on here.
Wasn't doing this on Team Fortress.
No, it wasn't.
Let's find out what the hell is going on.
It's too graphed with landing strength.
Should be.
Shouldn't be.
I'm wondering.
You're still on CT?
Oh, yeah. I got the flag.
Come get me.
Oh, you're on the enemy team, huh?
Come here me, okay.
Destroy it.
Oh, come on.
Let's go. 1v1, baby.
Oh, I got me. Damn. Got me.
It looks okay on my end when I'm watching the stream right now.
It looks okay.
Maybe it was just like a little issue.
I don't know. Not sure.
But yeah.
Look at all those people in that.
Oh, I get, I get placed. Niper rifle.
Yeah, let's see.
When you go down, look at the left and right of my screen.
See how I have that power meter?
That's how fast I'm going when I ski.
The entire time you're going to be holding down space essentially in this game.
This is the flag.
All right.
Time to pull off something.
Get him with an air shot. Come on now.
I didn't get that guy.
Oh, go with people going for the flag.
You got to get rid of these people.
All right. Pick up the flag. Pick up the flag.
I got it.
Oh, protect me.
Oh, the italics isn't this game.
Drag him in the call.
The quiziest there.
Drag italics in here.
That was you.
Oh, well, that boy.
You know, friends.
Talik just blew me to hell.
And I blew him to hell.
No.
There we go.
Look at all these people ready.
Grenade.
Grenades are locked in this game.
Oh, there's a flag. Give me the flag.
Where am I?
No, that was a snipe flag right there.
I just totally snipe that flag.
I'm losing momentum.
I'm going to go.
I tried to settle before it.
I'm not very good at it.
God, I'm being chased by like a mob of people.
Well, Chris Z and all the people start following you.
What?
I'm going to drop the flag.
Yeah, because I'm going to drop the flag.
Still got it.
Oh, maybe not anymore.
Protect me, still.
Oh, they got me.
Well, let me drag italics in here.
All right, he's coming.
There it is.
One more.
Maybe.
Give me that flag.
One more.
Oh, one more.
What's going on?
What's up, man?
Play in the flag, man.
Like I do.
Yeah, we got some good flag control.
It's about like burger boys like terrible at this game.
He could like really like do something right now.
I can't even figure out how to switch games.
It is.
And then go to change.
I don't want to be on this team anymore.
I think the mlsc still just lied to you.
That's absolutely true.
I just did it.
That's what I'm going to say.
I can't.
There's not enough people on that team.
Oh, this guy is so toast right now.
Here we go.
Oh, come on.
Get him with those shots.
Oh, fine.
Whatever.
I'll go with this thing.
There's just a swarm of red upside down triangles around that flag.
Oh, still you got the flag.
I'm going to do it.
Let's do a little bit of team work.
I'm close to here.
Watch how I go.
Yeah, if we're still playing already, definitely.
I get you in here.
Oh, that is burger boy.
Oh, burger boy.
Right.
Oh, right there.
Oh, burger boy.
That's what you're.
Oh, I think the teams are even.
Oh, no, no, yeah.
You're not yet.
I've been to all the auto balance moves, I guess.
Yeah.
Well, this game's almost over.
We're almost going to lose.
Oh, but I have a flag.
That's good.
Yeah.
All right. So do not die.
Nobody died.
Nobody won't.
That's going to be a long range.
I know.
I'm going to see you flying around the map right now.
I'm going to chase you for so long.
I'm going to be dead.
Like shooting burger boy from behind.
He's just like right behind me.
Oh, watch out.
Burger boy is going to take us all on.
Somebody took him out.
I don't know who.
Got an assist.
Burger boy.
I can't even catch up with still.
And I'm on his team.
Try and get on the steam out.
Like a phone.
Try and get on this team.
Burger boy, the insensitive one.
All right.
Let's see if anyone's made into the MPP statistics.
No, we sure didn't.
Yeah, you got the mLC still flag held top accolade.
Whoa.
You got like a top medal.
You didn't get a MPP.
I said I'm going to join.
Actually, you got two.
Fly held and fly killer.
Top accolades.
This thing is my most flying health medals is 41.
And that's because I got the flag right when the game started.
And I skied around for 10 minutes.
What did it get?
Why am I killing anybody either?
Why am I not logged into my own stream right now?
I just typed something.
How is that possible?
So it's oh playing team fortress too.
I'm absolutely not.
Do you want my delegate?
What do you do on bloody?
Yeah, go right when you count.
Is that burger boy just like click spamming?
Yeah, I'm trying to get in that.
That was your best chance.
Oh, no.
Are we going to get split up here?
I think we might get split up here.
I'll catch you guys.
Oh, I just made it.
Oh, burger boy.
You could have just waited.
You made it?
I made it.
I didn't mean I was a fly.
I got to change this.
It's just saying I'm playing tribes.
Try to send.
There we go.
I'm going to do it.
Try to send.
There we go.
Broadcast updated successfully.
Oh, got the flag.
Probably not for long.
I'm going to go soldier this time.
I think that's the best idea.
Wow, there is no one on my team over here at all.
Trying to tell it's there.
I'm getting behind you.
Nice air shot.
Oh, burger boy made it.
That's it.
All right, let's keep going.
I got to go buy an arcs and buster.
Whatever that is.
It's probably stupid.
Oh, you bastard.
Where are you doing?
Oh, that was the sweep under the bridge.
Flight right there.
Oh, you want to go assault rifle on assault rifle or something?
Oh, this guy needs one hit.
He's dead.
Oh, come on.
There we go.
All right, we got the flag.
Oh, I'm going to catch me now.
Right into the edge of the map over here.
Did we get the flag yesterday or flag?
Here we do.
Yeah, that's how it says to evil men chasing him.
Let's get over there.
Got some ninjas flying around behind me.
I can't believe what you're doing chasing it.
Oh, Talix's voice is smooth.
It is.
Somebody just said that.
Smooth like an erection.
All right, this is PG 13 Shream.
I was, I don't even know what that meant.
Yeah, how's it about the ass?
Oh, air shot.
No.
That guy just got me.
This thing doesn't go very far.
Forget that sometimes.
I'm trying to prove on the better scared.
Well, the classes have a lot of impact on that as well.
What about you?
Right.
Yeah, if you're like the fastest class, what do you have?
Oh, damn.
I am a reader.
Yeah, somebody behind you.
So I'll slow down a little bit and do them.
That's just this game is the person that just asked this game is free.
And it's an open beta.
I'm going to do it.
It's the person that just asked this game is free.
And it's an open beta.
You can just play it.
You play it as much as you want.
Whatever you want.
And it's a game about skiing momentum and fun.
The ski simulation game.
Yes.
Oh, this guy smart.
What am I doing with this smart guy?
Wait till he lands.
Oh, I believe I've been carrying the flag this entire time.
I really can't.
I'm taking care of that.
Yeah.
Wow.
Uh oh.
Are we going to get to see some real raw burga boy rage?
Remember, burga boy, you can't say any like wicked horrible swiss.
I'm about to run into a wall.
Oh, I ran into a wall.
It's over.
Oh, you're going to go with this boom.
Oh, nice. Nice.
It was a good run.
Very nice. Very nice.
Berga boy's in first place.
Berga boy.
There you go.
Oh, yeah.
If that's going to get that flag right, one of our guys got the flag.
Oh, come on.
You got to get better aim.
Come on land.
Oh, I got a win on that.
Oh, damn.
Not doing so well right this second.
Oh, that's not.
Not doing so hot right there.
I just grenade it myself.
Like as fast as you move in this game, that is nearly impossible.
Yeah, I know.
All right.
That's crazy.
I'm going to be able to do it.
Yeah, I know. All right.
That's crazy.
I got that guy on the couple of shots.
Oh, that guy.
I'm doing some speed.
I'll get this guy.
I'll thump this guy.
I'll thump this better than thump this.
No, not high enough.
Wait, the flag is dropped.
I had the flag on my back.
Get out of the tower.
I blew that guy away from you guys.
Or I could just sit down here alone by myself.
I could hit it again.
What's going on?
Oh, I just got I just got air shot.
Damn.
I'll losing momentum here.
I just got mad air shot.
I'm dead.
I don't know how I got to lose.
I should play.
Yeah, we're doing.
I believe there are some grenades
that can make you drop stuff like the flag.
That's lame.
Actually, that's pretty cool.
Land on that.
Oh, damn it.
I got to get more.
This guy's done.
That a town.
Back off.
I just got killed by a blue fat.
Somebody just said.
Juggernaut?
Yeah, that's a juggernaut probably.
I might want to pull out the...
No, I might kill him.
One more shot.
This is the one right here.
Oh, no, he's not dead.
There we go.
I need to go to resupply big time.
Oh, ship has got a new video.
Reserve shooter.
I think it's a challenge.
Oh, he's on the floor of the deal.
Oh, yeah.
Flag down, baby.
Should I?
All right, we're beating him by like...
We have like a 100% lead on them right now.
Get the sky off.
Trying to get like hit markers on him.
But man, I tell you right now,
this game is a lot of fun.
I probably wouldn't have even started playing this game
if it was not for a tellyx.
Thank you, sir.
Thank you.
I was like, you got to play this game.
You're like, ah, whatever.
I was like, I'll give it a try.
Whatever. Probably sucks.
Now, this game is very, very good.
I saw it before a long time ago.
Like months ago, when people were first started talking about it.
And I was like, yeah, it looks okay.
This game is very addicting and very fun.
It's not what he's behind me,
but I don't care to turn around.
And it's free.
Yeah.
As a huge class right there,
I just went on buy games that were like 10 bucks.
Yeah, Burger Boy doesn't buy video games until they are $10.
And we're talking like Skyrim,
which up, but it's like Skyrim,
do you never gonna get that game?
Oh, I'm gonna get Skyrim three years from now.
Yeah, you're gonna get Skyrim like when you're like 35.
10 bucks?
Yeah.
Is it 10 bucks yet?
That's always that's the Burger Boy quote.
I'll be like, oh, hey dude, you know like Diablo 3 just came out.
10 bucks yet?
No, it's not.
It's like 60.
Oh, well, fine.
It's all it's like 10 bucks.
I'm gonna try and help you with this dude.
Nice.
Yep. He was getting on you pretty good.
Yeah.
13, I thought.
Yeah, all right, let me know when I'm.
I already feel nobody would see.
Right, what did you just say?
I really just didn't even pay attention to where you said.
Oh, I need to get up here.
I'm dead. I'm so dead.
Yeah, absolutely.
Oh, Frank and like about.
I got the guy for you.
Nice.
Let's see if I can give a slider with the hair strike.
Well, if you walk right into it.
Oh, no, he almost got him.
He was in the air.
At least a look closer from over here.
Ah, I'm trying to get him in the air.
I'm not shooting far enough ahead of him.
No, still not shooting far enough ahead of him.
Oh, that could have been an air shot.
Come on now.
Mother, may I?
I need to wait.
I got to recharge like stuff here.
Oh, God.
Is that Marshall?
Yeah, black.
Here we go.
Victory.
All right, let's get our rain here.
First one of the day.
There is an area.
A vulnerable 12 kills.
Hold it.
A vulnerable, nice.
I would not buy Team Fortress Classic.
The only reason why I say that is because it's just,
it's very, and now it's just so difficult to play.
This grenade spam is, it's,
it's, unless it's like five dollars,
don't buy it.
I'll put it that way.
Winter, winter chicken dinner.
I think this is the first time I've ever gotten first place in
anything in drives.
Oh, right.
That isn't achievement in and of itself for me.
Not even first in the whole game.
This first in my team is, that's good enough.
All right, quick flood to bloody go.
Bloody go.
Everybody click.
Look at it.
Oh, there's a guy right here.
Oh, yeah, sure.
Nope.
Get the first kill.
That gives you that flagged death.
It does?
Yep.
Oh, it seems to defend on call it.
He never points in the federal government.
Hey, watch it.
I can't believe I didn't, oh, he's going to kill me.
No, Jeremy, you have to be the first kill in my first death.
I'm going to be the, I'm going to be the first death if I don't get Lord Chaos.
Damn death.
Wow, that was the luckiest kill I've ever had.
Yeah, I'll probably do videos for drives.
Eventually everyone, I got, I got to get familiar with it, get to go to edit.
But I'll probably do a few videos at least.
Yep.
Because this game is really awesome.
Boom.
The other boom, the other.
Where am I? I'm going the absolute wrong direction.
All right.
I'm going to get some speed here.
Pick it up speed, pick it up speed.
Got him.
And it's all got me.
Oh, we got to get that flag.
Got it. Somebody on our team got it.
MLC stealth is going to die.
Look at that chaos grenade into the chaos.
Oh, I thought I got that guy.
I did it by.
My game is just updating.
I'm really weird stuff.
Hey, when we installed it on burger boys computer is like, all his fans turned on.
This computer almost like.
Just load just random there with the surprise.
That is like awesome computer I have.
Nice shot.
That guy got a really good shot.
We've had issues that borderline, so we've had issues.
Burger boy borderlands.
Sorry, how many times have you heard burger boy like swear and say horrible things in borderlands?
Oh, oh god.
Basically he did rematch his keys for his special ability.
And every time we wanted to pick up an item he decided to activate his special ability.
And playing his break he was just screaming constantly for the entire three hours that we played at that time.
Worst time gather.
Oh, burger boy.
Come on, you can do better than that.
Oh, let's go shoddy.
I don't have any momentum.
I'm like walking around the man.
Oh, I got that guy.
Oh, I saw that.
Hey, you.
I'm gonna waste this.
Let's get this guy.
Double team.
Oh, I missed.
There we go.
Another guy right there.
Two guys.
770 and that's a direct shot.
Oh, I got a phone lover.
Oh, he knew it.
Wow, that was awesome.
Holy crap, that was awesome.
Yes.
And a guy threw a grenade right into my feet when I went over there and got me.
Two shame, I've written that was great.
Down.
Woo.
Ah.
So, general, what classes do you have in life so far?
Just the sniper Sentinel.
Nice thing about like yesterday we were talking about the,
like the ones that don't detonate on the impacts.
Yeah, they bounce around.
I have the grenade launcher right now and I've noticed that if you get a direct hit,
it's like the demo man.
You know, it was explode.
Oh, really?
Immediately.
And the nice thing about them also is that they usually do a lot more damage and have bigger radius.
Didn't like the spin fusers.
Yeah, I've noticed that the explosion is huge.
You just get a massive damage spike right there.
I keep falling in love like a video.
Hey, it's not like.
I can't help it.
Does anybody else feel like they're playing like Star Wars?
I like feeling like that.
Yeah.
What's that called?
I mean, even the noises like the,
I feel like the green room dream, it sounds like Star Wars.
Oh, thank you.
So, what are you guys favorite classes with the games?
I like moving fast and having zero.
Fast, find them.
Yeah, I'd probably say the fast find too.
Just give the shock on the cell to try and,
I would say a raider or infiltrator.
See, I don't even, I gotta get those guys.
I'm never again with the infiltrator yet.
Never been good with stealthy classes in any game.
That's still fun.
Yeah, so you can, you can cloak?
Oh, yeah, you can cloak.
And it'll, like instead of using your energy per your jet pack,
it'll use it for your stealth.
Oh, okay, that's a good trade off.
That's not like overpowering anything.
And there's a few items in my perks,
making up perks, but I know it's at least one or two items that
can detect stealth people.
Oh, really?
I don't have any of those yet.
Yeah, there's like 10 people around me.
Skate down here.
Oh, Tony Hawk presents, tribes is in.
Do a kick flip.
Okay.
All right, I'm gonna do like a shaky 200.
Oh, that's like 25 points.
All right, I gotta get some speed.
Yeah, I cannot catch up to the kick flag carrier.
Oh, it's right down here.
Straight.
Try and cut him off.
Hey, burger boy, come.
How did you know it was him?
How did you know he read that?
Hey, go right back.
I'm gonna like a stream.
I know Jerma's ringtone,
and I'm pretty sure burger boy's going to always be on his stomach right now.
What if the talisman?
I didn't think he would.
I thought it does more of a burger boy thing to have his stomach on him.
What that means about you?
Do you mean that?
Oh, yeah, I got flag.
Hey, we're losing.
Yeah, I got flag.
Just protecting me.
What I want, what I want?
Oh, I'm gonna lose speed right now.
I'm gonna be sitting duck in two seconds.
I'm gonna be your body shield.
Oh, my God, there's a whole crew just following you.
Did I kill that guy?
Oh, finally, cheese.
Oh, my God.
Oh, yeah, I got one up for you.
Oh, I'm dead. I got to kill though.
Good, man.
I got another kill.
I know I'm gonna land right on top of everybody that's right there.
Oh, no.
Maybe that's like, I've read right by it.
Oh, that bastard got it.
No.
Oh, we'll get the shotgun up.
Oh, damn.
The shotgun.
That's weapon in this game.
Yeah, I didn't pull it out early enough.
I should have pulled it out way earlier.
Oh, it's Alex. Don't die.
I got him.
I got him, man.
Almost died.
I have 13 health.
My strength.
I'm not saying you're destroying.
I think I just blew that guy's grenade up in mid-air in front of him.
I think that's actually what just happened.
Where is the flag?
I don't know. We don't have it.
It's a pretty close game right now.
I can't live this.
Oh, I just totally stole that from your burger, boy.
Bailey is so tough but so satisfying when you get it.
I only do like an 8k people or like snipers.
Someone's like-
Are they hats in this game?
Yeah.
I wouldn't-
Don't put a past in, man.
This game could have a lot of items in the coming future.
It's a guy with a pretty close.
Got him. I got the flag guy.
You got the flag?
We're going to lose.
Try and cut this flag guy off.
Yeah, we're going to lose.
It's a done deal.
Cut him off.
That guy's out of speed.
7 to 24. I think it's over.
5.
Oh yeah.
Oh yeah, it's absolutely over.
Somebody called in the nuke.
Oh.
Wait, no. I had 10,000 credits but I called in an inventory station instead.
MLC has killed me 15 times in a row. That's how he said.
I feel like a retarget.
I was supposed to call an orbital strike but I called him the inventory station.
Sorry, does nobody die?
Give me that flag.
No.
Oh, all right.
I think I probably one more round maybe.
You guys want to play CTF or just keep doing this?
I don't know. CTF can be very, very long.
So I'll just do one more of this.
You were here yet already?
You gave the game loaded?
45 seconds.
He says 20 minutes ago.
I don't know where he's.
I mean, I got this game when Beta first was announced for this.
I signed up for this like this in Firefall.
I signed up for like years ago.
Yeah.
Firefall is incredible.
I got the beta for that as well.
It's so jealous.
It's only two times a week though.
You can only have gone in those two periods.
It's a year and one for you.
But it is insane.
It's looking like an incredible game.
If you get a chance to get it.
What is 544?
It's another free to play game coming out.
It was like the highlight of the 3th past year.
How can you describe it?
What is it called?
Firefall.
I thought someone said 544.
Oh, okay.
When are you going to get 54421?
It burns you and then fall as it falling.
Sorry, English accent.
I'm going to come across great.
I'm just hitting it.
Firefall is like, okay, dimension.
Oh, fire.
We played that attack East last year.
Yeah, that's the one.
Yeah, 54421.
It looks like Borderlands with an MMO.
And then Open World.
And then Awesome Mart Style.
And the art style is absolutely beautiful.
It's one of the most stunning games I've seen in beta.
It looks good as it is.
Yeah, right.
That's cool.
Oh, this guy's going to land on that.
No, he's not.
Get blasted.
Come on.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, why am I sure he's over here with being the flag guy?
I'm going after him.
Let's just do it down here.
What?
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Playing Juggernaut.
I'm okay.
I'm going to get better with him.
Oh, come on.
Walk into that.
This guy is standing still.
Oh, I just got that guy in the air with everything.
I'm going to get a stick.
Did anyone else do that?
Yeah, I did.
I was watching him come out.
I was like 15 feet above the guy.
I just like look in front of him and just like pop the grenade right on his back.
And he dropped the flag.
Oh, maybe.
Got Chosen right behind you, Talik.
He's dead now.
Somebody behind me now, I think.
Is that you guys?
Get him?
Open Sun, I'm getting more.
Oh, boy.
Come on, land, land.
Nice shot, dude.
It's like a ballet of death right there, Journal.
You're on me.
Shies.
I'm dead.
I'm not going to do about it.
You're right next to me.
What?
Oh, well, where is he?
I'm going to get you guys to my friend's list.
I get him to walk into this grenade.
He's going too fast.
Where'd he go?
I just launched him somewhere.
Great. Where the hell is he?
Oh, of course. He's right next to me.
Got like two people behind you, Jerma.
Yeah, I'm trying to go. I'm trying to go for this oppressing.
I'm stuck. I'm stuck. I'm going to die.
I'm so dead. I'm like on the ground.
Nope. Nope. You've got it.
You've got it.
Oh, you just saved my life right there.
What's my graphics card?
I use a GTX 470.
In video.
It's good.
I wouldn't really recommend it.
If you're going to get a new graphics card, don't get the 400 series.
Because the 400 series, at least the 470 and the 480.
They heat up way too much.
They are not recommended.
They're good cards.
But they can get to be like 80, 90 degrees Celsius.
That's not really that good for your computer.
York, I did play Globla Gender.
I have something like 700 hours.
I think clocked in on that game.
On global agenda?
Yeah, I've got. I used to play both the ensues used to play it like seriously.
Global agenda is different.
I think in global offensive.
No, no, global agenda.
I was before it was free.
We bought it and we played it.
Oh, god, we put in hours into that game.
Then it all went downhill after a while when they went free.
They built tribes instead.
They took all their money out of global agenda and put it into tribes instead.
That's where the end.
That's cool.
What was global agenda?
It was a similar game.
It was a good concept.
It needed to be made by a bigger company.
If that makes sense.
It does.
Like APB, I guess.
APB could have been.
I don't know how to do that.
APB went into the crapper, didn't it?
They ran out of money or something?
They were in so much debt.
It was just like, oh, free game.
We'll buy you.
It just made it free for everybody.
It just went downhill from then on in.
There is no health kit.
By the way, there is no health kit in this game.
Oh, it's itself.
I think we're going to win.
Absolutely.
I had the flag of the entire game.
That guy just went standing around.
I'm going to come with me with this.
Oh, good news.
That was just beautiful.
That's a sniper execution.
Pretty sharp, gorgeous.
Oh, I got it.
I don't need it.
That was an air shot.
Oh, that was a pretty close air shot. I don't know if I would really count that
I'd get the more ammo and come back fight. Oh, blah. Oh, I got a four core quad core four cores
Oh, that was interesting I guess what I just did
The spin fuser. Are you still carrying the flag?
I'll see. Yeah, this guy just walking right he's like right by you say whatever I'm gonna come and chase you
Next I'm gonna come back to you
You're all right. Are you dead? What's what are you doing still? Oh?
No, yeah, I
Probably my fourth my problem. Oh
You got to do oh you got people on you now
Oh, did they finally figure out how the game was played?
If I could not be such a slug I would come over there
All right, they're not gonna be able to cap off juggernaut. Why do you forsake me?
Oh, you're a juggernaut. No, what do you can't keep up? I know I'm pretty much like in molasses right now
No, he's dead
Oh
They're trying to slide me. Yeah, they got a couple of snipers actually the most
All right, let's get some fun f in speed here
Well live
I look at that slug. I
missed him I
Can't even like go chase it me either. I'm like the heavy weapons guy
Oh
That's a character in swole to laugh. No, that's right. Oh
I finally died. Oh, wait. Am I actually gonna like move more than like two miles for our own?
Oh, so what else picked up the flag? Oh great. I'm going in the opposite direction that everybody is
All right, as enough. I'm changing the pathfinder. Oh my fine bag time to commit suicide
That didn't even kill me
Oh, what's that it's a big bouncing blue green ball oh
Wonder why is that you the flight? No, that's the clay. Oh
So beautiful. I'm going this way
MLG grandpa is on an offseason right now. It'll be back in probably a couple weeks. I'm assuming
I'm gonna go help protect the flag carrier
Oh
You
If you hit one of those water guys who's when they're going off, but it'll actually give you like a 10 air
Really? Yeah, it's gonna be see them they like going off on the mountains
The best thing I have started this one and the one I'm gonna play next and the worst ones I love one how we just got done playing
That's my opinion
I like for castle on the best
Oh, what did you put what just hit me
That guy doesn't gotta uh
Just go on this way
Guys on the top
You
Know
Yeah, sweet sweet grenade bliss
Dremel you have 10,000 credits easier super duper
Okay
Uh, you have like yeah, three four five. I'm just gonna shoot it randomly over here
See if I end the game
I don't even help how big it's all over the country. I think I end of it with my strike over. I'll start to shoot
Yeah, I got like four or five kills of them. Hey 31 flag health medals
Sick
Simpsist 99 yes, Alex is on that server. Yeah
Oh
All right, though. I think that's uh, that's gonna be it to the stream
First place second place third place at place
Cool
That's pretty legit. Yeah, almost
Yeah, sorry
Sorry, I didn't get it in time. All right, we move let's do it for next time
Yeah, no, I'm getting the next time
Yeah, um, thanks everybody for coming. Appreciate it
And I play clock to end the stream by yourself
End stream by myself. I am
So I'm gonna go get some butter toast because I just woke up and it's like five
All right, well for bandwidth purposes. I'm gonna just end the call
No, I'm gonna call because I'm the host. All right. Well, thanks for coming to the stream guys
All right, I want to see you next time
I'll take your latest
Oh, all right, let's play a little quap if you missed it. I'm gonna upload this whole thing to um to youtube by the way
So the whole thing will be on youtube if you missed the beginning
Quap make sure this is even lined up
Oh, what's this big annoying ad over here. Oh my god. I'm refreshing this. That's like gonna give me a seizure
Here we go
Let's do it
All right, I'm gonna really take my time with this
See if I can get the slug mode again
Yeah, thank you if you guys are taking off. Thank you so much for coming if you missed the beginning of the stream
It's gonna be on youtube in the next probably a couple hours
Whenever youtube decides to process it who knows how long that's gonna take but yeah
It's ended on this one last one. Come on
Now I'm going backwards going backwards. That's not what I want to do
Uh
Hey
If I get 10 meters I'll be happy that's all I care about oh
Yeah, feel like I'm doing a dance move like sticky left leg out for your left leg down
That's gonna be oh my god
Hmm, I can't I can't go forward
I can't my right leg is always the leg that I can never use. I don't know why it always ends up like that
And that's when we fall backwards
Oh
But yeah, thank you so much guys. I'm gonna end up with that. I am tired
But yeah, um, I'll catch you guys later
Thanks again for coming. This will be on youtube again like I said
So peace guys. Oh, I'm getting some acid reflux
But yeah peace guys. Thank you so much for coming take care guys
Bye