Let's see if I can do it with Samson.
All fingers are pointing to no.
So let's go guys.
So sit.
Wait, why?
Why do I have a spirit heart?
I'm not exactly sure why that happened.
It should be right off the bat, but okay, so Samson works.
Every time you hit an enemy, you get stronger tears.
Like every 5-10 hits or something like that, you get stronger.
See how I'm turning red?
I got like a pink kind of tinge to my body right now.
Means I'm doing a little bit more damage.
Every hit.
But as you can tell, he has only one heart, so it's just like, nope, you're going to die.
Why is envy in like the first room and the first level?
That's just a lot of Malarkey if you ask me.
Oh my god, why is this guy blue?
It has like a grape.
Hello from Alabama.
Hello from Boston.
City of Boston.
Well I keep living in a good hit.
City of hot dogs, right lights and a Boston Reds box.
Oh that didn't take forever.
Is it every kill?
Okay, it's every kill then.
So it can be pretty, if you get a lot of HP up, he can be pretty powerful.
But of course we're in the spider room, so I'm probably going to die right now.
Oh god, this is the worst.
If I die in this room, I swear.
I should have already been dead to be honest.
I don't know where that spirit heart even came from.
I should be dead right now.
But I'm going to take it and stride.
You know what?
I got a second chance.
It's time to do this thing.
Alright, come on.
Come on you like cupcake.
You meat cupcake.
Let's get that item.
Have I met the scouting Boston?
Yeah, I seem like riding his bike all the time.
He's always riding around wicked fast like a psycho.
Oh, so he got buffed.
That's what it is.
Alright.
What about Judas?
So why would you ever play as Judas now?
Isn't Judas have one heart or does he have two?
If that's a buff, I can't think of a reason why you would ever play as anybody else.
Well, we're Judas at least.
Come on, blow up the secret room.
Okay, I don't think I'm going to make it.
I don't think I'm going to do this.
Yep, it's widow.
I don't think I'm going to do this, guys.
I might have to stock this over again.
Oh, no, no way.
No way.
Not a chance.
We're going to reach right.
Okay.
Alright, hopefully I don't run into the spider boss again.
I don't think I will because we're not in the spider catacombe place right now.
Oh, don't worry.
I'm not going to rage.
I'm not going to rage yet.
Getting shots.
Good, good, good, good.
Hey, it's always good to get your binding and Isaac deaths out of the way in the very
beginning, especially when you play on the stupid spider level.
That's way too hot.
I think the spider level shouldn't be able to spawn until at least the second and third
rub because if you play it as a character like this, it's no way you're going to beat
that spider boss with one heart.
This is no way.
I mean, I guess he could if you were really good.
Alright, doing much better.
Let's continue down here.
Yeah, I was a little late today to the stream and that's because I actually went out last
night for the first time in a very long time and I got a little under the weather as they
say and woke up a little too late.
But should I get the key and get the crate?
Why am I saying crate?
Too many games to crate lately.
No, we're not going to do that yet.
I don't think it's worth it.
Yeah, unless you're like a character like Kane or even Isaac can probably do it.
All the other...
Oh, Magdalene can do with Magdalene.
Let's keep going this way.
Look at that.
You bugs.
Whoa, didn't even see that guy.
I came out of nowhere.
I didn't even check my review mirror.
How could you ever delete the binding of Isaac?
This game is too good.
Everything about this game is good.
Except there's one bad part about this game.
It has to end.
Like when you're playing it has to be like over.
Ooh, aces fades.
The aces fades.
No, not doing that.
Not with Samson.
Well, let me walk over the spikes.
That's a great idea.
Oh, I want that chest.
But I don't want that chest because it might be something not worth it.
Decisions, decisions.
Oh, you know what, Yolo?
You only live once.
Let's do it.
I'm opening this chest.
All right, give me something good.
Don't hit that habit, yeah.
That was so worth it.
Oh, well, you know what?
You got to take risks sometimes.
It's not going to pay off.
It's apparently...
All right, let's go and look at this guy's butt.
All right, Master-O.
Oh, two Master-O's.
That's not a very good thing.
And you got to fight two of the same Master-O.
Come on, Burger Boy.
Oh, come on.
Why did it have to be Monstros?
They're just so happy.
I feel like these guys aren't even really trying to hurt me.
They're just trying to play.
They're looking at them.
They're just like, hey, I just wanted to jump and throw up.
Oh, God.
Well, one of them just go away.
Just go away.
Come on.
Oh, my God.
You bastard.
Why is this still two?
Okay, gee, it took to like 10% health to get one of these bastards out of here.
Okay.
We're good to go.
Two hearts.
We got it.
Wait.
Do I have any bombs?
I do not have any bombs, so I got it.
Just go.
Who is Burger Boy really?
Burger Boy is one of...
Oh, Curse of Darkness.
This is...
Ah.
Burger Boy is one of my real life good friends.
And he's also crazy.
But that's good.
That's like a good quality.
Because we're all crazy.
But Burger Boy is also the egg.
And there's a...
Might be a special video coming soon.
Coming soon, not like tomorrow, not like next week.
But there might be the return of the egg.
That's the only thing I'm gonna say.
The egg.
Best worst character ever.
Mm-hmm.
What's this?
The Emperor.
Alright.
Forget what you do.
But that's alright.
You know, I actually...
I'm actually one of those people that really liked Meet the Pyro.
A lot of people liked it, but a lot of people really didn't like it either.
I'll tell you one thing though, I think Meet the Pyro was too short.
If there's one complaint I have about Meet the Pyro, it was too short.
Because I mean, they gave us Meet the Spy, which was like three and a half minutes.
Then they gave us Meet the Medic, which was like four minutes.
And then it's like, oh man, they're getting crazier and crazier.
Like more cinematic and more cinematic as they go.
And then Meet the Pyro was like two minutes and 22 seconds.
That's the only complaint I have.
Now, I'll tell you what you did to the boss room.
Good to know.
And I...
Sorry, I must be crazy.
I have another spirit heart.
Did I walk over one and just not even pay attention?
Or do you...
Every time you kill like 20 people at Samson, you get a spirit heart?
Maybe I'm just crazy.
But I mean, after the inner...
I think they could have done the interview stuff a little bit longer.
You know, in the spies, like, what kind of inhumane, just horrible, disgusting thoughts, sort of,
whatever he says.
If they flesh that out a little bit more, maybe get a couple more characters, like get
the sniper to say some stuff.
Alright, let's do it.
Alright, I'm not going in that room.
They blew the budget on the special effects.
Get away from me.
He's gonna...
This guy's gonna be hard to kill with this spoon.
It's gonna...
You know, it's gonna attack the things around him and not him.
Sorry, I can wait it out.
I'm also glad that the Pyro's gender is a secret to the couple of you guys that are saying
that right now.
I don't know.
When you have a mystery like that, you gotta keep it a mystery.
It's just like when you read a book, right?
If I read a book, and it's like you don't know what the character looks like, you get to
make up your own kind of version of the character.
Because everybody has their own Pyro.
I mean, I'll bring up a friend of mine.
Boo, you guys know a boo.
Boo has like the best perfect description of the Pyro.
It's just like a cute, just like cuddly little entity that runs around and just has fun.
Like that there is no man or woman.
It's just the Pyro.
I think that's perfect.
The Pyro is not a man or a woman.
It is a thing.
It's just a mindset.
It's an entity.
Okay.
I'm absolutely not doing either of those.
Ew, who reads books.
I'm not miss.
I gotta go.
I gotta go down.
I would use the Source Film Maker if I had any idea how to use it.
The Source Film Maker is one of those things where you really have to sit down and play
with it and be good with it and learn.
And artistically I was never really an art student.
I mean, I can, I went to school for film.
I could probably use it.
I could probably do like shots with it and stuff.
But once you get to the animation part of things, there's no way I would ever do it.
I didn't know what to do with that program.
Because I tried Gary's mod, even just like do anted, little dumb animations and little
dumb things in Gary's mod.
And they always end up as complete atrocities.
Like complete and like just horrible things.
Like, oh, I want to get like the heavy to smile and point his finger and he just ends
up going like, oh get it.
Like his hand comes up.
I'm just not good with art.
I wish I was though.
He agreed.
Oh no, please don't show me.
Wow.
I was going to say there's no way I'm that lucky to touch like five of the cut.
Oh my god.
Now I'm just being an idiot.
It's these stupid things that are in the way.
I suppose they have homing shots.
Come on now.
Oh, I hate Epicak.
I absolutely hate Epicak but I'm going to take it.
I really don't like Epicak and it's probably going to kill me but you know what?
I'm going to take it.
See if I can find the secret room.
This is full heart up here.
Okay, this too.
Good to know.
Oh no, no, no, it's homing too.
Oh my god, I forgot about that.
Oh man, this is bad.
This is really bad.
I'm going to kill myself with this.
Guaranteed because it's homing.
Oh my god.
Oh no.
I'm blowing this up.
Cool.
Yeah, this is definitely a run that is in the tank in my opinion.
This is no way I'm going to do this because it's homing.
I will open you though.
Oh, I'm not going to.
Oh, it's over.
Like a bit.
I'm getting out of here.
I can't believe I survived that.
The only thing this is going to be good for is bosses.
That's it.
Barely, barely that.
Oh.
What did I have for dinner last night?
I think I had a chicken sandwich.
Pretty sure.
Oh, wow.
I can't believe I got hit by that.
This is taking so much longer because I have to keep going back and healing myself.
No, super secret room there.
Super secret room is probably all the way to the right if there is one here.
Bunk.
Oh god.
Super wrath, huh?
I don't think I've never faced super wrath.
Oh, no.
He does not do that.
He does troll bombs?
Like the big ones that follow you?
I guess it doesn't learn a matter because he's dead.
Starry's blast damage.
Just blast damage.
Incorporate.
Epic Act shots.
Oops.
Why am I not watching the soccer finals?
I'm not a big soccer guy.
I never really was.
I grew up on baseball.
Baseball is my thing.
Where's his peep?
Oh.
Well, this might be like good.
Maybe I'll kill him easily with this epic act.
Oh god.
Yeah, this is all right.
I'm going to be good.
I'm going to be good to go.
Epic Act.
Oh god.
Bunk.
I'll take the tears up even though I don't really want it.
And let's go.
Yeah, I'm definitely dead soon.
I am absolutely dead soon.
Oh, screw you.
You aren't getting any of my hearts.
You aren't getting my heart.
Oh, it's stupid.
Actually, that's not that bad.
There's one who's going to stay away from it.
Favorite baseball team is the Boston Red Sox.
I live in Boston, so.
Well, I don't live in Boston.
I live right next to it.
Put it that way.
Oh, and get smashed.
Oh, no.
No, no.
I can't shoot this.
Oh, come on.
This is the worst.
This is the worst thing.
Oh!
What's this?
Poison bomb school.
Well, I think this is the end of Samson.
Let's find out.
Unless I get a heart right here.
The sun.
OK, I'm going to stay alive.
What's in this next room?
Goodbye.
Sorry.
I was not dealing with that, not a chance.
I'm probably not going to do a GTA IV.
Let's play her a walkthrough.
GTA V, though.
I will probably do a some type of walkthrough.
Maybe a Let's player or something, because I love GTA games so much.
I can't shoot that.
What's going here?
Of course it's greed.
Why else would it be anybody else but greed?
At least it's a steam sale.
Mike Lowell is my favorite Red Sox player of all time.
Mike Lowell.
Epic hack, you are the worst.
Oh, I've won, Dad.
It's good for those guys.
I will say that for sure.
Oh.
OK.
No, no, no, no, get away.
Good.
I'm stuck.
Get.
I can't hit these bugs.
Strike one.
Strike two.
Strike three.
Strike four.
OK, there we go.
All right, boss.
I am shocked that I've gotten this far.
I am legitimately shocked.
You know what we're going to do this already?
Hey, what's going on?
What's going on, buddy?
How are you doing?
You want like some of my hearts?
Eat this.
I missed.
Run.
Who's talking to me?
Getting tweets all over the place.
All right, let's fight this guy.
Oh, fantastic.
Well, it was nice knowing you guys.
I'm sure I'll be like in the afterlife as Samson.
Maybe not.
Wow.
All right.
I'll take that.
I'll take a swift victory.
Oh, I want mommy.
Carthus of the labyrinth.
That's exactly what I wanted.
That's I'm glad.
Oh, no.
No, boy.
Oh, my God.
I can't even handle this right now.
Yeah.
Well, now the jig is up.
Unless I pull off some real ridiculous moves,
I am not doing this.
Well, bombs are key.
I actually would rather have that.
Thank you.
This could be the end right here.
I'm going to probably say time to be quiet.
Go to try hard, well, to not scream when I die.
Because that's probably what I'm going to do.
Oh, come on.
Oh, my God.
All right.
OK.
As long as you take it slow and steady, just like the turtle,
you don't got to be the hair.
OK, but now.
No.
Oh.
All right.
It hurts every time playing this game.
I might want to just go.
I don't know.
I really have one heart.
Now I'll die.
I need more stuff.
That's not what I needed.
I'm afraid to even attempt to get in here.
Oh, my God.
You know what was going to happen?
I got it over with.
I got it over with her purpose.
How come that killed me, by the way?
I thought it only did a.
I thought it only did one half heart.
Why did I die from that?
Oh, whatever.
Let's just go straight up Isaac.
Isaac never did me wrong.
Samson, you're too hard with your no hearts.
I'm going to take this game by the horns with Isaac.
Attack fly.
That's good start.
I'm going to beat this right up.
You see that just maybe so sad that I'm going to beat this
now.
Got the key.
All right.
OK.
Come on, flies.
What do you got to get?
Isaac, grab it.
I'm speaking about those spikes again.
I swear that I mean, I had one heart.
Why would it do more than one heart worth of damage?
Maybe they changed it.
Or maybe I'm just not smart enough to understand.
Oh, yeah.
Keep throwing.
Bugs at me.
And then you run them over yourself.
Isaac.
Actually, I'd rather stay up here,
keeping from moving around so much.
Whoa.
Wow.
There you go.
Kill your own dudes.
That's what I like to say.
Now that's what I like to say, Samson.
Not that though.
Get away.
Whoa.
Dodge and bounce here.
Come on.
You can hit me.
You can do better than that.
Keep me.
Jump.
I'm smoking this game.
I'm going to smoke this whole game right now.
As the title character, as Isaac.
Screw that thing.
I don't want it.
Bam.
I wish they would come out with binding of Isaac 2
and have it be like not single player.
Have it be you can have more than one or two people in the game,
or probably two more than two would be ridiculous.
All right, let's go.
Cupcake.
You velvet cupcake batter.
Speed and range up.
And I look like a freaking psycho.
Yeah.
Nickel.
All right.
Got a nickel.
Good to go.
Let's go.
You uncooked chicken.
You can't kill me.
I think a bull was telling me that he 100% of this game,
which like that's incredible.
What a boss.
It's a very nice, not an easy feat to complete like everything in this game.
It really isn't.
See, you like use it on the secret room, which is probably right here.
Well, apparently it wasn't right there.
Probably was down this hall somewhere.
But you know, I can take it.
Whatever.
My favorite holiday is definitely Halloween.
I love Halloween more than anything.
The only time of the year where you are allowed to be a freak show.
And like nobody is to cares or gets mad.
Think of any other night the entire year where you are allowed
to hang out your car window as the Joker and scream and laugh at random like old people
on the street.
When can you do that and people just go, oh, he's just being fun.
There's not a, not another time in the world where you could do that.
Oh, you're going to curve your bullets too, huh?
Curve the bullets.
Angerly to jelly.
That's every day for me, mad killer.
Oh, the dark night premiere.
I guess that is the situation where you couldn't do that.
Oh, welcome to the dark night premiere.
Okay, like that's, you can be the Joker and like screaming people.
That's awesome.
Yeah, I kind of feel like an ice cream cone right now.
I feel like a big ice cream cone.
Oh, boy.
These guys aren't that bad.
I can handle these guys.
I can handle these two dudes.
Oh, if you're wondering if someone was asking about Team Fortress and how come I'm not streaming it or anything.
I'm still waiting for a fix.
And I think there's a beta driver right now for the 670.
Oh, the 600 series in general.
I'm going to download that and try it.
It's just I didn't want to spend like an hour or two troubleshooting when that was already like an hour late to the stream anyways.
So next week we will see what happens with that.
But for right now, Larry, Jr.
You're dead.
And you're not coming back as much as you want to.
I'm sorry.
As much as you want to be in your like fruit punch pool.
See, this is looking more and more like a clean run every single time.
Let's go.
Four hearts full.
I got no stamps on it to worry about.
You need to die.
Man, you are a persistent son of a...
I can't hit that guy in the face and he just kept going like...
I get out of my face, man.
Get out of my face.
Do I play MMOs?
Absolute freaking loot.
I played World of Warcraft for over six years.
I had multiple max level characters.
My main was Warlock.
Well, actually, let me refresh that.
Warrior.
Then it was a priest.
And then it was a Warlock.
And my main was the Warlock for the most amount of time.
But I had a priest warrior Warlock druid.
God, I had like everything in that game.
But then they did a bunch of weird changes.
And I don't know why.
They did a lot of changes.
Oh, it's lagging right now.
Streams lagging? What's going on here?
Are we good?
I hope so.
It just popped up like everybody was like...
Like my stream is on fire right now.
So apparently my stream is like inflames.
Try refreshing it.
Try refreshing it up.
Let's see.
Let's see just to make sure I...
Because a lot of you guys were just saying that it was lagging.
Let's take a look here.
Look at my stream health to make sure it's okay.
My event.
Life control room.
Because it'll tell you it'll be like, oh, your stream is lagging like crazy.
Oh, it says it's okay.
So it seems better now.
Alright, that's good.
That's a good thing.
Alright, well, I apologize about that.
Sorry.
Somebody just like rolled over and like tripped over my stream court at YouTube somewhere.
And they like to plug it back in real quick.
Somebody was eating a sandwich and they just like tripped like,
I'm not even ripped up my stream court.
Oh, oh.
Yeah, if you're still getting the lag trying to refresh, sometimes that fixes it.
It shouldn't be happening to begin with though.
My favorite superhero is...
Ah, that is a tough question.
Because there are a lot.
There are a lot that I could say.
Oh my god, this room is full of bugs.
Man, I don't want to say like, oh, Batman.
Because it really isn't Batman.
Or Superman.
What is his name?
I should be able to answer this question in three seconds.
I don't know why I can't answer this.
Super hero, super hero.
Deadpool, Deadpool, there you go.
Probably Deadpool, Deadpool or Venom.
I've been waiting a long time to say that.
Oh, I need more coins.
ASAP.
I'm going to buy this bomb and try to blow up the secret room.
See if it's right here.
But Venom is just such a cool character.
I love the way he is.
He's just... is Venom.
No, that was the wrong place.
It was up top.
God, dude.
Alright, whatever.
Let's go.
Gerdy.
I actually like facing Gerdy.
I can handle him.
I can handle Gerdy.
Gerdy, come on.
DUDGE!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, I did not dodge that right at all.
There we go.
Oh, you two like bubbles of puke.
Gotta get rid of those bubbles of puke.
I know, Deadpool, because the Deadpool comics, if you ever read them, he is insane.
He breaks the fourth wall all the time.
He'll just be like, hey, reader, if you want to like skip this part, go ahead and like go to page 14.
This part's like pretty boring.
I just talked to some broad for like five minutes.
I love how much he breaks the fourth wall.
And the Deadpool comics.
It's so funny.
Alright, Gerdy.
That just about enough of you.
And you like big, smelly body.
Oh, come on.
You're gonna do me like that, Gerdy.
I keep thinking that eye is not mine, and that happens every time.
You would again.
I'm not doing it again.
I dare you.
Oh, you messed.
You stupid.
Go.
The caves.
Welcome to the caves.
Down here, you'll never see the light of day again.
And you almost die from fucking into things.
What you know, Isaac.
I actually, when Vindictus first came out, I was, it's free to play, right?
I actually was going to download that, and I just forgot to do it.
So thank you for reminding me, because I'm going to go download Vindictus
like right after the stream is done.
That's the one where it's like an MMO, but it's like a hack and slash kind of, like third person.
That's the right game, I think it is, right?
I'll take that money.
Go ahead, blow up.
What's going here?
Now, what do you have for me?
If you don't have, if I don't win this in the first time, you are dying just to let you know.
All right, I know you heard me.
Do you want to stay alive?
We'll find out.
Oh, looks like somebody wants to get blown up.
No, please, no, please, no.
Yeah, couldn't even finish his sentence.
And that's enough of that.
Ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding.
Yeah, definitely downloading Vindictus at the end of this stream.
And I'm going to play it.
A bunch.
Aw, you turned into like a little piece of jello.
I feel bad for you.
Doing it.
No, it wasn't worth it for like the seventh time in a row.
It's never worth it.
Me and MLC stealth played DC Universe for a little while.
We play for like a few hours at least.
I'm cracking my back.
Hours at least.
Of course it's great.
Why would it be anybody else besides greed?
Get him eyeball.
Shum.
That.
I'm shooting a red tear every other tear.
Is that because my eye came out?
Yeah, it has to be, right?
Ah, green.
You bastard.
Why don't you go bottle like Edward Alrich?
Like leave me alone.
Never mind.
You dropped a lot of money.
I like you now.
What am I doing standing there?
I need to be in the corner.
I need to be in the review.
There we go.
Don't even need to do that.
Uh-oh, it's super toothless joke.
Whatever his name is.
These guys freak me out.
These guys are scary.
I've had all the Warhammer games for a pretty long time.
If you are a fan of RTS, I would highly recommend you get the original dawn of war.
I wasn't a fan of Dona War 2.
I'm not gonna lie.
I thought Dona War 2 was a good game, but I don't think it was nearly as good as Dona War 1.
It's quite follow me, dude.
Come on, come right here.
Come on.
I've got like candy and soda and chips.
You know what?
You're not gonna come down, so I'm just gonna kill you.
We're gonna have a party down there, but you like didn't feel like come.
That makes me sad.
How much for?
There we go.
Item room is all the way over there.
After this, I'm gonna have to go do that.
Get to the item room.
After all these toothless freaks.
There we go.
Oh!
Speaking of Leopard 2, someone just said Leopard 2.
Can they come out with a new map, Cold Stream, or Cold Land or something?
Whatever it is, I'm definitely gonna be playing a lot of that too.
Fork.
Isaac's Fork.
Okay.
Oh, if you're gonna come to the potty, you're gonna bring like Salsa, you're gonna bring Dip, Chips, Soda, Pfft.
Berger Patties, Frozen Hawk Dogs, a love for life, and a good attitude.
That's the only way you're allowed in my potty.
You sack of mobiles to get out of here.
Open.
Now open again.
I'm the dentist.
And your teeth need a real cleaning.
Pfft.
Where's this item room?
God.
Such a big level is this DUMB.
Oh my goodness, I need to damage up something.
Because it's taking forever to kill any of these things.
Open.
Yeah, once it comes out, I'll stream left for that too.
Once the new map comes out.
Open.
Come on.
I didn't even kill him.
My little buddy did.
Ooh, little Chad.
He's so happy.
Hi, I'm bro Chad.
I'm gonna drop hot for you.
Thanks, little Chad.
Don't know, problem.
It's a little Chad.
You're gonna tell me your life story.
Good day, sir.
I grew up in dishever, and then I pulled out hot.
That's a touching story, Chad.
Thank you.
Now, give me your hearts before I kill myself,
because I'm pretending to be two people.
Okay.
Well, that's a good way to lose three hearts.
Do it like a little Chad movie.
Pills here.
No, no, that's the worst.
That's the last thing I wanted.
Yeah, I got it.
There is a circus following me right now.
Look at this.
Like,
all I need now is brother Bobby,
and like more tack flies,
I'll be all set.
Hopefully I don't die.
Oh, Chad.
Oh, no.
Why is he so weak?
Was that my...
What just even hurt him?
I didn't do that.
Hopefully he doesn't kill me.
All right, little Chad and Big Chad.
This is like very surreal.
He's fighting his like daddy right now.
This is like weird.
Who side of you on, son?
I stand on the side of light.
What's in here?
I'm actually kind of tempted to take this,
because I could use the spirit hearts.
I think I'm going to take that.
I really think I'm going to take this right now.
Oh, I'm going to take it.
I'm going to take it.
I took it.
Thank you.
It was a decision I had to make, and I made it.
I needed it.
Oh, God.
I'm like, why is it crashing?
What?
Oh.
For a second there, I thought the game was just crashed and done.
I was just about to freak out.
Did my stream die?
You're still streaming, right?
Okay, you guys saw that.
It was just like...
You know what?
We might even do it again at some point if I need it.
Oh, pro dodges right there.
Pro dodging.
I wish there wasn't all these obstacles in the way, so I could hit them.
Oh, that thing was blocking it.
That was why.
Give me that.
And I'm going to blow this up for sure.
Good position.
Now, too bad I have stupid curse of the labyrinth.
Whatever this dumb thing does.
Makes it so I can't see anything.
Oh, I want to kill at least Mom.
I want to kill Mom.
That big fat...
Oh.
There we go.
Let's go down.
I just did this room, man.
I just did this room.
Okay, I'm going the other way.
I'm going around.
Ah.
There's too much stuff blocking you for me to shoot you.
See, if I didn't take that guppies hand, I didn't use it.
I probably would be dead right now.
Because I've been hit at least five or six times.
Oh, this is bad.
Oh, this is really bad, especially this room.
Don't spawn anymore.
No, no, get...
God.
I hate spiders.
Not only in real life, but in fake life, too.
That's a good thing to take.
Gappy.
Die.
Oh, you hairy...
No, this is going to be so...
I was going to stay in the corner.
No sense going out there and meeting my demise like that.
Get out of here.
Oh, no, corner's bad move.
There has to be this many things in this room.
Get out of here, you bum-bomb.
There's so many of these little guys that shoot.
I hate those ones.
I actually just tried to Samson Run.
Didn't really work out too well.
I got to like...
What, the third or fourth Roman I died?
Oh, come on.
I don't want any of your like cream cheese.
Get out of here.
This is the binding of Isaac, Wrath of the Lamb, DLC.
And this is me getting stuck and not being able to...
Oh, my God.
I had to do that.
You guys all saw it.
I might even have to do it again.
I'm going to have to do it again.
I'm probably going to have to do it again.
Oh, my God.
I'm going to have to do it again.
Oh, my God, no.
There's no way for me to go.
Oh, there was no way for me to go.
Oh, my God.
There was literally nothing I could do right there,
besides just get hit a million times.
Oh, now it is definitely over.
Oh, these...
Come on.
Okay, well, that's going to be the end of this run.
I hope you enjoyed this.
Have fun and whatever you're going to do.
And then however you put path you take in your life.
I'm silent.
God.
Oh, that was the worst possible thing that could happen.
No order on, no order hide.
No order go.
They were like...
engulfing me.
Oh, gosh, darn it.
Well, that's...
So now you know what's going to happen.
Is grandpa is going to play his question mark, question mark, question mark.
And that's going to be the end of the stream.
So I'm going to go get grandpa.
Grandpa can come in and he'll sit down.
He'll talk about how he loves this game.
And we'll see what happens.
Hey, grandpa!
Hey, you got to get down here.
You got to play binding of Isaac right now.
No, come get it.
Yeah, come down.
You're scaring the dog.
Just come down.
Okay, let me just get it over here.
What the hell is this game?
What game is this?
Binding of Isaac.
What is that?
Just play it.
Just sit down and play.
Okay, I'll sit down.
Ready, there we go.
Okay, hello!
Let's play the binding of Isaac.
What is it?
Did I just eat shit?
What the hell was that?
No, it's all under control of this game.
Up, down, left, right.
Okay, so here we go.
Okay, good.
Let's go this way.
What is it?
Ha ha ha!
That's a spider.
This game is stupid.
What a dumb game.
So you want to just kill spiders and that's it.
This is stupid.
Why would you ever play this game?
Okay, let's keep going.
What's that?
What the hell?
Oh, that hurts you.
Ha ha!
Oh, am I going to die?
Let's just go.
Okay, I'm going to beat this entire game right now.
Let's go, let's go down.
Okay, we're going to go down here.
Look, look, I'm driving like a farm right here.
A pet spider is okay.
Hey, spiders.
So today I'm going to feed you some little bugs that you're going to eat them.
Okay, shoot that.
So how do I...
It looks like a simulator.
How do I get out of here?
Well, whatever, escape.
One of the bugs escaped.
One of the bugs, fucking escaped.
That means you died, by the way.
If you escaped a hole, that means you died.
You bastard.
See, these guys are locked in here forever.
Can you get out of here?
How about trying to get down?
You're not getting anywhere.
I'm going to shoot that giant out of you.
You can't even do it.
That's it.
I got the key.
I'm going to go in the golden room, the golden palace, and pick up the lazy beam.
What?
What is this deal?
Is this a shoot right to a people?
So what's this practice deal?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Ew.
This game is gross.
No, I take money.
I love the money.
I absolutely love money.
It's the best thing in the world.
Whoa, that was an explosion.
We're going down to this room.
Okay.
Did I miss anything?
Do I have to go back up here?
Or something?
What the hell is this?
What is this?
Do I go in this?
Oh my god, this guy's...
What is this guy?
Can I help?
I'm going to get him down.
I'm going to get him down off that rope.
He's going to die.
Oh, whatever.
Scroll you.
Let's scroll down here.
And this is the room I need to go in right now.
Oh, I have to fight this little worm.
So much, I just...
Okay, so how many lives do I get?
I get like ten lives, right?
Like two at least, two at three lives, right?
What is...
Where's the other stuff that's all over again?
You don't get lives, and you don't get lives in this game.
Is that what you're trying to tell me right now?
How can I don't have...
This is the stupidest game I've ever played!
How... why would...
This is the time...
You know what?
I'm not going to do anything.
I'm going right back to that same boss.
Got worms out of a bitch that's going down right now.
Hey, worm!
Is it...
Is it a different guy?
Is it different...
Why is it...
Where's the worm?
The worm looked a lot easier than this guy.
What is it?
Is this whole game just like randomly generated?
Is it stupid?
I'm going to like punch him in the face.
I'll punch you!
I'm going to punch you right in your face!
You see, that's how you're doing.
That's a pro tip right there.
See all those bugs that were around him?
They're not there anymore, aren't they?
See, I'll do it again!
Get rid of them!
Stupid goddamn bugs!
And that's how you win.
That's how you beat the shit in your pool on them too.
And that's how you get the most massive points.
Cartetrate.
Cartetrate!
Neat the Cartetrate!
Oh...
I don't have enough life to do in a bug move again.
I don't have enough life to do in a bug move.
And you know what? That's what he's not much dead.
I'm going to beat the game.
I just beat the game!
This game's supposed to be on.
Just...
We're doing it again.
We're going to do it again. Go!
Get out of my way!
Just get him a stick!
You know?
See you later!
If you play that game, you're at the start of a bitch in my opinion.
And we're not friends anymore.
So I'll get that in here.
Stop tucking you, you old guy.
Die, slide!
Hello?
You see, um...
Did he die?
What am I?
Oh, I'm going to put these headphones back in.
I mean, he still has a heart left.
It's not like he didn't die completely.
Why is he playing this guy, by the way?
All right.
Let's salvage the grandpa run.
It's going to be impossible!
Oh, poor grandpa.
Don't worry, he'll get over it.
Grandpa rages all the time.
He'll get over it.
Ten bombs.
And he died three times.
Make it four, because I'm probably not going to make it out of this room.
Nope.
Oh, there's no way.
There's no way.
Like, there's not a chance.
Hahaha.
Ding, ding, ding, ding, and that's the... right there.
Well, that's going to wrap it up, guys.
Thanks, everybody, so much for coming.
This will all be on YouTube in the next...
...like half an hour or so, so if you missed it from the beginning...
...didn't really do any good runs.
Unfortunately, it wasn't a good night for Isaac.
So...
But that's okay, head phone, regardless.
So thanks, everybody, again, for coming so much.
You guys all rock and roll.
And I will see you guys all soon.
So take care, everybody.
And let's... end this dream.
Oh, and grandpa just says goodbye, too, and then he loves you all.
Right, grandpa?
Oh, and he's coming in here, hold on.
Grandpa, get in here.
You need to apologize to these people.
I apologize, daddy.
Okay, I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry, you know.
Rage takes over us all.
And the game was just a little too hard.
But I love everybody.
I hope you guys have a fantastic Sunday...
...and...
...gloved grandpa.
And goodbye.
That's it, goodbye.
Now we're gonna eat in my 10 minutes.
You gotta have a page, Adam.
Adam, let's go.
I bring you dog, too.
I'm gonna feed her.
All right, see you later.
So that's gonna be the end, guys.
Thanks a lot for watching.
I really do appreciate it.
And of course, again, take care.
Everybody.
Thank you.