Okay, so guys
Welcome to binding a Isaac I play through or my first one I guess
Ooh, I got the eye the pinky eye I
I figured what this thing does
TF2 would not work I couldn't get it to I couldn't stream it for some reason
It was all laggy and glitchy and crazy and I couldn't do anything about it
I'm gonna have to figure out why that's happening because that's not good at all
Not at all you have nothing for me
Didn't really find anything besides
Oh a chance to do poison that's pretty sick
I have any bombs or anything looks like we're just gonna go fight the boss
Kane versus pin right pin what you got
You ain't got nothing to be buddy. Oh
I see the one that just kind of jumps out. It's it's that agreement right there cool cool cool cool
Well you out
No, I wish burger boy was in this game as a playable character
Oh
Am I not hitting him? You just killed himself
What a stupid bastard
Dining Dining Dining Dining Dining let's go
The basement too
What you know I'm not playing as Isaac so I don't have the bomb the luxury of having like the bombs
Get out of here get out of here
Both both both actually I got a plug by headphones and that's one thing I didn't do
Headphones you're in and oh you sure you want to do this? Yes, I'm sure
I'm sure I'm gonna be party
Let's go
How do you record games as fraps F9 I think is by default
Oh
The book of shadows I love this thing this gives you a shield when you hit space
I'm gonna have the bombs
MVP oh
MVP
And he's got nothing on me and he's got nothing on you
Oh, and for future reference if you're watching this on YouTube and I'm responding to random questions on the stream
So I'm not like talking of burger boy like he's not like here with me and my auto's not like in the room with me
So auto what do you think about fraps like an F9?
This is wrath of the lamb
Wrath of the lamb DLC
Excuse me sure
Where I love the noise those guys make
Where
TF2 is not going to start unfortunately I
Have to do some bug fixes or find out why the stream was lagging like incredibly
Expl it was it was it was an exploit. I have no idea why it's something I have to spend some time with
Question is actually can I put the book of shadows on and walk in here?
I bet I can let's find out oh
Absolutely I can oh baby look at that and
Pills I'm cane taking the pills would be good tears up hell yeah, and what's this gonna be?
Health up like it in and on I'm gonna get hurt right here. It was worth it totally worth it totally worth it
Yeah, the YouTube chat is not really ideal
It takes it when you write a message if there's a bunch if let's say like five people write a message at the same time
It kind of puts everything in a queue and like spams it after like two minutes. It's very weird
She got room baby. Oh, that's a dime. That's a dime. Okay, now I'm gonna go in the coin room
Going in that coin room
Let's see all right
This is a bunch of pills I think isn't it that's the coin purse I
Think that's the coin purse. Yep. Oh my god. And look at this and I'm gonna buy these pills over here too
This is gonna be insane
Bombs our key
What's this one?
Health up health up again. Oh
My god, what is this balls? Look at this guys then I'm gonna buy this too. Whatever this is it's gonna be good
Or it'll be teleport pills. Yeah, Kane if you have any pills when you take when you're playing with Kane
They are just then you'll never get bad pills ever
Is a health in that room. I want it and I want this too
What what just happened
What the hell was that
All right, all right, I just put a bomb down right here moved over and put up and then looked over at the chat and then I got hurt
Which is happened the bomb like come up with me did the fly hit it?
What the hell was that
Oh, I like looked over at the chat like what are people saying dad get hurt
I wanted to open this oh
Come on now
The reason why I'm not streaming on Twitch anymore is because I get 720 on YouTube
I'm not partnered on Twitch
Because I have a contract with the shinnima that makes it so I can stream on here. I
Can't believe I didn't get that
I keep believe I did not get that item I'm an idiot
Eh, wait for me
All right, so it looks like we got some fruit punch right here some high-sea ectocooler
If anyone knows if that is you get plus 20 gem points
Yeah, that right there that like green stuff right here is ectocooler high-sea ectocooler the rest is fruit punch
Pinkie eye
Oh god
Why do they have to have such big tears?
Okay, I get the book a shadow again. I
Got the book of shadows
I need bombs I need bombs bad
Get away for me a
Nickel
These guys can't do anything just don't want to get myself hurt. I got a
Curve the bullet like unwanted. Oh come on. You're better than this germa
I miss every single time. Oh god. Oh
The wow, where's boo boo
Boomman 61 is my binding of Isaac
My binding of Isaac buddy. He like tells me all these things I need to know
Mmm pinky eye a matchstick I
Think I think I'm gonna stick with pinky eye
So wait you the 720 stream is bad is that what you guys are saying the 720p stream is not good
That's
That doesn't make a whole lot of sense. I don't understand why
Whole lot of weird stuff going on in today's stream. I don't know what's going on here. Oh
Yeah, you got nothing slough
Sorry slough, but you did
Favorite class and TFT was the engineer
Yeah, I
Just want no, I don't want that I want the
I
Want the book of shadows because the book of shadows is really good. I
Got my fly buddy fly him with me
He's gonna bend the knee and away. Where's he? Oh, yeah, it's right. He only comes out when I randomly when I shoot people
That's an amazing item by the way
Me and my fly
Go fly away
To the end of time oh
Oh, no mini greens book of shadows. I had to I'm not losing all my money
To the end these guys are shooting at me get out of my face
Ha
Well the resolution has nothing to do with the the chat. It's just the YouTube chat is is bad
I'm not gonna sugar code it the YouTube streaming chat is
This is not so good
Oh
I hate these enemies when you get in a room with these guys and there's more than three or four of them
Say your prayers because they are so annoying
I don't have like any money
Good luck on your test tomorrow, dude. I forget how your name got went by a great way too fast
But a good luck on your test anybody who has a test good luck on your finals if you already had them
Hope you aced them and if you haven't had him yet then go in there and sack them silly
metaphorically
I'm going in here get some get me some items
Oh
Big problem oh big problem triple shot baby I killed plenty of birds
Look at that. Oh, this is this could be a good playthrough if I'm not an idiot
Like that I thought I could hide behind the thing and move but it was a rock in front of me
I need to open this because they might be hearts in there I need to
No, but this is nickel
Across the pond and whales that's a far away. That's a far away is away. Oh the battery
This look at it's just sticking out of my head how gruesome
All right, I got a lot of good items, but not a whole lot of health right now. I cannot screw this up
I really need to like pay attention and not die because that would be so bad
All right, I got everything in need
Can't get to the secret room or an oven bombs. I am not going to do to you two again today because it's just I
Don't want to have to deal the headache. I'll have to try and test it out later. All right husk
No, this is gonna be hard. This is not gonna be easy
Right try hard mode how to like pay attention to only the game
Just for fun. I'm turning it on I don't want to chance it
Bump right into him come on bumper cars baby. All right. We're good to go
What is this eight ball?
Oh
It gave me like a rag on my head. What the hell? I
Had a magician
All right, doesn't the magician take you to the secret room? Well, no, he doesn't it sits this it's the I can now it doesn't
This game is not free. It's pretty cheap though
This game is only I
Dollar zone steam
Actually, isn't there a sale going on for it right now or is the sale over?
Yeah, the no damage achievements. I don't know man. I don't think I could ever get those
Because you'll get so confident you'll get to the end of a level and be like I got this in the bag and then you just die
Oh my god, I got rage now every time but
As long as I play this safe I will beat this whole game right now I
Can't I can't be stupid about this though. I gotta be I gotta be smart. I gotta be smooth. Oh
The Liberty cap is a random mushroom
Every room and this is a chance to have poison I think I'm gonna stick with the mushroom guys
Cuz I want those random mushroom achievement thingies achievement am I talking about
Yeah, I see I got massive like speed increase now and like I'm like Connors little or
Of my is my my playing a trick on me or is this just damage?
Not going in there screw that
Exam tips well good luck on your exams. I actually made an exam tip video
Did you did you check that out? It'll give you all kind look at how little I am yeah, hey look I tiny
Get away from me
There we go that's what I'm talking about
Who is a spy video from like a month ago?
How you see damage I wish you could see damage in this game be an interesting feature
Little numbers popping up over everybody's heads
What's that what's that dude? I don't know whatever. I don't want it pride
Get away from me pride get away from me pride
He's doing it too often I can't when you do the other move
Wow, he didn't do the he didn't do the other move once what a son of a bastard
I think it with the emperor card does boo boo. I need your help boo
Anytime I'm gonna skype call it boo. I'll just say an item and he'll go oh
It does plus 25 damage and I'll go thanks boo
I don't know what it does, but I'm gonna keep it
I have faith super greed he's a pain in the ass
He's a super pain. How did I not get hit right there?
Don't ask me how I did not get hit I have no idea. Oh, I need that heart
Take that and I'm gonna get this heart
Because I need it
Woo
Yeah, boo boo does have quite a sexy voice. I will tell you it's true. I
Can't get these bombs are
Teleport you to the boss room good to know. Thanks a lot, dude good to know. Oh, I'm turning this on because I need it
I
Do I have enough money for anything?
Let's find out
I'm gonna get it. It's always good to have and steam sale like
Probably should have tried to find the secret room to get the steam sale
I think it's gonna be right here
Oh
Yeah
99 bombs
That makes me happy
Now I'm just gonna I'm gonna go blow up every damn thing in
The item room down here
Well, nothing the gambling room
All right, hey, what's going on? I love you to look casino here everybody is gonna do wrong gonna kill myself
I just tried to make a joke right there and my brain is too dumb to be able to make a joke and do my joke at the same time so
Whatever
Let's go
boss room boss fight
Dot com dot edu
Cane versus fish should I
This could this could you know what I need to start dropping some but some tactical bombs
This guy can be a real pain in the butt
Oh
God that was some dodging right there. Oh my god
All right
Okay
Juicy juice Jesus juice
Pretty cool
I'm gonna go I
I
Apologize for the coughing I'm still sick
Full health you know what that means oh
Get away from me
Well, that was a that was a collateral right there. Oh
Oh
God
Thank you for saving me
Book of shadows appreciate it
Okay, that's it that's another situation where I hit E
Right here to drop the bomb I moved over here looked at the chat and I would have just gotten hurt because I wasn't big
All right, let's not do that again
What oh
Why did I thought why did that not work?
Okay, that's good to know that that's here
Huh, why did that not work flies get out of the way you've roared and everything
Thank you
If I find one of those blood donation machines I'm gonna use the hell out of it
Oh
Yeah, there's nothing I could do to get away from that I
Hate I hate these enemies
If there's one enemy I hate in the game okay, I could be quiet. I need to try out now
Oh, I'll take it for sure
Hey, that trap
Let's go down
Let's go another room with these stupid brain bastards. I hate these guys
You know what everyone just blow up right in here. Thank you
Some might call that a waste I call it a journey
Oh
Where
Okay, I
Think the secret room is oh no no
You know what everyone come here. Let's all have a family picnic come stand right next to me
That's how I deal with those guys got plenty of bombs
Oh great greed
Sorry, it's just regular greed is a worse
It's just regular greed don't worry
Give me that money and give me your key
Oh
Away
Mm-hmm, I'm not going in there those rooms always give me trouble. I always die
How do you shoot a nangle?
So if when I hit up and I move to the left a little bit it kind of like curves it
So if you hit left and up kind of at the same time you'll curve your bullets like bling bling
You can do it any any direction to it doesn't have to be up or down so you can do it left and right to
Do I think I'm gonna be all right if I can get some more health up I should be able to kill mom's heart for sure
Oh, okay, okay, okay, okay, I wanted this
Don't worry I promise you I'm not crazy
This room if you don't know because this is wrath of the lamb this is adding a wrath of the lamb
If when I walk over this it hurts me for a heart
But it has a chance that it's gonna drop something good in the room. So I'm gonna keep doing it
Come on keep hurting me. I know you want to give me something
Oh
Fine
Because now I can just go all the way over here and go back to that room where all those hearts were and
I'm fine
See yeah what what what what what what what what what what what what
Okay, oh
I almost just had a heart attack. I thought I could not get back into this room. I
Would it I would have just been so bad right there
I don't have enough of the ladder I
Probably get it later
What is the sword room the sword room when you go in there you can only go in there with full health and
It's a you fight a wave of enemies three waves of enemies and then after you get to have the item that's in the room
It's pretty cool. I don't I just never go into it because I always end up getting myself killed in there
troll bomb get away now I can get the ladder if I want it no
You bad pets I'll go get it might as well have it right
Might as well own it
Go go go go go go go go go go go go go go go go
I'll have you thank you very much. Oh, oh, I don't need the heart because I can go up here
The blue hearts are spirit hearts
So when I pick up a spirit heart it
Last only as long as it's there you see how the red hearts are there pretty much permanently
The spirit hearts are only there until they get if I get hurt right now
It's gonna take that spirit out of way and I don't get it back even if I get help
Playing bover band right now I feel like I'm like spulunking
Oh the rock oh
I'm not I must be doing max damage am I yeah? I'm doing the maximum amount of damage you can do in the game
So that's good that's good I'm stuck
I got stuck on the rock
Thing I had my book of shadows
Okay, that's epic hack. I don't want it. Is that epic? Oh is that epic hacker? Is that chemical peel? I don't know
I don't want it. I hate epic hack epic hack makes you shoot like those green balls and you can hurt yourself with it
And I always kill myself guaranteed with it every time
Kane versus war one of the four horsemen. Oh my god, I am destroying him
I am absolutely destroying him
Wow usually this guy takes a lot more hits than this. Okay, see I look hit him in
And I got a cube of meat
It's in its chemical peel that's chemical peel all right
No deal with the devil. I don't want the deal to devil chemical peel
If that's chemical peel then I will get it. I'm so scared. What if it's epic hack?
All right, at least a dozen people have said it's not epic hack. Oh
Thank God
This game is so worth it though that that somebody just asked it
Is it game? Yeah, it's worth it absolutely
It is probably the best game I've played for under $20 ever
This game's only five bucks
Without this without the sale
The expansion and everything it's I think it's eight dollars with everything
But I mean I've spent more money on games that I'd never played than I have on this
I bought DSX for $60 and I and I played the game for an hour and ten minutes. I like it. I didn't like it
I never heard this music before actually no, I think I have I hate these enemies these are the worst you have to kill their hearts
Dory
I
Thank you
Yeah, this game at this game is $4.99 to divide I
Have the expansion though as well. I think the expansion's three bucks
So it's gonna cost you eight dollars for everything, but there's a steam sale. I think
Still going you know what I'm going to quelch this once and for all I'm going to just look and see how much this is
You store page
Binding of Isaac
Okay, so the bind it. Yeah, so it is
$4.99 for the binding of Isaac if you can see and then the
Wrath of the lamb DLC is three to three bucks
So there you go the steam sale is overrun it apparently
It was over a while ago
It's a very good price
The last time I spent
Less than five dollars on a game or five dollars on a game and
I'm using this
The under twenty dollars last time I spent that and actually like really enjoyed it and played for a long time was probably orx must die
Orx must die I got a lot of play time out of that and the game was only 15 bucks
So it's yeah, I'd say it's a steal at this price
You'll put at least 30 to 50 hours into this game if you really enjoy it you'll put at least 30 hours into it at least
All auto
Where is auto my dog
And
I didn't want to open that I could just blown it up I could have just blown the damn thing up
Flat penny no, I don't want that I do not want you
Go
What a bad place for this these enemies
At least I have this I would have taken so much damage right there. It's not even funny. I would have taken a
Thousand point I would have died I probably would have died right there. She's oh
Get away from it you jumping frog freaks
Damn it
There we go see you later
Yeah, you know I looked I was looking at Daisy
Daisy looks pretty cool. I just I thought it was a like a standalone mod or standalone game
Arm a two is like 50 dollars for the whole package isn't it?
I need to drop some some cash on that
Because don't you need armor two and then you need armor two one of one of armor two's expansion packs or something to be able to play it
And I think armor two is 39 or 40 or something when I saw that I was like, yeah
Going this way so it does armor two is 30 and then don't you need expansion to do it
That expansion
Let's go you oh
You egg burger, you know what let's go let's fight come stand next to me. Let's talk
Oh
I keep thinking that bad bad I can't even hit this guy get out of the way you son of a oh
Ah
This guy is blocking the way of me shooting you stupid son of a B.I. I
I capital I
Everybody in this room blows up
Arm a two is free what
Arm a two last time I looked at armor two was money
Do you have a three is real money auction house? I have not even used it I
I don't I don't even care
I was mad about it at first and I was kind of like that's a little weird, but
It's it's gonna help drive the game for years. So I'm not I'm not really all that concerned about it
I
Open sesame. I think I'm gonna fight mom here in a second
Maybe this next room number dime
All right, let's go fight oh no no no no no no I need to get some I get some coins I
Got coins
Operation
2033 Metro
The deck is coming over the sequel soon, aren't they
I'll get the compass just cuz I'm not gonna be able to buy anything later
And I let's go fight let's go fight mom's big fat disgusting leg
Follow me
I don't want I don't want to go in the sordrome it scares me because if I lose health and I die to mom I am gonna be
P.O.D
Let's go mom
Oh, what do you say mommy dearest come on step on yourself. Oh she what she is just killing her so bad
Oh
All right, that's fine. Go ahead swap me. I don't care and she's gonna do it
Let's keep going
I only got two more rooms and then maybe I can go I don't know if I'm gonna be able to go to show
I don't think I've beaten the game enough times to go to show every time
Oh
What's that what's that I want to look at it
Cursed skull oh boo boo what does this do?
I don't know hey, what does the cursed skull do guys does anybody know?
Does anybody know
I need to know what it does because if it's good I want to keep it all right. We'll come back to it. I'll come back
It's gonna be there
Cursed skull is bad, okay, all right good at all
Do not get this okay
Chest inside of a chest chest exception
Yeah away from me
Health up exactly what I was looking for
Oh, it's me go get him flies yeah
This book of shadows is the thing that's making this playthrough possible it really is oh
Go go go go go yes
Oh
Lord have mercy on me geez
Health up
Health up again
Oh my god, you're gonna be kidding me teleport pills. Let's just take them I
Like to thank the book of shadows for making this possible because without him I wouldn't be receiving this award
And I want to thank my mother and my father and my parents
Go up
All right, I'm not going to the secret room just take a look who's in there my buddy greed
The name's greed oh
Gad see ya
If Isaac's if Isaac's health is brought down to a half of a heart Isaac is then teleported to the last room completed
Um, that sounds pretty incredible
That sounds pretty ridiculous actually, but to be honest if even if you complete the last room with half a heart
When you get to the next room after the last room you're probably gonna die
That's still pretty cool if I did not have the mushroom I would absolutely be taking that
Get out of here you spider I never liked spiders
Creepy crully
You want to thank your mother she tried to kill you this is true. This is very true
But I have a short short-term memory loss forgot though forgot those things
Yeah, I hate these guys. He's got her annoying. I stick my head up and then you know I joke by you don't hit me
Yes, I will take that
Every single door is now open down here
What's the game from E3 you're looking forward to the most um?
I you know the Wii U the Wii U is actually really really cool
It's it's very very interesting. It's kind of like when the Wii first came out it was like what is that I
Think I might just get it. It looks like it could be fun
Because the coolest thing in the entire world with the Wii U. Let me explain this. This is the coolest thing ever
So if you're playing on a TV that's and you're like let's say you're in your living room and
Somebody comes in and they say oh I want to I want to I need the TV
I want to use the TV and you're like dude. I'm playing a game you with this no no you can't take the TV and
Sometimes I mean back when I was younger. It didn't matter how much you complained or how much you wanted to oh my god
Or how much you wanted to stay in the room you had to get kicked off the TV with the Wii U
It's going they're gonna make it so when somebody kicks you off the TV
You can just I'm using like my hands right now. I'm not even like my hands are even on the keyboard
You can it goes to the screen and you have like a it's a mini TV on the screen
So you let's say you get kicked off
You can just play on the Wii U pad screen like okay fine. You can take it. I'll go in my room and play the game
That's insane. That's unbelievable
That is the one of the coolest things I think of that system so far is the fact that you can like
Take the system with you around the house
I'm gonna go to this last room
And plus I mean this might sound kind of like kind of disgusting, but like how how awesome would that be if you were just like you know
I'm playing Super Mario 15 whatever comes out. I mean I gotta take like a dump and you can just like you're taking
I know I know I'm girls I know
But still like it the possibilities are
Arameless
Somebody should actually grab those teleport pills I
Will no, I know I won't I don't have any I don't I gonna hurt myself if I go in there
Let's just go fight the boss
Bye, bye
The Wii U
I don't like the name that's I wish they would change the name
Imagine you dropped it in the top
I could imagine that would be one of the worst things to possibly happen
But I guess why how would you drop it?
Like oh, oops
I just thought of the noise they would make
It's a big thing man, it's a pretty big device
Let's go kill mom. Let's go fight mommy dearest
Oh
Go away for me
You know, I'm not even gonna go item hunting. I'm just gonna try and kill mom
Yeah, I'm not going item hunting. I'm just gonna go try and go for the kill I think
Tears up I think I'm at max tears to
How am I not a max tears doesn't make any sense?
You know you only live once
Yeah, gonna kill me sorry buddy
Neither is your friend over here I live
Wii U
Get
The noises I make when I play this game is really surprises me
I got back to 99 bombs you kidding me
Everybody blows up
Oh
All right
Good to go
No, I did I did not take the brimstone from the devil for a very important reason
Because brimstone I would have taken two hearts away and if I get to go to show
I'm gonna want those two hearts and I am doing so much damage right now
I it doesn't it doesn't even matter at this point. I have a very very very very very good setup. So I think I'm okay
I'll get it by a big rotten tooth
Double gluttony
Double gluttony no
Get away from me get away from me gluttony
Will you just die?
That's all I ask I just ask of you to be dead
That's all I ask
Oh
Get oh
That guy I'm just got a tooth collateral only in the binding of Isaac can you say the words tooth collateral
And have it make sense
All right, you know what I'm I'm going the other way. I'm I'm ending this I'm I'm literally ending this right now
I'm going into the uh
I'm ending this like I'm going into oh god, I can't even talk
Go go
I
All right, I'm I'm not gonna go the other way. Let's I'm just going to fight her. I'm going to fight her
She's got nothing on me
And who's in here
Yeah
Do what what's what's the super me boy challenge? Oh, I can all right the the real goal of her is to oh god
No, I'm gonna kill him. No
I always do that man. I do that way too often hold on I got I got a text
All right text complete
Do you remember
Derma turn around the trash room can only be one room away over there
Yeah, let's oh
That has to be right here
You are absolutely right my friend
Good eyes, but I guess at this point if I kill mom right here
Then and I don't go to show and that's over anyways came what what's this what the hell is this?
Oh
What is that
It lives who is this guy?
What what is that like a different version of mom's heart?
Oh, no, oh no, I can't fight those things. Oh, I can't good. Oh
Did you see that like ricochet?
Let's go it lives
Don't you know it's impolite to text during a live stream. That's true, but oh my god. It was my mother
Oh god, I'm such a kid. I'm freaking out
I'm gonna do it. I did it. I did it
Yeah, yeah, yeah, hey, yeah
It was my mother
All right, um looks like I'm not gonna be able to go to show
Oh, I finally unlocked that guy
Took me long enough
Because I played Isaac what what what's going on
What what oh
Oh dear goodness. I made it to heaven
Okay
Um
Oh god, I am scared right now is the first time I've ever done this
No, no, no, I I gotta blow no no, I'm freaking out way too much I slow down all right big
Oh my god, he's gonna kill me
I
Gotta get rid of all this stuff in the room. This is the problem right here
God what a mess
I
We what's this does no health bar left get out of here
Get get away from me
Oh
Just inside of a chest
That's sit-a-dale give me whatever's in here
Oh, okay, I have a feeling I yeah right say goodbye guys. This is it see you later
Oh, if I did not have the book of shadows, I would have been done
Again, I'd like to thank the book of shadows for making this out possible
Oh
Geez
Again again
Again
Is every single room like a boss oh get that bomb placement
Every single room is is a mini boss then huh wow
Oh
My god
Hmm
Two slots and uh spirit heart that's okay. I'll take it oh
My god, I'm actually I think I'm actually gonna be I'm gonna do this guys because I have the book of shadows
I can I can be incredibly reckless because I have the book of shadows
Look at how this reckless some being
Oh
Okay
Red patch don't remember what red patch does stream I need you up I need your help
I could go to the secret room
Don't get too reckless it's a good good advice
Red patch what does it do I don't know I don't have the time or the patience to look it up
You too
I'll stick with it I'm gonna stick with it
Okay, I got to use a smart advantage
You use the use the guard to my advantage
Just like shoot mania
No, it's gone. Oh my god
Gotta get rid of one of them
Go away get away
How much like does this one oh my god really know
Oh
And we cry and increases your attack when you get hit okay, I don't want that because I have max damage right now
All right, I'm gonna take the mushroom still
Let's go
I'm yeah, forget it. I'm going I'm going this way. Give me that heart
I'm
Secret room already was there
Oh, I'm gonna go up and then down
Oh, why did I waste that I didn't even need it they just scared me
Oh monstro you ain't got nothing you ain't got nothing burgaboy masstro
Oh get hit with the tooth
Get hit with a tooth
That was lucky
All right
Is there more than one secret room there could be one right over here
Maybe no, you know what I am not messing around anymore. I'm going right. I'm going there
I'm not gonna do any more bowl
snip
Going to fight what was in this room down here. Oh my god
Okay
Focus shadows can say to milling in times
Well, I just might as well go in here. I open the damn door
I'm gonna use it
And doesn't this do something now that's a book of bailout
There is no max damage in this game
Well, isn't that an indication how much damage you do
I thought that's what it was
And two greets
Ah, it's got to be two they got to have two of everything, huh? It's like double mint gum
Double you play. I don't even know the money doesn't matter. That doesn't matter or matter
Double you pleasure double you fun. That's a statement of a great man double mint gum
I'm doing it. There we go
A cane versus Isaac
Whoa
He's
God I gotta utilize this to as best I can come on come on come on
Come on. I gotta use this as best I can come on
Oh, okay
Focus shadows come on. I got the power. I gotta be quiet now. I'm really not gonna do this
God
uh
Oh
Oh, and I got a text.
Oh, I can't believe that.
He had no health.
He had zero health.
I should have placed bombs, I know.
I just...
Oh, I was so close.
I was so close to beating this the entire game.
Like, that's the end of the entire game of Rath of the Lamb.
And I didn't do it.
Well, at least it's right.
Yeah, if I got one of the 20-20 hindsight, if I had done what I should have done, I didn't
know it was going to be like that, though.
Oh, well, that's going to be a pretty funny video.
Hey, here's a full playthrough of Binding of Isaac, except for the very end when I die,
when the boss has one health.
Oh, man.
The death animation started.
No.
Well, at least I tried.