Go zie
evils early as both is because the began at Microsoft
force
and told you
that told you was a happened
What a great streamer.
You know, most people when they stream, they're like, they have like you, if you can get
used to their schedule, you get to get to the sky.
It's always live at this particular time.
He's always going to be, no, no, this is, it's 5 a.m. right now.
What, what am I doing here right now?
Ugh, I should be in bed.
But no, I'm not in bed.
Is there a reason why we're streaming at 5 in the morning?
No.
Actually, the kind of is, I'm trying to reset my sleep schedule.
And what better way to do that than to get my gamer license back?
Because if you missed the last stream, my gamer license was revoked.
I had guppy and like seven familiars in the binding of Isaac.
And I lost and my gamer license was revoked.
So to get it back, we're going to play Super Meatball.
This is an old classic.
I actually, I played through this game on my channel like three years ago.
But I'm just going to chill.
I'm going to play it.
I'm going to play Cryptarch too.
We'll see how far I get with this.
I might just do like the first or second chapter and then switch to Cryptarch.
Because that's like a current game.
But I'm going to warm up with some Meatball.
It's been a while.
Holy crap, my computer is burning.
You get, I would get a fire extinguisher and spray it.
But we're going to play a couple games to keep me awake.
Start with Meatball.
Warm up a little bit.
Play a little bit of Cryptarch.
If I'll be getting a juke.
If I complete the forest and into, I'd say like the first two or three chapters,
then you can, you know, you got your junior license.
I have my Learnage permit.
But without further ado, we're going to get this off the screen.
We all know the story.
I deleted this blast save file I had here.
So this is completely clean, fresh slate.
We're going to go for A pluses on every single one of these at least initial levels.
Why don't you put your chat in the stream display?
Well, I have no idea how to do that.
And just before we get started, I guess we'll address this.
We're going to address this, okay?
I get a lot of people asking me about, um,
well, I think that these first few levels are brainless.
Um, I get questions all the time about like,
what are you going to do this when you're going to do that?
When are you going to XYZ?
Where's this sub button?
How can I donate to you?
Why do you not show ads?
Your stream sucks.
Where's your overlay?
Honestly, this like first month or so,
trying to like stream a lot more often.
Is more so a trial run from me to see how like settings work than anything else?
You know, like, uh, could I do all that stuff?
But no, I want to make sure like I can actually stream with like a constant bit rate.
I'm actually going to do that again.
But fate like stuff like face cam will never,
will never, ever be on this channel.
You're your examples came back positive for LSD, cocaine and TCP,
but there were no performance enhancing drugs.
Well, that's good to know.
Shit.
I forgot to say this is supposed to be a non-death playthrough.
I wouldn't die one time.
Alright, how do you, this one's just a big add set.
I've already died too many times here, I think.
I'm gonna find out.
Alright, I think the band-aids.
I've totally forgot about the band-aids in this game.
Oh shit, that was a word.
I can't fuck this up.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Slow down.
I'm trying to get my gamer license back and not throw it at the trash.
Oops.
Okay, you can command a video for this one.
I actually don't remember.
Oh shit, I didn't even know I forgot about the ones at the top.
Okay, I gotta be careful with this.
Okay.
Sky pup.
Well, I did it.
There's all kinds of secrets that I forget in this game, but I did that one.
I think there's something else you have to do in there.
Was the Wonder Book video the video that cost your entire bank account? No.
Dude, a Wonder Book.
A Wonder Book is like $8 for the Wonder Book and the game.
It's not that expensive.
That stuff is so old.
Wonder Books is like, I really wish we'd see more of that shit though.
It's so cool. Whoa, whoa, didn't get an A plus.
Excuse me. I also didn't get this.
Fuck.
No, we're not getting the A plus zero. We get the band-aid.
Now we'll get the A plus.
It's magic for crying out loud.
What the fuck?
Was it five seconds?
What's the quick restart button? I know it exists.
Is it select?
I'll figure that out.
Nothing I gotta get used to is the Xbox One controller.
Shit.
The Xbox One controller is kind of odd because we'll go over this too.
Every single one of the, because I don't use the analog, all the D-pads are individual buttons.
So it's kind of odd.
You know, when you scroll your thumb across the bottom of the Xbox One controller, it's like...
It just kind of feels awkward because I'm pushing my hand over popcorn kernels.
I'll get used to it though.
No, that's not gonna... No, just die again.
Here we go.
My PlayStation fan, I'm an all-game fan. I like all games.
Doesn't matter what it is.
All the D-pads?
All the D-pads.
I'm gonna get the Band-Aid on this as well, because you gotta get the Band-Aids.
Shit, I blew it.
But if they made like a wonder book for the PS4, it's not because just like, oh yeah, I can't wait to make like a video on it.
That like is actually a very cool concept.
Shit.
They made four games for that thing.
There was an unannounced like...
Alright, hold on, hold on. Let me get this Band-Aid and we'll talk.
Fuck you.
Oh my god, alright, I gotta stop going on that one. That's the big-sum mistake.
Oh, I did it anyway. Alright, fuck it. We're not even getting the Band-Aid.
I'll get it later.
I don't know, we gonna do it again?
That was really sloppy. I could make that cleaner.
This is also really sloppy, but you know, still got it.
I actually like the feel of the Xbox One controller, where the buttons are placed and where the analog is replaced.
I could really do without how loud this fucking thing is.
Really, like every single one of these buttons, it's crazy. Like the bumpers, I'm gonna hit serious of buttons on this controller.
You'll hear it, ready?
Like half the buttons on this thing make a really loud annoying noise.
Especially the bumpers. Those are so loud.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I was gonna skip the Band-Aids for now. We're going for A-plosses.
I'm not catching them now, actually.
I wanna go on the warp zone.
Oh, the steam, that's right, the steam controller did release.
Or kind of, isn't it like, can you use it or something if it is a beta or something like that?
Oh, I sip on coffee. This is the commander video level, right?
I believe it is. It is.
Oh, right. Okay. You can like use it when you...
Okay. I got it.
Commander Video actually thinks my favorite character in this game. If I remember.
I must have watched the Super Meat Boy playthrough 15 times.
Well, now you get to see one live. I don't know if this is gonna be a playthrough or not.
I'm just kind of playing just to keep myself awake and warm up my video game skills.
Well, I officiate your bar mitzvah.
I don't think I have the qualifications to do that.
You know what I mean? I don't have... That's a easy bandaid, I'll get it.
I don't have... That's a easy bandaid, I'll get it.
I'm rushing it a little too much.
How many of these sound effects are using the Isaac?
Yeah, I'd be surprised. I mean, it is the same team, right?
That was stupid.
I'm not gonna use it.
That was still an A plus.
Wow.
How many times have I completed this game?
Maybe like three? Maybe a little bit less than that?
Maybe a little bit less than that?
What does that mean?
I completed it maybe two or three times.
Or maybe a little bit less than two and a half?
Yeah, that is true.
I've completed this game maybe two and a half times.
One of those playthroughs in particular, not the one that I did on my channel,
but just in particular.
I was really into it. Super duper.
Ultra into this game.
That was a long time ago though.
No, another here.
When did this game come out?
Whenever the launch of Super Meepoi was, it was like my favorite game for that like year that it was out.
2009 does 10.
Am I gonna go for all A pluses in the playthrough?
I can try.
It's gonna be fucking hard though.
Am I doing?
You just do this.
I don't want to get that bandaid.
It's really not that hard.
It's all about just sitting here.
I could just time it like this.
I don't have to go fast anymore.
Oh fuck.
Fuck.
Can't get caught up in the bandaid.
This is an A plus run.
Nothing more, nothing less.
I'm not having my chance right there.
The game, the game is gaming license never existed.
If you do it is tofu boy.
Are any levels even completeable with tofu boy?
I thought that the game was uncompletable if you played with him.
Because he can only jump like 5 feet in the air or something.
See you.
Whoa.
My eyes just deceived me right there.
That was weird.
For some reason I thought I was much lower than I was.
Hmm.
A plus array.
Burger boy should be playable in this game.
I agree.
These aren't that hard to A plus.
Am I streaming at 5am?
I don't know.
It's a fun.
For fun sake.
Because why not, right?
I'm trying to put the squirrels.
Give me that A plus.
Because you've lost control of your life.
Yeah, I guess.
Hey, we won.
No dark world.
Only three bandages.
Two of the two warps.
I don't remember at all.
But the other two warps are.
Oh, I don't know what your gold PS4 is.
I'm not sure.
There we go.
Have I heard the invasion TF2 update?
That's pretty good.
It was pretty fun.
I should probably use Bicer Use Commander video for more or less.
Oh, come on now. This is not gonna be an A+.
I'm just gonna walk into the wall because it's not an A+.
Now that's keeps on fucking me up.
Wow! What am I doing here?
Whoa, I got stuck there.
I don't even know how to do that. I can just keep going the whole way.
Oh, I got too scared. Still on A+.
Commander video is useless. Yeah, it's fun to play. I like being on a float around. It's fun.
It doesn't like float around this commander video.
Do I have anything planned for Halloween? I have a video I want to make for Halloween,
but I don't even think it's gonna be possible.
Like, I really don't think it's a possible video to make.
I so badly want to do it though.
It could be so much fun.
I
try marking the ninja. I actually told me that that game is really good.
I don't remember who it was.
Oh, no, no, I sprayed that up. I'm going for speed here.
Yeah, I sprayed it up again, but it's okay.
No, nothing more.
Yeah, there we go.
How often do my 30-year-old eyes deceive me all the time?
More than you would think.
Give me the band-aid. Give me the band-aid.
Give me the band-aid. Give me this thing. Stop it. Thank you.
Oh, the love of all the band-aid.
I don't think I had enough.
I
best one-to-book game.
I don't know. That's a good question.
They're all fun. They're all interesting.
I've been over here for a while.
Yeah.
Hmm, I sprayed it up again.
Just screwing shit up, you know. I don't know how we do it around here.
What am I doing wrong here? I like remember just being able to drop down, right?
Yeah.
I
punch game.
This one more wonder book to play.
I have no idea how it is. I feel like it's not going to be that funny, but I've said that before
and some of the most times I've said that.
End up being like some of my favorite things I've ever recorded.
Like that GTA 5, like grab the Auto 5, all like the mobile ripoffs.
I really did. I like I didn't know if like I was going to want to make that.
Like I sat there for a second. I'm like, do it.
Is this funny?
Is this like what am I what I'm doing right now? Is this worth me doing?
I downloaded like 30 of those games and I'm just sitting there thinking,
what was this the right call?
Should I fucking done this?
I turns out I was one of my favorite things I've recorded in the last like,
probably at least six or 12 months.
German Lemmy or Infinite Wisdom in God damn how to pick up the ladies.
I'm not sure you know this dude, but I am single.
I'm currently single right now man. I don't know if I can give you the best advice on that.
Fuck the bandage. What am I doing?
Get in there. Get in there.
How many videos get thrown under the rug only seen by like me and star?
More than you would probably imagine.
Well, let's put it this way.
There are a lot of ideas.
And maybe not so much like the videos getting made.
But there's a lot of ideas that I would say get half made in and swept under the rug.
I've made entire videos. I actually have an entire video that I made.
That I have never uploaded.
It's just sitting there rendered ready for me to upload.
And I'll never release it because I don't like it.
Oh, that was quick.
But I don't know. I mean you guys probably noticed this recently.
The videos have the uploads have slowed down.
And that's mainly because I want to like I've already talked about it.
I don't even need to talk about it again. I'm turning into a broken record about this.
Long story short. I want to just make the videos that I like to make.
Rather than you know, I gotta make a video every day. I have to make a video. I've
make like four videos a week.
I'm just I'm back to where I was a few years ago where I just was like, you know what?
I like making these videos. I'm gonna make a video. I like making videos.
Oh, shit.
There's no time limit on these ones. There's no gold to get. There's no A plus to get here.
Just want to stay alive here.
Whoa, he came out of nowhere.
Ooh, okay, hold on. Hold on a second here. Don't screw this one up. I don't want life left.
Oh, fuck. Shit. Fuck. Dick. Every swear you can imagine. We gotta go back.
Shit. I had that too. I just overreacted.
That was like a just a true testament to why you should never overreact in this game.
You know, you probably should be just waiting here. I'm trying to remember all like the strats.
Wow, I get it again. All right, stop talking. Quiet, quiet that mouth of yours.
I can just beat this one so we can get out of here.
All right, we're skipping this warp zone for now. We're gonna come back to it.
I almost salvaged that. Whoa, what? Oh, right. I had to run into warp zone.
Oh, that's stuck.
Hello.
Yeah, I got I got I got I got canned from the DMV.
I would have loved to have grabbed that when I had the chance to get it.
Oh, you fucker.
Shit. That wasn't cool.
Yeah.
Play it safe. Just get the band-aid.
Yeah, I got a new plus out.
I wonder who made all the squishy sound effects for this game. Yeah, you know,
that's a question gets on my mind sometimes. You call them fully artists, right?
Yeah.
Guys, they just pretty much make weird sounds and hit meat with baseball bats and squish up
toilet paper with their mouths to make sounds. That wasn't an eight plus excuse me.
I got locked my thumb. Got locked in there.
Yeah.
No, just I gotta die. I'm gonna get over that quick enough.
Here we go.
Oh.
Open up, please.
Whoa.
16 seconds is a plus.
I mean, I don't know. I gotta go way faster than that.
No.
Yeah.
That's tough.
13, 14, 15.
There it is.
That's why I'm single mean star.
I don't know about that.
Whoa.
I actually just forgot what this level did.
You just go right to the right.
Hey, how are you?
Oh.
Whoa. I missed that one.
Oh, I messed up that one big time too.
Fuck.
Oh.
No.
No, I messed up the timing already.
Just walking to the dude. You gotta go right off the bat.
You gotta go one, two, three.
Boom.
Boom. No. I'm not. Okay. I'm all right.
No, no, no. I'm rocking this shit again.
Oh.
Oh, fuck.
Okay. I'm gonna fucking step on a rake.
I'm gonna set up a rake in my backyard just so I can step on it like fucking side show Bob and the Simpsons.
Chewie up. Oh, no. Whoa. I didn't get no way. I got a plus now.
That's really, really annoying.
What the hell was that? How would I just got an A plus for that?
That was a C plus at best. That was like a C minus.
How high was I when I made the TF2 sound mod? I didn't, I didn't make the TF2 sound mode.
That was somebody else.
Hey, hey, all right. Let's try it. Let's try this again.
Bob, Bob, I was just looking at the chat.
Whoops.
This one has a specific pattern. I have just not going to even care about.
I was just gonna try to do it on pure skill.
Here we go.
Wait, what is it? What does somebody say?
Not YouTube because if it is, you must have made like $2 this three months with the rate of
uploads and the content of it talking about Star and ArcGerma.
You don't have to do something for money.
Like, yeah, you can get paid for something but not do it for money.
Does that make any sense? What I just said.
Like, just because Star or I get paid from our videos doesn't necessarily mean we like do it
to make money.
Okay, look, there we go.
What is the boss of chapter two? I don't even remember.
Oh, it's this guy. It's Chad. There he is.
Hey, I did a chat.
Oh, shit.
Some of these bosses I do forget the pattern zone.
So it's going to take me into your couple of different areas.
It's going to take me like quite a few times, probably here.
Shit.
Oh, I got locked out of that one.
Oh, you fucker.
Damn it. It's going too fast.
Can you, you know, there are no a fuss on boss. What am I doing?
Oh, I already do it.
Going for like eight pluses and they don't even exist.
Oh, here. Okay.
Is this going to be the first small wall that I hit?
You fucking.
Can I get up to the other side without having to do all that?
I don't think I can.
Oh, shit. I blew it already.
Damn.
First fast, I just did the first one.
This is taking me a little longer.
Just going to make it.
I do that a lot in this game.
I will say.
Here we go.
You know, this is used to talking about like needing a new game.
I do too.
I think a lot of people do it, right?
Like it.
You go through phases.
Sometimes you go through phases where you are having a ton of fun playing a one particular game.
And it's all you really care about.
The only thing you want to do is the only thing you want to play.
And then you're just like you need something else.
I mean.
There's no reason to rush into trying to find something that you are interested in.
Yeah, I skipped that.
I don't want to say I like I've put you in.
All right, this is where the A pluses might start stopping.
I can only guarantee A pluses on the first like two worlds really.
Maybe three.
Oh, shit.
Oh, shawty.
This one is.
All right, I can do this one.
Shit.
Give me that key.
I did a key.
Yeah.
Yeah, this is the chapter where people get really shawty.
I wonder how many people like I'll have a good one stream this game and gotten really shawty.
This part.
Oh, like it.
I can already feel my blood boilers getting a little shawty.
No, just just get me.
Oh, I thought that was going the other way.
All right, you know, you know, well, I've said that I'm noticing.
What's what's what's with the snake thing?
As I've seen it all over twitch lately like people are like doing like snake noises in a
shit.
What's the what's the what is the snakes?
Does everybody like keep pulling up to speed here with the internet stuff?
Yeah.
Yeah, see like that guy right there was just like his.
Is like snakes like invading twitch TV?
Oh, it's like a it's like a guy.
Yeah, twitch has been invented by fucking snakes.
Oh, geez, what have I done?
Yeah, I just don't know where things originate sometimes.
Yeah, this one's this one's not an a plus.
I can tell you that right now.
Okay, it is.
You shouldn't have mentioned it.
Well, I don't care.
Like stuff like that doesn't really like doesn't like bother me.
If you want to be like a fucking snake man on twitch or whatever like you know you do you
did I get an a plus there?
I did no I didn't I did not my did not.
We gotta we gotta go fix that.
We have to wait to fix that.
Here we go wait to fix that.
Anthana cake.
I'm not gonna go all the way down on this one like that.
No, not even like that.
Alright, what the hell am I doing wrong here?
Apparently that.
I don't know why I thought that this level went down.
I don't know why I'm trying to jump either.
This is the- hey hey, this is part where the stream is get all salty.
I've seen it before.
Is jumping off of this jumping off that doesn't do anything, does it?
Maybe it does.
These mechanics are some of this shit.
I don't even remember.
There we go.
Oh fuck.
Yeah, this one's hurting my head.
I like- you have to go all the way down with it.
But- oh hey, no more A pluses guys.
That's the end of the A plus run.
No, I get it now.
I'm just not hitting it at the right spot.
I gotta go a little further down on it like here.
Oh, wait a minute.
Okay, there we go.
You just have to touch the bottom.
That's really how there is to it.
I can just get a little bit salty, yeah guys.
That- was it just a thing that just hit me right there?
A little bit of fucking sly, a bit of potassium chloride.
I'm just gonna go for a stream.
I don't- what did I play on my first stream?
Oh fucking shut up.
Nope, this got me.
This one was really good.
I kind of blew it.
I could have had it in the first one.
Oh boy, oh boy, oh boy, oh boy.
What did I do that first time?
What the hell did I- what did I change that first time?
Oh, what did I do?
Alright, let me look, I was pinning into it.
It was binding of Isaac, was it?
He could have been.
I could see that.
Oh come on, hit the wall.
We call that dog shit, guys.
Hit the wall, you dog shit.
That's a person that doesn't have a whole lot of like weathered vocabulary.
I'm a linguist.
I know my dictionary words.
I hate these things.
You want to know like, okay, so everybody has like the, the, the, the vein of their existence
in me, boy.
Mine are these stupid rockets.
I fucking hate these rockets.
Really messing with my A plus run.
Really making me a little bit- what's that word?
I forget it.
You know, I'm not a linguist.
What's that word?
Like that, peppery.
Little two peppery.
Little two, you know, garlic powder.
He's getting real garlic powdery.
What am I doing?
Fuck you.
God.
Down there please.
I've got all day.
We'll go.
Okay.
What?
Ten.
Huh?
What was that?
Maybe I should, I think I should just fall right down, right?
Let's see.
Yeah, I'm wasting too much time there.
I gotta go straight down.
Dude, is that vanilla extract?
No, you dummy.
Toot me, I can induce rage in anyone.
Especially if you're trying to do all 100% A plus.
There we go.
Oh, I didn't register.
Control is broken.
Control is fucking broken.
I gotta get my distance.
I'm like, everyone's talking about this.
Did you see that streamer rage on Super Meat Boy?
It was so crazy.
He threw his controller into the ground and it exploded.
Oh my god, I can't.
It's gonna be everywhere.
Did you see that streamer?
That was like really mad and rage.
Fuck.
I'm so into almost a guaranteed A plus.
As long as you just write when that thing ends, you hit it.
Burger Boy's sunny day is a video that will never be released.
Whatever.
Whoa, what the fuck happened there?
That was odd.
Can't you just bypass that?
No, I guess you have to wait.
I hate waiters.
They come over.
They try to take your order and ship.
And you're like, excuse me, I'm here on a lunch date.
Come back later.
But please bring more bread.
Idiot.
He gives you that waiter look, you know, the like.
I don't even refill your Coke.
I don't even refill your Pepsi in shit.
Where are you?
I'm doing this one wrong for the A plus.
I gotta go on the other side, I think.
Like over here.
Far too much fucking mouth.
He's still got it.
No, I hate that.
I hate that.
Why must it do that sometimes to me?
Oops.
Don't you guys see that whiny, whiny streamer like that?
I don't hate that whiny streamer.
I can play Super Meat Boy.
What a whiner.
It's gonna be on the front page of our slash winers.
Let me through.
No, it did it again, whiner.
Rip it.
Barg, we got frogs taking over now.
Guys, I don't want to be a, you know, a widow about this, but frogs.
I mean, come on, let me take over.
Frogs wanted to take over, which, which, I think I'd be okay with frogs.
I mean, who really, who wouldn't be okay with a frog taking over, but...
Especially if they were giant bull frogs.
Ah, shit.
Oh, you dumber.
Dumber.
I'm gonna be making up a random insults for myself this whole time, so I apologize about that.
Unclog the frog, permit the curve.
I've never heard of these before.
Hey guys, look up where I at.
My least favorite thing in this whole game.
Our slash, slash, slash, whiner.
Ooh, I blew it.
Look at how much I just blew that.
You blew it, you know.
Ah.
This is where my A plus streak ends.
Now, you know, I thought about it.
I thought I was gonna end.
It's going to end.
Let's just put that way.
I don't know when, but it will.
Maybe around like World 4 or something.
Oh, shit.
Oh, god, god, god, god, god.
God, god, god.
You know, I don't want to get myself angry here and say this is a shot with snow level.
You know, I don't be mad about everyone else.
Angry streamers.
They get on the front page.
Alright, I'd like that way too much and he'd like stop doing that.
Hey, look, all A pluses did it.
Hooray, let's beat the snowman.
Skip.
Oh, this is the race.
Am I crazy?
Hold on, am I insane?
Or did he just go way faster than he's supposed to?
Am I crazy, right?
I can't be crazy.
I thought you were supposed to race this guy.
He's already done.
What?
Look, what the fuck is this guy doing?
He's coming so fast.
He's like times two speed.
I'm the guy who was supposed to beat him.
Is he going to get stuck at the end or something?
That's not fair.
Where's my like, drugs to take to go that fast?
I beat him.
I'll take it.
On to chapter four, I guess.
Has anybody ever seen that before?
Because I didn't like the three or four times that I've played or watched people play that part.
I've probably seen that done a lot.
I'm just going to pretend like I beat that fair and square.
But we're not going for warp zones.
We're not going for all A plus.
As fast as possible.
I've got my splits here.
And I am on world record pace.
That right.
We're going up there.
Why am I going up there?
No, no, no, no, you're going to go on it.
Shit.
Need more speed.
Is it where the A plus is stopped?
Just kidding.
I love that terminology.
I hate fuck.
Bring me my co-creep.
I got to impatient.
But that is how you're supposed to beat that.
I need to just make that jump.
This is a floater.
Oh, this is one of those floaters.
Still got it.
Did that incorrectly?
I did it correctly at the beginning.
But then the fire guy hit me.
I'm going to go.
Ah!
Oh my goodness.
Oh my god, wait.
I'm going to have to wait for a waiter.
You know how fast I want to go?
I don't want to have to wait for this shit.
Now it's getting in my head.
Always the damn waiter levels.
I just did the thing where I turned my neck sideways
and I'm getting mad.
It's a waiting level.
What is happening to my voice?
Oh.
If it's a waiter level, it's going to be an A plus
as long as you get there by the time the platform has to be there.
That's how those work.
So I don't need to rush it.
Like this one.
Just going to stand here.
I got to get some more bacon and eggs in me.
Why did I think that that was going to work?
Damn it.
Now I slipped the helmet.
How many seconds do I need to shave off of that?
A huge amount.
An absolutely massive amount of time has to be shaved off of it.
That's got to be right there.
Can I do that though?
Maybe it's not.
Let me shave like three full seconds off.
Oh, yeah, I could shave seconds out there.
I thought you were switching games after World 2.
I was.
Once I stop reliably getting A pluses within like 10 to 20 attempts on a level,
that's when we're going to switch game.
Oh, shit.
I fucked that up.
Shit.
I fucked that up again.
I'll hold on a bit.
Shit.
I fucked that up again.
Oh, shit.
Oh, that jump.
Good morning.
Need more speed.
You always need more speed in V4.
I should have grabbed onto the wall.
That was a mistake.
No, I went too fast that time.
I'm not gonna have fast enough.
I gotta get up there when I'm doing two jumps.
That's really important.
That has to happen.
Well, that was like four jumps.
Is there a meeple-drinking game?
Probably.
Oh, that was it too.
I just was too psycho about it.
Am I going to watch the Overwatch beta stream?
Holy shit, yeah.
I can't wait for that.
I just want to play the game again, man.
I just want to play Overwatch again.
That's so easy to get.
I like half to just get it.
I'll get it.
Just hold on.
I never chill out.
Everybody gets chill out.
Yeah, you missed it.
I better not see any yellow bells in that chat.
If I missed this again, I swear to God, if I see a fucking goddamn yellow bell.
Fuck the band-aid.
Let's go.
I'm seeing the yellow bells in the chat.
Unbelievable.
Oh, I forget how you did this one.
Pick it up. Pick up the...
See if I did that right.
That would have been fine.
Yeah, I didn't even get it.
You got it.
You get it.
Angry streamer.
You guys are so angry.
Somebody get this guy like a towel to wipe the sweat off of his forehead.
Oh, fuck.
Did it again.
Hey, look what's in this level, guys.
What is that?
What is that platform?
What am I doing?
I'm waiting.
And then I get all thrown off, and I can't do the next part.
Waiter, remember the check.
I'm going to fucking McDonald's.
What's this dog food that you are serving us?
Well, that's what that did.
I'm going to get a coffee soon.
I could add, you know, I got a coffee already.
I'm good, man.
Appreciate it, though.
Appreciate the offer.
Shit.
Ah.
Fuck.
I think I'm doing something a little bit wrong.
What am I doing wrong, though?
You have to go super fast.
Now, no, no, I'm taking too much time to do it.
I'm getting ready for school.
Come on.
Make sure you're not late.
I don't want to, I don't want you to have watched this movie
like late to go to school.
No, whoops.
I just like ran over the whole thing.
Sorry, me, I just want you to do the jump.
You don't want to land on that thing.
Try to remember.
I'm not going fast enough.
Stop.
Wendy's Big Mac.
Wendee's Big Mac.
Pick Doublemaker.
What, Wendy's, what?
You don't wanna, Wendy's Big Mac.
Macdevil ...
Oh, no. I do.
Okay, I remember that is now.
Glory.
That was fun, Tip LIKE
for that. And that was another fun video.
when he's double my fuck fuck fuck fuck devil yeah that that is something that was
stated I wish there was more fun games like that to play with your buddies that was a real
good buddy game
oh fuck I just forgot everything I was doing
hello just saying hello randomly
now just kill me already screwed up
you wish you didn't know about that secret strategy did you but you guys didn't
know about that secret strategy did you check this one out see that won't hit
you there that's just sacred secret tips and strategies with me I forget this one
I have to go back I think I have to run back down I yeah I do no I don't
mean maybe I do let me really look at this one you have to be up there so he has to
start up here and then you go down like that it's been a while fuck yes not
I just slide back down if I really want to I like don't even know how to do this
again we're at a waiter back and forward maybe
huh well I like blew through the entire game and now I like died don't know how to beat
this level even without April I don't even know how to beat the level
like how do you even beat this level it's taking me an hour to get through like four and a half
chapters in this entire game with a pluses I don't know how to complete this I know you have to sit
up there
they use one of the bottom ones to block or something
shit
oh wow
so
to beat this level walk into the forest and eat the first mushroom you see
fuck you
I did not think I was gonna hit a wall where I couldn't complete a level I beat this game like
fucking 20 times
fuck you that's what you do
do you know how many times I beat this game 20 times
I
that motherfucker keeps hitting me
Jesus I know I fucking figured it out
I think we long enough will you fuck off left eyeball
just fuck right the fuck off you know what I'm saying
fucking seriously I get I watch this ready I'm gonna get through this level in an A plus
the rest of this world in fucking less than 10 minutes is he stupid fucking dumbass levels
like have like all this fucking shit that spits do out of their eyes you know what I mean
get me on that fucking front page of our rage dreamer I'm gonna get on there
it's like the hardest level in the whole game
okay let's let's like continue let me like it at an A plus right now
much we get this A plus
much right here this is gonna be watch this A plus guys here it comes
I just actually like forgot what that what I got I didn't I didn't even know what that level just did
fucking dumbass saw blades
I'm not gonna take nearly as many tries
what just happened
all right we're changing games after this I'm about to flip out you want to see somebody freak out
all god it was a freak out
fucking waiter level
at least I'm gonna beat the waiter level in the first try oh dear fuck
that's what I give opening my mouth
okay
first try those dodges
okay let's let's remember what the level is before we try to do it
okay this is another part that this one too is in there if I remember correctly
uh well I
I
I just getting confused can't do this one fast what's the timer on this one
I bet if this one's probably like a minute no 22 seconds this is not like an 8 second one
just getting stuck on walls you sticky skinless fuck
should I be able to jump from that or miss him's hitting the top of the wall
oh no there that goes
probably jump underneath those two and just not doing it whoa I fell off
yeah
I guess I do now you just gotta go
all right now I know you can jump underneath them now I wasn't doing that before
all right I'm switching to crib talk after this I know this is never gonna end well for me
I'm just gonna get so mad and I'm gonna start like apt I'm gonna start breaking things in this room
I'm just gonna start swinging around in circles
no I'm not doing this one right
wait a minute am I going too fast
I think I'm just going too fast to be able to like complete this one
let's see
let's find out
yeah I think I have to like wait longer don't I
well I'll just wait till these go over the top of this then
yeah huh well shit that's not cool
maybe what another cycle like one two that would be one cycle there right
no I know that that was bear that was not a full cycle that was like a half cycle
one two no I'm gonna wait again
one
one two three
fucking have to wait around
I
feel like that's not correct I think you just have to go faster through this
not this one in particular but the other one like right when I get in here
yeah yeah yeah I had it all wrong you kidding me right now you have to be
kidding me give me like one second of teleport immunity please
can I please get that like half second of teleport immunity
what a pain in the dick
that is such a pain in the balls it really is
if only there was like a quarter of a tenth of a second of teleportation immunity
that shit wouldn't happen
all right get it
look at all those me boys
all right let's go
don't kill me please don't kill me please don't kill me
oh right I forgot he does that yes he does that
this is a pattern I have to rememorize
is it again on the other side
oh that's not
bang
and then he goes crazy it hits like a couple times oh fuck can I use
smashers his face
smash your face down and then he does like one two three four with his fist right
it's like left left middle middle or something left right middle middle
yeah left right and then he goes in the middle and then he does it again
wait too early but it's okay first jorma stream welcome how you doing man
it's an easy pattern you have to jump three times you know those are the
same but yeah I just I just have never it's been like a year so oh my god I'm too busy looking
and talking and not even paying attention
the last time I played this game was last time you watched me play it on my youtube
channel three years ago
do it go ahead
and then again side is left
till the right I know this smashers face again
fuck oh it's so easy but you just have to memorize it
trial and error memorization
I was just on such a stupid spot
oh
bad please drop the fire right in the middle where I want to stand it'll be great
no there you go thanks thank you do it it
you're dingus
oh oh I thought he smashed his face he smashed his face up to doing one
time
well we're I'm gonna change the cryptarch after this because this is like there's two more chapters
after this but you know I kind of want to switch
that seriously which is sitting there just blanking
I was sitting there just like zoned out I was thinking about like breakfast sausage
I honestly was sitting there going you know you know what's gonna be really I'm gonna have to like
breakfast sausages I don't even need to move
nice matches his face again right now don't pay stop paying attention to the sausages
and pay attention to the game I think this is a safe spot
which hand comes down I forget what's that one oh my god he does it two times in a row
I fucking memorizing shit
Jimmy Dean breakfast sausage and that's sound like good right now other than like
rememorizing a boss fight in a meat boy that you haven't done it three years
go for it
I might be in some trouble here
do it again
oh why am I moving I don't need to move I didn't need to move there I just don't I just like
don't care at all about this right now I always hated this boss I hate this boss because
it's so slow and you just have to sit here and like you just get bored and by the time you
know what he's doing
now I'm just like why is he a big a meat boy to me that's not fair I want to be the big one
yeah
do it again
smash your fucking head again please end the end thank you
all right
I gotta use the force the rapture size doesn't matter this is one more
rapture the end I don't remember
we're gonna get we're just gonna get an A plus on this first one we're gonna do it with
commander video that that that's how I get my gamer license back I have to A plus one of these
levels with with commander video that's that's not gonna be an A plus in fact I think some of
these video some of these videos some of these videos some of these I think are not possible to
beat with commander video because he doesn't go fast enough let's see
why am I forgetting how to do this
22 seconds how long is that
how slow am I moving with this guy oh it was right there that was that that was the issue
get that right the first time and I'll have it yeah definitely let's do that again
give commander video
I can go I guess I don't think I've ever unlocked the 70 plus characters
I was a little sloppy but whatever yeah I'm gonna start over that was sloppy
oh whoops it is hey
I
wanted to grab and jump not float
fucking gonna crush up fucking glass and put it in my cereal
actually you know I probably see that with me boy is like the easiest jump you could ever do
you just go right through it
oh
commander video oh my god what am I doing just do three of those I got it
dog
gotta go gotta go gotta go right now gotta go gotta go I didn't do that
like a name like 10 things you didn't want to do in your life floating right there as commander
video is one of them trying to go too fast
too slow
I remember when I played this game the first time just trying just trying to beat these level up
still too slow but how why am I still that slow right now I haven't nothing has changed
I'm still getting this one oh come on please
apparently you didn't want to float that time what the fuck are you doing commander video please
and all that is sacred what the fuck are you doing
go don't float this time
I what I had it I thought I was gonna miss the time I really did I really truly did
I honestly thought I was gonna get it I was gonna I was definitely gonna make the time though
so it'll happen it'll happen right now I had like three extra seconds I thought I'd only like one
yay I can't believe you've done this
all right last I definitely matter what happens here is the final thing I'm doing last time
after this like this is the last thing no matter what happens is the last life
all right do I get but I a plus to every meat boy is level into the into rapture and I want to play
kryptark do I have my learners permit back do I get to do I get to do the actual like the
driving test in like a week or two you said last one a whole chapter ago
what kind of freak is even up at this hour for any purpose other than eating sausage that's a good
question that's a really good question change my stream title
to rip dark
that's a lot of kryptark
set up a straw poll for what
what are we what are we doing a straw poll for for that's what we're doing is what we don't
it's really a carry rebirth run now that I did that's why we get we have to get our gaming license back
for
permit the current I got my I got my current learners permit
let me get let me get kryptark open
let's go ahead and open that
so I got to the I got to the I got to the kryptark I got to the end of this game
and I got a really really crazy awful generation and I lost but I'm just chilling I'm just
gonna do dumb builds I don't even care if I lose or not
you might even try the controller to to test it out and see how it is
what the fuck was that what are these weird animals
it's like animals always like outside making like weird noises
yeah
hold on a second I need to like see what like turkey or something is outside of her back
yeah that was where I heard a bunch of like weird animal noises outside I've been
not here there's a lot here and then I wouldn't got my dog
let's change it to this let's play kryptark
it's cap is shit out of germa what what
cap of him get him like let's get him cap of him I don't I don't get it you're gonna cap
of me why would you do such a thing
we're gonna do this do the easy stuff
just gonna do the easy stuff
capa imagine being that guy
your entire your face is a timeless internet thing
I don't know yeah we go you know I always go zip gun
no it's like the first level that's not even necessary it's gonna go to the
regular machine gun no no ramp spike you go just this standard blaster I think oh
mouse for no mouse war now works by the way my wife is a black screen what the hell
black screen what what
that doesn't make any sense why would that why why
oh god I figured it out hold on we gotta add this thought I added this already
apparently not apparently not
now I'm back hi now you can see
and bro I broke something I always breaks shit but anyways mouse for wasn't working for me
before it is now I can actually use grenades and not have to hit f which was a pain in the
uh but I'm okay with this in fact I don't even need this many grenades
load up max 100k no supply pods that sounds easy enough
you can take one of these down to probably
that sounds good to me
all right what are we working with
we've got shield here alarm system there and then cord to destroy this is kryptark by the way
you found your shield to mouse for in your second but that's actually not a bad idea I might try
that in a minute we'll see uh we're just gonna go in this way I'm taking the alarm system out
but I got up a bat get a couple tech upgrades get a couple keys and destroy this
but I cannot if I want to get the bonus as I can't take any supply pods
let's try to go around up to the top right and something I didn't know you can actually put
waypoints if you click did not know that at all the last time
let's go
kryptark
right in the door here oh
let's get it
now I can very effectively
that does work look at that you can actually block the
ship with your shield can't you you know it's triggerly alarm if you do that
something I didn't know before you know remember the last time I played this I didn't know
what the hell is going on well I sort of sort of do now he's the term very loosely
auto cannon okay that's one of the best items in the game
what we're going next we're gonna go down right here
yeah
yeah I think I got too many grenades too for the first level
maybe
away from me oh fuck green slime screwed my head there
it's anything else I want to do here go that way grab the tech
why do I know if I nuclear throne I don't know I knew that it's just to I never
never really appealed to me very much I thought it was cool concept but back when I
oh boy hold on I gotta pay attention here
these enemies are like awful they just shoot back they blow your stuff in random directions
try to get on good
the game was very very early when I first got like a chance to see it then like they've
been doing a ton of updates to it it's been getting a lot of updates pretty much
I can't figure out the wake or something right I don't know something I never really got into
one more yeah
I think I got all three of the bonuses too what's this an EU friendly stream
it is it's like afternoon plus three three max hole oh okay now wait I guess I screwed that up
did that wrong honestly games like this that are very very difficult that require a ton of
precision like a huge amount of concentration and a ton of like bullet dodging and I just
know I it my brain can't do it I get stuck in walls I overreacting and bad shit happens to me
I screw up one thing and then it's just a chain reaction but I have an auto cannon now so that's
really amazing I'm gonna put it on here really expensive max load up 60k I don't even care
got a trench gun
oh no stay with the machine gun for now I don't even actually know and take the auto cannon off
it's unnecessary for right now there's just too much money for it's like a level two place I don't
do that so let's instead put the blaster back on I will take another heal this time though just
no I won't I'm gonna take I think I'm gonna stay with that maybe do I need a key maybe
go right up here drone factory yeah these are drone factories are huge deal they just keep
spawning enemies can't do bullet dodging but plays pretty well in Isaac
Isaac I don't know Isaac is a lot slower right Isaac is a lot more deliberate and slower the
rooms are small and there's not a whole lot of things in the room this game and the games like
nuclear thrown in games that are in this kind of genre there's so much stuff happening around you
that it is almost impossible to slow down and like sin know what you're doing unless you have
like a really good like lightning reaction speeds that GPS wanted to take me in a really really
awful direction and plus I do I don't look I like the team meet games like Isaac
Meat Boy they're like very fun interesting games to me
all right where am I going here to go down in here
don't want to get rid of that yet
scared even touched that actually
oh shit oh fuck I forgot where to take me I don't even know where to put me
hopefully not that far away no thank god it didn't put me somewhere else horrible
forgot when you blow up those things they do that
is that affected by the alarm no thanks so put them on a mission
there we go no keep a keep alarm systems I hate the alarm systems I despise them so I'm
I'm totally happy with just blowing them up no supply pods I do want to take out
these the strong factory though no supply pods I can do that
stay away from that shit
yeah sorry I'm not like looking at chat right now this this game like requires you're 100% of your attention
it's very good though it's very good and it's in early access somehow this early access game
feels like it's it been done for a while I don't need a key
all right that's it that's all there is to it
you can actually cook the grenades I don't know why I'm not doing that more often
boom is the game for a game is not free I think it's like 10 bucks 15 10 12 so
might think it's on sale initially here
burn out all resources
you have your satis today or your what is it what's a p it's something like that it's the
original the first one the pre satis
I actually don't have frequently asked questions I feel bad for people that are kind of
just coming in here and being like oh who though what is this I'm not I'm not a streamer yet
but that's kind of trying to
all right I got money now stay will stay with the three
because these are very hard really like last time when I'm when I streamed this game
I was doing the hardest ones I was like going in with chain guns on every slot
it was really stupid so I'm just gonna stay nice and safe in my comfortable three
and eventually it's gonna be five but just to get this guess to get past the first few areas
there's no reason but in my opinion to blow money and waste it because you're trying to do like
the extremely difficult ships 48,000 followers and he's just starting out well here's my streamer
um story is the tale of my stream I streamed I've been like doing youtube and stuff for those of you
then I've just I've just I've somehow found this channel and you have no idea what's going on
I do I do like youtube I mean like I mostly do youtube and like four years ago I live streamed
like maybe once or twice a week for a while and then I stopped for two straight years
so like all these followers I would say it probably like 70% of the people that followed this
stream like four years ago or like three years ago that's where the majority of those
followers came from now I'm starting to uh start it back up again and get back into it a little
I guess you could say so do zip gun you're not gonna go zip gun I love this thing
zip gun will keep the blaster did I get any different grenades sticky grenades they're more expensive
I'm at 100k can't max 100k if I do another fixer will that
that'll be 10 could get rid of the blattin all I get I'll just stick with the regular grenades
that way I can stay on our 100k
do you think you started the new channel on youtube and no one knew who you were could you become
big again I don't know man it's a lot more difficult if you want to start streaming or start
doing youtube or start getting into this kind of like as you could call like I seen
back when I started five years ago there weren't as many people doing it then you know fast forward
a few years you go down there's just go to like browse a random game on twitch even if you open up
like one of the popular games there are like hundreds of potential channels maybe even at some point
like in like the multiple hundreds and hundreds maybe even like a thousand channels streaming
in a really popular game or something release hundreds so it's hard to stand out
shit it's got a cloaking device on it that sucks
sensor jamer repair what else we got this is the most obnoxious so that has to go
this kind of has to go
so
this has to go first then this then this so we're gonna go into here I'm gonna do I don't think I
even have the tech upgrade for the sensor I don't shit this is gonna be annoying I this is
really really really really we're gonna have to just go and blind I'm just gonna make sure I don't
die
let's see if there's an entrance up here if there's an entrance up here I'm gonna try to get rid of this
even though it's being held by repair there is an entrance right here but I don't want to trip the alarm
okay
tractor beam it's terrible it's dark in here
oh come on
it's too dark I can't see anything
I've already taken way too much damage I don't have the key to get in there
okay
key right there
these drones I gotta get rid of the drone factory
I might be able to go a different way but whatever
all right now that I have a second here sensor jammers been deactivated I need to go here I need
a key that's key right there we're golden let's go
I just a lot of shit on the screen right now I can't even see key right in the here
look at this
oh my goodness these stupid fucking things I hate these things
all right now that we have that out of the way
can get rid of the alarm system
I got your course I come back and I get hit that sucked
much I got plenty ammo be okay
that requires a key to do I have a key right no no I don't
I might just do this without oh yeah screw it who cares about the alarm
destroy sentry systems and no supply pods where are the sentry systems
way too far out of my way yeah we're just gonna go without it we're just gonna get rid of the
shield and just go right there and just trigger the alarm and hopefully we can destroy it fast enough
fuck that's not cool
I'm just behind the locked door
using ammo I didn't want to use
Is this behind a locked door too?
Please tell me it isn't. It is. Of course it is, but the least is a key right there.
He had a way for me. I saw you do that, you little shit.
I just fucking hit myself with a grenade. Be into impatient. I gotta slow it down. Be into impatient.
Let's get that key. This so many things in that room. How much time do I have left?
Not a whole lot. I don't think there is any more room. Now we have to go just boss the wall.
I'm just gonna have to go for it. Run out of ammo too.
So we're just gonna go destroy it and hope I can just spam grenades at it. Be on the win.
Anything in that room? No.
Wait for me. Alright boys and girls. We're going for spam strats.
That might have to clear this room a little though.
Spam scratch. Holy dog shit. Oh my god.
That's done to know where I am. Where I don't know what happened. That holy fuck.
Did you see how much stuff was in that room?
There were like four laser turrets on the walls. I actually did not. I saw the stuff.
That was dumb. Everything was behind a locked door and I didn't have any keys. That sucked.
Now I'm gonna look and see it. If every single god damn door is locked then I need to bring a key.
That was really fucking annoying.
Oh what's this? There is two locked doors in this whole place this time.
And look I can just go. Holy crap. You shitting me.
Well that's what happens when you roll the dice on a procedurally generated game.
Sometimes every single door will be locked and sometimes the brain will be protected by the shield.
That's literally 50 feet away from it. That's the way the cookie crumbles.
Look at this. Oh guys. I better watch out for this locked door.
How well I have a get in there. I have a get inside of that locked door.
Shit.
Alright. Enough complaining. Let's play.
Let me make sure there's nothing in here.
I don't care about that.
I could just get.
Yeah. I'm just... We're just gonna do the same thing.
There's no alarm system in this one either.
This one should be fairly easy.
Whoever made that door to lock it was shit-faced.
I'm just gonna do auto cannon.
I'm just gonna do auto cannon and get in there and just blow it down.
That sounds good.
I don't need any keys.
Right. There's all these doors are open.
I need one key.
Go in there and get the tech and then beat the level unless to a minute.
This game is cryptark.
It's on steam right now.
I'm not sure about if it's coming to consoles or not.
I don't know. I really just don't have any idea.
I wish I could TV that intel.
Oh shit. Hold on.
Make sure we're going the right way here.
There's no alarm system so I don't have to be worried about anything besides just clearing this room.
I guess I could put this shield down.
God, those things are so horrible.
Those things do like two points of damage ahead in this so brutal.
Okay, that room- this one's okay now.
I'm just gonna do this.
Watch out guys.
Shit. What are we- how are we gonna get rid of this?
I'm gonna get rid of this.
Oh, that's a bad way to go.
Oh wow, holy fuck.
I was wrong.
I forgot that. I forgot it was not the one-
Okay, right. That's what I get for not paying attention to that.
Damn.
At least there's no alarm system.
Put your shield down.
There's a lot of these turrets in this one too, unfortunately.
I might actually get the- yeah, I'm gonna get it.
I just totally forgot that it did whatever was connected to what-
So what was that shielding then?
That's the question.
This whole level is turrets.
Nikes.
More locks.
At least the ones that are connected do.
Kinetic buffer.
I've never heard of that one.
Ah, you are so annoying.
You are very, very annoying.
All right, so that will take that down.
What was it I have to destroy the flacking trolleys?
Oh, that's not a flacking trolleur.
Did I already get them all?
I got all the flacking trolleys.
I don't even need to do that.
There's nothing protecting you, but wasn't- what?
I'm kind of confused here.
I'm confused.
I'll have to attack.
Is there any more tech? I don't have any tech.
There's one up there.
Kind of running at a time, but- whatever.
Whatever. Let's just get rid of it.
All right, you're going to like the nest.
Do you have to destroy everything?
No, you don't.
I don't know if you- did I even take out another?
I like to watch that part of the stream back.
Because I took out the shield, and it was still shielded.
But the thing that I destroyed up there, that wasn't a shield?
Was it? Was it the thing that I went up there?
A shield?
I don't know.
Apparently not.
Where am I going now?
It was the redundancy building.
Potentially.
A door lock system and something else.
Yeah, I want to watch that part back.
No idea.
It was very odd.
Definitely keeping the auto cannon though.
That different machine, though.
These are- you know.
The current game is Victor-Vran.
It's not- it is not Victor-Vran.
Nightbot- you really screwed this up.
I need more ammo than that though.
What's the max?
A lot of 60k.
I'm not going to be able to do that.
Yeah, this is the Victor-Vran of the future.
The current game is a Victor-Vran.
This Victor-Vran game sure looks fun.
Maybe it really is.
I'm not going to stay.
Just try and true with the machine gun.
It's just too good.
And the auto cannon.
Yeah, we're just going to stay with that.
I also got a new- what if I got something new?
Didn't I?
Laser.
I'm not going to stay with that.
That's really expensive.
I'm not going to do it.
Okay.
Repair station up here.
Is there more than one reviewer?
There are more than- all these the worst.
These are the worst.
Yeah, I have a Twitch partnership from like four years ago.
So whatever the partnership was, four years ago is the one that I have.
So when you have two repair stations, it really sucks because you have to end up going in
and- both of these pretty much have to be destroyed.
So I'm going to have to go down.
Yeah, we're going to go in here.
We're going to go down.
There's a key.
I have a key.
There's also one there.
I need a key to get into the- the more locked doors everywhere.
I picked the wrong one.
Does this guy really deserve to have his gaming license back?
He's still going around using a faulty nightbot.
I don't have it back.
I have my learned experiment.
I'm going to go down.
I got a key.
There's a key right there I can take.
I'm going to destroy the two repair stations as we go.
So I'm going to do- sounds good to me.
How about it?
I don't want to go that way.
My GPS device is freaking out.
Greetings from Bulgaria.
Hi.
Greetings from the United States.
I got to go all the way out.
This is going to be a long one.
I don't know if I have faith in this one.
It might not even be worth destroying that drone.
Drawing- drawing- drawing facility just yet.
But I don't know.
I don't know how much time I'm going to have.
Because if there's two repair facilities, I'm going to have to call ass after this is destroyed.
Gotta go.
All ass.
Oh shit.
That's the thing that blows up right?
No, I don't want to go that way.
It's a waste of key.
You see what I'm saying?
With two of those facilities going?
It's hard to-
Yeah, it's going to come back.
But at least they've gotten rid of some of those drones without being too much of pain they have.
I really wish you two weren't so annoying.
I really wish you weren't that annoying.
You just block in the way in.
You chump get out of the way.
Oh my god.
Whenever the he's- it's just getting repaired too.
It's tiny little rum.
Oh, that was horrible.
I have to get rid of this other one.
Quick, quick, quick, quick, quick.
All right, call me crazy.
You can go ahead and call me crazy.
I'm going around the ship.
I'm going to go around the damn ship and go in the not so hostile way.
20%
Which way right in here and then down and around.
I need to get that fucking key.
Is there a key right there?
Nope.
Where's the key?
Up there.
How much time do I got?
41%.
No, what?
No.
What the hell?
Oh my god.
What the fuck?
I'm trying to open a door.
Refill ammo?
No, I don't want to refill ammo.
Okay, well now just get destroyed because you didn't open the door.
And I'm very, very angry.
I just got it.
Let's get rid of this.
Now we can take my time because now things aren't respawning every two seconds.
Get trolled.
I actually am going to take this because I want the cannon.
The cannon is so amazing.
That door is locked.
Is that stuck in there?
Can I not even go in that room?
I'm going to have to reroute this.
I can't get in there.
Can I like cheese it and get it?
No.
Holy shit.
No, you hit me.
See you in health.
Get out of my way.
God.
I really want to shut this alarm off.
It's worth me doing the key.
I will do this.
Don't want the alarm to go off because there are so many horrible things in that room down there.
I would not want to get swarmed with everything.
I'm going to get out of here.
What are you doing in here?
You're going to be a hero?
I don't think so, dude.
Well, so if you'd like to know what happened right there, my game froze.
I just didn't move.
I know it's worth probably freezing.
I don't think so.
Kind of a little.
I have to try and avoid all that for the game to freeze.
And you can hit by the alarm.
That's just fucking fantastic.
I need to look and see if there's one anywhere.
There is, but it's all the way over there.
I need to just sit in the corner and please game, please stop doing this.
I'm going to sit in this corner until this end.
Okay.
Nope.
I should be able to get back though.
Come on, come on.
This is going to be very, very difficult to do this.
I'm running out of time, but even if you run out of time, you don't lose.
But look at all the stuff that's in here.
This was a terrible, terrible one.
I'm just going to die because I want to restart the game.
It's just for some reason is doing like stuttering all over the place.
Give me a second.
Give me one second.
It saves my progress, don't worry.
My progress is saved.
Oh.
How am I going to exit?
Like that.
Remember me and Star we're talking about this the other day.
This game is amazing except for when it does that.
Should be right here.
Oh, key, key.
Yeah, that's Grova.
That's supposed to be good old Grova.
Yeah, that hold on screen was like 40 bucks.
I paid myself 40 dollars.
All right, are we good?
I think so.
I hope so.
That's a real run killer.
Keep the alarm systems.
I'm going to get on with the stickies on.
I like the sticky grenades a little bit better I think.
Now let's see what we got this time.
Oh, but I love God.
No, another one of these.
I got to try to get rid of that.
Is there any prepared things?
Yeah, all the way down here.
I'm going to go around this way.
These have to go down first.
Otherwise buildings just come back.
Why don't you have a stream of normal USA times that are like 7 a.m.
Because I'm trying to stay awake.
I'm trying to reset my sleep schedule in a way.
Max 100k.
What's my loadout right now?
123.
That's too much money.
Did I even need this key?
I guess I can't tell if I need the key because I can't save
there are any locked doors.
So we're going to keep it.
There's only two around the sport.
All right, well, I could try to keep none.
I don't need to take a supply pot.
Keeping the alarm systems is a really awful risk human over.
But especially when you can't see anything.
And I don't have the upgrade to be able to see things to go through it.
So we're going to try to get rid of the repair facility first.
I'm going to go down and around.
Where's my ship?
Up here.
I'm going to check out Victor Vran.
Hopefully there's an entryway down here.
Be great if there was one literally right here.
It would be amazing.
Yes, there is.
It's dark as hell.
I think I had a key.
Just keep coming from every direction.
And I don't know where to go.
I did to get rid of that sensor.
Sell that.
I just don't know the efficient way to move that way.
There isn't alarm.
Don't get touched by that.
I wish I had a better machine gun.
I can't even tell what a wall is.
That's really killing me.
He's not having a machine gun.
That's better.
Like a heavy machine gun or something.
Hopefully I can go in here.
Please don't make him go in there and get it.
Looks like I've done up.
No.
Oh my goodness.
Get away from me.
No, I can't go.
I got to go up through here.
God damn it.
Give me like a sneaky back entrance.
While I waste all this time looking for a how to move in this area.
Thank you.
Please let that be light.
How old are you going away from me?
Please.
You got no shield.
You need to second for the charge back up so I don't die.
Oh my brain.
Bullet hell.
Only the darkness wasn't consuming my body.
Oh, I can see.
Thank God.
Oh, we got to go down here.
It'll be so safe if I go down that way.
I love me a sneaky back entrance.
There's a key here but I mean mine as well just go that way anyways.
I just don't want to take unnecessary damage.
I don't know if it heals left.
I got 16 shots in the cannon.
I'm running out of ammo.
Thankfully there's not a whole lot left.
Is there a supply pod somewhere on the way?
We're going to play it safe.
I'm going to refill my ammo.
I know it'll be a really big deal later.
I'm going to be really mad if I didn't get it.
Keep alarm systems.
Extra money.
I don't know if I want to do that.
I haven't trouble enough as it is.
Quick shield.
No, is it worth it?
No, it's not.
Don't be a dummy.
Get rid of the alarm.
The dash across the whole screen in less than a second.
Make sure you get rid of those too.
Actually my put shield on a base button.
I feel like that would be a lot easier rather than have to hold down right click.
I said earlier, that guy is a smart guy.
Can't even walk into this room.
Dear Lord.
Open up.
Be really sneaky on this one.
Running out of health too.
That's a concern.
I don't want you to come up behind me and shoot right in my spine.
This is a busy ass room.
You just shot that away.
Running into the negative time here.
Whoa, getting stuck on shit.
40 seconds into the time.
Damn.
I'm going to lose money.
Running low on funds.
Why am I called Jerma?
My name is Jeremy.
That's it.
This is where we lose.
I only have 260,000.
It's going to be extremely difficult.
And you know how I do when it comes to like extremely difficult things.
Maybe we'll see.
What do we got there?
Let me look at the other ones.
Two repair ones.
Forget this one.
Two alarms and two repairs.
This one only has one alarm and one repair.
Look at all this stuff on this one.
Geez.
Did you do that?
Yes, I was the...
I'm the engineering in this game.
I'm like the tutorial and I tell you all kinds of things.
I teach you about how to play.
All that stuff.
Did you get my FOD email?
I did.
I opened it up and I immediately closed it.
You stunk up my office, dude.
Thanks.
Let's look at this.
Thankfully we don't have to deal with a sensor.
Seven minutes.
Shabba-batch.
Shabba-batch is all I gave you.
Only one repair, which is good, and it's right in the front door.
The juggernauts are a real huge issue if you're not taking out.
I think we're just going to have to go slow here and take out like every single thing in this whole area.
This whole part of the game here.
We're going to go down with it and then we're going to go up with it and then we're going to go right out this door.
And the landbam right into the core.
No, we are not.
We are not going to do that.
We're going to go here first because that's a nuclear device, which means in this tiny little cramped area,
if I destroy one of these, it makes a giant nuke explosion happen and we'll just kill you.
So we're going to go up there first.
Are there any more of those?
No.
So we got to go here.
Oh, you know what?
I could destroy this first and just get the hell out of here.
Come up here and then destroy that.
Which is, yeah, that's what I'm going to do.
That's a better idea because then I won't be able to repair.
I'm going to do that.
This is Cryptarch.
Did you just join us?
The point of the game is that you make a loadout, you go and you destroy the cores.
You have to destroy cores.
Everything's randomly, procedurally, procedurally generated.
I'm not a slagging.
Nice out of happening though.
There we go.
That was weird.
Everything's procedurally generated, which means you can get severely screwed.
Or, you know, it could be like a walk in the park.
This one shouldn't be too bad.
And I say that before we get going.
We all know how stuff like that goes though.
Where I'm really taking a big hurt hit here.
I'm not picking up enough tech upgrades.
So I'm stuck with the medium machine guns.
Which really, at this stage of the game, you need to be doing a lot more damage.
And all I've picked up, I've gotten all the shotguns.
But I'm not a fan of the shotguns unless it's like an assault shotgun.
I do have this though, which is thankfully really, really good.
Quick shield is hard to use.
So I don't want to use it in laser up.
I'm tempted to try the laser, but I don't think I want to, because I want to try to, like, at least get to the Cryptarch.
Maybe if that's possible, or at least get to like, I might just die here.
This is going to be really hard probably.
We're going to go with the zip gun though.
No, we aren't.
I need to save money.
I'll stay with the 50.
Those are so necessary to destroy the big tanky things.
I don't have two types of grenades, so they're staying.
And I'll keep the 5-5 and the key.
Never know when you're going to need a key.
Except not this time, because there's no locked doors that I need to go into.
If I go there up here, that's not locked.
This is also not locked, and none of these are locked.
So that key can kind of just go into trash.
Save myself a few thousand G's.
Oh.
I like that sounds really cool.
I shoot more, and they're more accurate.
For 15 grand, well, we kind of have to put all of our money in the pot anyways, because if I lose here, I pretty much lose the game.
Do you need good PC specs to run this?
I don't think so.
The only problem that this game has is, like, what happened the last time is it's a very precise game that you need to be paying a lot of attention to.
And sometimes the game will just hang, you know, that typical, like,
of the game just kind of stops for like two seconds, and it will get killed.
Even if that happens for like a quarter of a second, a game like this that requires like a quarter of a second reflexes,
that like, it screw you up, then it happens in this game.
But they're probably going to iron that out.
It is early access, so they're, I'm sure they're doing all kind of bug fixes and stuff.
It is a very, very, very fun game.
Extremely difficult, but very, very, very fun.
Let's stop talking about it.
Let's just show it.
Let's take a look, huh?
Whoa.
I don't think I've even seen the enemy before.
It's like a Reaper.
Fucking mine, right off the bat.
Two mines.
There's a room full of mines.
That's what that was, a room full of mines.
Slow calm down, calm down, calm it down.
Great!
Stick me in a room with eight mines in it in the front door.
Now I'm minus four health.
Now I got to be even more careful.
All right, there's a tech upgrade up there.
Alarm Laura, I don't need that.
I don't need that.
That's the detonator, right?
That's the Juggernaut factory.
I do not want to be killing that.
I've got to go down and around.
I'm going to go through the huge guy, great.
Still going to go this way.
Okay, I got to go.
Fucking mine!
Another mine!
Get out of the way!
Should've got that key!
Should've got that damn key!
Remember I said it didn't need a key?
Oh!
At least it's gone.
I feel like this is going to save Haven down here.
Mine.
All right, this is a drone factory.
It's going to do the explosion.
I can actually outrun it if I go all the way up.
I'm going to go for it.
The parastation is dead.
Let me get all the stuff that's down here that I need.
Rail cannon, I don't even know what that is.
Here comes the Juggernaut.
That's a dead end.
You shitbag!
Okay, come down.
Let's go get rid of that thing up there.
That will stop the buildings from exploding.
Hopefully, that would be great.
There's no mines in the front door.
Inside the fucking sealant vent.
Oh, my god, these mines are going to drive me crazy.
Something.
You can't even see.
I'd like to see.
I'm not going to get that yet.
There's a Juggernaut in here.
There's a Juggernaut in here with me.
There's two Juggernauts in here.
Oh, what a mess.
There's nowhere I can go.
I have to get that repair.
I got to get this.
What?
Jump dead.
Yeah, I'm dead.
Two Juggernauts in a tiny little room with all these explosions.
Game over.
Holy shit, that was impossible.
Without any more ammo in that cannon by default machine gun.
GG. There's no way I was beating that one.
If you're curious, the Juggernauts spawn every minute, I think, or every two minutes.
If you don't destroy the Juggernaut towns.
And they take...
It's pretty much a giant tank that has explosions that shoot out of it.
And they were just two things.
They were two of them in that room.
And there was no escaping them.
The turret's all over the walls.
Shit.
Well, I lost.
Game over.
There's Cryptarch.
So I got to two before the Cryptarch before I died.
But that's the worst part, right?
So there's like ten different building types in this game.
They're all horrible, right?
You have to pick you a poison in this game.
You either like...
Like for instance, those two Juggernauts...
The Juggernaut stations, or whatever you want to call them.
If I went and got those first,
the nuclear explosion was still what happened.
If I didn't, you know, if you don't get the nuclear explosion,
building destroyed, then you screw in...
Every way you're screwing yourself in this game.
You have to like pick which one you'd rather deal with.
So, and you saw right there,
I decided to try to get rid of the nukes
because they take up like the whole screen.
And I left the Juggernaut stations,
and then two of them were in the same room with me.
And then you just die.
Because if there's that many in a small area
and they just shoot the explosive, the fucking bombs.
But yeah, that's Cryptarch.
That did voice acting work for this game.
It's really fun.
It's just excruciatingly difficult.
If you're into that sort of thing, I highly recommend it.
You can... I would not recommend playing this game from bed.
Playing this game from bed would probably be a pretty bad idea.
You might die.
There are angels in the Elfield, bro. You gotta believe.
Alright, let me switch to this for a second.
I'm probably gonna do a video on it.
I might do a video on this game showing like the character
that I'm doing and stuff.
Talk about it for a few minutes, maybe.
Okay, let's close out the stream a little bit of...
It's only $11, too.
Now, hold on, Grover, man.
You gotta hold on one second.
Cryptarch, very fun.
It's just a very dice-roly.
You saw some of those places that had like, you know, almost every door was locked
and I didn't have enough keys.
And I kind of just had to run around like a check with my head cut off.
What the fuck is that?
Did I get tractor just drive by my window?
Did some dude do it like a tractor just drove by?
Alright, I'm gonna...
I'll close out the stream with a little bit of TF2.
Why not, right?
I need to beat that Cryptarch, though.
I will.
I will beat the Cryptarch one day.
You gotta change my stream title.
Thanks for hanging out.
Those of you that are here.
If it's early, early in the morning for you.
Thanks for chilling.
Well, I try to reset my sleep schedule.
Thanks.
I'm gonna go back to sleep.
Hold on a second.
Okay.
I mean, load up that game that we're talking about.
Fortress team.
Does this mean no Euro streams when you reset the schedule?
No.
Not necessarily.
It just means that...
That is gonna be random times, you know.
It might be two o'clock in the morning.
It might be two p.m., I don't know.
Change this.
Give me a second, guys.
Dung!
Where it is gonna go here.
I don't need to play anything in particular.
I just kinda wanna unwind for a little bit.
I just wanna unwind.
Now that I know it's a black screen, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry about the black screen.
Well, incoming Chrome, that sounds like a real big problem.
He might wanna call your local doctor's office and ask them...
What your course of action should probably be?
Okay, we're gonna...
I'm just gonna be a demo night freak.
Demo freak show.
That was a Windows 7 game, you know what?
I don't have Windows 7.
You don't...
I keep accidentally clicking on the Windows 10 thing.
I don't wanna do it.
Not yet.
And every time I go down to my taskbar, I end up accidentally having to sit through that loading screen.
It's probably not a good idea to do this on this map.
On offense.
Full demo night.
That's not a good idea.
Oh god, the unlock of Buser, damn.
How about we sit in forever?
Let's go.
I wish there was a way you could speed up the setup time.
Like, hold F and the speed up, it'll speed it up.
It's part of a spy.
Sojour on this car, I think.
Your spy seemed like you are.
Oh, that was bad.
I just like shot me in the wrong direction.
Yeah, I'm just doing this on wide.
I'm just doing this to unzip, you know.
Maybe we should really get...
No, maybe it could be 10 minutes.
We could be like an hour.
We'll find out, right?
We'll find out, won't we?
Anybody in here?
I'm always so scared to turn this corner because of right there.
There's always a century there.
We're way far ahead now.
Doo!
Where the hell is red team?
What's going on?
Are we just moving together?
Is anybody on the other team?
Okay.
Why would that far?
Like, are we that far ahead?
I guess we were.
Yeah, I was moving.
I keep thinking that, dude.
It's a spy.
Every time.
I don't know if we're just rolling them right now, but...
I've seen like two people on red this whole time.
One of them was that part of...
What the hell is that guy doing?
This is...
Okay.
Watch out for this guy.
He's got like arms.
What is happening with this dude?
He's got arms coming out of his back.
He's got four arms.
And he's about to stick that spy cycle in his own...
...boy.
Yeah.
Uh...
Let's go on red.
This is what's happening.
Okay.
Holy shit.
Is that two FLOG pyros?
Is that guy for Crits?
Okay.
I know that was fine.
I was doing the box...
...tongue with the boxes and showing.
Time.
Well, that was a crazy round, I guess.
I saw three people on red team.
And then I went to red team.
And then I was locked in by FLOG Geistinator pyros.
Stop distancing it once.
Oh, how childish.
How childish I'm gonna be dancing.
Fucking childish.
FLOG pyros are the true evil in this game.
Nah, I wouldn't say that.
So, is that a pyro?
And is that an engineer in a pyro?
Who's two hands of those?
Yeah, who's hands of those?
No, that's a heavy in an engineer.
Is it heavy in pyro?
I forget all the default loadouts look like.
Sorry, I'll get you next time.
Oh.
Hey, hey, quick dancing, man.
There's like shit going on outside.
Look, there's a battle going on.
We're under attack by red team.
There's no time to be dancing, I spawn.
Okay, well, you're over there.
I'm as an engineer.
No moving.
This is this pyro blow and flames in my face.
Okay.
I wish I could hit a shot, that would be great.
Oh boy, I'm being surrounded.
Centry?
Maybe? Centry?
Maybe?
No.
You want to try to stare at me?
Are we going to try to do?
Come on now, where'd you go?
Aha!
The night is seriously going to step right in my face.
Come on now.
I was trying to avoid that as best I could, it still didn't work.
Team fortress two.
What's happening right now?
My brain is kind of on ice right now.
I still haven't gone to bed.
I think I was just...
Shit.
I gotta play something.
What requires like zero brain power?
When did I go to bed last?
I remember.
I think it was like...
3 or 4 am yesterday?
Day before, whatever it was.
I don't remember.
Dude, it's like memento.
I don't have like no memories.
Dude!
I have a sandwich, I don't think so.
Oh shit.
Hey, when life gives you lemons...
Play heavy.
You still alive.
Maybe I'll take a knife in my face.
Don't get me, don't get me.
Where did he go?
There he is.
Nobody's on the car.
The car's just all the way back there.
What do you say, do a what?
Do a triple...
Do a triple chin chair engee for the end of the stream.
Do it again.
Do it again, get me again.
Holy shit, there's another one.
Come on, come on, which one of you wants it?
Which one of you wants to get me?
Huh?
Which one?
I wanted to punch that guy.
I'm not going to die.
I skipped school to watch this.
Don't do that.
No, it's skipped school.
The stream's ending in like 10 minutes.
I really hope that's a joke.
Oh, here we go.
I skipped school.
That's like, get out the popcorn.
I'm going to watch this live stream.
It's just a- it ended the stream.
All right, so when that happens, just go to school.
And just like, go with like a tardy notice.
Be like, I couldn't find my shoes.
That's a good excuse.
What teacher can argue that?
You know what I mean?
Going to school late?
Walk up to the front desk?
Hey, I'm here. I'm late.
Okay, well, sweetie, why are you late?
I couldn't find my shoes.
Oh.
Okay, well, you found them, obviously.
You found them.
Yeah, I found them, but I couldn't find them before.
Okay, well, please go to class.
How are you going to argue that?
What are you going to say about that?
Okay, that's going to be right behind me.
And he's second now.
He's right next to me.
I want to try to get the medic.
I'm not going to be able to.
I'm so paranoid of those two.
Trying to shoot my own guys.
Oh, stay heavy. Why not?
I'm so tired at this point.
I'm playing anything else.
This is a bad idea.
I'm a little bit of just walk the runway.
Hey, you!
Coming for you.
I'm going to be able to get the medic.
You saw the flash light?
You saw the flash last night.
The flash movie or the flash like TV.
Isn't there a flash TV show?
It's so close.
Somebody get on it.
Let's go this way.
Oh shit.
I skipped my breakfast to this.
I'm just going to punch a guy.
I'm just going to punch one guy and then I'm going to disconnect.
I would have punched that guy.
Oh, I did hit him.
I did punch him once.
I'm going to punch this guy.
Whoever comes out.
They're going to get punched.
How many scenes are we coming out of this way?
I'm going to punch him.
Punch him.
Punch this guy too.
Give me one.
I'm just top scoring apparently.
Who is this guy?
He sucks at team fortress.
Does he even play sixes?
No, I don't.
I don't play sixes.
Sorry.
Huh!
All right, I've been awake for like 20-some odd hours now.
Are they just trying to go to bed or eat food and try to relax and do something?
I wanted to stay up at least another few hours.
Go to bed.
I'm getting phone calls.
I'm going to answer this call.
There's just telephone call.
They'll call back.
It's pretty catchy ringtone.
I don't know how the fuck this is.
Oh, all right, but I, yeah, I'm going to take off guys.
It has been fun.
There's always.
I'm going to go try to work on a video at some point later tonight.
Maybe upload it tomorrow with the next day.
We'll see.
Yeah, I don't know if I'll complete me, boy.
I got to the end there kind of and I just decided to play Cryptarch.
And then got my ass kicked in Cryptarch, which is great.
But yeah, thanks for coming guys.
I love you.
Take it easy.
Have a good one.