I
Am I even live right now I can't even tell
Me just said German never comes back. It should be live. This is I'm streaming
Mine does not
Yeah, I might even live right now. I can't live. I go now. I hope everyone's going yeah
Yeah
Hey
You was making funny you you thought we you thought we weren't coming back
When I see something like that I see somebody tell you know he never comes back
We're back, okay
And I'm gonna play invasion stuff maybe with
Maybe these guys will play
Oh
Invasion is so like three days ago
I
Have a little bit of fun, man
That's all about 20 more hours and Victor friend
I'm still transmuted remember that's bad for your street. We're the worst streamer. I hey, I
Never said I was the best streamer today
Did you up your bit rate yes, and it was fine, right? I think so yeah
He doesn't even know he thinks I remember from what I can recall
Because that stream I did 10 minutes ago is a fucking blur
Shit
Was your favorite character in TF2
Engineer
Not the scout who you look like him
Scouts from Boston, German scout. No stars the scout Germans the soldier. Why do it the wrong way?
Does this count as the second stream this week?
Yeah, see this is two and one day come on
It's a lot
And a lot of you said of that recording studio
God damn it
Fucking pistol me
How does this map you this is the king of the hill map?
Which one of cough probe
I think I'm only I think I only played on this map for like two minutes
Where's there there's the spawns in their
respective corners because that guy was all the way over here. I didn't expect to see a scout back here
That's the map with engineers on it. Oh, well, that's good enough
I got this you're right there was a century told you
I'm gonna stay down
Why is the engineer your favorite German I think he's the best character
What just hit myself that was done
Because he ate yourself
I think he I don't know he's just like for some reason to think he's the most interesting
Well, like the characters in the game spy is also really interesting to
Ask your questions ease
Yeah, you haven't you haven't talked about this in a while. Yeah, you haven't seemed to really care
What um, there's a fair character and Overwatch
Bastion oh, yeah, talk about that given after the new guys
Yeah, I don't know bastion just seems I
Like the easy sentient robot that is very ambiguous and let's go easy
You like smart guys, huh, German bastion bastions like
Well, they did smart the spy smart national season the robot
Who's your favorite world of work craft character and don't say the guy that's the boss guy?
I was gonna say I'm
Never mind under the answer I'm gonna say it. No, oh, he's gonna say a car. Yeah, Jack in my car
How car is cool what just killed that guy century?
Shit Chris
If it wasn't bastion probably be um
For beer
No
Time to reap no
Maybe I don't know Hanzo's kind of cool
You're getting your buddies worth for that stock ambulance ambulance, what a Jarcha?
Yeah, oh, that's this neighbor that wasn't cheap
We filmed his neighbor dying I'm there you
Come on
Here oh
I'm healthy
Dr. Boom
Dr. Boom a law Dr. Boom a low-well credited in my movie. Oh
Yeah, you did do that then
But you're for a quest the dumbest joke ever made the end of the let's address that the amount of people not that but
The amount of people I thought that that I should have shot that
The amount of people I thought that that was like real oh my god
He filmed like an ambulance outside of his house. What is he doing?
Well, that's that was the stock footage
Wasn't wasn't me filming that yeah, you know you died
I really do like missed contracts
I
Miss like having something to do get every time I walk out of this fucking spawn. There's another person here to kill me
This is walk out was spawned and get attacked at the game
Cough pro almost like the enemies come back after you shoot them well, they're at the spawn
Like every time I go around this corner there's a person here
I
Would adore Jerma being taken by ambulance as a running joke I think that person wants you to be injured
Or an over I might not ever do it again
They'll do it again
Who knows that funny joke I did back four years ago
We're doing it again. I'm gonna buy her said that
constantly
Never out of those words. You said it five minutes ago
What actually doesn't like anyone
You get in a group call with Ashley. I just want to start shit
All right, well, it's over just like the outside my mentor
Shit, I just kneeled on here for a
Secretly count Chocula goodby
Oh, I got only strange knives shit. I forgot I had all the strange knives
That's just like scared me. Yeah, I did another Victor Ranner no demons holes
That's so weird
Did we do it the one time with all those hexes on them? That's when the David's will talk that
Maybe that doesn't crease drops
Probably it Derma, what's your opinion on them?
On what
molasses on
on
Coffee what like like on cheesecrumb cake
What about she's crumb cake what's your opinion that's actually pretty good?
Actually, can you get me some of that?
Didn't make it for you once oh
I don't have a memory of making it for you
I think it's end to me is not Edmunds and I don't know I just eat it. I'm gonna come over here. What the hell?
Like a memory is making a crumb cake and well to make a crumb cake. Oh shit. Oh
I didn't have anything wrote it in damn it. What the hell?
Well, I think you might have made a crumb cake, but not a cheese crumb cake. So I always I wish I had auto reload on but
It distracts me
It always distracts the hell out of me
I agree
Do you use auto reload? No, and if I do I turn a view models off didn't you used to long time ago?
Yeah, and I turned view models off
You claim I'm being Pac-Man for Halloween again
Dude I
That post for all I do is wine
No, I had Halloween this year. I'm not even I don't know
Dude, I really want to have a Halloween video, but are you gonna make that Halloween video you were planning on doing?
I don't know potentially maybe I'm planning on doing the next couple of days. I'm not to look into if that's even remotely interesting
But that has been the plan I've had for the last year. Fuck it. Someone else will kill him so
You know when you just when there's a game and you mean to play it and you don't get around to it and it turns out rates is bad
I
Made plenty of videos where I go. I don't like that wasn't good. I don't want well. No, I mean like
When you're gonna play like you you have a game
You know you're gonna play the game and like oh yeah, I probably make a video on that and then you finally actually play it
And it's just it's just awful like rake like I waited three or four months to play rake and it just
Wasn't into it
Maybe I should just play it from the start
How many how many hours did you how long did you play rake for?
Maybe an hour and a half I mean you can kind of tell what the whole game is pretty easily
Medic I think I can't even get out of the fucking area
We seriously this locked in what that book
I'm ready to get him the soldiers just standing over here
Hey, man, hi, dude
Did you get my message there?
No, I can't pause the game and I'm I'm in spider world again. I don't know why I'm doing this again
Find somebody to do this to I need an invite cuz my internet job for a second
Let me read
We have oh boy
We don't have any classes I can really give this to well, okay, it looks like I can give it to this pyro
Jeremy should bring back scare Saturdays man
That was hilarious because you would get genuinely scared haha
Scary Saturdays
scare Saturdays
Seriously though playing rake today. I fucking flipped out. I think you might have heard me scream
It was a genuine like who seriously are you fucking kidding me scream?
The jump scare dude kind of used your screams now. I know I didn't expect rake to be like a spooky game
I thought it was a goofy ha ha look at this
Wasn't it wasn't goofy it was scary dude. I can just let go about my day and not notice you screaming
That's how common it is get on the point
And see me
Get over here. It's up on the point with me. Yes. Nice job
I'm not like matched. I'm not like does other streamers items scream and
Dude I used to like roller coasters because they were the only place like in public where you could legit scream and you wouldn't be judged
concerts
Yeah, you can stream it a concert too
What?
Go watch beeps. I'm just shaking so violently right now. I
Would be the listen at concerts because I was polite
Who the hell is Ashley?
Who the hell is that?
Nice
Who the heck
Stars to screams like the three times a stream
You know I actually have noticed something about you do you do a lot of screaming I do you do scream
Don't I've become a scrimmer?
Sometimes I can't hold it back, you know
I used to worry about our neighbors, but not anymore because he's like a welder
Oh
I saved your life no no what no no no no
Get too many medics
It could be engineer guy I'll be soldier man
With my dirty ass hamburger gun I
Think I'm using the battle scar one because on purpose
That's priceless by I would have to my suit
I agree
This is Halloween this is Halloween
Where'd that guy even come from?
Came from Halloween
Shit
Do I not enjoy scare Saturdays? I mean it's it's just one of those things that it did I did it for a while
I played all the scary kind of games that were around at the time and
I did it I did it it was it was interesting it was fun for me when I did it but
Now it's all played out just like don't come at it
I don't know why I went up here
You
Walked up oh yeah
Huge century
The one day germ is gonna record a game that I've been asking to make a video on for like six months
At least maybe even a year at this point who knows maybe it is potential I
Got it
There is potential there could a good figure out maybe a Halloween video maybe that could be it. Oh boy
We're in the
In that thing there
Oh
Damn it
Yeah
He's gonna be surprised when he sees a heavy
Oh boy
We got a screamer that would have been great
I would have been good, but they did it like a half second earlier
I'm gonna play that new game that Stark keeps talking about
So I don't think it's necessarily a new game
It's actually probably quite old at this point
You're gonna check it out
What am I going to check it out
Oh, I can just crit the fuck out of me
I
Yeah, I do have that I think I just put this on really quickly forgot again should have that on
I'm not sure if I'm a fan of this map a lot of people I don't mind it
No truck truckers are not a fan I just boss that off my fucking own face
So I dislike it it just feels very cluttered and people can like come from every direction
They really can't though they can god this guy with the mini crit eviction notice is fucking me up big time
Spray the naran like crazy
After this round I'm gonna switch to the other map
Wow look at drama picking favorites
You know, you know who doesn't pick favorites mothers
What
That
that many
that is a trip across the map with that thing
should
is the invasion update the Halloween update
step
out on the
government
dot com
as wanted to
that guy went so high
are to
really high
right when I charged and I missed it that too. I'm gonna fucking pee my pants.
You always say that.
I know I do.
Yeah, you always do. I've seen your pants before.
Oh, I went for the greedy other guy. I got it. It's okay. We're cool.
Hello.
Maybe your game?
No.
I'm almost done with it that I'm done playing.
I'm gonna wrap around.
I always say that.
And then I catch you playing it later.
This people shooting me.
Are you becoming very untrustworthy?
Whoa!
Warning you.
No. What if I...
Does anybody...
That was really weird.
I like teleported to the right somehow.
I'm done with Cryptarch.
So it was a teleportation.
An hour later.
Stir and see you play Cryptarch.
What a day.
You're still understanding.
Nope.
All right.
That's not what I do.
I'm like, a gamer grad.
The worst part of that is someone living here. There's no bathroom down where I am.
So if I have to go... if I have to really pee real bad, I have to go all the way up
like the stairs.
Oh no.
I know.
No.
My god.
He's gotta go upstairs.
I need your new stairs.
There's something today.
All right.
I'm going to a server.
This... this probed map.
I am not a fan.
I'm not a hater of this map, but I'm not really a fan of it either.
I don't know if you just walk up the door like I don't know.
I'll tell.
You gotta pee on top of his pee so you know so that he knows that you're boss.
Let's go to...
I read that if you pee on top of pee, it's twice the amount of pee.
I think you read that.
I really didn't even like hear what you said.
What did you say if you pee on top of pee?
It wasn't important.
It really wasn't.
Now sometimes I just talk.
I do.
Yeah.
You do that sometimes.
Now sometimes I like don't listen to anything that you're saying.
No, yeah.
That happens quite often as well.
All right.
Give me a high coup quick about the invasion update.
I would have to count my hands and I don't have a hand free.
You don't have a hand free.
Yeah, how many is 575?
It's 575 or 757.
I think it's 575.
That's separately 575.
Yes, it is.
Wow.
I'm back in middle school right now.
The most popular poem structure in the world.
How does it feel to be a high coup?
High coup.
Let's go in the beam together, guys.
Actually, I know how this works.
How does this actually work?
We only play this with humans.
That's the beer bottle thing.
What's going on right here?
Like, no one is fighting.
Everyone just glitching into the beam.
Dude, I think the demon souls are from doing the treasure things.
Get those beer bottles.
You get more?
No.
Do you know where it's me?
No, that he's still alive.
You have to do the challenges, I think.
I see.
There he is.
Don't let him get away.
I get six beer bottles.
That means I can heal people.
I can't heal people.
Cool.
Oh, come back here, dude.
Come back here, I got you.
I ain't got a got you.
I don't want to lose your four.
All right, where's that soldier?
You fell.
Everyone's fallen.
I'm just going to deposit my beer bottles.
Hopefully I can do this without dying.
Okay.
Anybody, anybody, anybody?
I can do this, too.
Fine, you know what's going to, you know what?
Let's go for it.
Get that soldier.
I doubt you didn't hit that.
It's almost healthy.
I got switched.
That was the funniest thing you've said so far.
You have, you have to one off that far.
That was the best thing you've done.
I think your whole, your whole YouTube career.
That was it.
Help.
Only downhill from here.
Well, generally, you had so many beer bottles, too.
I mean, does this guy have?
He's only going anywhere.
Give me the hill.
Give me up there.
Give me all your bottles.
How many do you have?
Quite a few, but I can't do anything now.
Stop sneaking up on me.
Ah.
Where you go?
I was trying to go for some cheeky little shit there.
So this is the, that's text to speech.
I thought that was some guy just going, we are in the beam.
That's a text to speech program.
I'm like something to chat with, I'm using a.
That's not the first time I've heard it either.
Like somebody else was saying that, too.
I think Malo has enough resources to hire a guy to say.
The valve didn't make it.
They outsource.
I'm going to go for that guy.
Where are you?
Wow, that guy's got 19 shit.
That guy knows I don't have any health.
I don't even have, I just have like random dumb hats on the sniper.
20.
Deposit those 20.
Make our lead stronger.
God, every time I've aimed in, I'm going to hit with a fucking,
I'm going to put the camp around.
I'll give you a 14 to refine for that sniper.
Give me one.
Oh, yeah, everywhere.
Some little fine guy.
This guy is still here.
Oh my god.
I'll do a trade.
I think I was just standing there waiting for me to come out.
I could have got the health.
Let's do a trade.
Trade for a sniper.
Are you trying to seduce somebody?
What do you want to trade?
Let's trade you for a 14 to refine.
I hope it's not worth a night.
I give you a key, Jeremy.
I don't think that guy is watching the stream.
I really don't think he is.
I don't think so.
Jeremy, you should have the HUD that takes away the people.
That's right.
You have that cool, funny little HUD.
Yeah, I do.
And you never used a custom HUD in your life.
I say it.
So.
Yeah, I was fun for a day.
I used the Garmin HUD.
I don't know how that's missing.
I really don't.
And I get fucking crit to shit.
All right.
It's time to go.
I'm going to go pyro.
Flare gun man.
I'm going to go to the next one.
Don't, don't, don't.
No, that was way off.
Oh my god, fucking damn it.
They are in the big.
I really like this.
What's it called?
The no stromo or something genuine no straw.
Genuine no stromo napalmer.
I like how it's true.
Don't you have no stradamas is playing throw.
I trade him the key for it.
There's a century in there.
That's good to know.
Is that like respawning in 50 seconds?
Okay.
That's why.
If you trade me, I'll let you respawn 50 seconds.
I'll try.
I'll do that.
I run around as a scout guy.
I want to take this off though.
I want to put the hand sandwich on.
I just want to say real quickly that Demi God is still being sold for $10.
Is it?
I don't see.
Yeah.
That game that can't be played.
We can't play.
We can't play Demi Gods.
What?
I tried once and I opened the game and it was like, oh, those servers are down because this game is old.
Are you serious?
Yeah.
So I'm wrong about that or like they've added server again.
That's strange.
No, it's strange.
Is that a scattergun?
I'm trying to.
It's another one of my, you know, you can't have it.
Okay.
Why can't I have this?
You have all the purple glowers.
Yeah, it's not purple, man.
It's my favorite color.
What level is it?
Let's take a look.
I'm not sure if it's the real test.
Do I have any other ones that are?
I have a factory new.
This one's strong.
I don't like this one, though.
This one, you can't even really tell you're wearing it.
Like, look, ready?
It's like when you're running around, I'll put the factory new on.
Like, Broadway is hard to even know that this is a different scattergun.
You have to really, especially like a world model too.
Like, what is your design on that?
Night terror, that's what I'm all about.
You can't even really tell if it's accepted.
You can see it.
You have to press the inspect key all the time.
Like, as you watch me run around, it's hard to even determine if I'm wearing anything.
Alright, fine.
Okay.
You want to do that?
Is that what you want to do?
Turn it over.
Please wear some clothes.
105.
What do you got?
Let's see it.
I got 10.
I want to see how much damage you do.
Alright, go beyond your merry way.
That wasn't even as much damage as I did.
I only hit you once, too.
I only hit you once.
You hit me more than once.
I just want to see what you had.
I want to see what you got.
Alright, that's how it's going to be.
Okay, so that's the way it is.
Get away from me, pyro.
You're done.
Looks like you're streaming Team Fortress, too, to me.
I am streaming Team Fortress, too, you.
And a bunch of other people that are watching.
I'm sorry.
Someone says, check.
Kill that dumbass.
Please, Derma.
And he's referring to me.
I'm sure you'd go to jail.
I might jump on this guy.
I just like jumped at his sword.
Pretty sure killing dumbass is illegal.
I think the judge just says, oh, yeah, it was a dumbass.
Well, no, if you can prove that they were dumbass, you can get away with it.
I get so upset whenever I see a heavy crouch with melee.
It's like I'm conditioned to become angry as soon as it happens.
Well, there's a soda there.
It's called soda.
Yeah, you did.
Actually, truck truck always calls them soda pops.
How have you not died?
It's a hit point system that the game uses.
Get in it.
Come on, come on.
Oh, he's getting.
Stay in the beam.
Hooray.
So dumbass is our important resource and are protected.
So they're like migratory birds.
I can't see underwater.
Derma, how does it feel to be a migratory bird?
Oh, no.
Good one.
Fuck, it is misquicked.
We are in the stream.
I hit every other pellet from the gun.
Unfortunately.
There's a visual novel on steam about someone becoming a Starcraft 2 Pro.
It seems like the weirdest.
How can we not buy it?
It's free.
It's recommended by the curator.
It says it's great.
Curator.
I've been acting so much about Starcraft 3 Pro.
That's so on.
Wow, he just fucking curators.
Oh, that a case.
Where?
I still haven't seen a invasion crate.
Was that just a gun?
Hold on.
Was that a gun metal case?
Yes, it was.
I haven't played in a couple of days, but I haven't gotten the invasion case drop.
That seems a little strange.
They're dropping the gun metal cases.
Still?
Do you think that would drop would be replaced?
Thanks so.
You're not dead.
I mean those beers.
Holy shit, you have so many.
Oh my god, if I could fucking hit you.
Go with the ham.
Once you can't fucking hit shit, just bring out the ham.
That's very, very important.
Just strategy.
That was you.
That bloody loot, hey, box.
I got door cube.
That's what it was.
The door cube.
Be careful, sniper.
I'm not really spy.
Yeah.
Ow.
The invasion crates have a stupidly ridiculously low drop rate.
They're not more expensive after the event is over.
They're less expensive.
I don't know.
What's going on?
I had a Boston Bash just sticking out of his forearm.
That doesn't compute.
That's a fun new glitch.
It's weird.
Quite a game commentary with hints of conversation tonight.
Hits of conversation.
Derma can't hold the conversation while he plays a game.
I can't.
If I like, I'm like focusing on a video game.
I cannot talk otherwise.
The amount of times you've told me like, oh, like, why aren't you talking?
I usually like, conversate in your stream.
Same reason, right?
We are in the beam.
No, like, you've asked me to like, start up conversations before while you're streaming.
And if I like, ask you questions or try and talk to you.
I'd never get a response.
You're just like, not there.
I'm here.
Let's see how I'm here.
Hey, you want to know nothing right now?
Well, come on.
What do you want to know?
Auto.
Auto is right behind me.
You're sleeping.
Oh, you.
I guess I can tell the story of how I took him out today.
Tell us.
So I took auto out today.
And we were doing the, doing the, you go to the bathroom dog.
Go outside and pee and poo.
We all know how to look that slight.
The bathroom dog.
So I take bathroom dog out.
And we're doing fine.
He pees.
He poos.
And I noticed that there's like, there's some sticky things all over his feet.
We were walking around like in the wooded area.
You.
Well, we were like in like a wooded path.
So he gets, ends up getting these, he must have stepped in like sap or something.
Like tree sap out of no idea what the hell he could have stepped in.
He was climbing the trees, yes.
And he, uh, my shit, all right.
I gotta pay attention.
I'm getting, I'm getting critical crate.
Doesn't that count?
I didn't get creepers.
All right, I was, I was kidding.
So he ended up having these like flippers of leaves all over him.
He was, it was as if he was going to go scuba diving.
He had leaf scuba flippers for every single foot.
And he was just like, chuch, chuch, chuch.
Walking really awkwardly.
And I was like, what the hell is this dog doing?
And finally, I like, I looked at his hands and they were,
the ground was coming up with him.
So I spent like at least 20 to 30 minutes cleaning this dog's hands and feet.
And the feet.
And he didn't know the hell is your dog, Dormit.
That guy just died.
It might have been like a homeless man.
You found in a leaf pile.
Yeah, I confused a homeless man with a dog.
He spent 30 minutes cleaning him and there was a homeless man under it instead of your dog.
I don't think that's what happened.
Dog hands.
It was very, it was very odd.
And it's not the first time that's happened before.
That has, that's happened to this dog like at least one or two times before.
I think your dog is part gecko.
I don't know, he's got really, he's got really sticky hands.
Sticky feet.
I mean hands.
Sorry.
Well, both.
If you could give your dog one superpower, what would it be?
I would put money obviously.
One superpower?
That's actually a really, really tough question.
Because one could be like poop gold.
No, me and poop it all.
There you go.
No, we're rephrasing the question.
Your superpower also has to be a power that like someone from the X-Men or like a real superhero has.
You can't change their poop.
No one has.
What?
Come on.
It needs to have a superpower and it needs to be like a real superpower and not a real-changing power.
Okay, because he has weird poops, okay?
No.
Professor X.
He's just a powerfully chicken.
You're making fun of handicapped people.
For what?
For Professor X is like the most intelligent telepathic mind ever.
Yeah.
I would just be like auto.
Can he understand English?
Does he have these powers?
But I can't ask him to do anything.
Whatever power it is, you have to pick which power you want him to have.
Why is this popular?
1,000 viewers?
Question mark?
Team Fortress 2.
Oh my gosh.
Why is this popular?
I mean, if he had Professor Xavier's power, he still wouldn't be able to talk because his power isn't to talk.
His power is connecting minds with other people.
So like maybe auto could like be in your head.
Then I would have the beast power because then the dog could talk and it'd still be a beast.
I don't know.
I'd probably give him like...
Is there a character that can...
Beast is a good choice because he's extremely like smart and he can like move around and he's...
Would the dog be as big as Beast?
Does the dog...
He would slowly start turning like a blue and growing.
Like, would he be like huge?
He would be huge, but he'd start mutating I guess.
Or you could have like a night crawler dog.
He could let himself outside.
No, he'd just keep teleporting after everything and then he'd be...
Fantastic four?
What the fuck is...
How many blue people are on this other team?
Fantastic four, stretchy guy.
I want a stretchy dog.
No.
No, no.
There was just seven people there with no other red two people on this team.
I put my foot down on a stretchy dog.
I want a stretchy dog.
Even that or the flame on, guys.
It would just stretch it.
Yeah, come on.
It's a bed and poop in the bed.
The human flame.
Get his name right.
Fucking idiot.
Oh my god.
What's the name of the guy who stretches?
Doctor Doom.
Oh, not Doctor Doom.
Oh, fingerless.
This is a fantastic, that's his name.
It's a stupid name.
It is a stupid power and it's a stupid character.
The human torch on the human flame.
The human flame.
Yeah, you fucking idiot.
Fucking idiot.
The flame.
The fauverin time.
I hate the fantastic four.
The worst of yours.
What?
Why?
What am I stuck on?
What the fuck is happening with my life?
Don't be me, why.
The face.
The name is The Thing, darling.
He's covered with rocks.
I didn't know what does that.
Gumby boy.
And gummy boy.
Dude, Gumby.
Give me those gumby.
Cool, players.
But he's not an X-man.
So does a cap.
All right.
If I could be an X-Men.
Toad.
I think if I wanted to be in all the movies, I'd be willing to.
I don't want to.
You want to have the best exclusive deals.
I feel like no matter how good your power is, the less screen time you're getting.
Because that guy who could run really fast and slow time pretty much.
He was cut out because he made everything too easy.
But we'll read that.
Yeah, he had to do a really attractive man.
Really vascular.
His power was too good.
I'd be into that.
You could live for a really long time.
What about this?
Can't Jean Gray end the planet if she really wanted to?
Yes, why she dies.
Yeah, but she can't control it because she can't.
You don't want to be too rare.
What the fuck really?
Yeah, and people get mad at you for using her in Marvel.
You call you a scrub.
Yeah, maybe like four years ago on anyone here.
How come every time I go to a class, it turns into four of them.
That's where you go.
I like to spy.
Maybe a try spy.
Pixelver was cut out because of copyright issues.
You serious?
Who owns somebody else own quickseller?
It wasn't the Avenger movie for some reason.
Instead of the X-Men movies.
Did I find this suspicious?
That's weird.
And Scarlet Witch, which is a terrible name.
Jesus, what the hell is I think in there?
What the fuck was I doing?
No, I was staying spy.
I was just dumb.
Isn't there actually supposed to be a new season of heroes coming out?
Is it a spin-off?
Yeah, where is it an actual hero?
I think they killed some of the characters because actors aren't returning,
but heroes is hitting a new season, which I really don't think was around.
That show is so old.
The show is so random.
An in-read.
There's no continuity between anything.
Each season, it's like, oh, here's a different timeline.
I hear that somebody made pancakes in it.
That is the best scene in the whole show.
And that makes me like, I like love that.
So that scene is one of my favorite moments in television.
That's why I mentioned it because your voice did that little thing.
Wow, I got this one right.
You know, it doesn't seem siloer make pancakes for a son.
He's just like missing out.
Give me the water.
Who the spy has the beer stuck on him?
That's pretty funny.
It's like stuck to his head.
Oh, I get to ask me, I'm a sniper on this team.
How dare you try to kill me?
I want you to hype both.
I want you to be better call Saul.
I want it.
I want it in my life.
I want to call Saul.
Did that just fucking have it?
He got turred.
He wasn't even trying to hit me and he cripped me in the face and I instantly died.
Derma, do you watch that show?
Better call Saul with Gritio.
Yes.
Yes, yeah.
I hope I hope I wasn't really like a fan of how they ended that last episode.
Not me neither.
And I called it and you didn't believe.
I really didn't believe it, yeah.
I've already forgiven them who don't need to.
Are you okay?
Maybe I haven't forgiven them.
There are waffles on pancakes.
That's alright, that's a really late response.
You probably like looked it up.
I would have liked to have seen like what dragged out kind of like why that happened to him.
Kind of thing.
No one knows what you're talking about.
You can't see me.
Yeah, no spoilers.
Spoilers?
I was like that's an episode I don't pay attention.
If I'm going to be like not pay attention.
Never once in a while.
Last moment you've paid attention.
When I was just playing Spire right there that last life I was paying attention to everything people were saying.
And I just walked around and just swung at medics spaces.
Truck truck. Can you come in the call and laugh?
Probably he has a new horse fight.
You always take me seriously.
I'm booting you.
You're dead.
And he got me.
I thought I had this on for some dumb reason.
So you're talking understand language that's what you want it.
You just screaming.
Oh, die. Does he understand that you're playing a game?
Wouldn't he understand context?
Would he understand context or what?
I don't know. Maybe he missed out on the context because he doesn't know what video games are.
Like he hasn't learned that yet because he just came smart and now you're screaming die and he would like run away.
Oh, damn it.
I know.
I was just popular.
I was talking about dogs with superpowers.
That's a good question.
Whenever you're in like in like when you're a small infant child, the question is always like, oh, what's super proud would you have?
What's the proud word you dog have because you have to consider you're not you're not direct troll that.
It's very important.
I think that's a question that not enough people know their answer to.
Good point.
Yeah, you can't answer these questions like who are you?
What's the point?
Why are you even around?
Why don't you have a dog?
Yeah, why don't you have a dog, dude?
Get with it.
How is the invasion update?
You're watching it.
My dog would be crypto the dog because he could both talk and he had all the powers of Superman, which are you could pretty much just pull out of your pocket and just pick one.
Mine would be the super horse.
There was also like the power of the Superman, but it was a horse, but it couldn't talk.
It's just like a horse.
It's not real thing.
Yes.
I called a unicorn.
No.
There's like in love with a chick, too.
It's like, oh, I thought I could tell her I could how I feel.
There's like a horse.
Do unicorns have this?
Dude, that's a deep level of usually stuff.
I know.
Where'd he go?
I can tell that guy just come.
Comics, man. They're crazy.
They are crazy.
Wow.
I didn't hit them.
Friedjack.
I guess he got a fancy spellbook on.
Comment to the super horse.
Was that his name?
That sounds right.
That sounds really right.
I don't know if I want my dog to have like Wolverine powers because that wouldn't he like
not ever mind.
Wolverine's not immortal, right?
He just can't like die, right?
He feels immediately like after like a day or something.
He has a skeleton and Adam Mattinger.
That isn't part of his power.
So you're talking about that.
I know you're going to say that.
That's not part of his power.
Because it was built into him.
You're right.
That's why I explained it.
Because Dermal would be your dog would just have like long nails, which is
sabertooth's power.
Yeah.
That's the worst power ever.
I don't know how they like tried to like have him be cool and also fight Wolverine.
Toad.
I have a long fingernails.
Toad is cool.
He is cool.
He's because he's like the reject one.
Yeah, but he's toad.
Toad doesn't like really do anything.
He just kind of has a long tongue and jumps around.
Yeah, he can shoot mucus out of his throat.
Think of all the things you could do with mucus and a long tongue.
I know what you can do with a lot of mucus.
You have been real sick.
It sucks.
That's what he do.
You just like nothing.
You can't, what are you going to do with mucus?
I'm going to do with mucus.
I'm going to do it.
I'm just going to do it.
beni don't people.
That's what he does.
Did it.
It didn't like burn people, or is that.
Oh, no.
No, it's burned people.
It's bad.
It's a real disgusting.
I'm going to hit him with lightning.
It's in the worst line in any movie ever.
when it's checked by lightning.
The same thing that happens to everything else.
You got to remember the Wolverine does have his claws even without the metal they
were just made of bone instead.
For no reason.
Those bone claws are like dumb.
Who is he the bone guy?
Saber 2.
The bone, he had the extra long fingernails.
That's what I'm saying.
Well, I want Darwin's power so there.
He could like change his body into any shape.
He wanted.
How did I not hit this guy?
Like, are we fucking for real?
He was on screen for like 10 minutes and he died.
Did you just say you changed your body into a penis?
That's what anyone would do.
Not me.
Wow.
Okay.
Maybe I would if it was funny.
They're really funny.
It would be really funny.
I will use the ones.
My family wasn't there.
I think there's been a bit of a pain in the ass.
I'm going to put that on.
Merrill, what's your favorite dog breed?
What'd you say?
I got his almost 60.
Yeah, what's your favorite dog breed?
They all have good qualities about them.
They're all different.
They're lovely.
I think a husky is like the most attractive dog.
How to crit.
What did you say?
A husky is pretty nice looking, yeah.
They're like jerks.
You wouldn't actually want one.
Wow.
His chat has a husky and is like upset that you said that.
Hey, my friend had huskies growing up.
They were jerks.
Oh, so all huskies are jerks.
Yeah, pretty much.
I watched Animal Planet.
What was your favorite show on Animal Planet?
The show about dog breeds, obviously.
Is there a centred down here?
There's probably a centred down here, right?
Has to be, right?
I guess not.
No all the dog lower, OK?
Huskies are trained to pull things.
So in order for her to stop them from being crazy and just
barking all day long, she would have to get on roller blades
and never huskies toer around the block.
I guess I guess.
It just seemed like really badly trained dogs.
No, it's in their genetics.
Think about that.
Dogs, though, if you have a dog that's not trained well,
dog will lead us.
Yes, I am.
It's hard to really, it doesn't matter what the breed is.
If you have a dog that's not that well trained,
they're probably always going to be an issue unless you
can fix it, right?
I don't.
But their plan otherwise.
Yeah, I have to hit them often.
Hey, what the hell?
No.
Get in there.
Deposit all 40 in these.
That increases the dog's aggression.
FYI.
Totally shit.
This is a lot of beers going in here.
It also make me hate you.
Wow, that was a lot of things deposited.
Is that beer icon new?
Yeah, I don't remember that from last time.
There were a lot of people saying, what do I even do with the beers?
So I guess there's a floating beer and arrow icon now.
Yeah, they made it in like two minutes.
Beer goes here.
Best show on Animal Planet was the show about trying to prove Bigfoot
was real.
But at the end of the show, they were just like,
we didn't find any evidence, but he could still be out there.
Dude, you just described shows on the Discovery Channel
and the History Channel and Animal Planet.
You know, Bigfoot could be out there still.
No.
You never know.
Some of the episodes are cool.
Yes, I do know.
Like what was the show called, like Monster Hunter?
Try.
Monster Hunter, try.
Are you talking about a cartoon?
No, the actual show.
It was like a Monster Hunter show on History Channel.
Like they, I forgot what it was called, exactly.
Some of the shows were just like so bad.
Like the Bigfoot one.
That show did an episode on the Leopard Conds.
That's every Bigfoot thing ever.
They tried to find the Leopard Conds.
So we paid them to do it.
Mermaid.
They were like.
They were like, I'm getting from ear to ear for the entire
episode.
Like, yep.
We're looking for lepreth grants.
I'm getting such a big paycheck.
Leopard con.
We didn't find any, but they could still be real.
We're looking for real.
We're all getting straight, bro.
Yeah.
Yeah, we're going to win anyways.
There's no reason to just go on Mate.
Like a spree right now.
Oh, come on.
Come on.
Whoa.
It's getting scary.
Hurry up.
All right.
I don't think we've got to fill this map.
Jersey devil is real, by the way.
I heard a story about this guy that's already got him.
This guy.
They didn't episode on the Jersey devil.
And they said we'd go look for it, but we're too scared.
We already know what's real.
So we're not going to go to Leopard Conds.
Yeah.
Jeremy, probably need to stop staring at the UFO
when you're in the beam.
I'm a bug, dude.
You know, like moths, I just have to stare at it.
What's the one that I didn't play?
The arena map.
Brie.
It's a briar buyer.
Brie, I don't know.
Can we have a serious talk about your overlay?
What's wrong with it?
Can I make you one?
Can it be anything else?
If you want to make me an overlay,
it better still have that guy's face.
Why?
Why did you just need grove on it?
Did you just ask by grove a cast to be on there?
Yes.
Huh.
I don't even know where to start.
First of all, it just needs to be animated.
So people know it's not like offline.
I don't know if it's talking about animated shit.
I am an animator.
I could animate the grove or face.
You animate me grover.
I could.
Drinking a milk and being like, drink your milk, catch.
No, because that would be a mute reference.
That's a mute reference?
Yes.
He says it all the time.
Well, that's a grover top of the drink.
My milk and I drank it.
He was on the top of the drink.
I don't think you can add sound file to it, Journal.
What do you mean?
No, it's a word bubble.
Add sound to what?
Forget about it.
I can envision this in my head.
Do you give any superpower to your toilet?
What would it be?
Yeah.
The power to there is no superpower.
You give your toilet.
I would give my toilet in mind reading power.
So it wouldn't know one to open and close because I need it.
Yeah, unless it was like an asshole.
Who cares, though?
You can just that that's a one second solution.
This is how lazy story is.
You that lazy?
No, I just think it would be cool to have a telepathic toilet.
Maybe like everyone's a while.
I don't want my toilet to be sentient.
That's fucked up.
That's some real peewee Hermann.
Like, dude, you're talking about you want your toilet to be like,
oh, it has like superpowers or has like sentience.
Oh, please, shit in that thing.
You shit in that thing.
You want that to like know what you're doing?
No, if I had a sentient toilet, I would do something.
Dude, what did you eat?
It would just be like, oh god, make it quick.
OK, just go.
God, dude.
And then you'd flush and he'd be like, oh, no.
You just forced me to swallow that.
You fucking monster.
And then you'd get out of the room.
You'd close the door and you'd be like, fuck, my god.
No, I would say to you.
I would get you.
Nothing you can do to stop me.
And I'll be back later.
Does it like doesn't have arms?
They can't move.
And I'm going to go eat the cutoff fish.
What if they puke down here?
That's a thing.
But it would just be like crying at night.
You'd be like trying to sleep and it would just be like, god.
It's the most disgusting conversation we've ever had.
God, no, you never.
You've talked about like.
He'd rip out of the wall and start fighting you.
Oh, my god.
You've talked about like bunched up packages and men's pants.
And how like how noticeable it was.
This conversation is like a weirder.
Bunched up package.
Yeah, see?
You thought it was funny then, too.
Just listen to what you just said.
Bunched up packages.
I'm very funny.
Yeah.
I just think that's funny on its own.
Really ergonomic.
I'll draw a grover for you with a bunched up package
like animated for your overlay.
What the?
Oh, shit.
That's so messed up.
Grover.
And it's talking to us toilet.
Oh, boy.
No, I would not want to have superpowers.
I'm watching this while eating.
Fuck.
I'm sorry.
Sorry, Bonzi.
Have I played the game yet?
I'm like, have I done anything?
I don't think you've gotten a kill.
I'm dead serious.
Have I?
Did I just sit in the spawn?
I don't know.
I really have no idea if I was just sitting in the spawn.
Probably happened.
Oh, maybe you had to spectate this round.
Because like 12 people have to spectate.
Oh, we've got a lot of people.
Oh, that is next level.
This changes the topic of something nicer.
Like what's your favorite plant?
Jesus.
What's your favorite plant?
Why am I not going to hit me in the face right there?
Plant from Nukulu Throne.
Is it good answer?
My favorite plant is probably Snapdragon.
What?
Snapdragon.
You don't know what a Snapdragon is?
You answer that so quick.
Because that's my favorite plant.
I know what my favorite plant is.
Do you know what your favorite plant is?
No.
What her plant is, are.
Plant.
Oh.
My favorite plant is Snapdragon.
I can't get over it.
I can't get over the toilet thing.
God.
It's going to be with me for a while.
The guy in chat asks a really good question.
It's the toilet clog.
Is it choke and die?
No.
They have to pee in a dead toilet.
Jesus.
Say what chapter already.
All right.
Now, let's what we're going to spectate.
We're going to spectate.
Thought Jermy would say sunflower.
You have to give your toilet.
That is a very good point.
Very good point.
Have you mentioned sunflower before or something?
No, no.
Like, do they're just really, really big and cool looking?
Hmm.
It's personally, always you pretty well.
Impress us, Shell.
Get this.
Come on.
Get that sniper.
That's you or kill.
You've got to get that.
Get this.
The whole team right here.
They don't even know.
We're going to spectate.
All right.
This guy.
No, we're going to.
Okay.
You got this.
You're going to go in there.
And you're going to be the laggy guy in this whole server.
He got somebody.
He got him.
The chat is being silly.
He.
No.
Tell Star that they do make toilets with sensors that will lift the lid when you get near
it.
I like the toilets.
I've never going to try one.
Go and go and new plan toilet that like spits in your asshole.
Oh, my God.
I'm really curious.
That's one apartment.
The one apartment we looked at had one of those toilets.
It did?
It did.
Yeah, that one that had the fish smells that had that had one of those toilets.
Oh, gross.
I'm so glad we didn't go there then.
You have to do it.
Yes, you do.
You have to do it at least once.
You do.
You really do.
Oh.
We got it.
Shaking that off there.
I'm so glad I avoided that.
I know.
I don't think I mean fish apartment.
I don't know.
I'm trying to think of like if it wasn't Snapdragon.
Cactus.
And I'm not talking like the little cactus that your doctor has in his office.
I'm talking about the big ass Wily Coyote cactus.
The Super Mario cactus with the arms that stick up.
That's my second favorite plan.
I like how long between talking about plants you brought it back up again.
So sunflower is number three.
Nice walk to right into a heavy by the way.
Oh, you're a love walk right.
Snaptragons and cactus and he's a really big plank guy.
How do redwoods factor in your plant discussion?
Redwoods?
Yes.
The tree redwood?
Yes, it is a plant actually.
We had the largest plant on the planet.
Yeah, that's what I think about them.
I thought that would have been.
Well, it's your favorite animal.
Non domestic animal.
You're going to say like dog.
I got it.
I'm a good one.
That's a really good one.
Do you have an armadillo as a pet if you could?
If it was like legal and they weren't like a wild animal maybe.
Okay.
Yes.
And it has the flame on powers.
Just get a headshot.
Like this thing.
What the human flame?
Do you tell me it's got human flame powers?
I need to stop talking so I can get a kill.
It's so many lengths of fiction.
One for any toilet.
That's not I would not want that toilet.
Can I should I click on it or no?
Yes, should.
Okay.
You're almost should click on it too.
Ew, what the fuck?
Oh my god.
That guy again.
Ew.
Give me a break.
Ew, ew, ew.
Oh, I am seeing that.
It all of my dreams.
I'm not clicking on any of that shit.
Ah.
It's terrible.
I'm clicking on it.
She's overreacting.
She's trying to get more subscribers.
Never clicking on that.
Don't try to get me to click on that.
Who linked that?
No, it's really it's not gory.
It's not.
Okay.
All right.
This is a G-rated stream.
More like a bunch of.
Yes.
No G-rated, audience stream.
Okay.
I don't want to see that shit.
Get that fucking dumb shit out of here.
G-rated.
Come on, guys.
Is you saying the word shit?
That's what Jokey's trying to make.
He really stressed it.
You really want to make sure people call onto the joke there.
Okay.
Can I play again?
No.
I'm going to show you guys my.
Why are you playing arena on the stream?
Because it gives me, you know why?
Because it gives me a chance to talk.
You're always dead.
When I'm dead, I can just be like, all right, let's talk about plants.
All right.
Did you see my last round?
I got like three or four people in the last round.
But you like surviving arena.
It's different.
I did you just see the round that I just played in scout?
I got like four people.
Who's your favorite?
Are you watching the stream?
Right now you're equipping a sniper loadout.
I know.
Isn't it different than wacky?
Or...
Hotspin sniper.
You know it.
Say we did it.
Look at that.
You know it sucks.
I was the final shot.
I knew it would be a good shot.
I had some cool enemies.
That's some cool designs.
What was it for?
PlayStation.
The PS.
Nice.
PS1 and PS2 and PS3.
The PS1.
The first.
There were a lot of cool games for PS1.
That was the most random thought.
Hell, it was going on with this guy.
I felt pretty confused.
I was confused as you could be.
I'm not sure.
I blamed that on that medic.
That was civilianing around.
I probably would have...
If I didn't freak out at that, that was weird.
What is more than a good PlayStation 1 classics?
I was talking to Ashley the other day about a vagrant story.
That's not one of my old time favorites.
I'm a little less unknown like JP Koon.
Let's watch this guy.
The old Resident Evil games were pretty good.
Wow, did we just both?
Wow, Jinx you owe me a Coca-Cola classic.
Yeah, I'll fuck you.
Oh.
You did not just say that, did you?
On my G-rated stream.
It would have been a G-rated thing.
Like, you know, they don't show anything.
It's just like a fight.
On my G-rated stream, you're going to bring that up.
Thanks.
Okay, well, moving on.
You're okay, the old...
The old, um...
I figured what they were called.
Turn-based mech games.
It was like, it wasn't mech warrior.
Turn-based mech game.
Yeah, those are really good.
Did I do it in time?
Apparently not.
No, the mech warrior?
I think it was mech warrior.
That was a old PC game.
Is that no gear?
It has like seven games.
Oh.
Front mission.
That guy got it.
That guy wins.
You have to give them all.
Okay, why is this shooting out regular pills?
Everyone who said Front Mission was a winner.
There's a lot of weird shit going on in this server.
This is the Iron Bomber.
Why is this shooting regular...
Regular demo mails.
That's just gonna be tough.
Okay.
Alrighty then.
Should shoot chickens.
What does it do?
Armored core as well, actually.
You know Dark Souls people.
Armored core.
It's quite the good game.
I do remember Armored core.
I would actually freaking love to like PvP you in Armored core.
It'd probably fun.
You should get it.
I'll come over.
I would have to unlock all this stuff too.
You have to make a neck.
But then I play...
You are coming over though, right, Jeremy?
You better come over early so we can do something.
Someday.
What?
This doesn't sound like a commitment.
I'll come over like Friday.
Someday.
Friday.
Yeah, I'm gonna go...
I'm gonna go new server.
This time I'm just gonna do...
I'm just gonna do like regular payload, man.
Oh, I'm not convinced.
Then I'm gonna go to payload upward.
Oh, they are coming over.
I'll be there in like three days.
Is that allowing the traffic? It's gonna take you.
Yeah, leaving tomorrow.
You two non-drivers.
Hey.
You two non-vehicle operators.
I have my driver's license.
Actually, that's a good question.
What do you...
You gonna leave your car in like the train station parking lot for like three days?
That's what you do when you do something.
Do they charge you money? Like a lot of money?
It's like $1,000.
Yeah, just like...
You come back and it's like full of...
$1,000?
Yeah.
Yeah, I know.
What the heck?
What's going on here?
All right, we are on a Borneo server now, and I'm gonna play...
Looks like cart heavy.
Oh, the heavy that sits on the cart.
Is Grover still on?
Shhh. Ow.
On Sesame Street?
Yeah.
Do they still do Grover segments?
You're asking us?
Yeah.
They still do Sesame Street?
Yeah, did she hear the news?
Well, it's a news.
Kermit got a new girlfriend.
Kermit's taking...
Wow! Kermit's got a new GF.
I read like a forum post that's like,
it was good because she was like a domestic up user.
Gladly left her.
She was kind of like into...
BDS subway.
Talking about like the...
Hiya!
She did the high up high.
Yeah.
Hiya!
A lot of people.
Frankaz.
The old Frankaz.
That's a big century can I?
Cheeseball.
Let's find out later.
That's a good point, Mute Kermit is not Sesame Street.
That's a little muffins.
Wow!
Okay.
It's been a while.
Now.
Kermit's on.
That's worth three sometimes.
Is it?
Yeah.
Is Sesame Street the gym-handsome company?
Well, nothing.
They're all on play.
Frank, Frank, that's the connection my brain was making.
I don't think it was count.
I'm so if this is count, it doesn't count.
I'm all caught up in my chill.
I told you I was a show's.
Can I do a Kermit impression?
Everybody has a Kermit impression.
You don't need to hear mine.
Mind here mine.
Yes.
Yeah.
Good.
Got him.
Good!
Ah!
You can't have shoving?
Catch his bell down.
Ah!
Oh, man.
There's a chapter in a book I read about a lady that hallucinated an image of Kermit the Frog in the corner of her vision for three months.
It was just like a stationary image of Kermit.
It was just there forever.
Like overlayed on top of what she was looking at.
Was she doing some hard drugs?
No!
It was like a brain condition.
Really?
Yeah.
That's pretty insane.
Jeez.
She's like, I don't even like that character.
I don't even watch that show.
Why am I seeing that?
It's really weird what like the brain does when you're like not like unconscious mind.
It's really weird.
She said that sometimes he changed like emotions, but like for no discernible reason.
She had a Kermit HUD?
Pretty much.
No, that's what this guy just said.
A Kermit HUD.
Yep.
That she couldn't uninstall.
I do I read it's a book called hallucinations.
Those are really cool.
And she wasn't lying.
Which was proved to how.
Was there a case where some lady woke up one day and knew French and she never started
it and never knew it before?
She just like had something happen.
Wow, that sounded like an internet thing.
No, I think that that was a real thing.
Like somebody like had either a brain condition or something and they ended up like learning a language
that they didn't know somehow.
Swear.
Sounds legit.
Somebody somebody will figure that out.
Sounds legit like a Kermit HUD.
Kermit HUD?
Why am I so cynic, dude, when you've seen as much battle as me?
This guy's gonna hit me.
It's not gonna be nice.
Just go around and have so speed being card heavy, but I'm gonna be punch heavy now.
It's easy to transition.
Hey, remember I was gonna be punch heavy just kidding.
Oh, aw.
The person just got a French accent.
Oh, I see.
Thank you, Chad.
So she just woke up one day with a French accent.
That she never had before and she just was still interested.
Yeah, yeah, no, just so just miraculously like God on the news and was popular.
Fuckin' loser.
You don't know.
There's like the amount of difference in those two versions of the story.
Bigfoot can be put bigfoot.
They didn't find him last season, but they might next season.
There's a million snipers that way.
I'm gonna go this way.
I heard that someone had like a big foot hand in like some monk.
That he sold it and then they lost it.
Dramatic.
Oh, that's weird.
But if me and you ever hit like rock bottom, like just everything falls apart.
Do you really want to like dress up and go be bigfoot with me?
Yeah.
Like spend our last amount of money on like a bigfoot costume and just go bigfoot.
One that costs at least like 15 to $20,000 right?
With like fully animatronic face.
Like the old-missed little move.
Yeah, and like stills on the legs so you can be like nine feet tall.
Yeah, but we need two of us in the costume for it to work.
But yeah, no, no.
We don't have two Sasquatches so people would feel overwhelmed and they wouldn't attack us.
Because I mean you shoot you would shoot one Sasquatch, but when you see another one that can come kill you, you second guess it.
Oh, and like little fake Sasquatch babies so people would like no like one better say we've been Sasquatch babies.
I can't even comprehend.
I thought I got backstabbed.
We just shot me in a face.
German, we're making important plan here.
I'm already showing it.
Yes, I will be the two horse person for Halloween this season.
No, this is not a two horse.
This is your big foot and I'm big foot.
We're two big foots together out in the woods.
No, that's horrible.
We're doing a two horse person.
Oh my god, I'm not doing that.
This isn't going to work.
Which one of you is going to be the butt?
I ain't being the butt.
I'll tell you right now.
I'm going to be the brain.
You don't know the Sasquatch and I mean maybe the brain is in the butt.
You're going to be like a cat dog Sasquatch with like two ends to it and no butt.
Two faces.
No, you're no.
Dude.
Okay, so if we do hit rock bottom, obviously you're not in on the Sasquatch thing.
What do we do?
Do we hit rock bottom?
Is that what you're asking?
There is nowhere else left for us to go.
Everything is falling apart.
They all have blackmail on us.
There's footage of us killing nuns or something.
Well, then we go be a Sasquatch.
That's my strength.
Okay.
That's the good part.
Like people that try and run and like, oh, I don't know what's ever going to catch me.
I'm never going to jail.
They never tried to be Sasquatch before.
All right, so I think then I'm going to just go work it.
I don't know.
Do I still get to like work it like a regular just to make it hard work or something?
No, rock bottom is like if people find you, you will go to jail.
You owe so much money to like the government like you will be in prison to like the IRS wants you.
Because you could not pay all these debts and everything.
I would just I would make a video and be like, guys, I've been at rock bottom and I'll tell you how my plan to get out.
And I would tell like a detailed plan of how I was going to get out of it.
And I'd be like, I'm going to do this.
I'm going to get my life together.
I'm going to do this.
And what do you want me to say?
I want you to say yes, I'll be Sasquatch with you.
That's not going to happen unless we do the two Sasquatch.
I'm not doing two man like you're not going to get a yes from you.
You'd be living the rest of your life in a suit with me.
You really want that.
With a suit with no butt.
Think about that.
Heck, I not die.
I go.
I really feel like our friendships being tested right now.
No, but we could who said we couldn't get out of the costume.
Well, someone sees us getting out of the costume and it's all blown.
The whole thing is done.
We have to live in the woods.
What are you saying?
Yeah, we're pretty much harmits, but we're also dressed as Sasquatches to continue the lore of Sasquatch.
Maybe like someone will accidentally shoot us too with like a hunting rifle.
Unless one person in the chat said if you had a male one in a female one, then make one kill you.
That's right.
As you know, there's like hope for the species.
And then maybe your financial trouble would be solved because you could suit or shot you.
Get on that car.
Your Sasquatches don't have rights, but people in the Sasquatches do.
I have an idea.
How about we talk about something else?
You can talk about living toilets again.
How about that?
How about we talk about something else?
Way more important than any of this shit that you guys are bringing out.
Where the fuck is Grova?
If we can't talk about Sasquatches costumes, I think my knight's over here and I have to go.
You can do what Sasquatch does.
Excuse me.
Alright, how fast do you think I can do the flight, Grova?
I'm gonna be in fast.
Yeah, let's talk about that.
You could make a YouTube channel pretend to be homeless.
But one guy already did that.
How about I just just keep doing what we do.
We're just hanging out playing games and chilling.
And then at a number, we hit rock bottom and we...
We just like film themselves laying in dumpsters like, guys, please.
How do you have a computer to upload these videos to a homeless guy?
Don't ask.
You go to the library.
Don't tell.
And then after that, he would upload videos of him eating sushi.
Like, haha, you mad.
Fastest clicker in the West.
See me in Cookie Clicker.
It's trying to be popular.
I really recommend that a HUD German.
A Kermit HUD.
It's a picture of Kermit and like, no other information.
I clicked way too many times and I lost my ability to click.
What's your favorite fast food?
Like McDonald's hamburger world burger king.
I'm gonna read you a burger burger.
What?
It's...it's...
Fingles doesn't really strike me as what you call fast food.
That is faster than hell, dude.
It is a Fingles bagel.
Fingles bagel is fast food.
Oh shit.
Oh, I don't have it equipped.
Right now, Fingles bagel is my favorite place to like eat in the world.
So then I guess yes.
Got my wisdom teeth removed.
Got some oxy so I'm high.
What?
I just fucking...
What is...
Are you serious?
That was the quickest my guys ever died turning a corner.
They take...
They crack eggs beforehand and they put them in a drawer.
And they take out the eggs and put them on sandwich.
Hey, be careful with those things, man.
They put eggs in a drawer.
What is it?
We're doing real talk for a second.
Be careful with that shit.
Look shit.
Like, taking like the medicine from, you know, the dentist when you get wisdom teeth out.
Be careful.
Just...
There's no...no what it is.
Be educated on it.
And just be...
Take care of yourself, you know?
My mom had to cut me off of my pain, miss.
All right, that's the second time that's happened.
I was like, blah, it's still hurt.
That's the second time I've insta died by this guy.
Shit, no mercy.
Holy shit.
I don't know.
I don't think that one would benefit.
What, which hunt, you're the one that you use?
Just getting some hunt vibes.
A lot of people over there.
Dude, cheesecake factory.
Cheesecake factory blows.
I know, that's why you're not the perfect man.
Why? You don't like cheesecake?
Because he doesn't like it.
The cheesecake's gonna cheesecake factory.
I'm not gonna contest that.
I haven't tried it. Maybe it is.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Back up a second.
You just said cheesecake, the cheesecake factory blows.
And you have not eaten the cheesecake from the cheesecake factory.
As a restaurant experience where you sit down and eat and have food,
it's extremely mediocre.
Do you remember why it's mediocre?
Do you know what the name of the restaurant is?
Cheesecake factory.
Okay.
No, no, do you remember why you didn't like the restaurant?
Because all of the food is extremely mediocre.
No, no, because the decoration was too fancy
and it made you feel self-conscious.
That's the decoration.
Okay, I don't like that cheesecake factory usually is a fancy establishment
for how bad their food is.
How am I goodness?
All right.
Red conning it to have something to do with the actual food.
And no, because the first time we went to one,
it was really fancy and I was like in a t-shirt and it was weird.
So, yes, I was self-conscious.
I was like, maybe I should have worn some clothes.
But you didn't put my pants on me, so I didn't.
Yep.
Sorry.
Well, every day I keep forgetting to put your pants on you.
I want to just go without...
I don't think of it like my, uh...
It's my favorite restaurant.
That's like a chain restaurant.
I don't know.
Is it Mose?
No, no, no, no.
I mean like a sys down restaurant.
You know what I mean?
You're sitting down with friends and family.
Friends?
I don't know why I spilled that teleport when we were all the way up here.
I can't even think of one.
I feel like I'm in a remote room with two friends.
Phillips.
I think is the name of the place.
Phillips?
What?
Phillips.
It's like a seafood place.
There's a couple of them.
I think that would count as a chain.
There's one in the airport.
Whoa, I did not expect there to be that many people here.
What about the Phillips?
You like it?
Yeah, Phillips is awesome.
That dude, that dude's killed me every time I've been alive.
Dude, I hop.
That's another good answer.
This is the first reference to ever liking seafood.
That was it lobster macaroni I've ever heard.
Well, maybe you'll hear me say Phillips is good if we're ever, ever knew him.
Weird.
I'm like married to you.
I didn't, I never heard about this Phillips guy.
I don't know.
I don't know where any are besides there's one in Ocean City, Maryland.
And I went to a lot.
I guess it's like rocker with those peets.
I don't know how to solve.
It's a calamari.
You like calamari.
No.
And what's lobster macaroni?
It's too many people.
Delicious is what it is.
It's an Uber.
Yeah.
Phillips sold out.
Only experience I really do have with Phillips is from Ocean City, Maryland, which is probably
their best establishment just based on a location standpoint.
I was by a hero here.
I was in one of us during Ocean City.
Didn't you go a lot?
For every year for three years.
I went like every year for three years vacation.
What the fuck is that?
As a young and because you can't say no to family vacations.
Yep.
I want to play on.
I want to play on upward.
I'd go again.
I actually reallyidal like Ocean City.
Does it have dip in dots?
Has the Guinness Book of World Records like museum?
There's a window at the beginning where it makes you look at the window or this mirror or something.
It's like a mirror.
You have to give you some instruction.
You have to squint at it or something.
And when you get all the way to the end of the museum, you come all the way around and you get to look at the idiots in the mirror.
Because you can see through it.
Now you're in it for me.
Thanks.
Why would I go into Ocean City?
I wouldn't let you be the person, the idiot, looking in the mirror.
Oh, that's nice.
I just said you.
I'm going to be on.
Oh, yeah, it is Ripley's.
We're on.
Bad water.
I don't think I ever actually went in it.
I just heard a lot of people who had gone in it.
Dip in dots.
Dip in dots, please.
Dude, I'm in the ready for a yearly serving.
My yearly spoonful of dip in dots.
I cousin ate dip in dots one dot of the time and I just...
I can't contain myself when I have dip in dots.
I'm so fast.
I know.
I could eat that all day.
Remember when we were looking into ordering dip in dots from the internet and the whole day?
Where you could get it was like...
It's that free is dried and everything.
In dry ice crates.
You end up by like five gallons of...
Or your birthday party.
What's your birthday party?
Two and a half people.
It's so worth it.
What's dip in dots?
It's like three bucks a dot.
Oh, they are.
Actually, that ice cream you got.
It's also very, very popular ice cream.
Really?
It's comparable to dip in dots.
It's comparable to maybe the best ice cream I've had.
The best ice cream I've ever had probably really was...
I don't know.
I want to say it's like...
If you go to like an actual Ben and Jerry's store, not like go to the supermarket and get the pint.
If there's like a Ben and Jerry's ice cream place.
There.
There are double fudge like fudge chocolate brownie ice cream.
Oh my god.
With a huge fudge chunks.
It's like hitting a brownie in like a milkshake and it's just everything that's amazing about the world in life in general.
I think very shot, pink very.
It's sponsored me.
It's cool.
What if like Mr. Pinkberry wouldn't chat right now?
Did you freak out?
I would decline the sponsorship and say what's important.
Because not Pinkberry?
I'm not gonna sell out to you, Pinkberry.
I'm gonna have to do a new stuff.
Is there another century over there?
But what if you can have like a personal Pinkberry guy?
Or just like server to you anytime you want to?
Yes.
I'd sell out root for that.
Oh my god.
There's so many people.
I wish there was a demo right now.
I can like, I'm hallucinating.
Dipping dots right now.
Let's take this in here.
Just think about sesame chicken instead.
Oh, I'm now hallucinating that.
Very suggestible.
I'm feeling hungry.
There's a game going on.
I might even over it soon.
I guess I am.
Dipping dots about the ice cream of the future for 20 years.
This is the team of fucking engineers, holy shit.
This is like watching the stirs old streams.
You have two medics.
Everyone is cagga and ing in spawn.
Everyone's trying to high five you.
This is like when I stop streaming TF2.
When are you thinking of dipping dots in Boston?
Thanks so.
Oh, he's so low and I didn't get the last couple hits.
We got to go to that place one of these days.
We get the lobster mac and cheese.
We do.
Lobster mac and cheese.
I still don't remember the name of that place.
Oshiana.
Who did I kill?
Corporate headquarters for dip and dots is in Massachusetts.
Is it really?
Yes.
The headquarters of dip and dots.
We let's see.
I'll send them a message and ask for a tour.
The corporate office.
I think they do tours.
If they do, let's do it.
That would be so fun.
We probably would be only people there over like 12.
The dip and dots factory.
Wait, no, I think this is Rhode Island actually.
It's just south of the messages.
I was wrong.
I didn't see the little dots in the mess.
I already get our like our hopes up.
I don't know if this one is right.
Rhode Island is tiny.
Actually, yeah, the train does go right.
I smell a road trip.
Road trip.
Wow.
Yeah, we're not driving people.
We wouldn't understand.
Let's rent a bus and just pick up.
Let's rent a bus and pick up the whole chat.
Yeah.
That's a really long bus.
Oh.
Would you even be able to turn that bus?
It would be like playing a real life game with snake.
Or you know, that way you can start a biker gang.
You know whenever you see like a whole bunch of biker stridebuck.
It's like, oh, whoa, who are those guys?
That's cool.
Guys, it's so awesome.
Please make really loud noises.
Oh, this is awesome.
And then we just all be the chat going to dip and dump.
There is a different place that is 1.3 miles away.
Go run heavy.
Run.
You have the power of speed.
Dude.
I wouldn't recommend people use speed.
The power of speed.
That's a drug, Jabba.
No, like fast going moving fast speed.
Yeah, that's how they get you to take it.
I want to get in here and get everybody with a credit.
Oh.
This don't work like snake.
Let's die a re-adults.
Yeah.
I could actually really go for some fried calamari.
Yeah, not really a fan of calamari.
It's a little too salty for me.
Yeah, well then get it less salty.
I couldn't do that.
No, you got to build up your salt tolerance.
You're like just eat raw chunks of salt every day.
You.
Talking about salt makes me want to be like really lazy and eat like four cups of
cup ramen noodle thingy.
That's what salt always makes me think of.
That's so many of those things are salty.
That's a very average.
Come on.
You don't say that.
Ramen like the cup noodle stuff.
It's such a great when it's really cold out.
You just sit there and you got the broth and you sip it and ship.
You get to the very bottom.
Stir has seen a mind of a chef which like went back to the origins of ramen.
No, he just talked about why ramen was cool and opened my mind and then I had a really good ramen at that place.
We go and it's like my.
I think it's been blown by a good ramen can be there.
But you come and visit we're going to go to that place and we're going to.
We are while you're ramen mind.
Actually, I don't know.
Maybe on the day we come back.
You can go.
I'll go.
You will have at least two of the best things you've ever eaten.
Sounds good.
I like things that I like to eat.
Sounds like a point.
Wow, controversial.
I like things that I like to eat.
I actually have a lot of things that I like to eat.
Wow.
There's many things that I like to eat.
How old is mine?
Only a few things that I don't like the rest I would eat.
Like I don't like shellfish.
Other than that though.
I like pretty much everything else.
I thought you were a spy.
Like all other food except shellfish.
Pretty much that's the only thing I would like.
I'm like, I don't want that.
I don't want that.
Yes, cargo.
It's snail, right?
Yes.
I don't know.
It'd be tough.
Oh, shit.
It's this guy again.
Is this snail almost like a shellfish?
It's like a shell.
Not fish.
It does it.
It's just like the whole idea.
I just don't like it.
Lobster macaroni.
Do you like raw bugs?
Bugs.
Do you like bugs?
Also raw.
They're not cooking these bugs.
You.
I swear there was some study.
I'm going to say that when I don't know what the hell I'm talking about, I'm just going to say that it was.
You were paying so little attention, you went the whole way out of spawn by the way.
Yes, I did.
I know.
I'm aware of this.
I figured that out.
Don't run shooting rocket.
Yeah, I'm doing something.
My brain is trying to piece together the thing.
I was just going to say.
And I don't even what was it?
What was the last three words I said?
Do you remember?
There was some research that.
I was talking about the same people who.
The shellfish.
I don't know.
It's the kids gone.
It's just gone.
All right.
Some of my Bob bugs.
Oh shit, that's not a shotgun.
Here was a study that's the end of the story.
I know that there's a study down at one point.
I think it involved shellfish.
It'll come to me.
I think your team is winning.
I hope so.
Winning.
That's like what do I like the least favorite thing?
Winning?
Yeah.
Winning.
It just said it.
I'm charging here.
I watched that interview live.
You know, don't know why.
I don't want to.
And then the meme came out and I was like,
I was there, man.
It was there when it was winning.
Oh my god.
This fucking guy.
Can I have like a brain shield?
Can I put a thing on my, can I put like a fucking astronaut helmet on me to steal?
Is this like the medic amulet?
Yeah, I could really use the medic amulet right now.
That would be fantastic if I had that equipped.
Studies are usually inherently flawed.
I want some of that rummaging.
Not usually.
Ah-ha!
Ooh, I spoke to you.
Ooh, is Bullin the call?
Trying to scare that guy.
Poor Bull, he has no idea.
Where is Bullin?
Yeah, what's he doing?
What do you think?
Sleeping.
Probably playing Rocket League.
He's gotten very good at it and he plays it a lot.
I talked to him earlier.
And he said he was going to bed.
Thank you.
But how reliable is he?
Or reliable in German.
What is with the telephoto?
Not a high standard.
That easy.
I have to go to the potty.
You view better not.
I went to it three times during the stream.
That means it's mine.
I don't want to cause any trouble down there.
Let's see about that when I talk to him.
Where is he?
One day I'm going to wake up from a dead sleep.
I should have done the same thing.
When you see a spy in a tight corridor like that,
you just start swinging in every single direction.
And one of you will win.
I didn't do that.
I pulled out the revolver, which was a mistake.
That was a smart idea.
You just handled it very poorly.
He just went into the chaos tab.
I should have done that.
I didn't do it.
The chaos tab.
That's right.
I broke my own rule.
Oh, shit.
Shit.
Get well, bomb.
He's looking for me.
I wasn't a headshot apparently.
I think based on that scenario, I know that I could beat you in a night fight.
Oh, come on.
I wonder how many times this guy has killed me?
Probably like 12.
Nice fight.
I know escaping through that.
To be fair, he didn't swing in every single direction.
He swung in a very specific direction, specifically at you.
Yeah, that's true.
I did not.
I did not do that.
Dude, let's play the drawing game.
I've been running for that for months.
Turn him up.
Is it a draw game?
The drawing game.
Remember?
The vomit shield?
I do remember drawing game.
The vomit shield.
Caja.
You were paying attention back then.
That was.
Not anymore.
Now I'm trying to take out a century with his engineer over here.
Hey.
I don't think you just get, I don't think you get how this works.
Get what?
You're like flanged spy on a server where everyone's dream's looking.
I don't think you like get this.
I can't do anything to combat it anyway, so who cares?
Who cares, mate?
And oh, he knew, he knew, he knew, he knew.
I'm co-hosting your stream and not a mod in your chat.
I just kept like, blocked by the slow mode.
There's a lot of people who aren't mod in your chat and it's really rubbing on them.
Rubbing on them.
Do the drawing game.
See?
That's what the people are.
The drawing game.
Back to the drawing game.
Oh, I'll pull out.
Holy shit, am I going to be able to stab this guy?
But only 10 seconds.
Ow.
I'm telling my top scorn.
Stir just said, ow, as he went to the bathroom.
Maybe he stabbed his twitsy.
His twitsy.
It's possible.
It is very possible.
I like how his soldier looks.
Looks very wise.
It's just the travelosity.
No, it's really all of this.
I see it now again.
Are you shitin' me, dude?
What the fuck is this?
What is going on?
Does that guy have like 5500 HP?
Has the robot fucking medic again?
What is going on in this game?
Wow, that was a voice-up.
I don't even know why I'm trying to attack this guy.
He was flexing hard there.
The bolter is bouncing hard.
It might be time to change games.
Games to the drawing game.
Did you just see what just happened?
Yeah, the medic took...it was a tank.
Something's fishy in here.
Stinks.
Something's stinky.
Something stinks in here.
They're really stinky.
Look at my rocket jumping skills.
They don't exist.
There he is again.
There's the robot tank.
Maybe he's the alien, Jerma.
Maybe he's the invader.
Did they get invaded by civilian medic robot tanks?
2000 HP.
Yes.
See?
They put fun to this update after all.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
One more life.
One more life and then I'm going to go play something else.
There's going to be a pyro life.
You know, we're going to end out the TF2 run with a flag pyro run.
You're the bottom.
It's time to get in that Sasquatch costume.
Yep.
The medic comes back over here.
I'm just going to feed off him and then go crit people.
Feed her.
He missed the robot medic.
There he is.
Things do not add up.
I'm going to feed him.
He's just trying to have no.
Oh, but.
But he was right there.
I'm going to play the dragon.
There he is.
Now, I got to get one flock.
I got to get one turn the corner and flock.
Don't worry.
Everyone is stream sniping you.
So they'll know to stay back.
Well,
shit happens, right?
No, it doesn't.
Not to me.
And not to me either, dude.
Shit happens.
Ha ha.
So after this, we're going to, well, you want, are you awake to play drawing game?
I am.
I'm going to play with the monster.
Starry you.
Is that what you post pointing that for another day?
What did they come on?
Come on.
That was about to do it, too.
Would you actually draw a game?
Didn't we need more people?
That was the issue.
I can't go all the way like that.
Okay, Jordan.
Okay, he's in the stream.
Do we need boo?
We can boo.
Just want to play TF2.
Yeah, we can't do that.
So we can't do that.
I can't do that.
No, you can't do that.
There's a couple of things you can actually do.
Well, I could.
Another all going actually.
That medic.
Hypothomatic.
No, this is not the rope.
No, no.
You do talking about robo medic.
Yeah.
There are like five people chasing around trying to overstop.
Oh, fag-istinator.
Yeah, keep me over it.
Keep me over it so I can like actually get out of spawn and hurt someone.
Fuck horropo medic.
Everyone, why don't you have subs?
Oh, shit.
Dude, big Walees.
I
You see some of that the name of it. I think it is truffle
Stir
We need another guy
You know, not I am tired and we're gonna we need to get boys for it one day all right
We'll get some boys look look look look. We'll get some some gentlemen look at some
I don't lock gentlemen. I want boys
Suggestible boys
So that was it what I'm gonna do
See what am I gonna do right now
Banny
Banny you know banny someone said I think he was suggesting a boy
Sure, Banny would play it on blocks and invasion crate. I don't have an invasion crate. I
Probably would
Nothing dropped
All right, I'm going to use the restroom I'm gonna rest a little bit in the restroom
And then I'm gonna figure out I might stop streaming I might move to something else. Oh
I'd recommend
I think I might go you're leaving
Possibly this dog is looking at speed. I think that means it's time for bed. Oh she's sleepy
That's gonna be
Yeah, this is live streamer bathroom time
You know how we need to have one of streamer's like cameras everywhere for any room you go
And it has some all live at any time
So I'm gonna have like a nine camera shoot inside my bathroom. Yeah, swing galaxy style
There's just gonna be one in every corner on everywhere. Yeah
That way you can you can cut it into a montage when you're done with multiple angles
Make a frag movie out of it
That would be pretty
Pretty stupid
All right guys, I'm back. You two are leaving. I'm assuming
I guess all right, we're losing these two chumps
Good night everybody. Thanks. Thanks for hanging out in the stream guys. It was fun. Oh no problem. Be here Friday
He's he just killed come on didn't you get to say a formal goodbye?
Unbelievable
You
Tell her germa he needs to eat the cheese
What cheese?
I actually would play Mario maker right now if this room was set up to be able to play it
I don't have my Wii U in this room
But hang tight. I will be back in a couple minutes. I'm gonna grab a drink. I'm gonna take the take the bathroom
I'm gonna take the bathroom out of my bathroom and use it in my living room. Have you right back?
Hold on a second
You
Okay, I got some lemonade
I
What can I do right now just to kind of chill for a little bit
I don't know let's see what do I got what do I got on the steam library
Good play I
Can play more cryptarch but that requires a ton of my focus
I'd rather just chill for the remaining like however long I'm gonna stream for
So many games in liat nothing to play
You
Mind sweeper
I'll start actually went to bed. I think
All right, maybe I'll do this
Give me a second I will load it up
Yeah, that's a game. That's really easy just to turn your brain off and I'll you know we'll do how about this
For the last like I'm gonna be 30 minutes. I'm gonna play Diablo 3
Just kind of run around and swirl in people maybe
And maybe I'll play like a hardstone and be terrible
All right, hold on a second. I want to get this like to see
What would you guys would rather see here?
Oh, whoops, there is no game
I don't have a game to show you
All right, gonna either play a hardstone and be terrible binding of Isaac or Diablo
Which one
And I'm gonna warn you guys
Watching me play hardstone is going to drive a ton of you crazy
Let's do a let's do a poll
I'm gonna do one of those fancy polls that you see from time to time
Hmm
Stop changing
Yeah, this is gonna be very simple straw poll
Okay, I'm gonna put it in the chat why not
And we have you have 30 seconds to vote by the way
You have 30 seconds to vote on this poll
Well, binding of Isaac seems to be destroying everything else right now
All right, we're gonna we're closing this out in like less than 30 seconds
Play wonder book that is actually not a terrible idea
Not tonight. I definitely can't do it tonight
But
Damn, that would be really cool
Because those games that are really funny and really crazy, but they're actually pretty interesting
All right, it's very clear binding of Isaac is winning by way too much for anything else to win
So yeah, where the poll is now closed. I'm gonna play binding of Isaac is he gonna be
binding of Isaac and I'm just gonna answer questions. He may questions and answers binding of Isaac time
So let's load that up
Oh
Go play a real game
Yeah, binding of Isaac won by like it like it was like 60 percent or something or 50 something percent
I
Need to change my stream title to make sense
So I'm not playing to you anymore
To make sense. Oh, no, I can hear my voice. She keeps you presents messin with Sasquatch
No, there's like an ad playing now, too
Hey guys. Oh, thanks big and a sasquatch messin with Sasquatch
I'm getting a messing with Sasquatch ad
Here you go, fella. Try this one
Why
Why do I think that's so funny?
We were talking about Sasquatch this whole time
I applied wish I please tell you guys heard that
He's real Sasquatch is real
I'm at rock bottom. I hit it. I hit rock bottom
Perfect
Okay
Close that
And I need to change this
That's not right
binding of Isaac rebirth
There it is
So for the remainder, this is I'm just gonna be chilling and I'm gonna answer questions
How does that sound we're gonna do some questions and answers and answers
Currently on a minus two not doing hard. This is just hanging out
Take a sip of my lemonade. This is delicious
Are we gonna get a germa rumble this holiday? I really sincerely hope so
But I can't guarantee it. I'm going to do everything in my power to do this particular video
Hopefully it happens. It's gonna be hard. I'm gonna do king
I
Would have inspired me to create grandpa
Well grandpa I think I've actually answered this before
It's based on my grandmother that voice and that like whole character is pretty much just my biological grandmother
She used to talk just like that. I would imitate her
She lived with us in the house when I was growing up
And that's kind of how it worked
I'm ever gonna get real platinum god absolutely no
Well, it depends if the new
Isaac expansion is really really awesome and really fun
Maybe I'll play this shit out of that I don't know
I can't guarantee anything
Dude, guys, here's another thing. I don't even know what I'm gonna have for breakfast tomorrow
And like videos and and and all this stuff. I don't I have no idea
I'm gonna try to make whatever I can make and do whatever I can do
But I seriously don't even know what I'm gonna do tomorrow. It's always a mystery
I'm using a controller right now. Yes
I find it easier for me to use a controller
Oh shit, I'm stuck in here
Before I die from this guy
Did you go to college? Yes, I did I did go to college
I have I have a bachelor's degree
And what do you know I'm also a young bachelor
Hey, buddy
I
Tremble why are you bad at this game
Well, I
Have not particularly great at any particular game
Maybe maybe I was in my my wonder years kind of
But was my reaction with star beat kryptalk in a few hours
That's just what he does
Stodges beats every game and it plays it to its utmost like he plays the shit out of it and beats everything
Before I even like have a chance to even download the game
That's just what he does
I'm pretty good mobile game player
I wait with the secret room B
I'm gonna guess right here
And please be right
Shit
Are you still doing volunteer work or did that magical idea for rarry? No, I actually actually oh
I'll talk about that for a minute or two. I'm just gonna go. I'm not going in there
I did that where I was at a volunteer at an animal shelter for eight months
I stopped a while back before I moved
It was really interesting experience. I will gotta say
I walked to dogs
That was a dog walker
Sometimes there were a lot of dogs in the kennels sometimes there were like none
So some days you'd be kind of boring you'd go in and they'd be like really nothing to do
They'd be like maybe one real dog there, but then
There was a very large amount of dogs that came in
And for a while
They was a lot to do in fact after actually the last like
Let's say like a full like good seven months or something like when I first got there the it was
I don't know hard to explain
But there was uh
It was definitely cool experience if you like dogs I would do it
If you like animals why not you don't have to do it forever
Let's do it for as long as you can
Or just you don't dump
Kittens are puppies. Well, I just said I was a dog walker so fucking dogs puppies
Oh dog walker would have lame dude
It's volunteer work man
It wasn't lame
I was still doing YouTube and stuff at the time and I've been doing YouTube for like five years
I also did wedding videos and stuff like I've been doing things. I don't do that anymore, but I did
No, I'm never gonna do that with a cigar
Will you get out of there?
Get out of there dude
Oh my goodness, please come out of there
I want to explore
I'm everyone you were making a game. I think you talked about it. No, I wanted to write a book
Then I did start it, but
Came to the extremely quick conclusion that writing books is extremely difficult
So I wrote a bunch of stuff
and then
Life got in the way and I became too busy to even have enough like free time to care about that
unfortunately
I can't ever keep talking about undertale. What is undertale?
This is a new game again on
How come you lagged on insane aquarium?
You mean like the third video I ever uploaded to YouTube?
I don't know
Probably because I was on like a shitty like dog shit laptop that had like less than like two gigahertz of the CPU speed
Really it's not there
Did I just miss that or something?
Hmm, I don't have enough money
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa
That's what I get for not paying attention
Too bad
Undertale's a game is that it's mixed reviews and it's one of those games that is good because people say so but I'm not saying it's bad
Well, every game is subjectively bad to air somebody, you know
I don't want to go in there. Let's just get the boss
Do I watch anime? I used to not really anymore
Back when I was in college. I was really like into it. I thought it was really cool and I can't like what the fuck am I doing
One coin
I
Don't I'm confused of what actually just happened. I thought if that was a troll bomb and the troll bomb spawned after that
Apparently
No, I mean really I started to watch the anime back when I was in college because my TV was pretty much permanently on adult swim and
Saturdays I believe is when they did their like big anime block and about some of those shows are pretty good
Oh
I want to read this one. Let's see if I can answer it
After I've monstrosized
Over the years of YouTube and life and all that other shit in the mix was the biggest thing that's changed for you
Or just what have you noticed that changed you?
Um
That's a that's a good question because I really feel like over the last at least a couple of years
I've started to grow up and started to see really see a lot. I've been asking myself the questions of fuck
I'm being like the old person, you know, I'm like oh back then it wasn't like that. It was so much
We back when we were kids. I've been doing that a lot lately
And I'd never ever used to do that
But like I am seeing things now like in video games or in TV and movies and I'm just like what fuck is this?
You know, I was like 19 so much cooler
but
You come to realize
Literally that's every single person when they get older has that conversation with themselves
And also getting older too like turning 30 was kind of
It's got scary you know what I mean
Who's a scary thing when you get over that age you're just kind of like okay
I am 30 years old what the fuck is going on in my life
You start to reevaluate things that you're doing you start to re-evaluate like where you are and where you want to be
I wouldn't say it's depressing. It's kind of like
Almost like eye opening that you see you you start to see things you like differently
I have like a bunch of kids in my family now like my brother and sister both have kids
And it's just really weird
You start to see that your parents start to get way older and it's
Like wow life just kind of keeps going doesn't it
Let it go
Yeah, you when you turn 30 you have that kind of you have to let it go a conversation. I've let it go
You
Turn but looks eight
That is I guess one thing that I have gone for myself
I don't I don't like look like I'm 30 plus
When I look in the mirror I don't see like a 35 year old even I'm not 35 but you know you get the idea
You
Technology oh no no no this is this thing shit. I didn't want this
I actually don't like this at all. I thought it was one of the technologies
Favorite band is a gorilla's for sure
Since doing this whole move and everything no I've not been working out at all
Even a little bit before I moved like the last like four months or five months. I probably haven't been to the gym
Which that's I can get back there I gotta do that again
Open your face
In my fat now I don't think so I just made a video where you can see my whole body
I don't think I'm fat
All right, where am I going here
Oh, and I'm Kane what
What the fuck
Oh my goodness gracious
None of those were any good
Okay
Alrighty
But I want to join a racing league for Isaac. I don't think I'm good enough at the game to be frank
I would lose every time you probably fun to do it
Yeah
But now I'm not I love watching people speedrun and race
It's actually one of my favorite things to watch on twitch
A lot of the speedrunners that do their streams
I've been really into Mario maker been really into watching Mario maker streams
Now people that are like go to the game and like know what they're doing
Really like that a lot
You
Shit
Yeah
Almost my favorite noise or sound
Uh
Okay
probably
Rain hitting a roof
That extremely distinctive rain hitting your roof sound
Yeah, you know what I'm like that like
That
If I could make it rain like that just that gentle heavy kind of big water droplet rain every night
I'd probably do it
Give my dog those superpowers
Shot speed up helps a little bit doesn't it
The
The brain hitting your roof people's brains smash into my roof
If you could go back in time what point would you go to I wouldn't I
Would not I would not go back
And I can explain why I wouldn't go back
Go look if you ask me if I'd rather go backwards in time or forwards in time
I would probably say forwards in time
Like if you have it was like oh you could go forward 10 years or backwards 10 years
I don't know man like when growing up you
Like all the things that you can't do when you're the younger like oh yeah
I go back to when you're like 15 again or like 12 again or something
This so much shit you can't do
That you have to like wait again to be able to do
Nobody trusts you with anything you're like younger, you know what I mean like it's it's hard
Like the teenage years can be I mean they're a great time
I bet you a lot of you guys are probably like in your teens. I would assume probably half you guys are like in like that
You know 15 16 plus maybe college days. I don't know how old all all you guys are
But with special when you're I wouldn't want to go back and like do it all again
Oh, but you could go back and you could change everything and do it so differently
But I've ended up where I am right now and I'm the person I am right now because of the way that I already did it
You know what I mean
Like what if I went back and I like changed something would I have ever done half the stuff that I'm doing
You know, no
You
Teen 24 18 that's what I expected
Sound like the late high school early college
20 like the median something like 20 I can see that yeah
28 with a with a fail the phase palm dude don't I'm 30 man
It's not it's not it's not it's not old the world has changed
30 is the new 25 in my opinion
This room sucks
Hurry up get over here get that bet
How the fuck are you 30
Hey, I wake up and ask myself that question a lot it just happened
I graduated college and then I turned 30
What was that was a rock back here which room was the rocket
There
Now I can't do it there wait hold on could it be right here
Nope
Time seriously flies don't play MMOs I played World of Warcraft for a long time that took a lot of my time
I played that game for years
Yes, the more germ of wrestling the more wrestling's on the way
Don't worry
I'm I'm trying as hard as I possibly can
To be able to make this next one
There it is being worked on
Fuck where's my tear it's like all in the corner
Oh
For the love of all that is sacred
Oh about to just cramp as the son of a bitch here we go
Find a fancy 11
Well, you'll be opening up subs and donations soon. Oh no
No
Subs
Yes, but donations now
Now go go down to eight
Damn it. Why have both of these have to have bombs like that?
I mean if at some point I decide to do donations
I don't I don't know it's it's one of those things that I don't think I'm ever going to do it
What do that just do to me?
Well not that
Will your TF2 server ever come back? No, I don't think so
I don't think so
To be completely and totally honest it was kind of just a money sink that I had I had to just sort of get rid of
And I didn't have like very many good like I have one good admin and he was really reliable and he was always around
But I I don't know I don't feel like I need to have one
I had it for a while that was a great I made a ton of videos on that server
Some of you guys might have even been in those videos where I did like the weird like event type stuff
Did I forget to get that I did
Like two floors ago I didn't get that I need to remember that one
Let's go back this way
Do I still enjoy TF2 after all these years? I mean I was just playing it
The core game of team fortress two is does that do anything to this?
It does
That makes this arguably worse because it stutters
The core game of TF2 will always be like one of the best games I've ever played
But but there's always a but
You
Has only so much you can say or do about anything
If you guys are wondering why I like haven't really been making TF2 videos
So because I don't like the game
It's because I want something to say I want to like do something in those videos
And it's lately it's been like uh there's not really a whole lot I can say or do
Oh
I
Don't die here
Go over there you slow as ball
That doesn't mean that doesn't mean I don't like the game
Forget what the Joker does we're just gonna use it
Wonderful
I don't even wanted to get the key I'd rather just go in
You can't drop the trinket what is it but button is it
It's not that
Hold control I don't know what is on gamepad
I don't think I have it set up for this
Does anyone know what it is on a gamepad is it even bound anything on a game
Of course of course I hit the button that I'm going to need right now
There it is
It's right trigger
The brain just leaked
Are you a fan of Bernie Sanders um I'm just gonna say it I
I don't like talking politics
I don't I don't know enough about politics to
Really want to get into like a discussion about it
But if you want to know if you'd like to know if you if you need to know where I um
Where am I low you chaotic neutral are you neutral lawful are you lawful good?
I am right in the middle
There are I am as in the middle as you probably could be
But let's go
Any more hearts. I yeah this one
But I don't like talking to even with my friends
It's just like everyone has their opinions on things and you just don't want to get into like fights and debates with people about it
Because that's how it always happens where am I going
I don't know like like Benjamin Franklin once said the great Benjamin Franklin
Oh, it's in a secret room. That's why
The great Benjamin Franklin what's what the f
Which I'm just gonna go
Well donate the rest the great Benjamin Franklin one said
Error all things in moderation
If you're too extreme with anything
You're not following Benjamin Franklin the greatest president of the United States
Even though he wasn't a president
He still felt like one and he's on the hungry
Oh
Andrew Jackson's on on the 20 oh Abraham Lincoln's on the five but Benjamin Franklin is on 100
He's on the hundred
Like did we really have to have this discussion
Is George Washington on the hundred? I
Rest my case
It's probably things they can do but do I care
Give me that heart
Do I follow any sports?
Not really I used to follow the red socks religiously
The red socks were
Like my life especially but what it was so awesome
That 2004 and 2007 World Series. I got to see both of them like they're not live but
Watching that team win the World Series in 2004
Was awesome
They haven't won it in like 90 years or like 86 years or something crazy
And I was in my dorm room
Oh, no wait, where was I when was that 2004?
No, I was in my two was I in college in 2004? I was right no
No, I think I just barely was like a freshman in college
Yeah, yeah, I definitely was in college for that
I am 30 sometimes you forget things
Oh god, this is gonna be annoying
Get away from me
You
See do any role models or people you'll look up to
Well, I mean Benjamin Franklin has got to be like the but not uh-huh
Well when I was younger when I was like in my teens it was Jim Carrey
I like loved everything about Jim Carrey. I thought he was like the funniest
Most awesome the amazing dude ever
But as of right now, I mean I
I don't know I don't really have like a role model anymore
Will you stream FTL and the follow-up question is who question
Will you stream FTL and get a girlfriend
Uh, no one the first one because I I'm not that great at that game
And the second one I don't know I don't know. I don't know who knows
I
What do I want to be when I grow up? Well, I've already grown up
I wanted to be a magic wand maker when I was in preschool. That's what I said. I wanted to be
They asked all the kids what they wanted to be when they grew up
And you had the typical fire fighter doctor
Magic wand maker
I wanted to I didn't want to be a magician. I wanted to make the magic ones
What the
Why
Who cares? I do nobody nobody cares about the magic wand maker
People want to see the magician
Magic wand maker I bet to the audience probably all laughed
Oh my god this game is fucked
My little teddy wants to be an astronaut my little Jacob want to be a policeman and you're telling me your little shit child
What to be a magical wand maker. It's imagination. All right
Imagination is really important. Don't have a lose it
Doesn't matter how old you get
Don't have a loser imagination
What do you see yourself on your 30?
Well
Sitting right here right now doing this because that's where I currently am at 30. What does this thing mean?
I
Don't think I've ever seen that before
What is this
Well, okay, was it wasted bomb
No one cares about the guy that makes the plans stuff and lucky charms
I
Fuck lucky charms lucky charms is only good to get to the end of the marshmallows and then you don't want to eat it anymore
You just eat and soggy bread
I
That was the first grade I was asking my favorite book was and I said Harry Potter because it's real
Hey, like that. That's
That's awesome. I hope you ashamed of that
I thought Santa Claus was real until 12 months ago
Santa Claus is real that's what you guys don't understand
Give me something good
I don't want just a bomb give me something good
Dog food yes
I
Mean more keys. Oh take them
I've got out to two keys
Now fuck oh
Well
You get out of here too just cuz I you know you gotta get it all over
David Christmas movie
Jingle all the way
I'm sorry that's the answer
No, no, it's a puppet Christmas Carol what jingle all the way
Hey
It's a puppet Christmas
Oh, it's fucking stupid
Home alone is also extremely good that's the one you can't forget
Muppet Christmas Carol home alone or jingle all the way
I don't I don't even like why did I say jingle all the way
I don't like that movie
There was no reason for me to say jingle all the way I just said it
All right jingle all the way because I don't I can't think of my favorite movies
Oh
Yes, donate it out of care
Was that me in the Pac-Man suit yes it was
Yes, it was
You
Favorite album probably demon days by the girls
Girls are like the only band I like to listen to
There we go
I'm going here
Oh
I had
Cool
Auto I dog is snoring
You
Remember when I said I was going to stream for 30 minutes a half an hour ago
Well, I'm just here man. I'm just here chilling
If I was an action figure what accessories would I come with
I don't need the I don't need any fucking gimmicks
But just be me
nude in the box
I need like a gimmick accessories
I
Took me a whole week to listen to all the music on my computer
I know like you know I kind of envy
Hi Poe envy people like you I
Wish I cared a lot about music
Because it's so music is something you can just kind of turn on and like care about it and listen to it
No, that was a great song that's a great song out of my
5,000 song collection
I don't have that
I like put on plastic beach for 20 minutes and that's it and then I've gotten then I'm done
But I wish I cared more about music
Oh hey
Hey
If you were a giant sick how long would you be
I'm assuming that you're trying to say stick
I don't know it the yardstick
Yeah, I'd be like a yardstick. I don't know
What I study in college communication
Film TV radio
I don't know why I was walking towards that guy
Oh
You learned how to talk in college
No, I learned how to
Well, I'm not being learned is pretty subjective
I was
Shown how like radio life is and going to studios and working on demo reels and
How to use editing programs and more like shops and stuff like that and
Media marketing and relation public relations. I was it was was that stuff whole thing
But the thing I when I was in college what I wanted to do oh fuck
Damn it
I've wanted to do like voice work voice acting acting in general
I
After being a magic wand maker I wanted to uh not to be like an actor
Where did I meet star shoot many a tournament
That's like the first time we ever saw each other in real life
I
Think like we needed another person for the shoot mania team and
Him and I just barely kind of started talking like just barely and I was like oh
I know the perfect guy for the shoot mania team. He's like we could go to like a quake style games and TF2 and
Oh, his name is his name star
I like it. Of course. Oh my god you fucker. Oh
My goodness
crap
Yeah, and it was me orb
mlc stealth
And star and I think it was orb couldn't play
Because it was a us only tournament you couldn't be from anywhere else around the world or something
So orb was like oh shit. I can't play in this tournament
And originally I think we're gonna get shibi was gonna fill but then it was like star and I think shibi
No, it was it could be either one of them was who was gonna be
But started up
Filling that spot and him and mlc stealth well mlc stealth just carried that entire time we played
That was so cool
I will go down as one of my favorite things like in like my gaming quote how long have been playing games
Was like winning that tournament like being on that team and like being able to go to e3
Was like I just I had to do that. I was gonna get hit thousand times
You
You realize you have a entire two-hour stream posted where you do will calm the star
Yeah, but I mean we weren't like we weren't like friends and we didn't really hang out
I thought the question was like when did I like meet and like start hanging out with star like we talked
Not a whole lot like it was sometimes we were talked but it was really that like shoot mania tournament is when we started to become like real friends
Everything before that was kind of like I kind of know you a little bit. I don't really know yet all but you know hi
That was when our friendship started
He locked in
Any regrets
Everybody has regrets
Not really but I mean like yeah, I like shouldn't have eaten that taco in college when I was like had like colitis
Yeah, that's a pretty best of regret
You
Let's just go
The tinted rocks shit
You
How does it feel to be a washed up gamer? Hey, I didn't make the washed up gamer washed up youtuber video
I
Washed up I can't see my health
I just I just got I'm just a look at I'm the washed up gamer. I just got hit like three times in this room. I accept that terminology now
Can anything can I get another pill besides puberty will be fantastic
You forced start to make that no, I didn't
We had a conversation
About how funny it would be if in two months his in like next video is like another mod video
And then the ideas spiraled out and he started talking about like oh yeah, what if I I do this and then we could do that well not we him
Now you know a lot of you hear something you guys need to realize right a lot of the videos that star or I make I
Would say like half the time
So I gotta like focus here
Okay
Okay, that sucked um a lot of our videos or stem from us talking in a call
About just random dumb shit
And sometimes it's like I like it'd be really funny if you did that
And then one of us does it and we go oh wow that's funny
Let me think maybe some of you guys think it's funny too or maybe interesting or whatever
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, I don't want that
I do not want that at all. I don't even know how much health I have probably like none
I
Need hearts bad
I just like I honestly thought the brain was the ball
Really thought that was the brain was the tear
Going to blow this up because I want the hat bad bad give me give me
Okay, we need to be real careful here
Take it I'm not taking it all the lose
Destruction now I'm at the devil
Hey look butterbeen hung a sneeze
I don't want that we're just gonna blow that guy up
I honestly don't even know what this does
Does it what is this what does the tongue do
So
So I know I'm gonna walk out of this room and someone's gonna go you didn't kick up the cow tongue. What are you crazy?
Devil deal
Well, I mean it's better than what I had which was nothing
Please have this be a room with hearts in it
I think I'm willing to
Maybe no, what pill is that
I don't know I'm scared
Scared to go get that pill I don't know what it is and I might walk into the spikes because I'm an idiot
I
Was out of full helpful
Do you enjoy making skits over gaming videos yes
Yes
Really didn't want to do that, but I may not have been made into this room
Oh
What oh my goodness come on dude
No, um screw'd
Whatever cross your fingers
Oh
All right
I wish this would hit faster
Shit I'm in trouble I'm in trouble I'm in big trouble
I'm in big trouble
I did it
But I don't it's gonna be hard to do this
I myself two hearts
This might be a gg over here
Oh no, I didn't even realize she was here
Oh god
It's not doing enough damage I'm not doing enough damage
If you get to the cathedral and you're not like legit melting people it's gonna be tough
Not these guys again
Wow see a way to guys I'm done I'm dead
I don't know how I'm see what
Oh
Uh, I didn't have faith in that one
I don't like using that technique the ludu- ludu- we go wood ludu technique thing
You
Favorite TV shows I mean you could say breaking bad and that's everybody's favorite TV show
Uh
Now doctor stebral check it out with stebral
Yeah, it could be the best show ever
Never seen but we're getting boardies good too
It's hard to say what the like your favorite TV show is because oops
There's a lot of good shows right now
That are currently like around to that over the last five years or so last couple years
I hate TV and like breaking bad it's pretty good it's pretty good
The late night snack recommendations dr. Oakhurst pizza
Oh by the way can we just address this I've talked about it a bunch
I've talked about like doctor Oakhurst pizza being the best frozen pizza ever
How many of you guys have actually eaten it since I talked about it
There's has to be at least a couple of you had to have been like I'll try it
What'd you think?
Good
I want to know what other people have to say about it
Good yep, yes, no idea what it is
Never heard of it me it's really good
Oh
This is good
I need that charge to be faster
Dr. Oak
Am I gonna try to make it to the next tip of the hat's live yes
It was just not like possible this year unfortunately
I
Joe like it me and star the just moved
They were people working in my house
Like literally the night before
That tip of the hat started and even like the morning of tip of the hats
There was like
Shit I can't get that
They were people working in my
House
And like I came and late
To tip of the hats I missed like the first event that they did
I showed up at like two or three or something
But yeah, I definitely like wanted to go
There's just a bad time personally to be able to go
Well
Well, that just that just scared me that scared the shit out of me when he just did that
What
What I
What of one heart
Oh, that was the
The shuffle crap
The name of the pizza it's doctor oat curse
OETKER as I believe oat cur
You
Thank God I got that
Don't touch that yet
Give me that key and then I'm just there we go
You
Nothing close enough
Favorite water bottle brand uh
Whatever one is the cheapest at the supermarket
Fuck
I
Just got got just clipped on that wall that shouldn't have happened
I can't let this run go to shit. I have monstero
I'll be ashamed if I let this go to shit
Do not let this go to shit
Do I like dr pepper yes
Although I don't really drink it that often anymore
I just got the shot away from uh
From soda
Recently last couple of years years so
What does he do doesn't he do something specific if he gets hit or something
I don't know
Doesn't he do something specific if he gets hit or something
Oh
I mean soda can be good like I don't know I die
I used to drink a lot of soda
And I still do it occasionally I'm at like the restaurant or something I'll get like a coke
Out of the glass, you know you drink it out of the glass. It's just oh I'm drinking a coke out of the glass
Something about a coke out of the glass at a restaurant is just good
Yay
I
Shoot two different tiers each time the same as two of you
So if I have familiar as it'll do it
Hmm okay I'm here about the secret road
Hey, thank goodness and the devil room
Huh
Well, I could this could be real interesting
If I get baby brimstone
We could have a lot of uh
A lot of fun, but I would also be down to one heart
Is it worth is the words doing it
Yeah, I know I got to get the eternal heart to
Oh, I could I could do this, but I would have no heart
Oh
I'm gonna die
Okay, let's go for it
Let's do it
And how can he didn't do it? Why is he not doing it?
Did I just get fucking
What he's not doing anything
I
Just I
How come he's not shooting anything
Always doing flies but that's not I didn't want I wanted them to shoot out the
Second double brimstone
Where is it? It's down here
All right place your bets am I gonna get hit before I can uh use this in this room. I'm gonna hit five times
Oh
Oh he doesn't he doesn't copy brimstone
Okay
Well, you just instantly insta died
Figure what answers does
I
I feel like I shouldn't take that because doesn't that make everything a uh
The bad bloody chest
He's got to kind of get him in a way
Oh
He should tag of the flies
That doesn't do anything does it
Oh
Look at how long that is now
But does does that do me no does no synergy there I don't think
Damn it I thought that was gonna be synergizing
Is it more
Maybe it is
I
Can do the pa again if I really wanted to
How much of this game have I played like maybe 70 or 75 hours
The problem with Isaac though is if you don't I I'd never played
All my time in Isaac was when it first came out
So it's bit literally up until like a couple weeks ago or so was it's been like probably like a year since I played it
So I just forget everything that's in the game
And even still I was one of those wiki people I needed to use the wiki because I just didn't know every that I always forgot what stuff did
Come on that was blinking I did it
Oh
Not 4.50
Yeah, at least the flies will kill things while I'm charging that is correct
Most flies really are doing work
Oh
Just go oh no no no no way way
And shit to you
Getting all my hearts back that's a good thing
If I find the broken remote with the pa take it infinite teleports
Could go down and explore but whatever
Well you hit him oh my god thank you thank you thank you thank you thank you
Nothing in this room
Oh
How's auto doing fantastic he's right behind me
Sleeping being a good boy if you heard me say his name so he looked up over here
He's a good dog
He's my little buddy
This is really really good though
The only bad part about this is besides the flies it takes me forever to I it takes me forever to do a ton of damage
Gonna make sure I'm hitting things
This is pretty sweet
Oh
Oh boy
Would you look at that now we're talking
Shit's gonna uh
Shit's gonna really start to uh hit the fan if I get the familiar upgrade
I
Yeah
Oh
I did I really I just did that I actually just did that
I waited so long and everything
Even more health
But
Hmm
I could do the pa again and then take the book
I
What do you think guys
What do you think
Use the plug grab the book and get the cat
Oh
Get the cat you have nothing to lose I don't know if I want to get the cat
We're at least getting the book up a lot of
Because that's just it's just outrageous
Yeah
Yeah, I I hate that item
I really don't like the cat item
I'm gonna go on our merry way I'll just take the book
I still need to go into
I didn't miss the item rum
Yeah, I don't care we're just gonna go
Hey, guess what bet you I get hit by this shit again
Nope
Uh take the cat take the cat fine. I'll take the cat you want me to take the cat
took the cat
Now I now I got nine lives and it's gonna I'm gonna get too confident
And I'm gonna die nine times
Oh the cat gives you a heart
Whoops
What a washed out what a what a washed up video game player
I
Everyone's saying to go back to the putt I want it. I want the book of I want the book
Do you know how much damage I want to be doing
I don't care about it. It's a guppy
Say I want to be able to go like this
See now I go
I want a shit room
I want the shit room that was
If this was original Isaac yeah, I maybe I'm putting two together
You
Watch out everybody don't get blown up
Fill up your mouth let's go
Hmm
Rang up I'll take it
It's definitely to find some stuff
I don't know the chant like the chances of me getting more guppy. I mean what is the actual chances here
If it happens it happens, you know, but I don't know I never want to rely you can never read the lie on something dropping in this game
Because it's everything is just random
If I think just randomized it's a randomized dungeon
Oh god. Oh god damn it
Come on
I fucking hate these things
Especially when they're this close
spiderbox
Not that not as good as book of the lie
I could go in the coin shop today
I'm gonna scream I'm gonna just scream at the top of my lungs
Gonna fucking start screaming
You
Okay, so I have one heart right for two hearts
Shit
It's pretty handy
Now I get two hearts
I really have just been kind of skipping the secret rooms unfortunately
But we're just trying to go
You know we're just going
You're gonna give me another one of these you're gonna give me another one of these with an obstacle in the way I
Have to go around that
You know I have to I have to go around that how annoying
Well
Come on I might go it's good
I
Have to go back. Oh, I hate those rooms with a passion
Here we go, let's go again
Oh
Let's jump in all over the place if you stop moving do
Just have some hearts okay
Okay
What's your favorite flavor of ice cream pretty much just standard chocolate
If it's not standard chocolate then it's what I said earlier like the fudge brownie ice cream from Ben and Jerry's
This is crazy
Actually, I don't remember the name of it. It's like double fudge ultra fudge brownie guy mode. I don't know something
It's got a weird name all Ben and Jerry's ice cream has weird screwy Louis names
Like chip and Dale's rescue Ranger raspberry lime Ricky
Okay, could just call it raspberry ice cream
Where's the last one there you are
Fish food your fish food's good that's more than marshmallow, right?
The
Chocolate pieces
Half baked is good almost all of the Ben and Jerry's ice cream is good
All right
Is that do anything
How does that pulses it does it does that's neat
That's a real neat
Oh
Just hit that kind of thing
Trying just to make one of them hit them
you
no
oh
I got money to spend we're going in here. Can I see the chat? Of course I can. Of course I can see the chat.
Blackheart.
I'm getting so many HP ops. This game really wants me to stay alive with the current build that I have.
I'll just take that for this room and then I'm going to throw it away.
I'm going to throw it away.
Thank you for the numerous hilarious videos of Brighton in my life.
You're welcome, dude. Thanks for even carrying about them in the first place.
I should be thanking you.
Oh!
There it is. There's the item.
There it is.
That's what we like to call a good game.
Look at this troop I got now.
Nice. Oh wow, that's amazing.
Well, I'm going to just take this for fun.
Whatever.
All right, let's go ahead and win this one.
If you don't know what that does, that makes all of my familiars do more damage. They're just even better.
They grow stronger and they get probably more powerful. It's just, it's for what I'm doing right now, this is unbelievable.
I guess I could start hurting. No, I don't even.
Luck up. All right. Just I don't even care.
I could just like farm all this, but I have plenty of items.
I have plenty of bombs, plenty of keys.
I could get the blood bag or something, but you know, who really cares?
Do I have donations set up? No, I answered this before. I'll answer it again.
I'm not doing donations.
At least at least for the foreseeable future.
And that did a lot.
See you later, Mom.
Okay, did I win? I think I won.
Did I win?
Does I won? I did it.
I did it, guys.
I did it.
Yeah.
What the fuck?
I won the video game.
Look at me.
If I lose this game, I'm going to uninstall Isaac.
If I don't at least beat like mom's heart, something's wrong.
Now let's take the book.
Okay, I'm not going to take that. That's too much.
Look at a little cat.
All right. Oh, that was the end.
It's almost physically impossible for me not to at least get to Isaac.
Right?
If you don't understand what happened, if you pick up, it's three items in the guppy,
quote, guppy line, if you will, you turn into a guppy of the cat and you just
steamroll every single room.
Pretty much.
All right, let's go.
Let's see. Let's see what a guppy can do.
Let's move.
Whoops. Uninstall hype.
Uninstall hype, guys.
I just took that damage I should not have taken.
Uninstall hype.
Got these flies.
Oh, there's so many of them.
I think this is actually only the second time I've ever had guppy.
Come and get me.
Now we just pull out through the whole game.
I'm just going through every room out of the care.
We're not even like stopping. I'm only going to stop to charge before I go in a room.
Okay, no, hold on. We're going to stop here.
I'm just going to just range up.
Okay, the rest of those are paralysis.
You can fly over objects too.
What an unbeatable item.
I'll just take the case I need it for some reason.
Oh, thanks. Thanks for the heart.
Thanks for more free stuff.
Ha.
Turn on what is your real name?
It's uh, Arnold, Ellbertson.
Uninstall. Uninstall in the game.
Took another hit.
I should be taking zero hits.
I think I'm just getting overconfident.
Oh, overconfidence, man.
It's going to be the death of me.
At least I know those things will never touch me.
What boss isn't here that's going to insta die?
See you.
Another another devorow.
Oh my god.
Another one. Another one.
I'm not even going to be able to see.
There's so many people.
There's too many people on the screen.
My friends.
I mean, I didn't have to do that, but you kind of have to.
If you have this setup, don't you?
Why not? Take another one.
I'm not doing brimstone.
I already have this.
And I already have guppy.
So I'm not taking two full hearts for no reason.
I like the super spit.
I'm not taking this.
I can go like this and fly.
But there's no reason to have that.
I'm going to keep the book.
I'm not getting brimstone.
We want to have like a party.
Oh, the book of a lot of the book of bliles doing that.
Okay, let's go.
Oh, that's not brimstone.
Now, brimstone has the two lines in it, right?
Curse of darkness.
Oh, no.
Whatever will I do.
I can't see, but it doesn't matter.
It just doesn't matter.
I have a machine gun of flies.
Nothing can stop me.
Just going, y'all, give me that key.
The flies.
This is so awesome.
Remember I said what was the percentage of me actually getting guppy?
And I got it.
Is it the getter you don't, right?
It was hide over here too.
Is this such a joke?
Have I played the eternal mode?
Then Binding Visek 1?
No.
Did they, the original?
Didn't they add stuff to it or something?
Is that what they added?
And here we go.
Well, let's do it.
Hmm.
Melting.
Melded.
Jeez.
That is so awesome.
Although, hold on a second.
Did I not, I don't think I got the Polaroid.
Did I get the Polaroid in mom?
Did I just go try to be taken?
Or just be Isaac?
The Polaroid is for...
I don't even remember.
The eternal mode really isn't that fun, just some new boss effects that happen sometimes.
I did get it, yeah, I got it.
Let's go.
Let's go to the cathedral.
Okay.
Are we uninstalling the game?
I don't know, very soon.
You got it, Jeremy, where me?
Jeremy, where me?
Oh, it's that guy.
The reason why I got hit is I didn't realize it was one of those green guys.
I wouldn't have gotten hit if I didn't though.
It's weird to see the Polaroid unlock before the negative.
What is the criteria for unlocking the negative?
I don't think I have it.
Can you spend your 50 gerbobox on that question?
You sure can?
But that was your question.
So, there it is.
Tented rock.
I missed it, but I'll get it.
I'll go get it.
Can't give up a tinted rocket.
This is a good one.
This point in the game.
Satan five times.
I've beaten megastatin, I think two or three times.
Have I just not even...
You know what? I might have just kept going to the cathedral.
I'm pretty sure that's what's going on.
I don't like go fight Satan ever.
I always go to fight Isaac.
Whenever I get there, I don't know how many times it's been.
I hate these chump characters.
Okay.
Let's do it.
I'm gonna stall the game.
There are a good idea.
I don't have to uninstall the game.
I do not have to uninstall the biting of Isaac.
Oh my god.
Toad.
There's too many people.
This is...
I've never seen this many familiar.
I'm...
This is gonna confuse me now.
Try to just get the orbit thing too.
Try to just get orbit.
Do cares, right?
Don't pick up that.
Do not pick up that.
Okay, fine.
We'll just...
We'll just lose here.
I honestly might lose to...
Is it Blue Baby?
I don't... I don't like him remember what he does.
I might just lose here.
I'm not gonna lie.
That technology baby is kind of freaking me out.
Like I keep seeing it and I keep thinking it's an enemy of some sort.
Can I hurt this fucking dude?
What the fuck?
Get the contact.
Oh, you asshole.
Even more flies.
Get in my fly, brethren.
I hope this is the right way.
What the fuck?
Oh, come on.
You didn't just really do that to me, baby.
Oh fuck.
What the hell?
Uh-oh.
The baby is ended up screwing me over there, guys.
Don't, don't, don't, don't do that.
Oh my fucking god.
Come on.
Slow down.
Slow the fuck down.
Why am I getting hit by these?
Holy shit.
Slow down.
I was moving too fast.
I was just going too fast and I forgot that I had to slow down right there.
No, I think that's probably the right way.
Not like this.
I've been on that room.
Hey, by the way, what the fuck dude?
Why? What the fuck?
I went in the room.
I opened the door and died.
It was like, legit.
I, you guys saw, I didn't even move.
I didn't go anywhere.
Come here, break.
Am I just like getting blocked out from all my dudes?
I'm fucking terrified to walk right here.
It wasn't this way.
Shit.
I gotta go back through that stupid ass rum.
Oh my god.
I keep god of kidding me.
This is the rum that's going to end this whole thing.
This dumbass fucking room that I'm hitting the hitboxes on these things.
Go in, please.
Probably down on it soon.
Okay, then.
I don't know.
I really use the spirit heart right now.
Shit.
I forgot what these guys do.
Oh, damn it.
They spawn those things.
Oh, hey, by the way, uninstall hype was for Isaac.
Was for killing Isaac.
Not this.
This is nothing to do with uninstall hype.
Fuck.
This is why we game over.
This room is so hard with one heart.
No, time to uninstall the game.
No.
Ugh.
There's so many directions where you could die.
One heart.
I could have just bombed the door.
Hey, well, it was beating the...
It was getting to Isaac.
It beating Isaac.
I even said I don't think I was going to be able to beat this with like two hearts.
All I needed to prove was beating Isaac.
I should have used the fucking orb, but that was the problem.
Oh, you can't even bomb through rooms in the chest.
Honestly, let's be like real here.
Trying to beat the chest with one or two hearts is pretty much impossible as it is.
What really screwed me was the fucking stupid ass hitboxes on the red poo.
Like, what the fuck was that?
Like, I would walk in the door like this and die without even touching my controller.
I would just walk in and insta-die.
It happened like three times, at least.
That was really, really, really annoying.
Red poo pit boxes are extremely lame, especially when there's three of them in the only area you can move as your character.
I lost like three hearts there.
Like, it's legit. Let's be totally real here.
I went like this and died.
I didn't even move in.
I don't touch in anything.
Just, ugh!
That was what happened.
And that brought me down to one, which if I even had more than one hit I could take, that would be great.
That would have been fine.
Damn it.
I wanted to beat Isaac.
I was just chilling.
That wasn't a- that was a very, very incredible build, but I will say it.
I will say it. I said it before, I'll say it again.
Going into the chest with less than like two or three hearts, you're pre-
It's- it's- you have a huge, huge, huge percentage that you're just going to lose.
Especially those- those rooms with like two or three of those big horrible bosses.
They're very, very hard.
Especially those two. It had to be that fucking guy who spawns the turkeys that shoot in fucking four directions.
I didn't forget about it in third year.
I'm taking broom baby.
I'm not even- this is not even a real run. This is a fake run.
I'm just venting my frustrations about the red poo hit boxes.
If we all saw- we all saw it.
I don't have to pretend like something happened. We all saw what happened.
I'm going to call the gamer police on- on those guys.
I'm going to- I'm going to call Ed.
He can be like, Ed, just go on out those hit boxes man.
I'm upset about it. He's going to go, okay.
And then we're going to the hit. I'm going to hit. We're going to hang up.
This is not even- this is a fake run.
This is- I'm pissed off run. I'm very upset right now. I couldn't be more angry.
I just haven't really been streaming for the second time for four hours.
Really?
This is a fake run.
Don't wish little, but you know I can't wish little. You're going to mock me like that.
He's only doing that because he knows I can't do it.
I haven't even fucking real.
The term is very irritated right now.
I'm going to uninstall Isaac, but I never said I couldn't reinstall it immediately after.
I can uninstall Isaac and then immediately reinstall it.
I can take the game or license test again.
So what? So I failed- oh yeah, you failed your driver's ed test.
You can go- you try it again in like another six months.
You can pass it. I can get my game or license back.
I'm just going to take the test again.
Fair enough.
There's a great response. Fair enough.
I'm sorry.
Fuck.
So much stuff.
So much shit just fucked out of it.
I knew that was going to happen.
I did that on purpose. You guys were going to go, oh you should have done me.
I can kill you.
I did- there was a joke.
Hold on a second.
I'm going to get my game or license back.
I'm going to go take my game or test again.
Hold on a second. I'm going to take my game or license test.
I can't believe you just unlocked the scissors.
Why did I not have the scissors?
I have like 75 hours in this game.
How do I not have the scissors?
That's frickin- I don't know how that's possible.
That was a fake run, guys.
There's no real run.
I need to do something to get my game or license back.
Let's see. What can I do?
I can go to prove to you guys that I can get my game or license back.
After just getting it revoked.
I just crashed into a mailbox and they took away my license.
You alright, if I?
Your license has been revoked.
I just tried to parallel park and I drove over the curb four times.
I tried to play it off like it didn't happen.
The guy doing that was doing my driver's ed test.
He kept on going, okay, just squicked it out.
You know what exactly what he's thinking.
This dude failed the test.
You know, like, you go over the curb and he's just like, it's okay.
Just took straight knit out, please.
And the whole time he's sitting there going, I failed.
I failed it.
And then you really get an all worked up about it.
So you straighten out and you back over the curb again.
And then he hits the brake that he has on his car.
You know, like I can put the brake on whenever I want on his passenger side.
And he makes you get out of the car and then he does it for you.
And then he's like, okay, that was all right.
Up until that point.
Yeah.
All right.
Let me see.
Give me a second, guys.
I think I know just the way to get my gamer license back.
There's just a second here.
Just one second here.
Submit a urine sample to Janet.
Yeah, I'm going to piss in a jar.
And you guys could test it, Steve.
Does that get a gaming plasma in it?
I think you guys are going to hear this.
And you're going to know how we're going to get our gamer license back.
That's right.
Super 8 Boy.
Let's go.
All I gotta do to get my gamer license back all I gotta do I
Just got a beat the first level of meat boy
In ten seconds