But one last stop-long in the mark, Flats.
Alicia will meet you there.
Get moving. Beat the ratmen to it.
Ha-ha!
We're already in a game, I guess.
We're blessed.
Help!
Where are we?
Up here!
Whereup that way?
My ladies and gentlemen, welcome.
Just a moment.
To the New Year's Eve, Caltown Street!
Damn, they're definitely in this area.
Whoa, it was the drag.
It's got thrown into this game.
I don't even know what's happening.
All I know is I just got tossed in here.
I went to matchmaking and all of a sudden in somebody's game.
They're everywhere.
I'm going to go to the New Year's Eve.
Yeah, I would have done like a more proper intro, but...
It's got sucked in here.
Hi! Hi guys! Hello!
Welcome to my New Year's Eve, Caltown Street!
I wanted to do this, so that'll be fun to, like, Caltown the New Year.
At least East Coast.
Gatlin' Gunnar.
It's up here.
We're for East Coast.
This is Burmentide.
Burmentide.
Gunnar played it before.
It's kind of like Leffordead.
Holy shit.
No!
All right, if you ever played Leffordead,
it's Leffordead with rats.
That's pretty much all you need to know.
Happy New Year to those of you that have had the New Year go by already.
Well, also, the East Coast still has quite a little bit of ways.
Like an hour or so till we can count accounts.
This game has pleasantly surprised me though.
I held off installing this game for, like, at least a month or two.
All right, yeah, get the star sub-sound out of your system.
Yeah, we all heard it.
It was really funny.
Star makes the funniest jokes, right?
And by funniest jokes, I mean, he just, like, insults me.
And that's it.
Good joke.
Good joke, Star.
Really good punchline.
I'm okay on health.
Let's double check the market.
And nobody wants to mention the fact that he didn't stream for a month.
No, no, it's all, it's all got to be about how Jerma sucks, right?
Oh shit.
He's a fucking joke, Star.
I'll tell you that.
I don't even want to play this character.
I don't play the dwarf guy.
This is somebody healing.
I've never seen this in a healer.
It's not easy.
I thought it was only normal or hard.
I don't know.
This is just going to stream vermitide for a while.
I think.
Oh dear.
Hey, what left for dead bodies this?
Alright, get it out of your system.
Go ahead, get it out of your system.
Let's hear it.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
I knew I was just freaking out right there.
Oh, jeez!
Where the fuck did he come from?
What the fuck?
Oh my god.
I'm just stuck up here.
I don't want to jump out there.
Bye bye.
Holy shit, I'm still alive.
Geez.
Oh, what the fuck an assassin rat?
No, I don't want to do that.
We gotta hit this big motherfucker out of here.
Yeah.
I like this arrow because it bounces around everybody.
Can I hit him right in his face?
Whoa.
We have a decade of uninterrupted practice.
No, not even there.
You know, I could address.
I want to.
I've been very silent about it.
I've been very quiet about it.
Because I have to be.
Everybody wants to talk about Derma wrestling.
And God, guys, me too.
I really do.
But I can't.
I just can't.
Jess, Jess, be patient.
That's all I can say is it's not going to happen in 2015.
You just got to be patient.
You got to trust me on this one.
Yeah, you got to trust me.
Be patient.
And your patients will pay off.
I hope.
Maybe.
Do we have any like tubes, really?
This is called vermin tide.
That is correct.
I need a movement.
Mike, I'm not liking it.
Oh, somebody got a loop.
Sorry.
This is going to make a little bit of noise.
Hopefully it's not too loud when I move this around.
I'll put on a jump.
I'll put on a jump on.
Look at the spate of the.
Only grimness all right.
The scale can turn this time.
This isn't going well.
But this is I like this game a lot.
This this game sort of flew a little bit under the radar.
It wasn't one of those games that a bunch of people were talking about.
I think people were talking about it.
But it's just fun to play.
Fine shot.
How did I know it hit him?
It's good just to walk around and slash a bunch of rats, you know?
Are we going to move?
I would say if you really want to know when when Jerma rumble four is coming out.
The only thing I can tell you is probably spring 2016.
Very very I don't know but like it'll it'll trust me when I say that it'll hopefully it's worth it.
I hope it's fucking worth it.
It is a Warhammer game.
It is the war who are end times.
What let him know what level of my we are right now.
I've only not completed one.
I didn't beat the last campaign yet.
Oh shit that's not good.
Where they coming from?
Ooh that was a double.
I'm not very go with this character because it's not going to hit headshots with the bow.
This is very quick.
But this is actually balanced around arrow.
I really like.
I'll show you guys my items when I get a second after the start.
When I get a moment or two.
What characters are there in this game?
There's five classes.
There are five.
What the.
Flying fuck.
These.
Why was he shooting me?
Get away.
I am in deep shit.
I gotta stay back.
I'm going to stay away back.
Another Gatlin gunner rat?
You serious?
He's still alive?
Oh my god.
Oh god this is not good.
This is not good.
The gas rat is just fucking this all up.
No why is the gunner going that way?
Go that way.
Thank god.
If I could touch three in a second I'm dead.
Oh boy.
Oh god.
I think this might be done deal.
Maybe not.
Oh I'm alive.
I actually haven't played TF2.
I haven't played the tough break.
Campaign stuff.
It's been fun.
I don't know if I'll stream that tonight but.
In all seriousness is this game is supposed to be this similar to Left 4 Dead?
Ah yes.
I would say that this is as close to Left 4 Dead 3 as you could possibly get without it being Left 4 Dead 3.
Like take Left 4 Dead and rewind it into Medieval times with some magic shit.
It is Left 4 Dead.
But it has an item system which you like kind of craft items you roll for items and it is.
We'll see.
Is it bravery or stupidity that pushes you or does it?
I really could use that.
And so could you but I grabbed it first so I'm drinking it.
Uh oh.
It's getting grabbed by a stick rat.
I don't close me out of here.
What the hell?
How much is it cost?
I think it is currently on sale for 15% off.
I think it's $25 or whatever your.
Whatever $25 is for you or whatever it is.
I wish I was the voice for the rats in this game though.
It would be awesome.
I would love to be the rats.
Uh, is there any, yeah.
Give that to the cast or yeah.
You drink that.
Mm, yummy, yummy.
What time is it?
It is like 11.30?
11.40?
We're gonna count down the new year guys.
We're gonna count down the new year.
We're gonna do a big count.
I'm gonna put a big countdown on screen and shit.
It's gonna be awesome.
I got a party hat specifically to do it.
I got one of those like.
Those things you blow into.
A whistle, a horn.
A horn whistle.
It's safe to say this game is fun.
Yes, if you like the left for dead formula,
there is no reason why you would not like this game.
If you get a couple of your buddies and you jump in and you play and you guys all enjoy the left for dead formula,
there's almost no differences.
Besides the fact that it is melee,
predominantly a melee only game with side arms and bows.
Medical supplies.
What are you living in a barn?
I think we might defend this room for a minute.
Are we just gonna defend this area?
I must heal!
Jeremiah bought your glue man shirt.
Do you love me yet?
Of course I do.
Come on.
You even have to ask that question?
This is a very tense music for nothing really happening.
Watch out, watch out for the one rat.
What the hell are they?
What is going on here?
Are they all coming in this door?
I guess so.
I guess they're coming in the front door.
What about you idiots?
You could have flanked us.
You could have hit us.
Auto update.
I have an auto update.
Those are the ones that have been following my Twitter.
These last week there's two.
Counterins are like a little bit of nightmare situation with my dog,
for those of you that don't know.
Oh man, I PWM some rats.
He has Addison's disease.
Just got diagnosed like this past week.
I was in the vet for pretty much every single day straight last week.
He was getting blood work done, he was getting test done,
and all kinds of awful shit.
And it turns out he needs to go on Fredna's own steroids for the rest of his life.
And I have to give him a little squeeze out of this little syringe thing
into his mouth every day.
And I have to do that for the rest of his whole life.
But the upside is he is perfectly fine.
He has done a complete 180 from being all sorts of fucked up to be in the dog.
I know I'm a dog.
He is just auto.
He's back to normal.
Completely like almost 100% back to normal after doing the treatment.
So that's that.
That's a thing.
He's okay.
If I could show him on camera here in a minute, I really want to.
Yeah, when we do the big countdown, I'll show auto on screen.
Oh dear, that's a big donor guy.
I like and don't like this character.
Don't get split up.
Yeah, the doctor actually told me that with Addison's disease for dogs.
If you have a dog that is in very high stress environment, he can get all messed up.
Like if he had fun, he'd like thunderstorms dogs, they'd like run under the bed during a thunderstorm.
If he is that type of dog, apparently he can have all kinds of problems because he can't produce cortisol.
So the doctor's like, make sure you don't put him in any stressful situations and put a fucking kill.
Well, he didn't say that, but you know, that's what I took from it.
And there's a tank following us.
This is not a good opportunity to get a tank.
Where is he?
He appeared in my face last time.
Hopefully it does not do it again.
Oh, where is he?
I don't know.
I'm gonna pick up this egg sack.
Protect me.
Come on.
I need some protection here.
I'm picking up the fucking egg sacks.
Here we go.
Keep going.
Let them just deal with the tank.
I got to protect you.
You're gonna.
I have this.
I'm gonna drop one and you drop one.
Oh boy.
Don't look back.
He's not behind us.
I promise.
I can't do it a hell of a job.
He's still alive.
I'm gonna heal this guy too.
Once we get done with this other one.
I'm gonna get him.
Come over here.
Hey, you ready?
Come here.
Can I get it?
Oh, that was...
I guess that was not the guy I wanted to be.
I thought that was me.
No, it wasn't.
It was on her shit.
That's what I look at me.
No.
Where's the pack?
Where's the pack, Rhett?
I got you.
Oh, you're in such a bad spot, dude.
We're gonna have to get you later.
Can I get him?
Wait, what?
Oh, God.
Don't.
Those bad news.
This is really bad news.
Yeah.
You bring him back to life.
Holy shit.
That guy caught me out of mid-air.
He got me in mid-fucking air.
Have I had me docked to Oakers lately?
I have it all the time.
That rat is freaking out now, boy.
At least we killed the tank, right?
Did we kill the tank?
There's still an assassin rat.
There he is.
Shit.
Don't let him wrap around us.
Stay together.
Those winds won't close by themselves.
That guy's got a healing drone.
He's just drinking.
Drink that shit, dude.
Drink that shit.
There's only two more sacks.
You gotta go two by two.
You know what?
We should just do four by four then.
I'm not going over there by myself.
That's a fucking terrible idea.
Don't go over there by yourself.
Don't go by yourself.
Oh boy.
Well, I have to come with you now.
Oh, God.
Dude, I'm just distracting these dudes.
Hopefully you pick up that cereal bag and get it in here.
We're just kind of getting thrown into this game, like halfway through it.
Oh, never mind.
I spoke too soon.
There is no friendly fire.
Friendly fire does not exist in this game.
Which is good because that would kind of be outrageous.
It'd be hard to, uh,
because everyone's like throwing their hands around spamming.
Let's get out of here.
Dermot or anyone in jail running out of nicknames, Hokie Monk.
Any ideas?
Ultradon.
That's a pretty good name.
I'm thinking Ultradon or...
Dread...
Jim...
Ernest.
We got a couple of bonus die.
Alright, so to explain this in as tiny of a way as I possibly can.
You get dice.
All you have to do is you have to roll one face.
This doesn't have a symbols matter.
You just have to roll a face up.
So the amount of face upside roll, I get either a common or an uncommon.
I did it for me, but okay, here we go.
So that's 1, 2, 3, 4.
I got a green bow.
And...
Actually, I'm kind of curious what this is.
Black Mellow Bow Longbow.
And the upgrade is increased zoom distance.
Ha ha!
Give me a second.
I need to see...
Where...
Guys, we are...
Just about 20 minutes away from New Year's Day.
The big New Year 2016, going to count it down.
Just about 20 minutes away.
For the big countdown.
Alright, let's see.
Ah, wow, yeah.
So there are...
Exactly the same.
I think this bow does not have the homing trail.
So the only difference is this is just a longbow.
They are identical in stats.
This one has homing.
This one does not, but it has hires that I can like see, like, a zoom distance.
Let's just look at it.
Yeah, there we go.
So it just zooms in farther.
I'm not even upgraded.
I can upgrade and get even further.
I...
You kind of can get screwed sometimes when the homing arrow wants to just go wherever it wants.
It's still fun to...
How many bolts?
Arrows.
This has more arrows too.
This has 40 plus arrows.
That alone has 29, I think, right?
Let's see.
I think so.
29, so yeah, I lose like 20, just about like 15 hours or 18 hours or something, but...
Oh, something about the homing is cool.
I could salvage some shit.
Hmm.
I don't like this.
We're gonna get rid of it.
And we're gonna get rid of this.
28...
Yeah, I can make another...
Common, but I don't think I want to.
Have I decided on my game of the year 2015?
Of course I have Bloodborne.
Of course I have Bloodborne for sure.
Although, I don't know.
It's a toss-up.
I might need to like hold my own award ceremony to figure that out.
Let's see.
Let's see what the academy thinks.
Maybe I should just craft something.
I don't want this.
I'm gonna craft.
Fucking craft it.
Now I'm gonna use the gems to make...
What do I want to make?
What character do I want?
I want to make something for.
Let's go with...
I like the dwarf.
Ah.
I was gonna have to go with it.
Whatever.
Let's see.
All right.
What am I gonna get?
Sword in the shield.
Or Axon shield.
I played the dwarf.
Who is Rock?
Got it.
So I currently have a blue.
I did this.
Which is pretty good.
This is what I just got.
Sometimes it's fun to be shielded, guy.
What's the upgrade on it?
When hitting a man-sized enemy with a normal attack, there is a 5-15% chance to instantly kill it.
What does that mean?
Oh, thanks to all the subscribers, by the way, all the old and new ones.
I haven't streamed in a while, so thanks.
So a normal man-sized enemy is everybody a man-sized enemy compared to me.
I kinda like it.
I'll just, I'll try it.
I'm gonna upgrade it there.
I got the absolute worst I could.
I got the absolute bottom.
That could have been 5-15.
And I got 5.
By the way, if you're wondering what like that noise in the background is, that's my heater in this room.
Oh, it's talking about the special rats, like the bigger ones.
Oh, that's kind of cool.
Which is what it wasn't.
5% kind of sucks.
Are we doing another mission with these same dudes?
What's going on? Let's do it.
Oh, wait, no, this buddy.
That's fine.
It's my trusty shotgun.
Even though it just sucks, it's a regular shitty shotgun.
I wanna get a legendary orange item in the game.
Oh, cool.
Is it...
Those are players last year played this game.
Is has anybody has...
A...
Orange item.
And if you do...
Is there any real big difference between the orange and non-Orange?
Not like having this shield though. You feel more involved when you're using a shield like this.
A...
So here's my axe. This is the blue axe I have. It's a two-hander and it's big and it's a big swing.
Giant rats.
The orange items are a lot better. I just... I want to see one.
I want to hold one. I just want to hold it.
I just want to hold it.
I just want to hold the damper.
Here we go.
I am...
Am I ready? All right. What do you guys think?
Big blue two-hander or...
Sword and Shield Protect teammates guy.
I don't like this.
That means this is how many people you can hit with a swing.
That needs to be...
That's so much bigger. What is this? Is this a one-hander?
One-hander?
I don't know. I guess I'll use the shield.
Five-four-three-two-one.
Zero.
Prepare your shield.
They've agreed to bring supplies in through the sewers on the condition that I provide a way in.
Yes, there's more scabin' of mouth.
You cannot change your weapon mid-mission. No.
I can't change that.
You cannot change your class or your weapon.
The only time you can change is right at the very beginning.
There is an inventory.
Legitimately right when we start the game right here.
But other than that, nope.
See right here?
Hmm, I can change my stuff.
But I'll stay with this.
These will do a humus good.
I shouldn't have picked the shotgun.
It's two close quarters.
I'm coming.
Kind of just have to get in everybody's way.
This character.
The shield, don'ts.
That one felt good.
That had a lot of weight behind it.
Oh, that's an assassin rat.
He's still coming in.
He got a time these stuns.
He's not dead.
I would be careful.
The garros.
Damn it.
He's still alive.
And now we're getting a horde.
Bumps any more than one.
Don't split up.
Cut up in this maze of a sewer we have here.
That's a patrol of armored enemies.
I don't want to see that at all.
There's a lot of healing in here.
You want the fuckers?
Someone's blood on my screen.
I can't see it.
It's like water.
Oh, fuckers.
Oh, god.
What a perfectly timed bomb that was.
Good work, dude.
I got saved by ass.
They could break through my shield.
Let's go.
The vermin talk.
Oh, fuck.
Am I too little to jump this?
My little body can't jump over that.
I can't see it.
That's so far so good.
There's the thing to spin the thing.
Open the floor, Jets.
He said it.
There comes the race.
I can't see it.
Just a pile of rats.
I didn't get the shield up.
I can't see it.
The FOB is a little strange in this game.
At 90 it feels kind of odd.
I have it set to 85 right now just because I get a ton of
I can't see it.
Somebody kill him.
I think he's still alive.
I don't know.
Especially when you're turning corners.
I'll keep it at 90.
I don't know what it is about this game's 90 FOB.
Oh my god.
I know I have to heal.
Somebody hits.
You're just weird.
I already know that.
I can't see it.
Guys, we are less than 10 minutes away.
We are less than 10 minutes away from the new year countdown.
I can't see it.
He ran that way down the hall.
Damn it.
You're a driven man, Salt's Pire.
See that you don't interfere.
Oh shit.
I can't see it.
I already killed this guy.
Nope.
The assassin was still alive, wasn't he?
I already have a potion.
I just started using them more often.
I just don't.
Oh, free stuff.
I can't see it.
Let's do it.
Open the second floodgate.
Get off me.
What's going on?
I'm not the gate, man.
You got a gate to open.
Oh, there we go.
There's teammate number one.
Let's open it.
Pull it.
Get it open.
It's like that music starts to play.
They go.
They start landing.
You guys.
It's shit.
Not that much further.
It's dropping grenades everywhere.
Let's get the hell out of here.
I'm going to go behind myself.
Don't get jumped on.
That was a blind.
That went away.
Nothing no mood for this shit.
Luke died.
I mean to get the roll into the die.
No, one person can only have one last per game.
So they cannot be two dwarves.
I'd like to keep.
Let's get out of here.
Let's go.
Let's get in the bus.
All right.
Let's move.
That was a good run.
We are victorious.
I like that.
I want to get that roll.
The one thing I don't like about playing a shield character
is you don't do a whole lot of damage.
So you don't really get on the list anywhere.
All right.
I'm going to leave this game.
Because we got a countdown to do.
That is gentlemen.
We're putting up the countdown.
Give me back to the end.
We're going to be watching that clock like a hawk.
We're down to the last two minutes.
All right.
Let me go get my stuff.
I got to get home on the second.
I got to get the camera wrong.
Make sure we get to get ready.
I got to go get my stuff.
Countdowns in one minute.
I'm going to get the stuff.
Eight, seven, six, five, four, three, two.
Shh!
I got my fucking new year robe for nothing.
I bought this fucking bathroom. It's a special new year bathroom.
Happy New Year everybody. Happy New Year.
Hope 2016 is a good one. Let's play more vermin time. Have I just been at this
loading screen the entire time? Why have I not loaded into the in? What is going on here?
What time is it? Come on. Bloodborne thanks for stopping. Hey, the 2016. Let's hope
it's a good one. Right everybody? Cheers. Let me turn off this heater. It's starting
to like, swelter in here. All right, let me figure out. I think I'm fucking baby toy.
Shut up. Shut up. You fucking baby cell phone. Now, okay, what's going on? I can have to
like, and this process or something. Where's going on? My whole game is crashed. Holy crap.
Okay. Well, let me just a second here. Does this reload the game? Whatever. I can reload it.
It's fine. Why do you have bad reads in a baby toy? Because I have nieces and nephews
that come over here and need something to play with.
Happy New Year. Much love. Oh, wait, forgot. We forgot about the very important dog camp.
I'll show you guys how to. He's over here. He's over here. We're going to freak show. Hold on.
Hey, there's a dog. See, he's doing just fine. Hi, Otto. Otto. He's kind of sleeping over there.
You kind of freaked out when I jumped up there. He's lying on his little bed. He's new. Yeah, bad.
Eminem's beach party. You're right. What the fuck are you talking about? I don't want to play as
I guess they'll play dwarf, but I think I want to be dwarf big axe man.
I don't have enough to do that. Well, shit. I'm going to be this guy. I like this guy.
He's fun. He's a big two-hander man. The gun I have for him is a very powerful single shot rifle.
That takes a while to reload. This is a very strong pushes armor pen and it's very,
very strong. The normal attacks do a lot of damage and hits a shit load of people when you charge it up.
So let's play, right? Let's play to change my stream title. It's got to say 2016. Gonna be a good one.
2016, come off. We can't wait. It's gonna be such a good one. New Year's resolution.
There we go. 2016. Gonna be a good one. There we are.
What mission do I want to do? I don't know. About...
I'll try one on hard. Actually, I haven't even beaten it. I don't have one mission I haven't done.
I don't know if I want to do that right now.
Smugglers run the enemy below waterfront.
The vengeance of war will try it on hard. I'm gonna get my ass kicked, put, you know, whatever, right?
It's fine to game. So take that as a no. We can't join you. I mean, if you just, just queue up,
queue up for engines of war on hard. It does not very many people play in the game right now.
You know what I mean? Like, just if you're in the game right now, just queue up for that on hard.
And if you're in the United States, I'm sure I'll meet up with you.
Thanks for the sub shout out. Oh, Mr. Twig, man. Welcome to the new year. Welcome to the 2016 year.
I'll only reset if you finish your bio. I'm never finishing my bio.
It's never gonna happen. I don't want anyone to know who I was. I want it to come with a channel and just be like,
you fuck is this guy? I'm gonna bring this bio and be like, fine, bye. It doesn't have a shit here.
I can't even play M&Ms Beach party, guys.
You want me to play M&Ms? You want me to play a game for the original Nintendo Wii?
How am I supposed to hook that? I can't hook that shit up. I don't have that in here.
I think I like broke that disk in half, by the way. I don't know where it is.
Just give me somewhere to donate to you. Now unnecessary.
Your subscription, or you already subscribed. That's...
That's good enough for me. More than enough for me. So thank you.
Don't worry about it. Are you watching the stream? Is this guy watching the stream? I wonder.
Do you're watching the stream? Turn and nod.
That wasn't a nod.
I'm on to you.
I'm on to you, you little snake.
Yeah, you're gonna watch the stream. You think you can play this game and watch the stream? Don't you block it me?
All right, first person to fall off wins. I fucking won.
Look at how hard that word.
Fuck it hurt. Imagine how much this would hurt. Just like...
Hey calm down.
I said calm down.
Let's do it.
Turn me, you dummy. What? Why am I dummy? What does that do to deserve that?
There's no way I can do it.
There's not hard. This is gonna be hard.
I want to give more money to you. Is it really so hard? I just want you to have my dollars.
It's weird. I'm gonna weird spot.
I don't know. I don't know. You guys know how I feel about that.
I just like to make videos in play games and stream sometimes.
I make videos and hang out. I don't like... I just don't care.
I don't want this stream or my YouTube channel to be about how much money I can make.
It's never really been about that.
I know some people will say like, what the fuck are you talking about? What are you stupid?
Yeah. That pretty fucking stupid.
There's nothing to do with it. How dare you.
Hey everyone talking shit about me streaming?
I've streamed every single day in 2016 so far.
What's that? Every single second of 2016.
How many streamers do you know that can say that they've streamed every single second of 2016?
That's tough to... I don't know. That's tough to come by, man.
Well optimistic pick. Thanks for sticking around and hanging out and watching.
I like that guys, boys.
Why? Untamed.
The acting in this game is actually really good.
They say a lot of interesting things and they're very good.
I don't know.
The acting in this game is actually really good.
They say a lot of interesting things and they're very good at it.
Oh, you guys are only dead?
Why is that like...
Left for dead rats edition.
I'm just sniping.
I like just sitting back and shooting. It's fun.
Ooh, that was a headshot. I got that, dude. That was an armored guy too.
I'm proud of that one.
I'm very proud of that one.
That's so satisfying. When you get the big club in the head and they explode their heads, it's great.
Like that.
Oh, whoa, whoa, easy.
I've not tried the Steadfin trailer.
I don't know if I'd even like to either.
I don't really have the necessary reason why I want to use it.
Where are we? We're getting kind of split up here.
Rattling gun, shit.
That was lucky.
No, he's dead. I got him.
This is actually 90 FOV believer or not. Somebody asked if it was 120.
It feels like it is, but it's not. That's why I made it 85.
Advanced trackpad. Yeah, it's an interesting idea.
But I just don't when I play a game, right?
If I have a controller or if I'm using keyboard mouse, I don't really necessarily care or need and in between.
I don't mind using a controller. I don't mind using a keyboard mouse.
I don't know. I feel like it's kind of an in between with the steam controller.
I'm sure it's cool, but I just don't have the necessary reason to use it.
That's why I'm here.
Now, the interesting thing about this game is there's these things called tones and remores.
Remores, everyone say, where they give you bonus opportunity to get here with more dice that have higher chance to roll face up.
But if you pick up a grimoire, grimoire, I know. I just, I have to say it like that and I'm going to die.
It lowers your health by a pretty large margin and it's two in each level.
So if you really want to try super duper hard, you pick up both the grims and you end up with like 30% HP.
And it is hard.
Oh, oh, oh, wow, wow.
Stay down.
Grimoire, grimoire, grimoire, grimoire.
I always have to assassin that I hear it is. It is. I thought the dwarf was an assassin.
I feel like I'm missing somebody. One thing I wish you could turn on in this game.
Atalus mentioned this as well when we were playing before.
I wish I could turn on faint kind of permanent outlines because sometimes it is hard to turn like for instance the dwarf.
A lot of times I just turn around and think the dwarf is a rat because he's like the same size and has the same body shape.
Oh, yeah.
That's what I'm talking about.
Oh, you feel it.
You can turn on from an outline. Where is it?
I didn't see it in the options menu.
There isn't always outline button.
Hold on a second.
Come on, I want to investigate this.
Most sensitivity weapon switch.
Dodge jump, dodge on diagonal, double tap dodge, disable, and then the next up will engage the tutorial.
Player outlines on.
It's on.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, oh, oh.
Did you look at that?
I thought it was either on or off.
I didn't know there was another one.
I don't know, but that's a little, that's a little too much though.
Let me try it for a little bit.
I wish it could, okay, is somebody else correct me?
Can I make that even fainter?
Or probably not?
That is much, much better.
But I wish it was a little lighter.
Yeah, I mean, I saw, I looked at it, it said on.
I was like, oh, on and I figured on or off.
I didn't know there was also like super on.
Yeah, we have on off or super on.
Whoa, you guys can't ignore.
Yeah.
We're in a bad position here.
I don't know if I said very much though.
That's a tank and look at our health.
This is not gonna be good.
Wow.
God, you guys just come in and know where.
You lost that team.
Oh, the knife is spying.
Yeah, this game is not, this game is not easy.
Hard is actually hard and then there are two other difficulties harder than this.
There is nightmare and cataclysm.
I don't even want to know what this game is like on cataclysm.
And if you do the glimmer wars, I don't even know how difficult that game is gonna be.
There we go.
I missed that really.
How is that possible?
I've learned when to speak.
Make sure we're gonna get wrapped around.
How are we doing?
Sassin.
Very nice.
That was a good shot with the shotgun from up here.
You get a plus one.
Super skill.
Oh, the other.
Cheers.
Oh, the hands of the next.
Yeah.
Holy charred.
Get some barrels.
We're just gonna go as a team or we're gonna wait and get all a couple of them.
Is it okay if I drop some pickup lines in here so I can get it.
You can do it every one, man.
Get out of here.
I love that sometimes they just run around looking at you like, who do I hit?
I don't know who it is.
Where's the last one go over there somewhere?
Let's carry it.
Let's go, man.
Watch out.
Hey, stop procrastinating.
Guy that just asked about procrastinating, stop doing that.
Don't procrastinate anymore.
Do it today.
Do it right now.
Close the stream and hold on.
I don't want to shoot the barrel.
They can shoot the barrels.
You can't shoot everything up.
Push him.
Get the fuck out of here.
And three.
Woo.
I've got it done last year.
He waited a year.
I love that big swing.
It's great.
It feels so fun to hit people with it.
I'm not doing anything stupid.
I was trying to do something fucking silly.
Never do anything silly when you're on hard.
Warhammer is a universe.
They license it out for different developers to make different games.
The Warhammer game that you play is not made by the same company.
It's kind of here or there.
Some of my favorite RTS games ever were the 40k series Warhammer 40k.
Donovan War was probably one of my favorite RTS games.
I've got a lot of stuff.
I'm just playing as the Tao.
Somebody else just picked that up.
I already got one.
Wow, he's cleared that up.
Nobody's gonna take that.
Fine, I'll heal.
I'll heal and I'll take it.
Game of the year was a blood one.
Blood going victim brand.
Probably bonny Isaac.
I didn't really play a whole lot of the top big games in 2000.
A tomb.
I'm gonna grab the tomb.
We have two tomes.
Somebody do that.
Let me eat that.
Follow four.
Follow four was game of the year.
I wouldn't put follow four in the top five.
I can't believe they put a fucking entire Egyptian tomb in that book.
I like saying tomb.
No, it's tomb.
The tomb of unknown secrets.
I don't think follow four was a bad game, but I don't think it was necessarily a great game.
I don't think follow four was game of the year good.
I just don't.
It wasn't a bad game.
It just means it wasn't the best game I've ever played.
I don't think we might make a mark for the view.
I am not even close.
I want to go inside.
This is a bad idea.
I didn't do anything for me.
All this did was get me stuck.
This is not the right way.
The half man of the woods.
We're not going up here.
Apparently not.
I haven't put enough time into under.
I've played Undertale.
I have for a couple hours.
I haven't put enough time into Undertale to say it was the best game of the year.
I haven't played it for more than a couple hours.
I don't know what to do here.
I gotta leave.
There's two gunners down there.
Jeez.
What are the bullets?
This is not good.
Not good.
I don't know what to do here.
We got to leave.
We got to go jump down.
Too many gunners.
Can't go back up there.
She's just gone.
Look at our max health.
That is what happens when you pick up the two tombs.
You have no help.
There he is.
Oh geez.
Anybody have any guns?
That's a terrible place for him to be.
How the fuck are we going to get through that?
No!
Rocked right into a pack guy.
I'm still miraculously.
Fuck.
I was trying to block the attack so they could go.
Trying to jump.
Oh, we're in deep shit here.
Those two machine gunners being spawned right behind us there.
It was the worst thing that could happen.
Good luck to this guy.
That's game over.
That is a game over.
Oh well.
Hey cool.
You know, upgraded that item.
Dark Souls 3.
Looking forward to other things.
Dark Souls 3 for sure.
Let's just try it again.
We kind of got a bad deal there.
The scuven are up in the anti.
They're out in the forest building wall machines.
Never go to Grims with pubs.
It's hard.
Oh, italics wants to play.
Video game called vermin type.
I don't know.
I'll tell you what we'll get you in the next one.
Is that cool?
I just like these guys just joined.
Not like more than 15-20 minutes ago.
Oh, by the way, italics there.
Look, do you see something?
Do you notice the always on outline?
It was actually in the options we just didn't even see it.
There was another option to keep it always on.
Rather than just on sometimes.
You guys all have to leave.
We need to free up one spot.
You guys are going to have to do rock paper scissors.
Rock paper vermin type.
Oh, did he just appeared in my face?
You guys all saw that.
That was odd.
That's a bad reason.
Let me have her there the way about.
Now, it's an ambush.
What?
Oh, another opponent.
Oh, I'm too old to kill the few.
What you doing?
Stop.
That kind of been worse.
Totally worse.
Watch, watch, hey, watch, watch your six.
Where are the healing things?
Is there only one or two?
Some of you guys are quick.
This guy with the bow, you are quick, man.
I thought I was going to kill that guy.
You are a quick one.
No door ring.
I want this game, but I don't $25 want this game.
Yeah, I mean, it's.
It's good.
It's a full done complete 13 mission game with a bunch of items.
It's, I would say it's probably worth the $25 because it's not necessarily a play that game.
I can complete that whole game in like an hour and ten minutes.
I mean, you want to experience all levels and play with the characters and items.
I think it's worth the $25 price tag.
Like you said, is it worth it for you?
Is that like, is it worth the $25 for you?
Which may am I not be the case?
It does just follow the same leopard ed formula.
So if you got your fill out of leopard ed and you don't really care about that type of game anymore,
it's just a lot of the same shit, a astronomical amount of the same stuff.
But if you ever thought to yourself, hey, a melee only, like 80% melee left for dead in Warhammer's storyline,
is a game that I think might be cool, then this is a game that you would want to play.
We all shot him and he didn't die.
Let's guys have a lot of health.
Yeah, there you go.
It's worth $25 if you have a couple friends that also get it too.
Because then you can all enjoy the game.
I would say solo buying this game, it might be hard to get a group.
Because it's not like the most popular game ever.
I think people still play it. It still has pretty good numbers either.
So look at how many are on that bridge.
Holy shit.
I'm not sure.
Get him.
Got him.
I want this game with Lord of the Rings. Yeah, it's Alex. That would be amazing.
Yeah, that's a stash I will take.
Hey, I could use one of those.
They're adding a solo mode eventually.
That's cool. I wonder what that would be like.
I don't know what that would be like.
I took that guy's head off. Don't worry about it.
I'm not a bridge.
Thank you. Thank you, Foxy.
You've been hitting some nice shots too.
We're all just skipping. There's a tomb.
This is a fun game just to stream.
It doesn't really require.
I can just sit here and just talk and hang out and hit the hammer.
Look at that. Do you see the reaction time?
Good fucking job. Then here comes a tank.
There it is.
I don't think it's wrapped around.
Shit. God. God. I'm on a fucking tree.
I'm on a fucking tree.
Right in the head. Right in the head.
I blocked that last second.
Nice.
I'm on a fucking tree.
The door.
He's got a Scottish accent.
Where is he? I heard him.
Oh, is this guy?
Heard it.
The women's high.
I do like how this is pretty much always a one hit kill though.
Very nice. Very nice.
Very nice.
I need more bombs. He's barely any.
Hey, thanks for subbing.
Panda man. Thanks for the sub.
Thank you.
I'm probably not in this.
I don't have any fucking shit.
I don't have any sub notification for anything.
It's been like a hectic couple weeks though guys.
Last like three weeks.
There's been so many things I've wanted to do that I just haven't been able to.
A thousand different reasons.
But you know, that's life.
That's life.
Where they going?
We'll put it over here.
Oh, you already got it.
Oh, scut thanks for sub.
Thanks to anybody that sub.
I thought I missed.
I'm going to kill that guy.
I want to hit that guy in the head.
I got to get that guy in his head.
I hit the other guy next to him with a head.
I'm going to kill that guy.
Hey, princess awesome.
Thanks for the host.
Thanks for the sub.
I got it.
Nice.
Let's get out of here.
Damn it.
I don't even know why I'm shooting these little shits.
I shouldn't be.
You need to save those for special rats.
Come on.
I'm going to get him.
I got him.
Watch your back.
Where is he?
Hey, you.
There's a little dodge.
You can do backwards.
I'm not forward.
Give me the dodge.
Did we get a grim?
I think we did.
It's gonna be tough.
We're gonna have the healing.
Does anybody have a bomb? We got two bombs.
We should be able to do this.
And that should be the...
...question.
Alrighty.
Wow.
Are you good?
I think we're good.
I'm excited for the Deadpool movie.
Yeah?
I'm unissue.
I don't know. Should we...
Yeah.
I'm dead.
I think we just had so many superhero movies over the last few years.
I'm sort of desensitized to them all at this point.
But yeah, I mean I'll watch it.
View 12s, a bloodstain for them.
is
what we died last time right
further past this
let's make it past this one let's get out of this
slah
the
looks
to do say questions
my shot
and we have two crimes now is this is what we died last time we're going to be
very very careful
this is exactly where we lost last time with these two grims
yes
from
to scare to the enemy
take to the last time
on
take
from
the
one movie are you excited for a lot of movies that I wanted to watch already came up and I've already seen
enjoyed them I think I liked the hateful eight more than I like Star Wars
I mean I like Tarantino guy Tarantino kind of guy
where is he gonna show up right there
namely
I did go to the 70 millimeter showing and it was glorious.
I'm going to have one.
13 is a weird guy.
That's one way to describe it.
I think we're almost out of the woods here.
Where is he?
I'm going to go this way.
I'm going to go around.
I don't want to get stuck over here.
Shitload of people coming this way.
Where is he?
Really?
I thought I got you with that.
Get away.
Goodness.
Tarantino also loves closing car trunks.
There's a lot of things that Tarantino likes to do.
That's in almost every movie, right?
I'm going to go around.
Just make sure they're dead.
You got to hit them twice.
It should be close to the end here.
Looks like a person has no one.
The rest of the way.
We still have two two.
Actually, wait a minute.
No, you need this.
Come here.
You need that more than I do.
You need that way more than I do.
One more to defend event.
That's what we do.
I just get so self-conscious.
When we have this few health, it makes me so nervous.
You take a couple hits like this and you're just done.
You get too nervous like this.
I don't like doing two of the rims as much as it's awesome to get items.
Especially not hard.
We've got to have more confidence.
Get to full health.
Another health.
Somebody gets a dire.
Gunner up top.
He's dead.
Anything else?
What's the ammo?
We only need to stand somewhere.
Is that the strategy?
I guess it is.
Look at this.
Back in the left for dead days, we used to do the bathroom strat.
All four people would stuff into one of the tiny bathrooms.
It worked for about a minute or two until a tank came.
The bathroom strat was fine.
They won't know we're in here.
What does wait for the boat?
I love shit like this.
I have to come through one door.
I'm not sure if I can get out of here.
They were just phasing through.
What the fuck is happening?
Why?
I was just getting stuck inside.
No one's trying to open it.
What is this?
Oh, easy.
The one that was just stuck laying around.
What the fuck is that?
I'm so confused.
Getting a lot of kills right now though.
I'm not sure if I can get out of here.
Who's shooting the gun?
Why do I hear a machine gun?
This works.
It's all the green goo.
Let's go.
Anybody else?
Hey, we did it.
I gotta get this guy.
Nice work.
GG.
That was an interesting strategy.
We're going to have a lot of chances to roll.
We get a legendary.
What they're called exotic.
Come on.
Do I need one, two, three?
Let's go.
Shit.
That's a trinket though, right?
Engineers tools.
When throwing a grenade, there's a 15% chance that it won't be consumed.
Hold on a second.
Happy New Year to all of you central time zone people.
There was a blue trinket right above it.
What does that do?
Engineers tools.
I can just equip it.
So what is the trait?
I have to unlock that?
No, I guess I don't.
That's kind of cool.
Can I upgrade it?
What news?
I guess you can't upgrade because it's already there.
You can equip the trait.
Tools of the trade.
That's kind of cool.
That means that there's a more...
Most of the time when you throw a grenade, it's randomly sometimes it's not going to get consumed.
But that means it doesn't really matter.
That's my favorite Tarantino movie besides Pulp Viction because that one's too easy.
We talked about this the other day, like ranking Tarantino movies.
I don't know.
It's hard to say.
But was trying to think of like...
The first kill bill was pretty cool.
The whole kill bill was interesting.
I need to look at like a list of like all the Quentin Tarantino movies he's directed and produced.
Reservoir Dogs is an easy one to say too, but probably Reservoir Dogs or Kill Bill.
Alright, it's Alex, you want to play a video game maybe?
Yeah, you are.
I liked the hateful 8, man.
I thought the hateful 8 was like one of the better movies.
I like the whole...
I'm not going to talk about plot points.
But that whole movie just like how it's like, oh you got these 8 people and they're all different people.
They're all up their own stories.
Who the good guys are?
Who the bad guys?
I like that dynamic.
It's very interesting.
I like Kurt Russell.
I like Samuel Jackson.
That's just a good movie.
I recommend you see it.
Okay, it was a...
Not to me, just very briefly.
Do this.
Uh, Alex, can you invite me to a game?
Well, we uh...
Turn out dog cam?
We're going to do dog cam while Alex invites me to a video game.
Okay, guys, you ready for the...
Oh, he's like sleeping, dude.
This is going to be really cute.
There you go.
He's asleep.
There he is.
Sleeping.
Uh, invite me to a game, Alex, if you can.
Well, we see Otto, the sleepy dog.
My fan of clue, yes.
That is a great movie.
Look at how he's just...
He's like a little blanky dog.
Oh, hold on.
Uh, he's going to hide now.
The good men before are do so now.
The metal table will show you our current situation.
He's going to hide.
See, he does that in bed too.
Like, he sleeps in my bed with me.
And he just stuffs into the covers and just sleeps under the covers of me.
He's a great dog.
I'm so glad he's okay.
He's a good boy.
My name is Otto.
Uh, Alex, do you want to speak on the internet telephone?
Would you want to do that for like a round or two?
It's up to you.
You write in the chat if you want to speak on the internet telephone for like an hour.
I will join the internet telephone if you want me to.
Okay, he's currently in the internet telephone.
Uh, here we go.
Uh, I don't know if people can hear you or not.
Yeah.
Hey, I'm happy new year, dude.
It's just 1207.
You're time.
Yeah.
Uh, you should know people should be able to hear you.
Dude, happy new year.
Good.
Happy new year.
Welcome to the new.
Oh, now, now I've got to get used to writing 2016.
That's the new joke.
Shut up.
Shut up with that.
I got to lower you a little bit, I think.
Where are you?
The hell are you?
Say some words.
Hey, everybody.
What's going on?
My name is German 95.
We're with the team.
Gameplay commentary.
He's gone.
Yeah, you're good.
You're good.
Okay, let's go back to reality here.
Um, what?
What would you like to do?
Um, doesn't matter to me.
I want to play.
I would play as high star.
Oh, I'm going to be witch on her.
Salt spire.
What a mission have you not done?
I've only done two or three.
So like there's ten.
I have not done smugglers run.
Or black powder.
Really?
So take your pick.
I would do.
Either one of those is good.
Whatever one you feel like doing.
Let's give black powder a try.
Do you want to go ahead and begin?
Or do you want to wait?
Uh, those are the guys that were playing.
If you guys queue up from black pub.
Difficulty easy.
Sorry.
This one is just baby time.
I'm going to take a toy for you.
Hey, usually I'm not the one that chews for this.
I can use to it.
What the crap is that?
This is my fucking baby discellphone.
Take on me Elmo.
Listen.
Good night.
Uh, messy.
There. Is that better?
Yeah, we'll do normal. That's fine.
Do you want to do hard?
It's up to you.
I don't know.
Is that like a you normally do hard?
I'll do whatever you normally do hard.
Let's make it hard.
Okay.
Which one has these, uh, you can use these two guns.
I go bang bang bang bang.
He's very quick with his shooting.
And he's got the pilgrim hat.
Yes, I think he's my favorite voice character.
But it's like how he talks.
Let's go and save the kingdom.
I actually kind of want to try the wizard again.
Wizard's fun.
It's just hard.
I don't know.
It's hard to play.
I want to try the new electric.
There we go.
I guess I'm going to join it.
Yeah, if you're currently playing the game and you'd like to play just
queue up for black powder hard.
I'm sure it's in the server browser as well.
So it's the one with two or three people in it right now.
He's great.
I love all the voices in the game.
They're great.
Can you do like voice commands?
How do you do emotes?
I don't know.
I don't think you can.
I think they just kind of do it whenever they feel like it.
Uh, uh, maybe there was just like a this way or.
All right, we ready to go.
Kiss me.
It's been like, they're a missile toad.
They already passed the missile toad time.
Missile toad.
This is not.
Christmas, man.
I also like when you swing the sword how you kind of stop in mid-air and you.
Yeah, I'm ready to go.
Yeah, I'm.
This game, not this game.
This sword has a lot of stamina on it.
A lot of stamina on it.
What does that mean?
A lot of attacks.
A lot of shields.
Yes.
Which one is this?
Reaper clone.
What, uh, what mission is this?
Black powder, I think.
On hard mode.
Oh boy.
This is my first time on hard mode.
Oh well.
I'm going to be gentle.
You wouldn't you like to know.
How's that guy already moving?
Did you just like escape through that?
I don't know.
I was like just watching the cutscene.
Well, I don't want to do one thing real quick.
Hold on.
Let me see what happens here.
If the stream goes down for a second, I apologize.
Proficially.
Well, let's see what happens.
Ladies and gentlemen, the stream might just turn off.
I will turn it back on though.
I promise.
This is a job for the stewardors.
Why are they never out of work when you need them?
Did it work?
Did you just...
Are we still alive?
Because I...
I... I... I put it up to 40 frames a second.
40?
Yeah.
What is that going to look like on stream?
I've never seen that before.
Did the frame rate increase?
Can you not stream this at 60?
Oh.
I wonder if that did anything.
I mean, I probably...
I could try.
But I...
For some reason, I was on 30.
I don't know why.
I might have been the last thing I was recording.
Noisy.
Just like a dwarf.
Hmm.
I don't know.
I actually want to know what that looks like.
Wow, 10 more frames.
I've never seen a 40 frame per second stream.
This is the first one ever.
Just a...
I just didn't know if you could do it like on the fly.
There's a foam here.
I need to restart the stream to do the FPS change.
Oh, I'm going to restart the stream.
Oh, whatever.
Who cares?
So, on this...
Is this like the whole mission right here?
Yes, this is the whole mission.
So, if you have any experience with using the bolt staff,
the bolt staff...
Zero.
Because the default basic attack seems like kind of weak.
What about the charge up?
Pretty low.
So, charge up.
It's been on 30.
This whole...
I didn't know it was on 30.
I usually stream it 40 or 45.
Has it been bad looking?
Or has it been just...
It's somewhat just normal looking?
Were you watching early?
I was not watching on source.
So, I can't really answer that question very well.
I've been trying to stream when I stream at least 40.
Wow, why was it a 30?
I wonder what the hell that was.
Oh, Jesus.
Whoa, people behind me.
You do take fall damage in this game?
Yes.
We need to pick up some...
All right, go on to pick up some barrels.
I don't want to leave this guy alone.
There's got tackled, but it's okay.
I got someone covering me and there's three guards up here though.
So, that's not good.
We need to try to get to it at a time.
There's one up top all the way up top.
Are you going for the one all the way up top?
Ow.
Yeah, but I'm getting a little low.
All right, I got the one up top.
Rage and man, yeah, I'm getting pushed around a little bit.
Is this the first one?
Is this number one?
Oh, wow.
That almost is bad.
Holy crap.
And a tank.
We have one barrel.
It's coming after me.
I can heal you in a second here.
You know, once we kill this guy.
I'm guessing jumping in the water is not good.
No, it's not good.
All right.
All right, come over here.
Are you the right way, is it, right?
Yes.
Well, I didn't go off because I got it.
What must you be doing?
Hey, there we go.
Thank you.
Trying not to suck.
Is there any?
Even the sound cues are coming like leopardhood.
Yeah, that's actually one of the things I like about it.
Because it feels sort of familiar, but still unique.
Yeah, it's very, very familiar, but it's still fun.
How many do we have to it at 33 to 43?
3 to 8?
Uh, uh, get away from me.
Get away from me.
How the fuck did you get over there?
I hear an assassin and I'm terrified right now.
I need to come over to you guys.
He jumped right past you and then down.
Yeah, he's right.
No, not past you.
He jumped past the barrel guy.
He's still alive.
More to 8.
I need help.
Yeah, they're on the other side.
I'm going to die.
Oh, dear.
You're more.
I'm done.
Those people are by themselves.
I'm having to try.
So hard right now.
Yeah, this is hard.
I should have healed myself.
I shouldn't have given it to you.
I should have taken it.
I should have ate the fucking cupcake.
All right, we need to bake our way over there.
Yep.
There's the assassin right here.
The problem is I don't stone on the animals.
I haven't played this.
This is like only the second and third time.
There was ammo on this side.
It's top floor.
All right, who wants to make the trip?
We're making the trip.
This is bad to be split up like this.
Oh, come on.
Where are you?
Please, nobody's snuck me.
Don't pick me off.
You're on the wrong side.
Wait, I'm on.
What made like from the ammo?
An ammo is on this side.
I'm at the barrels.
Although, what's in here?
Oh, yeah.
All kinds of shit in here.
The ammo and air as well.
You don't have any ammo, but...
Bolt staff is an awful lot like just being a character in Dragon Ballsy.
I don't want to accidentally shoot with the tank.
Oh, you got a lot of people behind you.
Yeah.
That's accurate.
Only two more and we win.
One up top.
Come with me.
We're going to get the one up top.
They can get the one up.
Yeah.
We'll go get the one at the very top.
I followed the wrong view.
This is not the only exit.
Oh, boy.
Am I by myself right now?
Alex.
Why did you find myself?
I got myself.
This tap isn't really just not good.
One barrel.
I'm going to go up.
I'm by the barrel, but I'm scared of dying.
Actually, how do you get up there?
I don't know.
I can throw it down.
Oh, I'll watch out.
There's a fucking machine gunner.
I'm going to toss this down to you.
Hold on.
Don't do that yet.
Machine gunner.
I'm stuck.
I'm in this wall.
Holy shit.
It's explode on you.
Oh, I heard a bad spot.
No, I'm unreachable.
I just heard an explosion.
I am unreachable right now.
I'm on this little way.
I might be able to get you.
Is it easy, Dad?
We might be able to just look up there.
It's the one rat hitting me right now.
Good luck.
Doth butt crust just subscribed.
Hey, Doth butt crust.
The most powerful sith, Lord.
In the whole galaxy.
Yeah, we're falling to pieces right now.
As long as we get this last one, it will be fine.
We just often move with it.
What you're going to give the team moral support?
You buy yourself at the moment.
You're currently trying to not take any hits.
Hit with me, Nidah.
All right, we're going to get it.
We're going to get it.
Set free.
Can I get you?
I'm going to try to get you.
Possibly.
I think I'm going to get you.
Uh oh.
Please, please, please, please.
Please do not hurt me here.
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
Do not.
It's coming.
What?
What happened?
I'm up.
I rescued you two times.
That's weird.
But the hoard is here on top of us.
Run.
Just get on the boat.
Get on the boat.
I can't.
Oh, she's.
Bring the potion.
Get on the boat.
Jump down.
Do you have any?
I'm coming.
Hold on.
Get on the boat.
Leave him.
I'm here.
Don't leave me.
Yeah, nice job.
Oh, thanks.
Special thanks to Darth Buckrust.
So you went left.
I went right.
And if you go right, there was just like a walled off wooder and planks.
So I just like got into a dead end, basically.
Thanks for saving my life, guys.
Ooh.
That's a gun that's a legendary.
Come on.
All face up.
Shit.
Come on.
One more and I would have got a blue.
It's a staff.
Hard mode was the right call.
It was too tough for a poor old me, but still good.
Hey, I got a, is it a trinket?
Is my first trinket?
Yeah.
They have random effects.
So it can be like, oh, you're just a 20% chance that you're 2% move speed.
Oh.
Let's go back to the end.
2% move speed.
Yeah.
That doesn't sound like much.
Maybe.
I can just outrun you guys now so they'll attack you first.
Was it a green or was it a blue?
Green.
I'm assuming there's probably a blue version.
That's 5%.
Maybe.
I don't know.
Yeah, that would be pretty nice.
5% would actually be noticeable.
2% is just, you don't know if it's lag or if you're actually moving faster.
There is no campaign mode.
I mean, no.
Yeah, but what we're doing, there's no versus mode is only campaign.
Busted.
I feel like they were probably convinced they couldn't do a perfect balanced versus mode.
If you can't get a balance, then it's better just not to include it.
Yeah, that's probably true.
That's true.
I can probably craft down some shit.
Actually, I kind of want to play.
Look at how many people that hits just with a default normal swing.
That's kind of insane.
It does like no damage, but that is pretty damn cool.
You can just clear people out with it.
Craft it.
All right.
I'm going to try this staff instead.
I think it's going to go better.
I don't even like, I don't even keep fucking craft it.
I don't even care.
The only one I haven't done is smuggler's run.
Have you done that one recently?
Much earlier, I think.
I don't know.
It was one other you would rather play.
I would rather.
Your options are Horn of Magnus, Supply and Demand or Wizard's Tower again.
Lab.
Or smuggler's run.
Which I haven't in my item.
What's going on here?
Did you just like, did I eat it?
I didn't even get an item.
I didn't even get anything.
I just wasted what the fuck was that?
Okay.
Well, there goes 50 green gems.
Just took stolen from me.
Oh, geez.
Hold on.
Did it just not show?
Did I have this before?
I don't think I had this before.
I think I just forgot to show it to you.
I don't know.
I don't think I had this before.
I think this is new.
I don't know.
I'm going to try it though, because it's really fast.
We set up that torch for you, Loh.
Goddamnit.
10%.
It's so bad.
Oh.
Oh, well.
This is really fast.
And I can shoot.
Okay, I'm ready.
All right.
Oops.
I may have just hit the cancel button.
Oh, I hate you.
So hit F2 again.
You chump.
Prepare yourself.
Carefully.
All right.
Prepare yourself.
An emotional challengers.
here. This delete system 32. Just do that. Just do it and fucking just shit the bed.
Just reformat your hard drive.
It pulls you. Stab is fun.
Oh, city whose roots go unnoted.
I don't know about the gods, but I certainly approve.
So is.
Alright, let's find a bunch of dice.
We're gonna find all the dice, all the grimmeries, all of the poems.
It's gonna be great. I don't know if we're gonna do that.
We're gonna export every nook and cranny.
Oh, yeah.
That was odd.
Happy Valentine's Day. Happy Valentine's Day.
Happy Earth Day.
Happy Enchantment Day.
Hey, how you doing? Happy Enchantment Day.
Hey, I found a thing.
Give me a smile. Give me a smile.
This way would be fast.
Yeah, this, this staff actually one shot basic rat, which is a big improvement over shooting them six times.
Dead. I hear guards on the other side of this door.
Do you do do you?
Yeah, this way.
There's something wrong with this door. Everyone's like standing.
I don't know. I'm scared. I don't want to get hit by the troll.
We'll get this. We'll get fucking owned.
We're like, oh, there's a lot of boys.
We should hide.
And they're coming up by it. This is very, very great.
Hide in here. Come over to the right.
I may have shot them.
Why are you shooting them?
Oh, goodbye. We're gonna lose this.
Eat, bomb.
Get the speed.
Just gonna hang out of here.
He watching me.
I didn't do it.
What a dummy.
You are such a dummy.
We just, you had to rip it off like a bandaid.
You just had to get it over with.
You know, what it is is you're lucky.
What is it? You're lucky that we had two bombs.
There's a healing trap here.
Yeah, we're good.
We had two bombs ago.
Yeah, but they were put to good use.
Maybe.
We get this guy right in his face.
Oh, he got his friend in the face.
There we go.
Look, it's fun.
The stab, stab.
There's a lot of potions over here.
Is it like a new sword?
A new sword?
I'm gonna get like shit faced on these potions.
Yeah, what's that one?
I don't know.
There's got to be a blueberry.
What's this one?
Oh, yeah.
All right, let's go.
Open the flood gate.
What is this thing on my screen?
This isn't left to harm or die.
Why is it there?
Is it like a tool tip?
That's just the, I'm the middle of my screen forever.
Yeah.
It's waiting for this giant door to come down.
When they start crawling down the walls and stuff,
they really do remind me of like
the Lord of the Rings or just orcs crawling around everywhere.
I think everyone's like waiting on you to say that.
So by conflagration like,
we just light people on fire for the most part, I guess.
It seems pretty awesome.
The fireball one like pretty much instant destroys them.
This one's more like a dodge.
What's the, what does it call?
Is this that one?
It's a conflagration staff, I think.
Conflagration.
See, it's Alex can say where it's wrong too.
What is it?
He's in a conflagration.
Maybe.
I don't think I ever said that word out loud.
Oh, no.
Apparently it's almost dead.
I seem to get a lot of bullets that I just didn't need to use, but all right, whatever.
Ooh, a chest.
What the, what the, nothing.
Absolutely nothing inside.
I hate when that happens.
Yeah, it's annoying.
I don't know that just like not have a chest.
He's in the stuff.
We're blessed.
Yeah, this much brings my clothes.
I just, I like like just moving around.
We get fast to swinging this around like crazy.
It's definitely, it's great.
And you can shoot the sidearm.
Medical supplies.
This is the eye like a, I found my new favorite item.
Oh, really?
Yeah, it's something about it's fun.
Oh, the big opens, this is a pretty big area.
Lots of room for activities.
Yeah, we're gonna get some warm tear.
All right, is there a gattling gunner?
Grown here?
Because it just gave me a tool tip.
Really?
Hey, watch out for the gattling gunner.
Just to let you know in case you find one sometime.
It just gave me a random tip about the gunner.
Oh, that was fun.
But just like head exploding.
No, I just sidearmed that guy and it's a friggin temple.
I can definitely tell it's different between hard mode and normal mode.
Let me say that.
Yeah, like I was saying earlier, can you imagine doing this on like anything besides what we're doing right now?
Like going another step up.
Another step up just.
I'm gonna play that expert on left for death.
And you needed the utmost coordination with everybody to be able to do it.
Yes, you have to like move and like a speck ops team.
Is a bomb on her?
I will come get it.
It's a bomb.
They're extremely useful.
Toast to the emperor.
Who?
Who indeed is the emperor?
Uh, or hammer guy.
He's a war hammer guy.
That's all I know.
Oh, pack guy, pack guy, pack guy.
No, I'm just throwing a grenade at him.
Fuck this guy.
Where?
Like down there.
Give me the load.
I want the dice.
Please.
I guess I wasn't supposed to jump from where I just jumped.
We got two more dice.
Two more die.
So we've got two dice already?
Yeah.
Hello, Tim.
Um, he's kind of far away.
Boy, he's in.
He is umm indeed, shit now too.
Yeah, me too.
Two more for the fuck.
Whew.
This might be eight.
You love it.
They have it.
Second floor gate.
Yeah, this is going to be hard.
But you know what?
You could always just be crawling around on your knees
and sliding around.
You know, you couldn't do that.
You could just like make sure you're looking for your contact
and find it.
Yeah, let's just let's just come and create
corner crepes.
We have to come in a creep here.
Otherwise we're screwed.
They're going to be dropping from here.
I'm dead in one hit by the way.
Uh, yeah, I'm dead in about two.
Oh, geez.
I'm dead.
Get in the live.
It's just this one guy.
You got me.
Holy shit.
Now three of us are down over here.
Oh, you got it.
You got it.
Okay.
One two more.
It's blocked.
Block.
All right.
One more.
Pretty good.
It's got, it's got deep tapetated.
That guy just did a full swing and hit me.
Holy shit.
Try and hit him in the head.
He's moving around too much.
We live another day.
And we're all bleeding out of the sink.
Yeah, we are.
So good luck.
One one hit from one rat is about to put me back down.
Yeah.
Like I'm about to bleed out, just follow on these guys around.
Just run.
Run.
Like guys, like guys really far ahead.
Anything, anything post.
Oh, I just got the way for myself.
I just got the rest.
I just like, I used my, my spell and it took me above the threshold.
Look at how many of this too many.
There's too many.
We're never going to win.
Just keep moving.
Just sit dead in.
No.
I'm about to bleed out.
Yeah, I got you.
I'm bleeding.
I'm not going to make it very much longer.
Oh, this wasn't that.
Just getting some turn around.
I think we have to actually go in here.
Yeah, I think we have to go into this pit where they're all spuing from.
Probably.
Oh, dead apparently.
Oh, like no, no, I am done done.
Like dead dead dead dead.
You're going to have to go find me.
I think it's anything with left for dead if you go down like three times
in a certain amount of period.
Yeah, that makes sense.
Well, good luck.
Yeah, about that.
There's a gambling gun guy just chilling in here, but we're hitting him with my legs.
They were two.
They were two gambling gunner guys in there.
Yeah, look at well, give all credit to the teammates because oh, geez.
I have nothing.
Is there any any potions there anything?
No food in there.
I'll get up that ladder.
Whoo.
Oh, come on.
Oh, do you see where I am?
I'm in here.
The line down.
Oh, wait, we won.
That's it.
We did it.
Should we just get in?
Yeah, I just get in.
Forget about me.
Okay.
I died for a good time.
I'm sorry, germa.
We didn't want to leave you, but we had to.
It's okay.
You can loot right?
Oh, yeah.
That's good.
We get less experience.
You don't lose anything.
You got two extra die.
You get bonus points for going with everyone, I guess?
Yeah.
You get more experience.
All right, time to roll.
Two, three, four, five.
There's a legendary at the top.
No.
What's your gun?
I need to roll it.
Two.
It's a man.
Actually, the first time I've seen a mace.
It's for the empire.
I get.
I got a green axe for the dwarf.
This guy was fucking carrying hard.
Yeah, he was about to say the exact same thing.
I got a hard carry.
He isn't the best.
Good work, dude.
Good work, guy that won us the game.
He's very humble too.
I want to look at that mace.
I got a red axe for the empire soldier.
I don't think I can.
I'm on a bow.
Come on down.
We're off.
I'll cut you.
Won't do this.
It's like around how many missions do you need to do
before you start crafting stuff?
Once you get a handful of greens,
you can start to break them down and make them
and make them.
I'm going to do this.
You can start to break them down and make things.
I mean, the one hander is cool, but
I got the...
Do you have the crossbow for the witch hunter?
I'm assuming, yes.
No, I mean, I've been crafting down 90% of the things I get
to try to make something for a character I like to play.
Oh, really?
Well, I mean, don't you like the witch hunter?
I do like the witch hunter, but I also like empire.
So I like witch hunter, dwarf, and empire soldier.
Way watchers fun, but I don't know.
I like playing big two-hander or big, you know, fast super dude.
But I suggest buying the complete edition instead of the normal one.
What's in the complete edition?
Are you sure that's not like a soundtrack?
I'm like being completely honest like I think that would be...
You get a digital art book.
I don't know if I just bought the normal version I thought.
I like these because...
Now, how does that make any sense, right?
So this is a big two-handed mace,
and it hits way less targets with...
This hits so many people with a little one-hander, really.
I guess they kind of reverse, right?
So the big two-hander, the charge attack hits a million people,
but it's normal attack hits like one person.
But the one-hander hits way more people on a standard attack,
but doesn't hit barely anybody with a charge attack,
but it does more damage.
And I'll give it a try.
I'm gonna try it.
Ah!
Keep moving, Dory!
We already have an empire.
Ah, we already have an empire.
Soldier.
I think I'm gonna try two-handed dwarf.
I'll keep that for now.
I'm scared to crack that thing.
Yeah, the charge attack most of the time.
That's what I was doing when I was playing with it,
mostly just sweeping side to side.
Yeah, you kind of do just bop people with a big two-hander.
Oh, again, I can change to the empire soldier.
So here's the new mace.
It's got an odd animation set.
Looks like it's left, right.
Up, down, no, down, up.
Is the charge, charges just straight up and down.
All right, other one more.
Let's do one more.
Oki-doki.
It's too much more.
I have unlocked new missions.
Let's do one of the ones you've unlocked.
We can do...
Garden of more.
Man the ramparts.
Engines of war.
Or wheat and chat.
Wheat, uh, that's one where you grab bags and bring them.
It's a short one.
Do that one.
We'll do that one.
It's that one's short.
That's one of the only S3.
Oh, god, are you sure?
Are you sure?
Oh, yeah.
Baby.
Let's get our asses kicked for the little...
Let's get our asses kicked to end the stream.
That sounds like fun.
Stick together, please.
I do what I can.
Mom.
Die, will you?
I like that's one of my favorite lines.
Free to you.
Die.
Die, will you?
All right.
Let's make it a good one.
The sky then seemed to have overlooked some of the farms.
But it won't last for long.
The end time.
Fill out the wagon with food.
The Uber Shroyk resisted.
So what are the odds of them making another game in this vein?
I'm sure they have for like 40k.
Probably very close to zero.
But what are the future plans?
Was this game successful?
I mean, isn't this by the same sales?
Is this by the...
The war of the Vikings, guys, didn't they make this game?
I feel like they just do different games every time they make a game.
I feel like people like hire them out to do games.
Yeah.
They're just for hire.
Did they do mountain blade?
I know they did some...
ARPGs.
Like one or two ARPGs.
They've done...
I already knew the creator was one of them.
I know they did.
Were the Vikings.
Were they published for the Vikings?
Was that paradox?
I don't even know.
It's politics.
Gaming politics.
They don't...
They don't stick with one particular series.
I don't think they kind of just make...
Whatever games they feel like making.
Although they did it.
Maybe they did it.
War the roses?
Um, you know, I feel like I should know the answer to these questions.
I should know the answer.
You're a talix like the gamer knowledge guy.
I'm like the NDE person.
I should know answers.
Can we couple horse?
I think so.
Paradox published mountain blade.
Yeah, but mountain blade and war the roses are not...
Same thing.
No, not... maybe I'm confusing it too.
Mountain blade was published but not...
It was like...
It's a different thing.
Like the new mountain blade is not Paradox.
Okay.
But...
I don't know.
It doesn't matter.
I think we're going all the way.
It looks like we are.
I mean, I think since it's start with the far ones early on.
That would make sense.
Move back.
There's a lot of guys in here though.
That would make sense.
So can the sex also burn?
I don't like it.
If they get damaged.
I'm terrified to eat.
Oh boy, you are in deep shit by yourself down there.
Not me.
Oh, that's right.
You're not playing that character.
I am the dwarf.
Oh, why am I taking damage?
Oh, I must be able to swing.
Big swing and hit everybody.
Oh, dear.
I can't even see where is he.
I got the poison.
He's effectively blocking my vision.
You killed my ass.
I'm just not a bitch.
You son of a bitch.
Stay with me.
Do we have all the sacks?
Is there one more?
We got him.
Oh crap.
I'm stuck.
Hang on.
What do you mean you stuck?
Oh, God.
What's happening to you?
Getting wrecked.
I'm going to run around seven to ten rats to drop in front of the door frame that I was in.
I'm the tank.
And the tank's right next to me.
Are you serious?
Yeah.
He's just hitting me.
But I'm trying to get close as I can to you guys.
I'm going to run around seven to ten rats.
We got two playing as the soldier or the witch.
Empire soldier.
Because I am saying it's both you as possible for when I bleed out again.
He's dead.
Hey, we're fine.
Come here.
Where are you?
I was glazing over the screen.
Not fine.
That wasn't a short joke.
That was a short fact.
What's that?
So where are the sects?
Have we already deposited the other ones?
We'd be able to deposit it too.
Oh.
Okay then.
Did I know?
I don't like this weapon.
I don't like it.
You decided that you don't like it.
What is it again?
It's a one handed base that barely.
I don't like the breach.
Isn't German shortened real life?
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, whoa, whoa, whoa, easy.
Five, seven, five, eight.
This is a very average average.
I've heard average person.
I just saved us.
I will take credit for that.
I will take credit for the saving of humanity.
Two sex.
I'm definitely still like I'm playing above my my grade.
You're doing fine.
We're doing fine.
We only have two more to get after this and they're right next to the cart.
Long as we don't get screwed over by a don don't jinx.
I'm just like I have.
At apple pie.
Long as an apple pie doesn't fly down and shoot us or something.
We find.
Get it here. Let's close the door.
Come on up.
Are you going to come get this one?
Yeah.
We just tossed him down.
Just got to keep him up.
I'm going to put it down.
I'm getting smirked here.
Oh, I got pulled.
You're okay.
We're good.
All the sacks are right here.
So much happening right now.
Really.
Really another one.
What the hell?
That is like three and a really.
We all this is it.
We can get these.
Then we can just get in with the truck.
We're so close to the coach.
Just don't get pulled by anything.
Look at our clothes.
There's no pull rats.
No bullshit.
We'll be fine.
Just do the just be like a wide receiver and dodge around.
Mule residents.
We're here.
And there it is.
Look at that.
Four.
Five.
And six.
Get in.
Let's close it up.
Let me just stay.
Let me just blow that guy's brains out again.
Yes, you're so bad.
Well, they're really good teamwork.
They got kind of hairy there for a second.
There was such good teamwork.
Everybody was sticking together except for me when I went down and had to get rescued.
This is when we're going to get the legendary legendary acts.
They're going to be all spaced up.
How tough is it to get like the extras on this map like the dice and the tones?
I'm not joking.
I just got all face down.
Is he really?
I only got one.
So bowl head.
Well, it equipped your health is increased by 30% while knocked down.
That's that's pretty good.
So that means that you'll just stay alive longer when you're knocked down.
Yeah.
I just said, yeah, I have an idea.
Let's go.
All right. Well, I think, um, time is it.
It's probably getting late.
It's like 2 a.m.
Oh, it's almost happy new years in mountain time.
Hey, you know what? We'll stay up for mountain time for a for a mountain time happy.
Mountain time.
This guy's level 37. This guy plays this guy's played this game quite a bit.
I'm level 63.
This dude is level 63.
Damn, you're a pro man. This guy is a pro.
He's probably like really complaining about us when we can't hear him.
I wonder. I wonder if he's just like, he thinks we just suck.
He's like, oh my god. He's the idiot.
He's don't even know how to do like the real strategies.
Fuck these two.
He didn't even 360. No scope that guy.
Okay, I wish, can I like inspect him?
I want to see what he has. He probably has cool stuff.
That would be cool.
I want to see it.
Those onions? Are those onions?
Dude, he's got like garlic.
It's a fucking anti vampire. He's got like a bunch of cloves of garlic on him.
When I crouch, I feel like a baby.
I want to see his garlic belt. Look at that. Look at that.
Look at that. Garlic.
She's got a two. Look. She got a two.
Nice.
What about you?
You don't have any garlic. You suck.
Okay, what are we going to do?
What does this look like?
What does it look like?
When I crouch dodge like this.
You gotta just jump backwards.
I'm crouching though. I should be really little.
I don't think you have a crouch.
I'm crouching right now.
Your crouch is you kind of just peering over and looking at a situation.
You're just like, oh, I'm crouching right now.
Now I'm crouching. Now I'm crouching.
Your crouch is just you hunching your face forward a tiny bit.
I'm like taking this tactical position.
I gotta make sure that like I stay as low as I can.
You're peering around a corner.
You're hiding from somebody and looking like, oh, can you see me?
What is this shrine of solace? I just am on it.
Oh, this is a case when you go to the shrine.
I'm going to go to the shrine.
I'm going to go to the shrine of solace.
I just am on it.
Oh, this is a case when you go to here.
When you salvage items, whatever rarity they are, you get the stones.
You can take those stones and you can craft a random item for whatever melee slot character you want.
You put the trinket in here.
It looks like you can choose ranged or melee.
Or you can save a little bit and pick a random.
So it'll be a ranged or melee.
But it's cheaper.
It is cheaper, but you don't know what you're going to get.
So if you specifically want to sword and you do the random and you get a bow or something,
you're going to be like, oh shit, I should have just waited.
That's pretty cool.
Yeah, I mean, guys, we're talking about, thanks for joining me.
Thanks for joining me in the, you know, us, me and the talc, Talc, Talc, K-Boy, and his hung out for our entire year of 2016.
Entire entire year of 2016, stream.
I haven't turned off my stream the entire year.
This is 365 days of streaming.
Full 100% have not turned off my stream all year.
Everyone wants to talk about how I don't stream.
This is the longest stream of 2016.
I don't know about that.
No, no, it is.
This is the longest currently running stream of 2016.
No, it's not.
It's tied for first.
How do you know that?
Because you physically couldn't have been streaming longer.
Well, what if some, a bunch of other people that were streaming and were streaming at midnight exactly?
Yeah, well, you're tied for first.
This is the longest stream.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I am tied for first right now.
So therefore, you're just like having a world record.
Yeah, I did say that.
But here, let's break this, before I end the stream, let's break this down for just a second.
So that was like, I was talking a lot about Overwatch and streaming Overwatch a lot.
And then they decided to pull the plug on it.
And I was like, oh, well, I can't play Overwatch anymore.
I need a game to stream.
And I didn't have a game to stream.
And then the holidays happened.
So there you go.
I agree.
But I'm back now.
I'm ready to go.
My dog is fine.
I'm fucking ready to go, guys.
I got a video going up probably the tomorrow the next day.
I'm fucking ready to go.
Oh, it's happy new year mountain time now.
Is it? No, no, it's not.
Yes, it is.
Happy New Year, you guys in the mountains.
Everybody in a mountain.
All you guys that live in the mountains.
Happy New Year.
Right?
At least I caught a good deal.
You were three out of four here.
You got three for four.
Time to redecorate.
Happy New Year, mountain, guys.
You got two East Coast West Coast.
United States, Europe, Asia, wherever you are.
Australia,
Antarctica, Africa.
Uruguay. Did I forget the continent?
You want to change equipment.
I wasn't listening.
I just know you didn't say Uruguay.
I did not. You're right.
Or the Congo.
No, I said Africa.
But you didn't say the Congo.
That's a specific place in.
Right.
You got to say like the Netherlands.
Yeah, West Coast is in an hour.
That's true.
That is true.
All you West Coasters.
All you West Coasters will see.
We'll see you soon.
We forgot the Bermuda triangle.
Oh, yeah.
Happy New Year, D.
Bermuda.
Prang, guys.
I just like fell asleep halfway through saying that.
Happy birthday.
You just said happy birthday.
What is my...