Oh.
Hello.
Wee you.
An Nintendo Wii U.
Hey good uh.
Good evening everybody.
I turn uh I turn 30 in like eight minutes.
It's about 30.
I want to be I want to be 22 again when I was young and free.
And now whatever.
So we're going to celebrate my 30th birthday prematurely by getting angry at a video game that I'm not good at.
Hey.
Sounds like a pretty good time to me.
What do you say?
And this time I actually have I put my monitor.
Well my other monitor.
It's over on like the right here.
So I should be able to see chat a lot better this time.
I moved my setup a little bit.
I'm uh currently transitioning into the experiment office.
Not quite 100% there.
I need to get a couch delivered here first for this downstairs area.
But whatever.
We're good.
I'm already on expert.
So I hopefully you guys can't hear this.
Make sure my like web cam's not on not like pointing at me.
Okay we're good.
Let's stand up.
Is one of the problems I'm having with streaming a console game is it's it's on the screen right now right.
And it's audio is obviously coming through.
I don't want to pick up that audio.
I don't have like this.
I can't plug headphones into my TV.
I just want to make sure you don't make it down here.
It whatever.
Have a good 60th birthday.
60th birthday.
Not that old.
Actually I have a couple of levels from a star.
We'll get to those.
I haven't warmed up at all by the way.
And I'm still playing on the brick.
So don't get your hopes up.
I've seen me get past level 3.
And hopefully I've got the audio input delay.
I fixed it hopefully.
I don't know.
So it's very attractively called coin hole.
Easy enough.
Is he going to come down?
He is.
He comes right back up.
Off to a great start.
Oh geez.
So I guess I do have to wait.
How long does it?
No, I got to wait.
Second cycle.
Way from to come up again.
Oh geez.
Maybe not.
There's only one fly over here.
Apparently.
Alright, let's figure this out.
I got to go now.
Yeah, okay, okay.
I got to go right on that first one.
I don't know.
Maybe I'm screwed here.
Did I just screw myself completely?
Apparently I did.
Here we do it.
Here we do.
This is the one.
And there we go.
What?
I might just skip this one.
I don't know.
What the hell is even going on here?
Do I have to get it to like come over to me?
Like we're going to aggro range?
I like that.
Okay.
That was very confusing.
Gotta get those coins.
It's the most boring thing.
Look for hidden blocks.
People put them everywhere.
Okay.
Looking good.
I can just run across that.
Am I going to die if I go down here?
Yeah, I am.
I'm not doing that.
I'm not going to fool me on that one.
What would have happened if I just died if I went down there?
Yeah, after I absolutely not get through this expert, I will do levels for you guys.
If you got some good ones.
Are you star?
I don't know.
All right.
You know, to save myself a little bit of time, I probably shouldn't just sprint directly through each level.
My first or second life, I should really just kind of look and see what happens.
So very obviously I have to jump on these to get across.
Okay.
Would it be you say game?
I guess I could do this though.
No, I don't.
I don't have it.
Maybe I do.
Nope, that doesn't work.
I thought that you could bounce on those things.
Oh, that's not that bad.
I should get to the next one or two times.
I'll try this.
Just about bounce enough to the second one and then you're pretty much free.
Oh.
You can bounce on those things.
You can't not.
I just died doing it.
Don't troll me, star.
What's going on here?
Can't I bounce on those things?
There's no way I can beat this unless I can, right?
I didn't even try to.
I didn't even say I just freaked out right there.
That was stupid.
I hit this fucking ceiling.
Something else I have to invest in is a wired controller as well.
This thing in my hands, I sweat a lot.
I'm a little sweaty.
I'm a bitch.
I get greasy on this brick.
Shit.
Oh, yeah.
I get it.
You can spin jump on those.
You don't have to do like the Tony Hawk's Pro Skater strategy.
Although I probably should still because I'll mess that up a thousand times.
I can do it to them too then.
I can't do it to that unfortunately.
Huh.
I wonder what I'm missing here unless there's something I'm just going to jump.
There's something I can do about it, right?
Was there a mushroom over there that I missed somehow?
Oh my god, you gotta be kidding me.
That's where that is.
I did that by accident.
If I did not just by accidently do that, I would have never ever ever beaten this stage and I would have skipped it.
I would have had to skip it.
Like how the hell are you supposed to know that's there?
Oh my god, this is all no, no, no, no, expert level.
I have to like carry it at least to the next part.
That's not even an expert.
I don't even know where it is.
I don't even know how to throw it.
Okay, right here.
I'm not gonna focus on this too.
I thought I had that one in the bag.
This is not a bitch shit in my fucking hair and use it as shampoo.
Where is it?
Just overshot it.
Get this fucking ceiling again.
I actually might step on this so I don't have to keep holding down why.
Because that's what's like throwing me off.
Is having to hold the other button.
No, that's such a bad idea.
I'm not gonna make it.
Because I can have to rush the hell out of this.
Just don't rush it.
I rushed it immediately.
I said not to.
How would you have ever known that was there?
Is there no clue that that's like a thing?
I rushed it again.
I might skip this one.
Oh fuck.
Three more attempts and I'm skipping it.
I hate this one just because of what happened in the beginning here.
I'm already getting upset at this one.
How do I put this down on the ground?
I don't want to kick it.
I don't want to kick this.
It's gonna get kicked.
Yeah, I can.
Oh boy, here we go.
Mother fuck.
That was going fine.
I just screwed it up at the end.
Let me move back a little.
I don't even know what happened there.
That would be so bad if I kicked it off.
Easy now.
I wonder if I'll make this easier on myself if I use the Wii U stick sideways rather than the brick.
Is that better?
Fuck.
It's that last one.
That last jump always gets me because he ended up hitting the ceiling.
The hole just fucking thing for so long.
Dear lord in heaven.
The Wii Mode sucks too.
How much is one of the regular Nintendo controllers?
Are they like 60 bucks?
God.
I'm trying to see.
Not in doing it.
Never mind.
The classic controller is only 20 bucks.
I should get one.
It seems like a much better idea.
That last one just gets me every single fucking time.
It's funny because I actually said to myself like maybe I should wait till I get like a real controller before I actually play this on stream again.
And what do you know?
I turn the fucking stream on without a pro controller.
We're getting locked into this one.
I might skip it.
I might do skip strats.
Oh dear god.
You know what? Hold on a second.
I think I have an idea.
No I don't.
I don't have an idea.
I see the weight.
Hey look I made it.
Shit.
If I step on this.
Oh my god I just did it.
I didn't even understand what was happening.
I don't know why I just activated.
Oh boy.
Those patterns seem to be off half the time for me.
Alright we're gonna do this one more time and I'm skipping it because I'm not gonna have another stream where I sit on the same level for like 40 minutes.
After this one that was level 69.
I can't end on that one.
Come here at you.
Oh I was gonna hit silky.
Oh there's an actual shortcut on this level.
Where is it?
If I just hit this we'll just show to me now.
Why have I not been doing that?
Holy shit.
Why the hell have I been not doing that?
I'm just gonna do that.
That sounds, it looks like much easier.
Just jump the whole thing.
Oh what?
That's not fair.
I'll try this with this strategy a couple more times.
No I hit it too high.
Come on.
No that was a bad idea.
Nevermind that's a terrible idea.
Alright this is really the last attempt before I skip.
Okay, try to always skip.
Get me out of this fucking level.
Bye.
We're gonna play a different one.
Look at this level.
This level is much better.
Look at those in mushrooms.
Where's the inner here?
Oh shit.
Damn it.
The next one was the ticket.
No way.
I never would have beaten that one.
It was just too awkward.
Oh boy, I was like talking.
Those guys are going to be aware of it.
I'm gonna hit by those spikes.
We'll let you go by.
I think he will.
What's his pattern?
Yeah, there he goes.
Oh I start off float.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, easy, easy, easy.
Get in the fucking boat.
I screwed it up already.
Maybe not though.
Just to go through this with fast enough.
Keep them behind the wall.
They will not be able to hit you.
Boy, this is actually gonna be very difficult.
Is it possible for me to still do it without the cloud?
Shit.
Oh, that was a mistake.
I was not able to get by fast.
That was toast already.
Slow this one down.
I don't need to go that fast.
That guy will hit you every single time.
I'm gonna go for like that.
Some reason he still hit me.
Shit, I hit him.
All right, so how long till I rage quit this game and go play like fucking checkers?
When am I gonna start like live stream and be like eating snacks?
Oh, my god, that's just like not paying any attention anymore.
Still doable.
I just rush things way too much.
Maybe a little while.
There are like secrets up here.
I guess not.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Secret.
That was a mushroom.
A mushroom just came out of that guy.
What did they come out?
No, they came out of the, okay, okay.
I'm gonna stop being such a fucking dumbass and like using these lives instantly.
Both of them.
Slow the fuck down.
How am I supposed to know how I was gonna avoid that?
Wait for this guy to come up.
Okay, geez.
Oh my god.
I'm just gonna die.
I was gonna jump into the fucking lava.
Probably, I probably still would get angry playing checkers.
I don't know when the last time I played checkers was.
Whoa.
There was a mushroom in here though.
Where was that mushroom?
How did I get it?
It was like, I went up here.
Drops down and out.
Okay, I say, I say, I say.
You might not be a bad time to go.
Too many things on the screen.
I wonder.
Waiting is bad.
It's always bad for me to wait here.
Because another one's just gonna come from the other side, right?
Kind of, I guess.
Oh, not really.
Okay.
I have three hits now.
Maybe even four.
I'm gonna get the power right through it.
Oh shit.
They follow through the...
I just realized that they come through.
I thought I could just power right through that.
But I forgot that they can like move through the thing and clip through everything.
That's gonna be a lot harder than I thought it was gonna be initially.
So I can't just blow right through and just damage boost it.
I just need to wait.
That's gonna be fun.
Is he gone?
No, he's gone.
I ran right into his fucking little bridge.
I just grabbed the wall.
Hey, remember what I said last time I played this?
Grabbing the fucking walls in this game.
I wish they deleted it.
I wish I could like hold like L and R to like grab a wall.
I hate auto grabbing walls in games.
It drives me fucking crazy.
All right.
What the fuck is happening?
Why didn't he not go in it?
Okay, I need to get them on the both the same side.
They're in such a terrible spot.
They need to be, they need to both be on the same side.
Otherwise it's impossible for me to go through this.
Come over here.
There we go.
I'm trying to figure out what the opportunity is to go.
All right, so it's this.
Over here.
Not really.
So what determines if they're gonna follow you and not?
Like, it sprint like that fast across the screen.
Like that.
I just gotta go down, up, up.
So they bounce back, bounce back, bounce back.
It's shit.
It needs a shell.
Hey guys, it beat a level.
Can you believe it?
I know it took me like 55 lives to beat a level.
I'm just gonna jump.
I have to do that right.
I have to immediately get rid of Yoshi.
Sorry, Yoshi.
Sorry.
That's me.
Holy crap.
What the hell's going on here?
I just freaked out for a second.
That's all these spiky guys.
I gotta ditch you again, Yoshi.
I'm sorry.
Yeah.
Okay, go in there.
Shit.
That was the follow-up to that one.
I can spawn them again.
I don't think it matters.
Can I get back there at the question?
I think I've lost it.
Fuck.
These are serious.
What the hell was that?
Is that what I have to do?
I guess that's what I have to do.
Oh.
I'm on the left.
I like this level.
So you've got to go one, two, three.
I can probably skip it right if I go now.
I can't get back there.
Shit.
No, not really.
What's the correct way to do that?
Go off the first one.
I assume it's just go off the first one.
Right?
I'll figure that out in a second.
It must be a leap of faith off that first one.
He goes the highest.
Spin jump.
Maybe.
I'm going to assume it's one, two, one, these ones.
Let's do it.
I'm not out of the key even.
That last one doesn't go high enough.
I don't think.
I'm going to assume it's going to be another one.
You have to make a staircase at this point.
Maybe that is what you had to do.
That was just kind of there as a screw.
You had to go fast through this one.
Nice.
There we go.
Skip.
Don't need to skip that one.
Some of these, man, some of these with the hidden blocks that you have to just find.
Those make me very angry.
And I get pissed off and I start to grab and squeeze on my controller and use it as a frying pan.
Because look at this thing.
It's as big as a fucking frying pan.
I don't know if I believe this.
Probably some type of hidden thing.
Whatever.
Oh shit.
Gigantic goons.
Haha.
You can't go through it back.
Can they go walk through those?
Yes, they can.
Of course.
Why wouldn't they be able to do that?
Well, shoot the big shell.
I knew it.
I need that.
I need this.
I need to carry one of the smaller ones through.
Why is there a coin there?
Is the point of the coin being there?
I don't want any of these little shits ruining this.
Can I not grab them?
You can't pick them up, can you?
How do you get over that?
I don't know.
I think I understand.
Yep.
What is below this?
Please don't just y'all.
Oh shit, a look at you.
Oh my god.
I wasn't going fast enough.
This one's doable.
Very, very much so.
No.
Now wait till the firsts or second shot.
I wasn't going to be running with it.
That's something I was doing that first time.
You just got to go right over him.
Oh, fucking eat my ass.
Thank you.
I get rid of these turtles.
Okay, let him come back.
No, that's not it.
This seems actually pretty difficult.
He needs to be on the way back.
That's for sure.
That was it.
I'm going to do wrong there.
Please do our kids are watching.
At this late at night, I'm not sure about that.
You know, be really easy if I could just get it on the first run.
I have to get it on the first run otherwise I'll never get it.
I could do the mid air spin too, but twirl around.
I always forget you can do that in this game.
That thing.
They're awkward spot from my finger though.
It's like up on the top.
Because the Wii U gamepad, it's like that's so far above where my thumbs are.
So hitting the right trigger is like extremely awkward playing this game.
I can't wait until I don't have to ever use this thing again though.
Holy shit, this thing sucks.
There it is.
He just keeps throwing him.
What the fuck?
Wait a second.
Where did I go?
I got to kill him.
I got to jump on his head.
I thought there was going to be a little ledge I could go over on the right.
Okay, I got to jump over him, hit him and take his spot.
That's going to be kind of a pain in the ass.
Shit, this too close.
There we go.
Let's move.
I want instantly died by something.
Nothing over here, right?
Oh, he can just jump up.
What the fuck?
Come on.
I didn't even have a time to react.
There's no reaction time.
They just threw me in a room with a ball.
Whoops, run.
It's just bouncing around and shit.
Come on.
That was so stupid.
That was not fair.
I love how expert levels.
You take the word expert and actually you can just put in a different word.
It's called random unfair shit.
Are you out?
No, no, no, no.
When you go in this room, you're fucking guaranteed to die at least once.
Now I'm mad and I'm just walking to stuff.
The stream lagged for me so it looks like you just walked in and died.
That is exactly what happened.
I walked in and died.
I'm going to get some of the passion back into this because I'm just walking into stuff and dying.
That's going to come back at me.
I'm going to be careful here.
Hello.
What?
Are you kidding me?
Please just walk through this.
Hurry up. You're so damn slow.
That was doomed.
That was doomed from start.
That would, they didn't want me to win that one.
That's such dog shit.
That was perfect.
You can't do it on that first time.
You have to wait till it goes by.
You have to wait until it goes by one time.
Otherwise that's just going to happen to you every single...
...fucking time.
Every single time.
That's going to happen to you every time.
Jump the first one and do it on the second one.
I didn't do it.
Mom, I didn't do it.
No, I didn't do it again, mom.
Come back.
We'll try to get him, mom.
There we go.
I did it, mom.
Okay.
Just, what do I do here?
I don't know.
I've no idea.
That j- I'd...
Lucky, didn't even do it.
I've no idea what just happened.
Holy shit.
Is this a... is this a completeable one?
I'm going to lose it.
I don't think I got it.
Oh, there it is.
This is my completeable mom.
I love the guy in chat that just said,
What is he trying to talk to his mom?
A fucking fireball.
It's so stupid.
I think I might skip this one too.
We'll see.
If I get there again,
I don't just...
I just don't know what to do there.
There's a big skeleton blocking the road.
Okay, this one I had to...
I just jumped.
Yeah, you just got to jump immediately.
Here we go again.
Do I just slide down the left and just not even care?
What?
What do I... what do I do?
Does anybody have any strategy for this?
Obviously, I have to hit that guy on the head from above on the ceiling.
So if I hit the...
But then I have the ghost that's just sitting there that whole time.
But I have to pull that ghost away.
That's gonna be...
That's gonna be very, very difficult.
And I don't think my brain is capable of completing that.
We'll find out very shortly.
Oh, you son of a bitch.
You didn't even fucking do it that time.
You only get hit dry bones once.
It might be doable.
If that's the last area, but that's the last screen, then I might be able to do it.
But I don't know.
Probably not.
Don't get your hopes up.
Oh, this one.
I have no idea.
Seriously.
Seriously, I think...
So I've done that room five times now.
I've done the exact same thing all five times.
And half the time I land on his head.
So I guess I'm just gonna roll the dice in that room.
I guess.
Oh, what the fuck was with that little dinghy fireball sitting there still?
You little dinghy fireballs.
That was close.
I'm just gonna do it.
You didn't come in that time.
You didn't even come in.
I'm skipping it.
We're out of here.
Hit the skip.
Where's the skip button?
Give it to me.
Get me out of there.
See ya.
I ain't doing that shit anymore.
I look like this one.
There's a shoe in this level.
Oh, I get to be Link.
Oh, shit.
Whoops.
I'm trying to figure out like...
Is the one cavity moves?
Or did you get...
I'm just trying to figure out what he does.
Fuck is happening right now.
What just...
I don't have any idea what I did.
I must have just done something correct.
No, I did.
I don't know.
I should have gone there, right?
I guess.
I guess we're still okay.
Oh, he shits.
I don't even know.
Fuck.
I'm not gonna do that.
Fuck is this game, man.
Oh.
I can't play the game right now.
I'm sorry.
I was gonna run.
I'm supposed to beat this.
And there's a change-up coming up.
This is what I'm gonna do.
Fuck is it?
God.
I need to just stand still.
I just stand still.
I'm not gonna get the stand still.
Are you serious?
I'm gonna get the instant die.
Well, I guess I could kill that thing now that I know that.
So I just can't move.
Alright, I'm not going to move.
I'm going to stand up on the last one and I'm not going to move.
I hope that's correct.
Okay, I thought there was a thing there.
It's working.
There's so many things chasing me right now.
I hope this is the correct strategy.
I thought I was unaware.
I thought maybe I was supposed to kill one of them and take one of these ships.
I did not know what to do there.
Do I want the fireflower?
I don't know.
I don't want to boot anymore.
It's making me move too weirdly.
I think I'm just going to jump out of it.
Wait a minute.
That thing's supposed to hit the...
It was killing the other ones, wasn't it?
They're at the same family.
There is a pipe here.
So yeah.
I don't know if I'm going to get the right way or not.
Good luck.
Thanks.
I appreciate it.
How do I get over there?
On the pipe down here?
What is all this shit?
Should I just fly up and go down the pipe?
That on my way.
Follow me down. Can I take this in the pipe?
Holy shit.
That was insane.
I almost just died.
I don't know.
Kill this guy.
One more time.
See you later.
Did I win?
Another pipe.
I'm protected.
I have a lot of protection right now.
I'm not that scared.
It's not very long.
I could have gone that one.
Holy shit in my pants.
What the hell?
Should I go in there and go down?
I wonder if I should go down there.
Nope.
Doesn't do anything.
Oh, just shooting coins.
Okay, that's funny.
That's funny.
I like this level now because that guy put that there and it shoots out coins.
Holy goodness.
A lot of trolls in this level.
Looks like a knock this guy down there, right?
Holy get him.
Yes, he will.
Not all of them.
Well, that's what I get for standing still.
I didn't realize there was fire underneath me.
I get.
Okay.
What the hell?
Where am I going?
What the hell's going on?
I'm dead.
That was weird.
You just put a bunch of random shit all over the pole.
Airship.
Hard.
Okay, last time I did expert.
I got to, well, I got to level five and it was over.
I couldn't beat it.
I got to level five and it was over.
I knew it.
Is this a scroller?
No.
Not really.
I guess kind of goes up.
I should have nothing I'm missing, I guess, up here or whatever.
speak
the
ship they will center
Why would this be here if they wasn't a reason for it?
Yeah, okay.
Shit.
What the fuck?
Geez.
I thought it was going to keep going.
That's a pretty big skip.
I can remember that for next time if I don't beat it.
Tap fast again.
Come on.
Get over here.
Oh.
I kind of screwed over here, but yeah, I shouldn't be standing over there.
That's a mistake.
Set it.
Yes.
The hitbox on that was a second away from heading.
I just don't know.
That's the worst part about these levels is you just don't know.
Thank God.
Thank God that wasn't something stupid at the end.
Those moles are the worst enemy in any Mario game.
Yeah, they throw those wrenches that just go very, very slow and they're very, very annoying.
That was a good one.
That was fun.
Although I kind of just skipped everything.
Okay, well, that's what I get for reading over here.
I'm looking over the chat and the saw blade just spins me right in the spine.
Come on now.
Get away from me.
You serious?
I like this one.
This one's awesome.
This one is really, really great because it's just like good luck.
Okay, I'm definitely going to vote this one up.
This one was amazing.
Like what a dick.
This is great.
This is the best level.
I don't even care if I die 50 times on this level.
It's worth it.
This one's awesome.
Please.
I should just run underneath them.
I probably just keep running.
No, not on that one.
After this first one though.
I don't.
One of these things.
I can like, oh, what?
I have to climb them.
You.
Actually, that bad.
I thought it was going to climb the whole thing.
What?
Do I reach out?
I wonder.
Yeah, I do.
This German reach out.
I'm on to how responsive he is.
Responsive enough to take two deaths because I'm over here reading.
The whole goal with this one.
This is, no, it's already done.
Just get me.
You have to get so far ahead on this first run right here.
I got to go so fast.
I got to get by.
I got to have a lot of time.
A lot of leeway.
Like here, I got to get a lot of good time on this one.
Last jump too.
This is going to be so hard.
Creatively he made it so you really just can't run.
You have to jump from time to time.
Even if you want to try to do like, I'm not going to do it.
I'm going to sprint technique.
I don't want to pick it up.
Okay, I've got a lot of time here.
Oh god.
I did it.
If I answer with high, you'll become a nun.
Well, time for you to become a nun.
I don't have very many lives left.
Well, this is a scroller.
Auto scroller.
No time to touch anything.
That was a power button.
This is very, very messy.
This is a mess.
There's a lot of mess going on.
What a mess.
I just got off top.
What the fuck is Bob doing over here?
What the hell is happening?
What's happening?
Am I just going to skip this one?
The only thing I can think of is just, nope, you can't wait it out.
Did I not die?
I was still alive.
I was still alive for like five straight seconds when I fell.
Where was I?
I am extremely confused by that.
I can jump up.
I can go on top of that and jump on top.
That's what I'm going to do.
Ready?
This is the strategy right here.
Got it.
I was trying to fly.
Am I going to die?
No, good lord.
I had that one too.
No, this is not going to happen.
Can't jump on his head.
Give me the pow.
It's just so much shit happening at the same time.
Maybe it's better to go up the left.
I love that this one's called epic battle.
Oh, thank God.
Give me the mushroom.
Great.
It's no, I fucked it up.
There's no way I'm going to be this way.
Shit, there's a guy with fucking everywhere.
This flames and shit too come on.
Hi.
This one would be easy if the very beginning you didn't get hit by everything in the game.
Look at all this shit that they throw up on you.
I have to sit here.
I'm trying to jump on his head.
Get the fuck out of my goddamn way.
Getting locked in the corner.
Anybody remember where the bridge is?
Not there.
Not there. The bridge wasn't there.
I couldn't even see it.
I don't know where it was.
God.
How annoying is this?
I love that I have to have just a fish come out at you too.
Nope.
Oh, I got stuck.
I was trying to do a re-attack to get it to work.
This is so fucking stupid.
I wish I could make that jump.
I just did, but I'm not gonna help.
Get away from me, everybody, please.
Alright, let's do it.
I'm not gonna...
Please.
Don't even tell me I was about to lose that.
Epic battle.
This one's called my best level.
Got a wall of coupas to start.
I'm liking the wall of coupas.
I feel like I should get up there faster.
I'm just waiting for it.
What the hell is even here?
I don't know.
What on earth is going on here?
Is there a shell I can grab?
I guess I just have to take the damage and keep moving.
Apparently.
I don't know why that hit me.
I'm just flying things.
Musical notes.
Stuff that falls.
I'm just going to get that out of here.
I'm gonna pick it up and start out on my way.
Well, we all have to assume that this is what has to happen.
Why would I ever go in there?
Why would you ever go in there?
Yeah, I missed it or something.
Apparently, I guess that was just went too far, apparently.
There's just a bunch of random platforms with enemies surrounding them all.
That shouldn't be too difficult to get back there.
Apparently, it is though.
I don't even know if I want to play this one again.
I'm way above the sky box right now.
I couldn't hit them.
Would that come on?
I'm gonna pick this up.
Really, really now.
Apparently, it wasn't high enough.
I'm just gonna get another one of those.
I was trying to place that, but I don't need to.
Maybe I should just break this, but if I might be in a lot of trouble.
Maybe I just shouldn't go as high as I did before.
I mean, what if there is something in here?
It might be.
I really appreciate if you stopped moving.
This fireball coming right at me.
Oh, I saw a chat told me that it was the equipment that could have been a secret door.
Can you even have secret doors in this game?
Did I just die for no reason?
I actually just forgot that that was right here.
Well, this doesn't even matter. I can just walk right through it.
I'll tell you right now, I don't like being able to clip right through those fucking doors.
Those blocks.
Are you gonna just walk through them?
And it seriously gives me like a freak out for a second.
Okay.
What the hell is that thing?
Looks like I'm picking up.
I'm not messing around with that.
I can't do it.
Take up the spindle.
Help.
I'm coming.
I don't know if I'll get there in a pretty sense, but I'm definitely coming.
Oh, no.
Thank you.
Thank you for the instant, instant, instantaneous death.
That's very nice of you.
Slipper-y-ass blocks.
I need to just go then.
This way might be harder than the other way.
Don't look at that door.
How do I get in there?
Is that like- is that an accident?
I feel like that person did not me to put that there.
Maybe they did.
I have no idea.
Trying to figure it out.
Oh my fucking god.
Yeah, that does not look like an entrance.
It looks like you go in it.
Or there's an invisible block.
You gotta do it.
Shoot the stupid thing.
Now I'm paranoid.
Every time it's just not in the right spot for me to jump.
Can you please be in the right spot for me to jump over to it?
I should probably go in here.
I don't know.
I went in the third one.
Okay, third one's death.
Third one is- Third one is you just die.
That's good to know.
I'm just going to go in this one then.
Maybe this will just bring me-
Okay.
You got it?
We get two more lives.
Cool.
So that's what that does.
I was hoping maybe there'd be something else to do.
There's like a safer or something.
Whatever.
Is this the first one?
Huh.
So.
I guess you do-
You do want to go in the second one then?
You have to go through this-
The whole thing.
Because I only have like one second to go here.
Wouldn't it wear those two jump-up?
Right there.
Am I going to shit by this if I walk?
I'm scared to walk.
Whatever.
Moment of truth.
That one comes up there.
I'm so-
Oh my fucking god.
I just went too high.
I pressed the button too hard.
It happens.
Sometimes you just press the button and you just jump across the whole map.
Number two.
Just for the shits.
Okay.
Number two seems to be the one that you want to use.
Boy.
I think it's-
I think it's over though.
Is there anything else I can do about this?
Yeah.
I-
No, I just had to go faster apparently.
Well, there it is.
That's it.
I don't know any more lives.
Oh well.
I got to level eight.
Let's give one more go.
One more attempt.
Mario memorization should be how this game gets renamed.
Because you have to memorize every level.
They give you 100 lives so you can spend 20 of them memorizing the level.
Oh, this is-
You have to be small to get through here.
That was-
That was Mario memorization.
Guaranteed to die.
So I'm assuming you I shouldn't touch any of these.
What?
Just run, right?
Do I have enough speed?
Yeah, I do.
More mushrooms.
If you touch a mushroom, you just-
You fail.
Oh shit.
Where did they come up?
It's 1, 2, 3, 4.
Okay, I've got time there.
Where's that at?
That might be it.
Ooh, does this want me?
To get one of these and jump in damage boost up, I think it does.
I can't see how the-
I have another reason why.
No, no, it didn't want me to do that at all.
I thought that's what it wanted me to do.
Shit.
One of these can see-
One of these can fly up and touch me.
Nope.
Okay, well, this one's cool.
I like this one.
This one's interesting.
Shit.
This is dumb.
I forgot about that one.
No, this course isn't too hard.
I love how-
Thanks for doing that, by the way, Nintendo.
Thanks for doing that.
Thanks for popping that screen up and making me have to hit A and then instantly lose the level.
Appreciate it.
I really like that.
I tried the jump, but I tried.
It just didn't work.
The dreaded sometimes you press jump and it just don't work some.
It just doesn't work.
It's dreaded.
When I look down here, I'm curious as to why that isn't Arrow coming up here.
Maybe?
No.
I don't think that would work that way.
I don't know.
I guess I could go this way.
Maybe?
That will-
What's that?
What's going on with my character right now?
Why am I like drunk?
I don't like this.
I don't like this at all.
Okay, it's in temporary.
Waiting.
Oh, okay.
There you go.
Sure.
Patterns.
I thought he was going up.
Fuck.
I thought he was seriously on his way up, but he was there for an extra quarter of a second.
I'm going to try that again though.
I'm going to do it again.
Somebody's texting me.
Who's texting me?
Oh.
Star wants me to play his levels.
Star text me your levels because...
My computer is being aware of it right now.
Text me your two levels.
I want to beat this one though.
This one's interesting.
Get away from me.
Thank God this is just a visual.
There's nothing else.
Whoa, shit.
That was close.
Oh boy, that last one really is just so.
So.
Buh.
Yeah, text me your levels.
I'll play them.
I might just do that so he can go to bed.
He wants to go to bed.
Poor Star.
Poor Star has been waiting for me to play his Mario Maker level.
And I just haven't done it.
He's there really.
That was happening.
I didn't get a good look at what's down here.
I might just die right now.
Can I box like that?
I wonder if I...
I think I can.
I can.
See you later.
That was...
I like that level.
That was really cool.
That was a very interesting level.
You can butt slide everything.
Yeah, you probably can.
Let me see what he's writing to me.
All right.
I got stars levels.
I get it.
You're texting me.
Now you just maybe die.
God, we get it.
You want me to play your level.
Blowing up my phone.
I have no idea.
I guess you just have to.
Oh, shit.
There's a lot of stuff going on here, man.
It's too scary to move.
No.
That's it.
Oh, my God.
All right.
We're going to play stars level.
Because this one's out of control.
Take him quick.
Sure.
Why not?
So...
Oh, coursepot.
What does coursepot even do?
How do you just put in a course?
You just go to Maker or something?
Okay, there we go.
So here you go, guys.
Here's your star level number one.
What the fuck?
Not as zero as in this one.
All right.
This is called Pound Town.
Oh, this is actually Ashley's level.
This is not stars level.
I don't think maybe it is.
Maybe he just didn't change his avatar.
All right, Pound Town.
Whoa, almost got me.
Yeah, almost had me there.
Again, again, again.
No, he tell me.
See?
He thought I was going to fall for it again.
He's got to be something in this last one.
No.
Oh, sacred blocks.
And a star.
We're just going to go up.
No, we're not.
We're going to go right back down.
I could have used that star.
What else is back here?
Let's explore the rest of it.
Okay, jumpy springy.
Lots of spikes.
Put this here.
Now let's go right there.
No, put it down.
Another little...
Ooh, this is a fly thing.
What else is over here?
Interesting spikes, a bullet bill.
Get out of here.
Look at this.
Oh, there's a little bit of a thought to do.
This process.
Ooh, I didn't really even notice that one.
Get out of here.
I didn't even need that.
How long does this level take you?
Whoa.
It's going to happen again.
Well, that was dumb.
Yeah.
All right.
Nice.
Very, very nice.
I'm not going to do that one this time.
There we go.
There's the mushroom I was looking for.
Well, now I can't get this.
You know what?
I'll take some damage.
Why not?
I'm going to go back up there.
I guess I can't.
It was the middle one, right?
Yes, it was.
Hmm.
Let's move.
I don't even need that right now.
I can just do this.
Oh, my God.
Why would I look over?
Why did I look over at my monitor to read the chat?
I saw a star set something in mid-jump.
I looked over and was like, what do you say?
That was not smart at all.
I'm not going to be able to do that.
Hit me.
Oh, shit.
I waited like way too long.
I don't even need to do that.
Let's just go.
We saw all the sites.
We can leave now.
Maybe we can't.
No, we're not.
We're not going to leave that.
We're going to get the thing that's in here.
Because we have to.
Because it's so easy to get the star and just sprint through everything.
Run.
Ding dong.
Watch out for that thing again.
Don't jump into it.
I come up.
Is there a secret up there?
Should I be aware of a secret?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
We have to see what it is.
You put him on a...
Oh, he's over here.
He's going to keep deleting things, isn't he?
Where does this go?
What's going to keep going?
He's going to break this and then what do I gain from doing this?
Nothing.
I guess there's just nothing here.
Maybe I could just go on the pipe.
Can I even...
Am I going to make that?
Find out.
Oh, yeah, it's right.
You go back to the start.
Oh, that's cool.
All right, well, I got to the end of that one.
I wanted to see what was in your secret troll pipe.
Let's do the other one.
There's two more.
So who was that yours?
Was that Ashley's?
I don't know how to rate it.
Yeah, are you going to do something with that pipe?
Is that pipe just designed for you to go run all the way backwards?
Or is your plan to put something else there?
Like a one-up mushroom.
Here's another star level.
And six, two, three.
Firetown.
Very creative with these names, by the way.
Firetown, pound, town.
You get really good with these cities.
You're going to do that to me the whole level.
Killing me.
Okay.
So I'm safe if I...
No, those go...
I'm going to remiss.
All right, I'm going to remiss.
I'll slow those things.
What else is in here?
Oh, whoa, easy.
Easy with the hidden block there, buddy.
Look at that.
Look what he's doing here.
He thinks he's such a clever little shit, doesn't he?
I don't know what that is at a wall.
I can't tell.
Is that a wall?
No, it's not.
You see that was very good.
Very good.
I'm a fan of this level because of that, you know,
that be careful.
You could get hit by this shit.
Very nice.
I'm enjoying it.
See, I didn't time that right.
I forgot.
I didn't realize it were on the different spectrums.
What was the first one come up right there?
I don't know.
I forget what these enemies do.
Can I destroy them by going like this?
No, I can do that.
Whoa.
Ooh, very, very clever.
Very nice.
What else we got?
Okay.
Anything else down here?
Get a dangerous mushroom.
Those are going to keep coming all the way, aren't they?
They're going to start exploding.
Ah, I got two cocky.
I got two cocky there.
I should have waited.
Two cocky.
This one, I like this because this, what's with the bomb?
With that bomb guy, whoa, whoa, whoa, what's with this broken bugged out fucking level?
What's with this broken buggy technical mess of a level?
That bomb guy came back and was there and ruined my run.
Actually, I probably just, can I do that?
That's very, very dangerous.
But it might be fun to try.
Do you, is this encouraged star?
Is this something you wanted to try to get people to do?
Is, is it one, two, three, one, two, three?
Now, I guess not.
I'm sure it's probably possible, but not a probable thing to get every time I would assume.
Watch out!
You need to have a lot of patience with this.
I actually was trying to kill that guy.
I guess you can't hit them.
I'm worth the shot.
Ooh, I just figured out what you are attending people to do here.
Interesting.
So you, you want to get somebody to blow that up.
So, okay, that's cool.
You drop one down there and expose the wall.
You can get the mushroom if you want.
That's cool, dude. Very cool.
Very cool.
And you got those shooting over.
Wow, you know, I'm impressed.
Doesn't do much.
Okay, apparently I hit that button twice.
That's the end right there.
Why the fuck did that happen?
It just went like, dude, dude.
Shouldn't have done that twice. That was the end.
So you got to bring a bomb over.
Cool.
I swear, man.
I swear this controller does like fucking ghostly shit.
I'm telling you, this is the, these game pads are possessed by fucking Satan.
I was trying to save that.
I don't need the mushroom.
Oh no, we're gonna fall.
Didn't do anything over here, did you?
No.
Oh, I guess trying to do the thing.
Oh, fuck, it shut the other side.
I'm just sitting there waiting for it to explode.
I was sitting there waiting for it to explode.
I was like, get out of here, bomb.
Woohoo!
Hmm.
Ha ha, I got him.
Not even to worry about that.
He can just dog him.
I do see this fish here, though.
I can't kill him with the fire.
Oh, one of the feet.
Hot feet, hot foot.
Okay, I got a bring one.
I got a bring one.
I just have to kite him over here.
Yay!
Alright, what weird shit did you put at Bowser?
Oh, I guess nothing.
That was cool, though.
I like the bomb aspect of it.
I like the character development with the bomb.
I'm just gonna get out of the cannon and start to flash red and finally explode.
Alright, let's do Ashley's level now.
This Ashley's is actually a town level as well.
We'll find out.
Watch him just really, really just get under my skin right here and just give me the code to a level that is one of the impossible ones.
Yeah, it's pretty easy.
Just give it a try.
It's pretty fun.
Spiny tank invasion.
You got it.
Whoa, we're already moving.
We're already moving.
That was expected.
Wow!
Alright.
So you got to go over, bounce, over, bounce.
Wow, okay, I did that way too early.
Shit!
This one's gonna take a little bit of practice, I think.
Jesus!
Wow!
I don't know, Star, I think this one might be harder than yours.
There we go.
Oh, boy!
There's another thing to jump on.
Oh my goodness.
Oh my god!
That 140 second input delay is going to try to be crazy.
And no.
I didn't even do it.
Wow!
Oh my god!
Who yikes?
Oh!
This is hard.
Come on, two.
You know, maybe I should just jump over that.
Now I did too early.
Did it too early?
Too early.
One more.
Holy shit!
Those are spaced differently as well.
Oh my god!
It's a B press B and you jump and it doesn't like to want to do.
It doesn't like to work its thing.
Oh.
Find the hidden blocks.
Nope, that's it.
I can't go over it.
Jump.
Oh my god!
The spacing on those is so perfect for you to lose.
That is an evil, evil, evil shit.
I'm going to get too long.
So you got to hit the second one on the last one, don't you?
I'll get it.
I will get it, don't worry.
I got it.
I don't know.
I'm having trouble with that last one.
I don't have enough speed.
Maybe I should jump first.
Yeah, that maybe.
No, that was unnecessary.
Jump.
Oh my god!
So you have to land on the first one, I guess.
What the fuck?
What is going on right now?
Why do I keep hitting the side of this right now?
There we are.
No, it didn't do it.
Run the fucking recording back.
Listen to me press the button and it didn't work.
Run it back.
You'll hear it and you'll go, oh my god, he's right.
I did it.
Check the tape on that one, you'll be like, oh shit.
The gamepad is a bad controller, it has like three frames of lag.
I know it sucks.
It sucks using this thing.
But until I get a plugged in controller, I have to deal with it.
Look, I cleared it.
50 attempts.
I did it.
Oh, is that, did I didn't do 50 attempts?
Did I do no?
Did you beat this one?
Why didn't you beat this one, Star?
What the heck?
What else is here?
Do you guys have any more levels?
Why am I not Skyping or in a call with Star?
The audio delay is so long when you're capping a console that I have to offset it.
So he'd come in and he'd react to things like four seconds too late.
I wonder if there's a game mode on this TV because isn't there something to do with like the TV sometimes too?
I wonder if there's a game mode on this TV.
Let's see.
Noise reduction.
Why would I want noise reduction?
I don't think this TV has any of those problems.
I guess I don't think it has anything for it.
I know that can be a problem.
What's featured today?
Let's take a look.
Scroll madness.
12,000 attempts.
I don't think I should be doing this.
You probably won't read this good night, Jerma.
I can delay the audio coming in from me.
But that didn't let him his head.
Look at all those X's.
Got a stagger in there.
Wow.
How do you turn off comments?
Is there a way to do it?
Oh, comment.
That's how you make a comment.
I looked up some tutorials, Ronnie, to see a stagger.
There were a few tutorials explaining how to do it, but still.
I wish I had an explanation for why that happened.
If I could explain to you why that just happened, I would block him.
Yikes.
Oh, dear.
Boy.
So this level with the 12,000 attempts and the 1% clear rate, I think I just wanted to see what it was.
I'll give it like maybe five or ten more attempts.
Geez.
That alone, I probably shouldn't even do that second the last jump.
That one again.
Is it just because the big brick gamepad has the teeny tiny, tiny little analog, not analog, the D-pad?
Maybe my big ass thumb is pressing every single button because the D-pad is as big as a thumb.
Next time you're playing on this big brick, hold your thumb up.
It's going to take over the entire D-pad.
Is it good that it's as big enough for one button for you to press?
Shit.
I could get there.
I wasn't breaking the button.
I'm not going to do that.
See, I don't have to, you can just count go.
Oh, I missed it.
I missed it.
I had that.
I was going pretty well too.
Oh, I know I should be using literally anything but the gamepad.
But I don't have anything.
The only thing I have is the Wii U, not the Wii U, the standard Wii mode.
And I've heard that's just as bad.
I'm not getting it.
I've already lost it.
Nope, I can't.
I probably could have.
Oh, come on.
Oh, stop doing that.
I don't know why I'm still doing this.
I really feel like I can do this.
Oh boy, I should just get it so I can take a hit.
I don't know why that doesn't work at the time.
I'm going to have to come back to this level.
Once I get a control, I'll come back.
We'll do one or two more attempts.
I have to damage this.
The whole way to land and then jump within 30 milliseconds.
I wish there was a way.
I'm just going to get that.
I'm not doing it right.
Holy shit, go down, please.
I'm still scrolling.
Well, I don't know what's happening.
Oh, I just freaked out.
I just don't know what's going on.
It was disco.
Do you see the disco party that was happening?
I don't know.
I think I just figured it out.
I think you have to jump into it.
Well, that's how it always happens.
One or two more attempts and then you end up playing for like two hours.
Please let me attach and jump.
Is the pro controller is good, right?
For the wheel.
Or should I get the classic, the original classic controller?
Almost screwed that up.
Okay.
That's all I had to do.
This is over here.
Oh, one of these.
I feel like a wow.
Oh, come on.
Okay, this is the final.
No, no, no, this is the final attempt.
Last one.
Final attempt.
Jump, please, you fucking slug.
No, that one didn't count.
That one doesn't count.
I have to get back to that like last part.
Very the one I was just at.
That one didn't count.
I'm not gonna say I get it.
But I didn't get it.
Never let it end.
No, it has to end very soon.
Before I have a fucking hard attack.
I'm trying to stagger it.
Oh, my god.
Add me to like the 2000 attempts to this.
I'm just speaking.
Playing these difficult levels.
Something about it.
It scratches some weird fucking dumb fucked up itch in your brain.
What you have to do it.
You just have to keep doing it.
I just have to keep going.
I can quit, I can quit whatever I want.
Really, really, really, really, really, really sloppy.
What I keep doing.
What am I keep doing wrong here?
That's what I wanted to do.
I didn't want this to be even more difficult now.
Oh boy, what?
What was that?
Holy shit, where am I?
What happened?
What the fuck?
That's the end.
That's the end of the level.
That's the very end.
That's the very end of the fucking level.
That's, I beat it.
That's the end.
That's the end of the level.
You see that?
I'm freaking out right now, that's the end.
I just did it.
I did it.
I beat the level.
Stop.
I won.
Okay.
I just beat it.
Very cool.
That was a fun one.
Yeah.
Not even hard.
One percent.
If only we all were bad enough to fall down that hole to find that.
Can I see?
I want to download it.
I can download this, right?
I take a look at it.
Because I'm curious as to like what the outs is there.
I'm going to put it here.
I want to take a look at that.
Because if you do it the right way, I wonder.
That's fine.
Let's take a look here.
Because here's okay.
You jump over this.
Bang, bang, point, point, point up here.
Watch out for this.
Watch out for that.
Oh no, we're going to be going.
And then in here.
Okay.
You can go down here too.
Really.
That's interesting.
Put it in there.
How do you make him go in?
I haven't been really playing with this particular part.
How do I get him to go in here?
Can I just like play some here?
I haven't been making a hole.
I haven't even had the opportunity to do this.
I guess I could just play test it.
Hold on.
Look, there's a lot more.
You go through this whole thing.
You have to do any of this.
Go all the way around this.
Look at this.
This is why it's 1%.
Look at how much you have to go through.
This is where I think you'd be holding up most people.
This is because they shoot the crap out.
They shoot all the spikes and everything.
And getting back there must just be so annoying every time.
There's another cloud right there too, just in case you fail here and have to stop.
What are these things?
Those are the chops.
Let's just do it.
Let me see.
I'm interested.
I was waiting for them to move.
Did that will they move?
I hope that they did like the launch at you.
Currently these ones don't.
Wow.
That's a pain in the ass.
I guess it's not too bad.
Yeah, it is.
Especially because they're still coming after you at that point too.
Yeah, I wonder what the school checked that too.
Let's go look.
You got the chain chops to deal with here.
I'm assuming this is going to bring you right to where Baby Bowser is.
Where I wait, you fall.
Yeah.
That's crazy.
That is crazy.
The underwater set will arrive.
Okay.
Thanks.
Thanks, Nintendo.
Is there anything else here?
That's crazy how easy that is if you just get there and fall down.
See, in my opinion, I would delete these blocks.
So you can't see that that's down there.
And I would probably even delete like these.
Just to make it so it's not.
If you jump down there, you find that.
It's still kind of difficult to land there.
I don't know.
It's still cool though.
It's still interesting.
Hard jumping around.
This was not that hard.
Very cool.
What is that annoying cat hand?
This is the featured one.
What else is here?
Look at this one.
What is going on in this one?
It's just a big long line.
Check it out.
I thought it was going to go across.
I have to kill everything.
Like that.
Okay.
I mean, I would feed a star's level.
Man, Ashley's level was much more complicated than that.
Why is that one featured?
It seems like somebody just made a line of goombas.
I was waiting for something to happen.
Goomba castle.
Koopa castle.
Mega castle.
What is going on in this one?
There's a gigantic gap here.
Check it out.
Well, 33% clear rate.
I'm assuming that a lot of people did what I just did.
And that's just like walk into the thing that hits you.
From the shell when you hit the shell across the way.
There's that.
What the hell is going on here?
Why is bother stuck in there?
Is there some item in there?
I'm Mega Man now.
Can I shoot?
Maybe I can.
Oh, this is going to do anything.
Okay.
It's one way to do it.
I get to be a spring.
Chalk this up to the things that make sense.
Trying just to get off the thing.
And a star.
I can't go through those with a star.
What's up with that?
Oh, that's why they gave me the star.
Okay.
I don't think I need to see any more of this one.
Everyone else, let's try to complete it.
Let's sake it.
Now that I know that there's no reason to do anything here.
I did.
They just hit this one.
Oh, God.
There.
Wee.
I don't think I'm going to be the spring for theirs.
Okay.
Well, we're going to do another one.
That one was very odd.
I did say I was stopping like 10 minutes ago, but sometimes it's just got to keep playing.
I mean, I'm still up, right?
I'm going to get big.
Look at this one.
It's long and it's complicated.
Start ranking.
I believe we've already seen this one.
But let's look at it again.
This is one of the automatic ones where you don't do anything.
Yeah, we saw this one, I think.
No, we didn't.
How many hours do you think it takes?
I don't know if Starf you're watching right now because you're like, may I?
There'll be those made levels.
How long does something like this take to do realistically in hours?
More than 20?
More than 30?
Because this is outrageous.
It's completely and totally outlanded.
You're able to do something like this in this game.
Yeah, I feel like I'm looking at a motherboard.
It doesn't look like a computer.
This hasn't stopped.
Less than 10 hours.
No, poor Yoshi.
Look at Yoshi's running on the treadmill so fast.
Somebody save him.
No, sweet.
This is a lot of testing that I'm actually hard to make.
I would lose my place hundreds of times.
I would get to a point where I made something like that and then something would go wrong in the middle.
And I would lose my mind and I just realized that that's Bowser's face.
That is Bowser's face, right?
That's a really, really cool good job.
Great work.
Is that the one we saw on the Mario Kart one?
It's a May race.
Okay.
Run.
It's a music level, huh?
Fantastic.
Oh, cool.
I could just do this.
Fuck playing the game and getting mad at all, dying and losing over and over again.
I want to just see people make music and do automatic fun levels.
There are over 1,000 comments.
Zelda song.
Let's hear the Zelda song.
That's cool that you can actually put notes to actually have.
No, I don't want to end.
No, that wasn't the end.
Come on back.
Come back so I can see the rest of the song.
It'll come back.
Don't worry.
I'll be freaked out.
Oh, okay.
Now let's do it in reverse.
Come on.
Yeah.
Let's start over.
Let's see.
Does anyone have a Pac-Man song?
Smash.
Look at all that shit.
Smash Brothers theme.
Which one?
Is more?
How would you even be able to know that was happening?
There are some people out there that just are very good at things.
Making a level like that must just be so fun for those people to make.
That's so, that's so awesome.
I'm so glad that stuff like that exists for everyone to enjoy.
Nice job, Matt.
No wonder these are like the most highest rated ones.
Don't touch the sheroom.
Did I do this one?
Is this the one that I did earlier?
Or is this a different one?
This one only has a 13% clear.
I'm not good at everybody's good at something.
I lost.
I touched this room.
Restart.
Oh shit.
Can I get hit by something?
Oh, I can get it down there.
Why does this only have a 13% clear?
I can't get it down there.
Oh, whatever.
That's cool.
Well, you made that map.
I know I'm brilliant and made that map.
If that's true, then you did that good job.
We saw that at the sonic level.
What was up and comes?
Let's take a look at the up and coming list.
Might have to backtrack hard.
Let's just take a look at it.
I'm going to be the first person to play this level.
No one else has attempted it.
How is this an up and coming level of no one has played it?
How does this level has a 13% clear right?
Looks at it in the leaves.
Yeah, I'm a contributing factor that.
For sure.
I'm just throwing shit around for fun.
Walking into it.
You know how it is.
I missed.
Check everything.
Check for the top ones.
Just jump on his head.
Is this going to be one of those star levels where I need the bombs to explode on something?
I feel like it could be.
Got this asshole now.
That's one way to do it.
Yoshi, am I need to get him?
I thought you could eat those.
I was certain you could eat those.
I need them.
No, Yoshi, come back.
I'm going to fall apart here.
They look like they could have been something down there.
Just checking it all out.
What else is new?
Oh, nothing.
Give me cloud guy again.
I want to get that out.
I guess it's right here.
I'm going to get it.
Yoshi.
What is going on here?
Okay.
Should I have gone up and around?
I think it's just a matter of time.
I don't know.
Come on, all you don't.
I guess you can't go up.
I think I've screwed this one up.
I guess you just don't get into this thing.
You have to go down.
I'm just going to skip that.
I'm going to go up.
I'm going to go down.
I feel like this person had to go to bed.
They made this level and they started it.
We have at least two or three bosses at the end of our level.
We'll redo it.
I'm not going to keep this moving.
We're not going to even get in the same.
I'm going to go up.
What the hell is happening right now?
Why am I running into all these hidden blocks?
I saw the arrow pointing up in the beginning.
That's what we're going to do.
T2 come over here.
Come over here.
Let's go.
What's going on?
I was just stuck up there.
This is what Yoshi is for.
Yoshi.
You got to go in the cloud with Yoshi.
The cloud car.
I want to make him angry.
I want that thing to redden angry at me.
Let's go get in the cloud car.
Why don't I think that's so funny?
I don't want to be in this.
I'm going to get in the cloud car.
Nope.
What does that mean?
He told me no.
I didn't believe him.
I'm going to be like, what are you doing?
What are you doing?
Oh, shit.
I'm not going to have any more fun.
I'm not going to do it this time.
Don't worry.
No.
What a troll.
He trolled us.
I will take one cloud car.
I wish I had stopped doing that.
I'm trying to do the song.
Here comes the nope.
Nobody tells me no.
I'm kidding.
Cheese.
I'm going to get in the cloud car.