Hopefully I'm not low now. That's the one scary part.
You're going to hear it echo in a second. I need to listen to it.
That's my first time streaming from a console. I had no idea what the hell I was doing at all.
That's my first time streaming from a console.
That should be good.
I'm going to have to watch chat on my iPad.
I can't have to turn and look at my screen.
It sounds better. You can still hear the game.
I should be able to. I hope.
I can do it right here.
That would be swell if I could do that.
Can I?
I think so.
Let's go.
I'm going to load up the chat.
I mean like fuck.
I'm going to add on my iPad for splatoon.
This is just Super Mario Maker.
I'm going to get like in a better position here too.
No. Looks like someone left this course unfinished.
It's up to you to complete it.
Oh shit. I need my other iPad.
I'm hearing myself again. I need to put this.
This was not well planned.
It was my stylus.
I'm going to get my stylus so I can do this.
Okay. So we've to finish this level.
This is Wii U. This is Mario Maker.
Why do I have two iPads?
I have Wii U iPad.
I have a regular iPad so I can read chat.
I'm just covered in fucking iPads.
I'm probably like microwaving my penis right now.
This is bad.
Let's do it. Let me just turn this chat only.
You can do that on your iPad.
There you are.
Follow the on-screen guidance and place elements to build.
Let's just finish it.
This is cool.
That's real cool.
Do you put goombas too?
You can put like a million goombas.
I probably shouldn't be doing that.
We've got to finish the level.
This is where you're going to put the bra.
Just like a regular Mario level.
I get you.
Fill it in.
Just like that popular video game Minecraft.
I'm sure you've heard of it at some point.
You can't tell me what to do.
Oh, hold on.
I can give it wings.
Can I give anything wings?
You can.
Let's beat the level now.
Let's do it.
That's undue.
Let's just close this up.
Let's get out of this tutorial.
Let's do it.
What do you want me to do again?
Let's just follow the instructions.
That's it, right?
There's the goal.
A race mode.
Just some just going through to see what the hell the stuff all does.
So now where's the...
Where's the I'd like to play this level button?
That's like the start.
Oh, that's what you can do with the start.
That's cool.
I promise I'll get this.
This takes me a minute or two.
That's what I did, isn't it?
Does it want me to put him here?
For...
Oh, I guess it wants me to do this.
I think.
Yeah, okay.
Give me the race button.
I get it.
I have to do it the way the game wants me to do it.
I can't do...
I can't be creative with the game yet.
Okay.
There we go.
How's your course looking?
Why not give it...
I'm going to return to the beginning and give it a trial playthrough.
Tap the S to go to the start.
Okay.
I was below through this.
Can I clear my own course?
Of course I can.
See?
I did that on purpose.
Let's get them all.
Oh no, I died on my own tutorial level.
It's okay.
Sometimes you die on the tutorial level.
Doesn't happen very often.
Jeez, what about what's spawning me in a random spot right there?
I gotta say I'm not that keen on using this big ass iPad screen to play the game.
I'll get my Wii U controller in my hand.
Okay.
Now, tap the course button to save your very first.
I don't want to save that.
These little sucks.
Okay, well, looks like it's going here.
Okay.
Ah, not allowed.
Not allowed to call it that.
Haha.
Three new icons in a row.
Didn't they have this stuff locked behind some type of nine day unlock system and then they went back on it or something like that?
Whatever.
Can change the game or day and night underground.
That's cool.
I'm not going to change the game up here.
Super Mario brother.
This is the new one.
This is the one for Wii U, right?
That's cool.
And now what does it want me to do?
What have we gone?
Oh, rocket ship.
You now go to the basic tools needed for the course creation.
Try different combinations to see what you can come up with into the UQ,
course elements.
So it just wants me to mess around.
Well, let's detonate this.
Let's start over from the beginning.
I'm trying to get my, I'm trying to look at my other iPad.
People used to, people set their clocks ahead.
Was it daylight savings time?
All right.
What even is this?
Oh, okay.
That's a real easy level.
Okay.
You want me to go to the main menu.
Touch.
The key to making fun courses playing lots of courses.
Sure.
Okay.
So this is where I can play other people's levels, right?
I guess.
Let's do it.
Let's see what these people got.
What did it just take for me?
Stuff is unlocked by pacing.
Yeah, auto almost broke the Wii U.
I don't know what it is with my dog, but he's, what the fuck?
That's, again, my dog and flies.
If there's a fly in the house, he loses his mind to a point where he just starts
rambling into walls and shit.
He starts crashing into everybody.
Thanks for the one up.
Does somebody make this level?
I'm assuming they did.
What?
Get out of here.
But anyway, so.
Oh my god, that was cool.
So there was a fly in the house and he ran into a bunch of chords and ripped the Wii U off the shelf and landed on the ground.
I thought it broke.
That's kind of cool.
See, this person knows what they're doing.
All of my levels are going to suck.
Dude.
He's got doors too.
Cool.
This is a green door.
I'm about to fall.
Okay, that was cool.
Oh, this is an official Nintendo level.
We're just going to go next.
Try Blung and Blow through these.
This just goes fast as we can so we can get to the most important thing.
And that's making a level.
This is Super Mario Maker, not Super Mario World.
Well, this one's the different Mario.
All right, we're going to go off shit really.
Is it?
Where's the door?
Where's the innovation Nintendo?
Can I whack that?
You have a double jump.
I thought you could jump on the wrenches.
I was certain you could jump on the wrenches.
You're going to give me nine tries to do this.
All right, let's go.
Blow through it.
I'll go this door this time.
Let's go.
People saying some at some point is laggy.
I don't know.
Maybe that's something to do with how I'm pulling through the connection.
Oh, oh, the Strayva is lagging.
Somebody.
Wait, this is the...
I already did this one, didn't I?
Oh, did that just make a horn?
Like a clown horn?
I don't know.
You can do sound effects too.
That's cool.
It might just be a rough patch of my internet.
It happens sometimes with this...
The router I have is kind of a piece of shit.
You can record your own voice in these.
Oh, my goodness.
We're definitely doing that.
Watch out for boo.
Fuck.
Oh, no, no.
I'm just trying to do the rush tactic.
You know, we're still going to do the rush tactic, I think.
No, we're not.
Let's just go.
See ya.
Generic bird noises.
Recorded voices only play on welcome machine, not online.
That's still kind of cool, though.
Help.
When his tip of the hat starts, it's tomorrow Saturday.
Ooh, this is Mario 3.
That's cool.
How many different Mario games are in this?
I did not know.
I actually did not know that that's what that was.
I thought that was just a little thing I could jump on.
And then fire went right up my ass.
Oh, I got to ride this, I think.
What?
What was this in here?
I'm going to hit him like 50 times, it'll break.
All right, we did that and do something over here, then.
I'm going to hit him.
I guess not.
Huh.
Oh, you pick these up, can't you?
You said that you could.
You know, you wait for the P block to come over.
What the fuck am I supposed to give that?
Oh shit, that shoots fireballs too.
That's good to know.
A piece which is journey, but I guess it's in the title.
Oh, okay.
I have to knock it up there, so I get it.
There it is.
Here it comes.
I actually require that.
Requires a lot of timing.
Oh my fucking god.
I waited for the exact moment where that was going to happen.
That's going to be a long night.
If I'm going to do shit like that.
Not even going to watch it.
Just stay over here.
Come on.
Come on, I'm getting antsy.
Don't, I hope that go for it doesn't steal it.
Do I have to go up?
No, I don't.
Yeah.
There we go.
Yeah, somebody asked about Superhead.
Superhead starts tomorrow at 12.
I think.
This is Mario World.
I used to love this game.
This is a fantastic game.
Okay.
I'm going to take it.
Why would it give me another one?
There's definitely a reason why it gave me another one.
Take?
Oh shit.
Oh fuck.
That's why.
You know, my brain was clicking there for a second.
I saw the stairs going up and I'm just like, oh no.
I shouldn't have done that.
Good thing there's infinite amount of them.
No, I don't even need to do that.
There's no reason to do what I've just did.
See?
There we go.
I actually just made that harder for myself.
All right, for it to open.
That was annoying.
Okay.
That was screaming.
Yay.
That's it.
All right.
Thanks for coming to the stream.
I just beat Super Mario Maker.
Game over.
I won.
Am I going to make an impossible level?
I'm going to try and make a weird one.
I don't know about impossible.
Ooh.
Something about the aesthetic of Mario 3 is just such a cool looking game.
Out of all the Mario's, it's probably my favorite looking Mario.
Just do it how everybody looks cool.
Wait a minute.
Can I still work?
Didn't this do something in the other game?
I think I did.
I thought I fucked that one up.
I'll put the kick it that way.
But these things distracted me.
There's so many of them.
How do you get them stacked like that?
Whoa, that's not.
That's weird.
Let's fly.
Whoa, that was awesome.
What innovation?
Seriously Nintendo?
Let's fly.
Here we go.
Can I get the one up?
This isn't enough for me to run and fly.
I hope so.
Yep.
No!
Shit.
Nah, it doesn't go anywhere, whatever.
I believe no, these are not custom levels.
These are the Nintendo official sample courses.
This is the last level here, I think, right?
I just hope so.
I think I got seven lives.
Lucky number seven.
That'd be okay.
Just don't even stop running.
Don't stop at anything.
See?
You just can't stop moving.
There's the secret to every Super Mario Brothers.
Each shit.
I just beat that like, I'd be like, that'll problem.
Because I did the don't stop moving to active.
Magic flute, I remember the magic flute.
The thing is so cool.
Sorry, your princess is in another castle.
What was he saying?
He's not paying attention.
To be continued, please buy Mario Maker 2.
New courses will become available each time you complete this mode.
There are lots of fun courses to play, so be sure to come back again soon.
Okay.
Well, should I just go back to the main menu?
Course World.
Let's do that.
Let's see some of the cool shit that people have made.
Comment on use courses, okay?
Okay, cool.
That sounds like fun.
What the hell's going on there?
Oh, he's doing sit-ups.
Okay.
Good to know.
100 Mario Challenge courses, makers, let's just go to courses.
Featured.
Mr. Chomp's dog house.
I mean, look at that.
What the hell's going on here?
Let's do it.
Mr. Chomp's dog house.
Okay, whatever.
Yeah, I gotta ease in.
We're gonna take these really slowly, because some of these levels are probably extremely difficult.
Go up if you want to have- oh, fuck.
We did it.
We already died.
What does that say?
Go up if you want to.
What?
Go up if you want an easier time.
There's another way for me to go besides up.
Oh, no, this right here.
Okay.
Oh, no, we're gonna go to the right.
We're not gonna go up.
Wait for the- now go.
Ooh, that was close.
That was real close.
That was an accident is what that was.
Ooh.
Oh, geez.
These hammer brothers.
This is- and fireballs.
That's gonna be hard.
That's gonna be real hard.
Is there a mushroom over here?
No, we're not doing the- I forgot that that was there.
Alright, so this is like one of the harder levels.
Where's like the your 11?
Welcome to Super Mario levels.
You know, you kinda just have to memorize everything.
You should be good to go.
Oh, yeah, like that.
Like that.
I should fucking memorize that too.
What?
Attack.
What am I doing?
I'm missing the most important tactic of all.
Are you serious, guys?
I would have had it if I had gone when I should have gone.
Oh, fuck every time.
I keep forgetting that this- that comes right down.
I need to wait.
How long is this level?
It's probably much longer than this, too.
God.
Alright, so we're gonna- we're gonna do this one more time.
And then I'm going to rage quit and play a different one.
No, watch out.
Oh, fuck me.
I never go into beat this level.
If you gave me a thousand dollars to beat this level in the next ten minutes,
I don't think it would happen.
Oh, my god.
I see I'm rushing it now.
They have fucking Russian.
Too much rice.
Alright, one more try.
I'm gonna go up.
We'll see if it's an easier time to go up.
Like, like, he states in the instruction manual.
This does look easier.
There's a mushroom.
Okay.
That isn't easier time.
Give me this thing.
Okay, give me the fuck out of the way.
Give me out of this level.
Let me skip the whole level.
Oh, god.
The cloud's gonna end.
Where's the entrance?
Shit, it's a door.
Shit.
Now I gotta do that.
That going through here with the hammer brothers is seriously, geez.
Gonna wait for a good opportunity.
Just stop moving.
Stop this thing.
I love a god.
They're all on the ground.
They're down, down, down.
Throwin', throwin', throwin'.
He's gonna start moving again.
Oh fuck.
Mmm.
You were doing an easy way again.
Nope.
You gotta have momentum to do an easy way.
Like that.
This time I shouldn't lose the mushroom.
Because I know what's down here.
Give me that.
Oh my fucking god.
What happened there?
Okay, how do I say I give up?
And I'd like to play a different course, please.
Here we go.
It's a cool level.
Now what else is there?
So what does this mean?
13 out of 44?
Like what does that mean?
I was right at the end too.
Is this underwater?
Jump or dead?
Okay.
I'm gonna do jump or dead.
This one's called jump or dead.
Let me get this like fucking iPad off my stomach.
I have two of these iPads on me.
It's causing me all kinds of discomfort.
See, look at him.
I'm like moving and shitting.
I don't want to be.
Let's see here.
This is like yellow.
I didn't play any of these old Mario,
so I don't know what the hell these things are.
Okay, well, I didn't really do much.
I'm confused already.
Okay.
What does that stuff do?
Alright, so if I can, I can wall jump.
I think I get it.
I think you have to just land on that one softly.
I think.
Okay, no, you have to bring it with you.
Holy shit, what the hell is going on?
Does things just firing all kinds of power-ups at me?
Alright, well, can I jump on their heads?
Yes, I can.
Let's just move.
Got it.
Wait, no, I can have wall jump.
Or do I?
Yeah.
I have no idea.
At least I know what to do.
This one, I'll just wait.
Should I bring this with me?
I feel like I should just bring it with me.
I think my life a little easier later.
I guess I can't bring it with me anymore.
Get out of here, you giant gumbas.
Oh my god.
Okay, that was weird.
That was very weird.
Holy shit, dude, I'm so fucking bad at this game.
It's like unbelievable.
I got it.
Hey, look, I picked up the fucking item.
Hey, you know those things when I told you about like having to be very like pay a ton
of attention when you're playing a game?
This is one of those games.
What the fuck was I thinking?
I should just like play, I should just like actually make a level.
I'm getting more fun than dying over and over again.
Wait, this is a dick?
Is that what people are saying?
Okay, maybe it is.
That's gonna wait.
It just like spits out a ton of things.
What is going on there?
Why does it keep doing that?
Alright, something's going on here.
Why do I keep going down?
What the fuck was that?
Jesus!
We're gonna go to like the little kid ride.
Where's the kid ride?
Is there, are there levels like specifically designed for fucking old people?
Let's take a look at the up and coming.
Wow, look at that one.
Three course meal.
Let's check out this one.
Actually, I'm gonna use this.
Forget about the We-Mo controller.
I keep doing like ground pounds.
Okay, that one falls.
That feels a lot better in my hands now, other than sitting here playing it.
I say that now.
Fuck.
So I have to break in my hands now.
Get in there.
Ah!
Holy shit, this is fucking terrible.
I'm so bad at Mario.
Alright, can I get past like the fur?
Look it up there.
You think I'm gonna get by that shit?
Oh.
Oh God.
I can't fucking play this game.
Alright, I'm gonna sound like a crazy person here.
Maybe I'm a crazy person.
But I feel like I have an input delay.
I really think I do.
Because when I'm hitting the jump button, it's almost like it's happening like...
Maybe like two to three hundred milliseconds later.
Maybe that's what's happening.
I'm just gonna tell myself that's what's happening.
I think it is happening.
Alright, we're gonna go up.
Can I like plug this thing in?
Just read it or something.
Maybe no idea what's going on.
But gosh darn it.
I'm protected.
That's really cool.
That's a cool idea.
I like this way better.
This one gives you the helmet.
Oh, dear.
How did I get through this?
I guess there's weight.
Just wait.
They'll all just murder each other.
That's perfect.
Okay, come on.
Get the fuck away from me.
Hey, look guys.
I beat a level.
Do I sound like I'm like one second behind I do?
I don't know.
Maybe that's what's going on.
I gotta figure that out.
Let's see what's going on.
Okay, okay, I'm gonna...
How do I give this like a 10 star rating?
Like I beat your level.
Good job.
How do I say that?
That was cool.
I don't know.
You comments?
Around the comments.
I don't want to let up the me verse.
No, I don't want to get me back.
Close the me verse.
I'm gonna make a level.
If I'm having trouble jumping,
then I can't really play Super Mario Brothers if you can't jump.
Where's the stylus?
What I do with it?
I want to make a level.
I had it sitting here.
Maybe in one of my tie raids, I just threw it.
Did I throw it?
I don't think I threw it.
Now, why would I have done that?
Let's go back to the menu.
I guess I can do it with a man.
Let's make a cool course.
Touching a me bow to the...
I don't have an me bow.
Then one me bow is here.
Okay.
Let's reset this whole thing.
All right.
I don't think I want to do this Mario.
Let's go daytime.
Is there a way I can extend that to?
All right.
This one's gonna be called Mushroom City.
It'll be very particular.
It'll be very, very difficult.
You see?
Start here.
Here's one of the stairs there.
You need to hit that.
And inside of that, we have Mushroom in that one.
And then you get that Mushroom.
And then you go down a little.
Let's clean this up.
Let's put that there.
Put a pipe over here too.
No, I just want one pipe.
How do I extend the pipe?
Should be able to do right.
I gotta have a Goomba over there.
That's the very scary enemy that you first encounter.
There's some bricks down here.
There goes like that.
No.
We gotta go back to this.
Couple of coins.
Mushroom, because you know this is Mushroom City.
You can't have it be Mushroom City without a bunch of mushrooms there.
And then we got a couple of things there.
A long jump.
Be aware of this long gap.
Ladies and gentlemen, you might not make it.
Now fuck that.
Now you move.
No.
Now you might not make it.
You have like a broken blue.
You know, just to like just to just to piss you off a little block there.
Oh, there's a broken block there.
Fuck you, I did.
Like that.
Mushroom City.
Like this.
Mushroom City, you know, fucking Mushroom City.
And there you go.
Ladies and gentlemen, I present to you a Mario Maker level that was made by a seven-year-old.
If I gave this Mario Maker to like my little cousin or something,
and I said, hey, make me a level junior.
That's it.
Mushroom City.
Very good.
This is wonderful.
Let's play it.
Oh, why did I start here?
This is not how Mushroom City is supposed to be.
Did I mess up?
Did I mess it home on?
I messed it up.
That it.
Where's my spawn point?
Right here, right?
Is there a...
Like start.
Yeah, start right here.
So what the hell is this?
All right, it's just where I'm standing from.
I get it.
All right, let's play.
What do you think there's in there?
Mushroom.
Yeah, now this is what I'm talking about.
Now this is like a Mario level.
I can get behind.
Say it's just jumping around.
What is going on with that?
Whatever.
We have to expand.
This is not good enough.
No, you know what?
This is how this is going to work.
You can't touch this yet.
Delete some of those.
Let's go up here.
This is really cool that you can actually do this.
Is this even going to work?
Can I like jump up here like this?
I think you can.
There it is there.
This doesn't need to be there.
New course elements will arrive on Sunday.
Okay.
Put a guy here.
For pipe right there.
There we go.
Where is the...
There it is.
Move this.
You go up there.
That's going to be a hazard.
Coin right above them.
The troll the people that want to play level lake.
Look at all these coins.
You're going to get eaten by the thing from the little shop of ours.
They have all shrimp in there.
See that they can't get these.
They are going to be very disappointed that they can't get those.
Good.
Yeah, just a couple of coins.
This is going to go up.
How much further up can I go?
Then you have to fall.
But the real scary part about falling.
As you never going to know what lake you might like run into.
Let's test it.
Test it.
We'll go from up here.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
I got a mushroom.
Nice.
That's a fuck.
I think I might have just...
Where is he?
Oh, there he is.
We fall.
See? What a hazard.
What a hazard.
I think I understand the basics of how to do this.
Now let's make a real level.
Do I have to play through the other shit to unlock the other stuff?
I'm assuming I do.
It seemed like there was like the other courses to do.
This is a...looks perfect.
Publish that map.
That map would give zero stars.
And people would tell me like how much I like suck.
What's the 100 Mario challenge?
I don't know.
Let's take a look at it.
See what it is?
100 Mario challenge.
You get 100 lives to clear 8 courses.
Take on different courses every time you play from makers all around the world.
Sounds straightforward enough.
Although they give me you 100 lives.
I don't know.
You saw how much of a catastrophe the last time I tried to play like the more...
The featured levels was.
Who knows what the hell is going to happen here.
So these are just random levels from the community.
That's really, really cool.
Whoa.
What does that mean?
What is happening right now?
I can't jump in that.
I thought you could jump in those.
Can you and I just...
Did I miss it or something?
I thought you could fly around on those things.
There's got to be something in one of these.
You wouldn't put these all here.
Right?
You wouldn't like these all that, but out...something.
Is that a fireball?
Is it a fireball coming right at me?
Oh, he shoots it down.
Okay.
Oh, whatever.
What is going to skip that?
This is a big smiley face.
You can go in them.
Is that Bowser?
That was Bowser and Bowser Jr.
Of course, it's too difficult.
You can press on it by touching it.
Oh, okay.
It's giving me the use suck.
Please don't hurt yourself in Mara.
Don't like strain yourself.
Is what it's saying.
It's like bumper cards.
Okay.
This is impossible to do somebody said,
okay, well, we'll be the impossible.
The impossible loss.
Is it safe and quit?
For what?
Just in case you can't do it anymore?
Well, for ten levels, hundred lives.
That seems like a lot.
Holy shit, I thought those were gopies.
What is happening to my character?
What?
How do you figure this shit out?
The game's only bit off like a week.
Get up there.
What?
Is it like a beanstalker?
I'm not sure.
There you go.
That was there.
I was wondering why the f-
That was an awesome level.
I wish I could give that one two thumbs up.
Oh, boy.
I'm not sure yet.
Outta my way.
I feel like I made this level.
Okay.
Well, that was pretty good one too.
Where were these before?
I feel like I found the jackpot of dumb goofy levels
and I'm not sure if I can find it.
So, I hate the water levels.
Give me like 98 lives.
I'm scared to go and get it.
More important.
Whatever.
It didn't even matter.
These levels of the people just spam the enemies everywhere.
This is easy.
This is really easy.
Why would I even go up?
I'm not going to go up though.
It would be a terrible mistake.
So, yeah, this is a...
This is Mario Maker.
This is very long.
Okay, this is kind of scary in me a little bit now.
What are the cannons for?
They're just shooting them out.
Why is this so long?
Okay, now I understand why those ones that were featured were featured
because people make hallways with spammed monsters.
Yeah, why would you even go up there?
Unimpossible.
Yeah, that was an unimpossible level.
Still have 100 lives.
What do you know guys?
Here's another fucking nightmare level.
I'm not even going to get it.
It's hurting my eyes.
This level's giving me a headache.
The star is here too.
Well, already been.
It's just a goof.
What the fuck is Bowser at the end?
This probably took the person a long time because every space is a coin.
Let's just go this way.
Can I even go anywhere?
No, no, so he got lazy up here.
Does there are a few spots where there are not coins?
I guess I don't need a bump there.
Who needs a bump there?
Did I win?
Is this the end?
It was the three Bowser's.
I think I got a star bait.
So random levels, you're probably going to 90% of the time get weird ones like that.
This one's different.
Let's see what the difference is here.
Does Booz going to fall on me?
Those doors.
I got to have Bowser in your level.
Like, he's just in here.
Make sure there's at least a boy.
Give him credit for that one.
That was cool.
I wish I had any idea how to actually attack Bowser in these games.
Oh, well, that's the trigger buttons.
Gosh, Jeremy, you sure are great at this game.
Over halfway through, and you still have 100 lives.
I don't know, Star.
I'm not sure if you can even put checkpoints.
I think you can.
Maybe in the older Mario games.
Get inside of the clown guy.
Make sure to go down and over and up.
I really enjoyed putting these arrows down.
Where is this take really, really, really, now.
No, hold on.
No.
What?
This guy didn't, he made this whole elaborate level.
But you just to be able to skip the entire thing?
Look at how this worked this guy put in.
All for seemingly no reason.
Yeah.
This is just all for show.
This is all for you to look at.
Okay.
Can I?
No, I can't even go down in here.
Sweet.
That beat it.
Goomba, torture chamber.
Maybe we can...
These are too easy.
Maybe at the final level, I only have 100 attempts to beat this last level, guys.
At least a different game.
There's another one over there.
Well, I asked for the easy grandpa levels.
These are definitely the easy grandpa levels.
I don't know.
Bowser's over here.
That's a very strange Bowser.
What game is that Bowser from?
What game is this Bowser from?
I'm like...
It's flabbergasted right now.
Whatever.
Oh, you can't go through it.
Is that like a DS Bowser?
This is...
I can't lose this.
It just spits these flowers out over and over again.
I might as well just stand here and tap as fast as I can.
I did it.
So, I beat the 100 Mario Challenge.
What do I get?
No Bowser like that in any game.
Can I skip this?
Yeah, I'll do the normal version.
course design
what a Japanese
most of those levels are made
by Japanese it's kind of cool
it's worldwide it's worldwide guys
new mystery must mystery musterim costume
cool
all right normal
so that's on normal we'll do the game on normal
so this one is more levels interesting interesting interesting
cool cool land
but this is where it actually is this is where it's this is where it's going to get hard probably maybe
maybe not seems pretty standard
I think it fly
oh my goodness
what a troll
just go over him
I knew it I knew it I knew it was going to be something in there
there's gigantic ones
can I go up I'm going to go up in the room
rain hell on them from above
at least this is like an actual level
I'm going to get stuck down there if I go down there on I
this one's longer too
and there we go
so what after you do this you unlock hard is that what works
let me listen in
and we'll sneak my own stream
so what after you do this you unlock hard
how bad is the delay
I thought I had that in the fence is actually somewhat on the more nuanced side
I like look I just looked down at the chat and I was just sunk to my death oh great
of course I wouldn't the worst one possible running into like oh I was on his head I was running his head
that's baloney
yeah I thought it's a one second delay but I thought I thought I fixed that in OBS I guess not though
get away from me
damn that's just making it worse
watch out for the bullets
actually don't even shouldn't have even gotten that mushroom just go go go go go go go go go go go go go go well you have a second oh come on
fuck I have plenty of lives
I'm gonna go on the top one this time
fuck I got too itchy
yeah because bringing in console footage it takes like three seconds or so before it actually gets to the computer
so you end up having to go in and do all kinds of weird audio delays and I thought I ended up doing it right but apparently not
oh boy that's that's super annoying it just launches you up you can't touch them
I'm gonna be careful here
I did it again my hand just like
I was looking to chat I shouldn't be doing that
I got plenty of lives I'm okay
I can play in fucking flappy bird
no I can't sit it again
wow I'm just gonna skip that mushroom entirely the bounce back from that mushroom ends up just launching around like a fucking pinball
it's a good idea to get it but I think if you just try to swim through it should be okay
well you know I'll just bait him we'll take it slow there we go come on come on over here
I love all they split into two
damn it damn it damn it damn it damn it damn it damn it damn it how come the bullets I did not know that that hit me
I did not that cake to go to know the hit detection because that was like an inch away from touching me
unfortunately oh my god
damn it damn it
hundred marios 100 of them
I don't want to touch that mushroom till at least these two are gone
well actually hit his head I will okay good
all right much better shaped than before
dear
much up for the bullet
they really want to want you around that is that's some shit right there
damn those shoot in a very long delay come on
get me out of there fuck you please
whoa whoa I did not know that happened fuck
can't as long as the over the level hard where's the checkpoints no just wait
don't do anything stupid you're already here those things can go through goddamn walls
come on come on move move yes finally
woof yeah wonder if I can let's see if I can do it from here
let me see how many milliseconds it is
all right I'll try something in a minute here
once I go through this I'll try again doing different a different tactic
don't know what this item does I didn't play this game so we're gonna figure it out right now
to me this looks like a propeller okay that's what it does
still floating hell am I of course
I thought I landed on them but I didn't say I just try to go too fast let's try to rush like crazy
I got to the end there I got stuck up top I didn't know the hell I was as a blue that one
is there was just a fall fast but this or no you just always going to do that
that's why it's dangerous to use it okay
I think I can hit this guy when he jumps up jump up again maybe just spawned that's
probably what happened getting too greedy with those jumps just see I was
way further bounce back holy shit that was good thing I got hit
Mario time you can do the ground pound okay cool
Mario three
cool we have a multi layered multi level let's go
good feeling I'm going to have to utilize those
Beanstalk
oh shit I should have jumped
that's right for the fucking assholes that throw the wrenches oh come on come on now
yeah screw you
is that a shoe it is it's a giant it's like a high heel
what's going on here oh that might be a mushroom it is in fact it is a mushroom
but not a mushroom but one of these things what is happening here that's the you
got to go there right when it ends so right
gives a shit about coins we're trying to like me the level this is a really good
one this is a really good this is a really dangerous one too though oh damn it I had to go up
and around and I know I didn't what I'm invincible what am I missing here oh shit right there
got to be getting close to the end yeah you can wear those boots yeah you can I remember that
for next time shit go the door was right there I should have waited oh that one was tough
that one was tough that was not that was not simple all right get it together here let's go
who cares about the beanstalk oh you need to go on the beanstalk I think
somebody bullets oh it wasn't up yet well that's just too bad
you know it's kind of deceiving the stuff like blends in with the wall I think like I can go through these sometimes but I can't let's take a shoe this time it's going to get it's going to get the killed without a doubt but this does go in the shoe this is not a good idea the shoe is a bad idea
I already don't like the idea of having to shoe on and I just crushed these things these I can step on these guys
does it keep you protected maybe I feel maybe I feel more confident inside the shoe
holy shit don't throw that at me getting there's even more there's more to this I don't know what enemies down there I don't know
to do I don't know how to fight that thing I don't know how to I don't know what to do okay stuns you he does a stun you have to jump in the air I'm assuming
right okay yeah I remember I remember these holy fucking dogs shit in my mouth okay we're good
something something something ain't right here something's not right here I'm gonna get one of these I can't blow this I cannot blow this don't blow it I blow it
I fuck it I blew it I'm like actually upset right now does it reset thank God
God he resets to fuck no no I'm gonna die and it's all because I had to blow it I'm just gonna throw him down there that's such diarrhea
if I just toss him down there what happens what just happened to me go get him did I get him no I didn't you just do it you break it I have 80 I've 86 seconds come on do you think
we break everything come on smash it all up I can't believe that happened that seriously so that's so depressing after all that that was like I
that was a good run I actually like got through that one I was tough but I walked I like I like pain in the ass this game dude who
have made this level props to you this is fucking awesome I got to make one of these we've
gotten somewhat used to this weird delay I have it was definitely a terrible idea to do those very difficult levels first without
having playing Mario for like five years shit give me the shoe give me this I'm feel a little bit safer now this time don't
fuck it up like a dickhead you know what a really cool part about this game really is if you're a fan of Mario games you're just
like never ending content you can play Mario games forever easy easy now easy now
shit let's go this time do not screw this up holy shit what the fuck oh my god hit it did I win I won
I won
I'm silent no I'm just gonna silently beat this how was I supposed to know that's what was gonna happen I didn't know there was a one
little tiny little dickhead plant in my way and I'm getting sloppy I'm just gonna get him getting a little
irritable I'm getting a little sloppy but who gives a fuck just go I don't even need the shoe
eat my fucking bottle okay what the fuck am I talking about it go I just got to be another one yes come on one of you has to have one you do
I at least I'm completing the levels right you give me some credit for that one this one I can't slow down here
now I just go now that I know that that's there I essentially can just skip this whole thing right like if I just
press this it just go down the tube right that's what we're doing go right down the tube you punk you fucking
piece of shit and god I don't know what's down here don't like please don't be a whole it's over I did it
whoo that was a good level that was very good level I commend that guy that was really really cool let's keep going
what do you say huh
another one of these regular new super barrio brothers we we you we I don't like this one already
don't ask me how I'm alive from that I don't know how I stayed alive I don't I have any idea
but is this level that you've created no you don't don't know can I not get out of here
this dude has made a level you just get trapped inside
okay let's let's sit here and just pray I'm just gonna wait for the chat to tell me I have to
like press up down left right in like in like smash through yeah I just got I just got
faded we have to restart I can't can I know I don't know I don't think you can
crap I'm too big I'm not gonna sit here with start over just whatever I still have 92 lives this
is not this is not going as terrible as I thought it was going to go be careful too much too much
air now that's the mushroom I can probably get right I go down here then slowly can I make this
jump oh eat I was trying to do the jump off that shit you know what I think they're all
baits I I really do I think everyone of these mushrooms is a bait so we're just not we're going to ignore them
I just squeezed my eyes closed after that how do I get that the first time
that's about that's much safer to do it like that so if I don't get that mushroom just go over it
try I can get that one can I can I not I get stuck in here I swear okay now I'm good
all right let's continue on I get stuck anywhere this is such a leap of faith it's terrible
there's no reason for me to do this no reason we're it's safe I don't know I don't I don't know how am I supposed to know
okay I can see how do you make that jump how do you make that jump how do you make that jump how do you
make that jump are you even supposed to feel like you're probably not even supposed to
now that way is just total total death I'm not going down I'm gonna stake that would be
spin dodge probably I think the spin dodge thing yeah that's definitely it
I can just go for up here can I look at I do it from up here I might just overshoot it I don't know
we're okay we're fine that was a huge overshoot but I'm all right
oh no you have to go around he did the thing that I did in my terrible shitty level
I need to see what's down here I can stand on that but no more no further to the left
I'm gonna get his touch the plant touch the plant pot I don't care
I do have another screen to see comments unfortunately it's hard to see it because I have to look
down on my on my iPad because I don't have really set up that well unfortunately
but I can't yes every so often I am looking down and seeing
almost halfway there I want to do something cool for Mario maker actual level
like that could be fun oh shit I lost you what the fuck happened to me I'm really literally
reading chat there's got high man made this oh that's what that's what killed me I lost the chat
hold on I got a reloaded chat there it is there's the chat
all right sit here in contemplate what's going on here
hmm okay I understand
coolest one so far that was the coolest one so far I don't care how short it was that was really
really cool
if that was that was that was pretty sweet too hard to is this one too hard to so this is too hard
one apparently it's too hard this one just called level one
so remake of the old classic classic level one that's something hidden in these some like hidden
shit in here no all right that doesn't work that doesn't work you plumbing is all screwed up
we're still on normal right we didn't just trek back to easy for some reason
well nice speak so soon forget it we're just moving in the jump
you
got these flying things actually not out now it just got really really annoying
oh that one that one this one's not even hard I just I missed represented where I was going to be
following there it shouldn't have happened trick not have happened again we're just going to go
with the jump forget about anything else I didn't I didn't want that I didn't want that I didn't
want to pick that up I didn't want that I didn't want that I didn't want that I didn't want it
I picked it up anyways though God this the easier level now this one's giving me the trouble for some reason
just do the jump don't pick up the thing wait be patient wait
actually didn't even see him go up that was dumb that was dumb that was real fucking dumb
what's the name of this level again like hi
so when you name your level high it means that you just like made the level in 10 seconds and you
just testing it I'm having trouble with the fucking test level can I kill that with this I'm not
even going to try because I don't know we're just I'm just fucking jumping over the whole damn thing
I'm jumping over the entire thing no balls yet I'm just gonna go over the whole thing
I'm not putting in those
get that out of the way
okay I said I was gonna do that but I lied
oh
thank god oh fuck
my whole body hurts from that my whole body hurts
like any more of that of that like kind of straight and I would have thrown up
you see how he's spacing these he's spacing them ever so slightly different
that was a nice one you almost got beat the end there
is this the go until I throw up stream you mentioned before could be
much how we got these fucking ground founders
you're gonna put enemies in my way you're gonna think you're gonna you're gonna fool me with that
not easily fooled okay thought that was gonna hit me
well that was another one of those levels where you just kind of run forward
you
run for your life castle huh that is
did you do what was that picture that face what was that big like face
I want to draw a picture like that
don't move
you gotta be kidding me
you're kidding me this is I'm not moving I'm not touching anything
oh my god that was fucking awesome
now that's the type of stuff I like to see that was really cool
that was awesome
all right
all right was this like a swear word can you get a hundred
I just did right I don't I don't know what he's asking me I'm not I don't know what he's asking me to do
you
going up
can I get a hundred what coins what
but what's that what kind of one up mushroom was that
see yeah he's got something over here yeah there is something over here
I don't I can't I don't speak that language I don't know what that says
just a secret door over there hold on there might be more things
odd level doesn't even shoot bullets
okay we got a shoe I think I screwed up I'm pretty sure I had to hit that
but whatever I got the shoe
well we'll move over here
oh okay what's the point of that
it's just it's it's gonna be a coin whatever let's just go
what
why did I just he just put random things in boxes
all right let's hop skip and jump out of here fall down this hole
let me guess there's gonna be an enemy in here
nope oh that was oh yeah I did that whatever
yeah that was that I that was I actually kind of liked that level it was really really odd
it was just odd
get them on hundred coins easy
it was pretty easy
I don't know that that could be some type of warning I don't know what it says
again I'm gonna assume I had to just do that
whoa it's just launching around hitting everything
yeah I should have went with it see I didn't go with it I didn't go fast enough
to know I'm at the mercy of walking very slow slowly
oh no no no no no okay oh this right in my fucking way
okay you have to follow it I didn't know that was gonna be right the way
I'm actually still going I can still see it
no no stop hanging on to the wall you glued to the wall
there's just going all over the place
so I just end up at the end I do
so okay what happened here these levels were difficult kind of moderately hard the first like four
and now we're getting hey watch a bunch of the turtles get hit by a shell where there's
level 12
yeah this this this looks like it's a it's like to level
who needs it skip the whole thing
three one ups does that mean oh boy no it's all right it's done I beat it
you were on your glue man shirt nice good old glue man
yeah what happened these these were parkour
you know my chic right now wow I move fast
is that gonna kill me is that gonna kill me probably oh dear goodness I feel like that's
I feel like I can just make it I think I can just make it I can make it I can just make it
up like that how do you unlock shit like that see that's what good cool I want to like put
chic in my level getting close and then I'm gonna try to make a level for real a real this is just
keep running the other one told me not to move this one's telling me to move so I'm just gonna move
uh oh I just
that was so many stars that was too many stars
damn it I didn't run fast enough
run this time don't overshoot it just wait for the cloud
I thought I missed it in fact that probably did
you get a transfer so there's like a relay race
what is this here for it's like watching my mom play Mario
you
getting closer to the last one second the last level let's go
what was this one called I was looking down a chat who knows
well let's go
that doesn't hit him
tune
okay
interesting
okay not do that maybe I can be going here
I guess not
how do I get up there
is it supposed to take that shell or something or jump on top of it
I guess I have to take damage I guess
so I think I don't think this is possible for me to go in here anymore
no I can't go in here anymore I I I I I walked myself out of here
so you know it's it's time to do
yeah goofed it up
I goofed it up first try the name of this one
maybe I would have had that first try if I didn't I didn't fucking muck that all up
like that I didn't even goop that all up
get out of here oh shit
come on I don't have time for this
that doesn't do anything
can run past that
why did I freak out why did I just freak the fuck out right there
I did I didn't think I was gonna make it for some strange reason
it's the last level and hopefully I unlock some more stuff
the final level very cool
what the hell is this mess of a level
I was just taking that all in what's taking that in
what's one of these the platform moves
what a mess what a mess
yes
whoa okay your safe as long as you don't do that and here comes Bowser
they're all locked up there 100 man Mario challenge will normal has been completed
all right it's time to make one
I finished it
I have 94 more tries to beat that yeah I know
okay let me see the credits remember that one hey do you guys remember that one
that one was cool remember that one hey do you guys remember that one
I'm for level one hey remember run for your life Castle we had to like run real fast oh my god
I remember that one remember parkour she come on oh that was so cool
mystery mushroom
you know what does that mean do I get some new stuff you've unlocked expert mode
expert mode huh okay so I get I guess just I'll here here we'll hold on
I'll do this I'll do this let me say do you want me to do expert mode and lose and be sad
or should I try and actually really make a level I'm gonna do a little straw pulley
I know what you guys are gonna pick I know it's I already know it
but through just for the sake of it doing it
let's see what happens
okay guys go ahead and vote vote vote now
oh
take actually it's it's that that's 50 50 I'm very surprised
this is as neck and neck as I've ever seen something like this
should I hate myself and play expert and not do it and not win
well should make a fun level please pick me
let me have some fun
expert is winning it's very very close
expert is so lame
well uh the the the votes are in
all right I'll do expert until I get down to like 60 lives
if I get down to like no we'll say 70 if I get down to 70 lives in the first like two levels
I'm just I'm just gonna make a I'm gonna make a level I'm not gonna uh
I'm not gonna lose my mind tonight
he's just gonna make levels that make himself feel good
okay well that's it 52 to 48 that was very close though very close
okay no game make sure expert is picked let's go
isn't gonna suck I was getting like mad in the beginning because
doing it with like in the first like 15 minutes of the stream I was playing very difficult levels
at least in my opinion and I was I was not I was getting not happy at all
now I'm gonna do that again sure
I was told to run so I believe that
I'm not sure what's gonna happen here but maybe I should just follow it just run right
I I I didn't just run I held up
I didn't I didn't just run I could have jumped over that possibly too
oh
holy shit what what what that was a wall of bousers oh just kill me now
I might get there again but what you I've only died like three okay that just scribbling
what what the fuck you just you're gonna drop down like a drop down army when I'm trying to run
through with a run to just run level that held me up for a quarter of a second that wouldn't
have happened whatever just run but if you just run I think I actually do have to make this
thing nope I fucked it up we're not just running we are not just running just run huh
what's the skeleton thing therefore then what do you got a skeleton for you want just to run
just wait till these things are all dead and I'm just gonna go down here and just start
this star right there this is the star there's a star give me the star
fuck no okay I'm gonna do that same strategy same strategy I already screwed it all up
that's over already maybe not yeah but
did that star down there is I have to get that
yeah that is the strategy that's the strategy I'm going with I'm gonna stick to it
wait for all these idiots to go I forget which one was it
I did not have a bunch of unnecessary enemies I believe it was this one
so then I after this I can just run okay it's this one nope it's this one yep
there's a spring there's a spring chill out okay I'm good
okay good I thought that just like I thought that just killed me at the end
that was good that was a good one
blade jumper I love Mario 3 oh Mario 3 cool just run
how do you even know that you can get that to happen is my question that's crazy
people are smart
okay easy easy I said easy I told you to be easy I told you to be easy and you freaked out
that was so that was so easy that was the easiest thing at that whole level
you
get out of here yeah and your little dog too
fuck it just jump over it fuck who cares jump over the whole thing
you're over complicating things for yourself that's pretty usual
hey it was not you there was no reason to do that I don't believe this I don't
believe it I don't think this is real I think it's trying to screw with me maybe not
too much thinking then I go right through I have a lot of trouble with those because you can't
keep moving you have to just go straight up I got it this time
you can skip levels no we're not doing that I'm not skipping levels
they don't drive angry never never drive angry and that's what I'm doing right now I'm time
behind the I'm driving angry just take a deep breath okay we're good move
fucking drive an angry don't drive angry
not like it matters anyways this one just go just do it you see what I'm talking about
you see what I'm talking about like you just like when you land on it instead of just
I can feel I can feel like my my face is heating up you know you know when you're like
feel your face just heating up and you just feel them in
somebody needs to put like a fire extinguisher into my face because it's fucking flaming right now
get up feel like something down there you know let me look down here no it doesn't look like it maybe
there is I guess not whatever
that was a tried and true strategy and I know no no no no no no no more talking no more excuses
excuse us we just got so ridiculously incredibly lucky right there yeah words can't even
describe so let's capitalize on it it's like you know sometimes why does it not just not work
sometimes that when we get it's one inside this tube is where it's really really annoying
ah I thought that was the end I thought that was the end I thought that was the end I was desperately
trying to find the end there you can't be serious don't do that right when I'm near the end
whoa there's more this even more to this fucking shit show thank goodness
they there's always they always try to screw you at the end I know it see there was a possibility that
I was just gonna run straight over there there was an opportunity for me just to walk right off
that was a good level let's go okay what I say like 60 or like 70 lives spin jump
okay spin jump I'm assuming you had to spin jump the whole way you see how he perfectly
lined that up to get hit right there don't ask me how I survive that what what oh my god jump
this is a paper airplanes everywhere to
I'll give you a spin jump I almost just didn't do it right there
there we go
I gotta beat these can I jump on them yes you can
just wait for these get the spindy little head and that's the end
oh
yikes yikes I think I'm gonna do it look at this guy don't like it
all right well he his opinion was heard
you
hold on just a second
get probably just do this real quick
yeah
I think I think I just killed it did I did I kill it no I think we're still here right
yeah we're here okay
oh no I don't want to comment
let's go I don't know what was the name of this one epic ghost house
let me get a feel for this one
that's what that's what's gonna happen
okay like there's another one why how else would I be able to get up here
did I miss something when I was like looking at stuff
feel like I missed something maybe something flew by
I know it I know it of course of course there's gonna be that
as far as it goes that what a dumb idea what a fucking idiot like what a fucking dumbass
yes
why would I why would I do something like that
I just I just jumped off the edge in an unknown level
what the fuck was what
epic ghost house more like hidden blocks are going to kill you oh my god
well don't go there
now it's over here right
gonna hit it again there it is no where is it
look at how now I know now I know now I know now I know now I know what's going on I'll be okay
I understand now
oh I get it it's not that one it's right here
let me took me like 75 years to figure that out now don't do that
okay I was certain that I was dead there
I
can I get out of here okay this is this thing goes so fast
I don't know I'm just gonna do this I'm scared I don't know what's going on mom
oh oh should I miss it I missed the boss I just missed the boss
that is crazy that is crazy you just have to get lucky you just have to get lucky and and hope to
God that you can make it through that
I hit it again I hit the now I'm just none I'm getting angry again starting to get
not happy again
there's got to be a rhyme to that right there's got to be a rhyme of reason to what's going on
there I just got to figure it out please disappear thank God
that comes down it comes down
they come down right there you know the really is I was gonna say slow down a little bit but no you
just you're just gonna take that ride and hope you can jump over the stuff
I don't know how to I don't how to avoid that it's a jump if I think it's a jump over it huh
I'm assuming you had to just jump over that because it'll just that'll
trigger it every single time you hit by it every time
well try to rush it
I tried to jump I tried to jump I did you hear the button did you hear you heard the button you
had to have heard the button I tried to jump my guy crouched
I'll have to like sit in a certain spot on it
and I said I could actually get back to that part rather than just like hold my eyes closed like
Mario was doing let's get right on the front oh boy that didn't work
no oh you can't hit that guy
shit this is a pain in the ass
okay so if I just walk on it no oh it's just going too fast
it's going too fast for my fucking brain to handle us
I have to jump on it and then run the underneath that thing and then not get hit by the giant
flame wake at the end of it and then jump jump over the guy's head I don't even know
I was not in now I'm just I'm just being a fucking dummy
oh only a few more tries at this and you know it's just all repetition
after doing this like 300 times I'll probably figure it all out
start the end walk forward I didn't do it fast enough
but the hell what how did he hit me
I'm gonna take this one down to 70 and I'm just skipping it you can call me the skipper
this one is crazy crazy crazy crazy crazy crazy crazy crazy
almost
oh again it's just trial and error there was no way for me to know that that was gonna fall
there was absolutely no conceivable way I would have known that that thing was going to fall
and unless I died by it like I just did
like that was just somebody just threw a fucking beer in my face now that is not a good idea
oh
or at least I might have this down at least this part okay I'll take don't take the hit here
here it comes oh shit
ah what did I do there
I did what do I do there and I just flipped out I just got to I got to
might be okay I still might be all right
screw you boob
oh
oh my god I had the mobar
I said 70 once it gets down to 70 that's when we that's what I I throw the
throw the skip into this one
at least I figured out this first part
although it's so hard to even determine what time it went to leave
I'm stuck here I'm stuck here forever
all I can potentially do is like I don't even know I'm not even sure I'm just gonna hit
this button just go no there was a flower down there I could possibly have gotten
this is excruciating
at least I'm not gonna hit by the first uh block guy
okay good shit shit shit shit
I'm gonna try to get this it's it's totally worth it or is it
I'm I think I'm gonna trigger the the fall I kicked it I just kicked it I kicked the damn thing
well this is where here we are
here we are and of course of course the creator of this level made sure that if you try to
rush this beginning you're just totally 100% going to screw yourself
you
got hit by the dumb easy thing that's that's gonna be it this one's done yeah
I'm gonna you know I'm gonna try I'll try the door I'll try the door
if the door if the door puts me the beginning of the level I'm going to skip this level I'm
gonna just pull up the start menu and say get me out of here
oh
whoops no one in the door
oh oh boy oh boy oh boy
stay with me stay with me step what
what the fuck no touch it I did it
I did it thank god
got it
you're not only wasted like 20 lives on that one
so it's called blowing blowing
interesting I had to go way before that I currently did
because now I'm just at the mercy of this
10 that did okay go I just gotta run otherwise you just get overwhelmed actually
might be able to get the mushroom before they all get over here
yeah I can I definitely can I was wasn't quick enough I didn't use my quick draw showdown skills
I would have had it if I wasn't such a fucking dumbass
got it let's do it
down arrow right here up arrow
easy though I don't I don't want to get see that's why I was being easy those
see this probably what I have to go down there what what what what what
oh I think I got not entirely sure what's going on but I can just go in this let's hope I can
I
all right I'm gonna figure this out let's try this
don't get it yet just in case something's going on over here I need to see
what
yes
um
hmm
there we go there we go
I knew what I knew what was going to happen I knew what was going to happen I
fucking did it anyways
yeah that could I needed that koopa
no I was looking to chat I think that's a yeah see you later that's that's a done deal right there
oh my god my head my head just my head just shook around
get out of my face all right now I need to get I need to save that shell
I'm gonna clear out all these things because they will tell me I'm certain of it
oh boy okay well
well
don't you come over here um oh boy is that gonna come back that's gonna come back to me the
community at the I didn't follow them shit oh no no I'm dead just barely made that so I
can go up here even though I screwed that up I can still go up here hopefully this will bring me
around don't even grab it it's not even worth me attempting to get that
bouncing all over the place shit's bouncing all over the place come on
I'm reading I'm reading the chat again I'm looking okay time to stop looking I was gonna
I was gonna just say say something to me that was gonna respond to somebody good no we can't
oh god damn it god damn it oh fuck
I gotta be focused for this one I missed it I missed it
oh
hello auto
missed it again you know I'm just I think I just gotta stop going for it it's just it's like a
50 50 shot if I'm gonna hit it or not okay that well that's what's down there found what's down there
now I'm supposed to stop doing that all right I need to stop fucking this up that would be great
got a better idea I like this idea much better
I I don't like this idea because I needed to keep one of those things alive
is it even possible for me to do this kind of no holy shit
just shooting up at me now
oh come on the thing is about to disappear that thing was about to disappear
that was disappearing as we spoke nope I got stuck got stuck
oh oh oh oh oh that was that was not that was luck it's all that was
get it do it yeah
yeah that's what that's all that did that was the point of that okay apparently that that was
the point of that one I don't know if I like do I just I guess I just have to I guess I
just have to go up there this was kind of unnecessary trip I guess
I'm not as small I can go down that room right yeah what I could shop anything
fuck
yeah I gotta get in the cloud I have to go in that cloud
cloud is necessary for that so it's get cloud where's cloud guy there's cloud guy give me your cloud
let's move at least now I know what to do this should this should go much more spooky next time
because I'll kill him and just go right over here yeah let me scoot that
okay such a goofball I keep killing myself because I'm glancing down at my other screen and dying
fuck me
oh that was oh that was great what a what a real not waste of fucking time that was
I'm about to rage quit this game and play like fucking iPad games see now I'm getting mad I'm just
fucking pissed off and this shit's just go downhill you know what I mean you know what I think
shit just go fucking downhill and you just I get real angry shit yeah I don't get
died I don't give shit about that guy maybe one of these get this dude I'm not gonna get him yet
follow me all the way over here then I'm gonna jump up to this thing got it let's go move move
I don't even care I don't even know what's in that thing this thing's gonna run out yeah this is
gonna run out I just have to jump over the plant I think yay at least I made it back to the place
where I was in less I can new expert wasn't a good idea
you
any expert wasn't a good idea consider just made my little shitties dumb shit level
listen all right last try is it
what a what a good good job very good good worth
get over here where is the cloud man over here I just want to get I just want to get a safe
trip to that next area
and then I guess like you know what hold on what's in here it's a mushroom
but you didn't imagine it
might have to give you a mushroom right here seems kind of like there's no reason to have it
if I were to take a wild guess it would be something along the lines of I'll take that
yes I would I would love one of those just break all this shit
give me those mushrooms give me the fucking mushroom
I want to tell you every time I say it's the last try I'm doing it every time
I say this is the last one and then I beat it
casual cheap cheap
cheap
with the name like castle cheap cheap feel like it's not going to be the most fair of levels
duck okay well that's that's
holy shit
guy don't even know I don't even know there's a lot of questions I have on this one I
slid down its own because Mario likes to hold on to the wall in this version of the Mario games
you need to let go Mario let go
I guess you just take a look at this
okay hit by the
cheap cheap
no you did it again don't tell me the fucking wall
I can't touch any buttons otherwise we'll do that
yeah
jump
it's such a good erratic pattern pulling those things shoot out let give me let's take one
second here to figure out what the hell is going on here okay they jump all over the place
I'm gonna have to do some wall jumps I don't know what's in that box but I'm scared to go
over and try and to do it but here we go of course it's good to shoot one right there
so that's that's like a that's the I want to troll you thing right you get hit right by right
when you land it goes
as long as I don't get hit by these things I should be okay at least somewhat okay staggered a
little bit there we go
just go do the jumps Mario please I want you to hold on to the walls this time
I it's gonna shoot oh whoa are you serious
what hit me is there oh the stupid piranha plan over there
well at least I know that that first no I'm gonna hit that
the first one is the is okay I can get that no problem now
first one wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait second one should be able
to have a good clear view here Mario please all right here we go
Here come the homing missiles.
One end out, just go!
And of course, the course that one piranha plant down the lower left, that didn't need
to be there.
That guy was just giggling to himself like, oh god.
I lost, oh god, why is my chattel screwed up?
What the fuck?
Don't stand there again.
Don't do that again.
Please.
I'm probably gonna run into the lives here.
But you know whatever.
It takes me a while, but I will beat it.
I will beat this.
I never played these Mario Wii U games.
So the way that he's playing these walls, I'm trying to do it like it's a meat boy.
There we go.
Though that was actually there, I'm pretty long time.
Long enough I think I'm late again.
That second one shoots a fish face out straight ahead.
You know what?
No, boy.
I don't know.
I didn't know it was gonna come out at some point.
It's so hard to climb that up that with those fireballs going at every second being
shot out.
That piranha plant is such a pain in the ass.
If I can figure out the fucking pattern to get around that piranha plant and things should
go way more smoothly.
Oh my god, and he didn't do the jump.
He's paying balls.
I'm gonna sit here.
Then I can go shoot in one of the time.
I'm gonna go shoot three.
There's three.
Go to billhoming missiles.
You didn't jump off it.
I don't like you didn't jump off that head.
You know what?
You gotta go quick here because you're gonna come these guys.
Yep.
They're just so erratic.
I should go right now.
I don't know.
What?
What happened?
That's a wall.
I have to jump over the wall.
I got right to the end there and I just had no idea what the hell that is.
There's a wall there so you have to go over it.
Right?
I mean, what the hell was that?
Oh my fucking god and it didn't jump again.
Shit.
Damn it.
Once I get to that part, it really shouldn't be that difficult.
I just didn't know that I had to go all that far over.
Give me a mushroom.
It's a fire flower.
That might have just helped a ton.
No, that's gonna get me killed.
Go down one of them.
I thought that was still on his head.
I didn't think that was a U-die position.
I thought that was still his head.
I'm just scared when I actually get back over there because this guy is doing her.
When I get back over there, the real just don't know where it ends.
Every time I'm gonna get hit by that thing, that's all.
I'm really fucking scared.
Yeah, now I just get to get to the game too far over.
I actually am enjoying this as hard on my brain as this is right now.
It's actually still pretty fun.
What is he doing over here? Get out of here.
Cashel cheap cheap. I'm gonna get hit by this.
It's been too long.
I'm getting something wrong with that, by the way.
Everything just went wrong on that one.
Yeah, I need to get the fire flower.
That is a good idea.
I can get three hits three times.
I'm gonna get to the end of this one.
And something else is gonna happen.
And then I'm gonna throw up the blood.
Fireflies in there.
I can't get it. I'm not small.
Hit me.
Let's go.
Oh, come on.
I jumped off the fucking wall.
Oh my god.
That's the worst part about games with a wall jump.
Sometimes you just stick on the corner of a wall and you're not trying to.
And you'll just watch off.
That happens quite frequently.
I actually totally forgot that that's happened.
God, he puts him in such fucking shitty places.
Each one of those piranha shooter things is in the worst possible position to play this video game.
You're in every single jumping trajectory and every single spot where you're like supposed to stand.
And they're firing at these erratic fucking patterns.
Forget about the firefly.
I don't need it.
I don't need the firefly.
What I need to do is I need to get by this without getting hit three fucking two three times.
I'm gonna take a second of one two three gets three seconds for them to shoot that one.
You got the asshole behind you.
Followed.
Oh, wow.
How?
You have to jump over one of those bullets.
Do I have to jump on a bullet?
Get one to follow me and then launch over in the jump.
I think that's what I have to do.
What a world.
Salt.
Yeah, I am.
This shit is fucking hard.
It's all shit.
I stuck too long.
Yep.
I mean, I'm already this like this far.
I gotta try to beat it.
I can't let this one defeat me.
We didn't do expert to stop it like level seven.
I did expert to beat this because I want to beat this.
And I'm talking and nothing attention.
I've already lost tire.
Here we go.
This is gonna be this is the one.
Number 33.
That's my lucky number.
Nice to call me that in high school.
Three three.
Let me show you why.
Let me show you why I got the nickname three three.
Because of that.
Show me this.
I did the thing where I left on a fucking wall.
I'm gonna walk again.
I'm just impressed with a fucking chimpanzee.
You know, high school used to call me fucking 31.
Show you why.
You wanna know why?
This is why he's the copy used to this to copy a high school number 31.
All you guys are gonna see why right now.
That's even the principal.
The principal was like, God damn number 31.
You're so awesome.
I was like, yeah, I know.
Let me show you why principal, the grubber.
Got one to do that.
Here we go.
Can't kill those with that.
This is more to see what that fish was.
I'm going to take a shower after I play this game.
Hey, you know what, these are calling back at high school.
I don't know what to do.
This is what I need to say about me, never.
I said this is about 29.
Fuck!
What they used to call me?
Let's see this coming.
Let's see this coming back at high school.
Hey, did I ever tell you guys what they didn't used to call me when I was a nice boy?
A number that they did not ever call me was 27.
What a weird nickname that would be.
A number?
Yeah, my nickname is a number.
No, no one ever called me that.
Why would they?
What kind of a strange person would you have to be?
To have that kind of a fucking stupid ass fucked up nickname.
I don't know what happened there.
God, this is so fucking hard.
I just wish there wasn't any more after that debacle that is jumping over all their heads.
There's a ton more.
There's a ton more just like RNG after that.
I don't know what I'm talking about.
Wait a minute.
Wait a minute. Do you see what he's doing?
He's shooting the wall.
We're going to take this to our advantage.
That's been the biggest pain in the ass.
Wait for the shoots.
Let's go.
That just made everything so much easier.
Oh, please shit.
Come on.
Why do you have to jump that fucking high?
Why?
It's like the guy doesn't want you to beat this level.
He's doing everything possible so you make sure you do not win.
Fuck you. Throw him at the throw.
Like a fucking grandpa level in here.
Sorry.
I can't get a no.
I can get this mushroom down here.
So that was in a weird spot.
Oh, come on.
Come on now.
God, I got a st-
That one was doomed from the beginning.
That was doomed from the fucking beginning.
I think I have 500 seconds to beat this.
See, somewhere this guy is going to watch this whole thing.
Yeah, I did that.
I made that.
I'm just going to be like, dude.
You're a jerk.
I didn't time that one right.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I wanted to go back and get the mushroom, but you know, whatever.
You take away the random fish at the bottom.
I probably would have beaten this like 25 minutes ago.
Not even choking.
You get these fucking random ass jumpy shithead fish out of the picture.
And you got a victory.
It comes to fish.
Both fish.
Yeah, first one.
It's okay, it's okay. Easy, easy, easy, easy.
It comes to full.
Come on.
I'm waiting for that fish.
Where's that fish that comes up here?
Does he come back?
These waps don't, the, the, the, the, what, what are these?
The stompers or at least they don't come back.
Fucking fish is going to shoot right over here.
Fish is going to show up.
Why did that other one go away?
That's weird.
Oh god, no, oh god.
Damn, I should have just jumped on the fucking first one.
I should have just jumped on that.
Okay, when I get there, jump on the first one.
Do not go on that other one.
You have to wait.
I could have had that too if I just didn't make that same mistake twice.
That's so annoying.
You have to jump on these.
That's, that's the ticket with that.
Hey, you had, guess what happened?
I could have guessed what happened.
I attached to the wall and jumped to the left.
Because I grabbed onto the wall, which is like an inch fucking thick.
You're all sweet.
Well, I think I'm going to get it.
If I can get back to where I was, I'm assuming that's near the end.
Why does that sometimes?
It's really, really, really.
Fucking, I want to get that.
I need to do it.
I'm going to wait till that whole thing cycles out of here.
Because I will run into that.
Of course.
Okay, there's the other one.
No, just screwed.
Yeah, I'm screwed.
I can't let this level beat me.
I'm not skipping it.
Getting that far and skipping it is like, no.
That's just like deflating a balloon and having to make that stupid fart noise.
That's how I would feel as a person if I skipped this right now.
No.
Shoot it. Shoot, you stupid thing.
Oh, go ahead.
A third one comes out.
It's over. It's definitely done.
Yeah. Now I can't even get past this fucking part.
Well, I might run into the lives.
If I run into the lives, then I'm just going to go make a level.
And not play this fucking level.
Not play these people make the levels are so hard.
They take like a hundred attempts to beat.
That's not going to be my level.
My level is going to be sunshine and fucking rainbows.
And where everybody, you just got to even beat it.
If you try hard enough, or now I'm just talking.
This thing's going to kill me.
Way too long.
Yeah, this is pretty much done deal, I think.
Yeah, this is my way too long.
I would make like a joke right now, but I'm just not even close to being happy.
I got to get like happy.
What's some happy things we can talk about?
Funny rabbits.
They're pretty cool.
Just hit me. I don't give a fly shit.
Give me the don't attach to the wall like a dumb shit face.
God, it doesn't have to be this Mario.
I fucking hate that mechanic.
I fucking despise that mechanic.
They're like, get in, get in, get in, hang on walls.
It serves to make sure we want to fucking throw up.
This is probably going to be the hardest one of this whole.
All the other ones were like, this is level 6, level 7.
The other ones were hard, but they were like,
like, completely in like 20 or 30 attempts.
This is still fucking doing this shit.
This is like a 100 attempt level.
Do it, shoot it.
Not enough air.
I don't have any momentum either.
This could be.
Oh my god.
This is the one.
This is going to be the one.
I don't know how many times I've been killed by latching onto the wall and trying to jump.
This is the worst thing.
Come on now.
Maybe I should wait for like one or two cycles for this.
Yeah.
Oh god.
Fuck.
I will prevail.
Go ahead, hit me.
Oh my god.
My hands are like sweating.
I have sweaty ass hands.
And that was a good run too.
Oh my god.
That was a good run.
And it just got like my sweaty, sweaty ass hands.
Just like throw up all over that one.
Oh, I don't have very many attempts left.
I have seen the same thing so many times that like by certs who think things are blending together in my brain.
I have seen the same thing.
What the fuck is going on?
Why did I just do that again?
Oh man.
I think I'm just tired and losing it.
Why am I over thinking that one so much?
Oh boy.
Boy.
Boy, oh boy.
Oh, I was looking at chat.
Seeing the inevitable.
Oh boy, I'm over it.
Oh boy, oh boy.
I'm getting there more reliably, like way more reliably than I was before.
And let's get a chill.
Come to the other one.
Oh, right.
The other one.
Pull down apparently.
I actually would rather be small here.
I think I should actually need it to be small here.
There was no way to go.
Yeah, I got to be small there.
That makes it way easier.
But remember, a bullet bill comes down from the ceiling because, uh, because fuck you.
That's why, like apparently, fuck me.
That's why a bullet bill has to come down from the ceiling.
Creator of this game.
You had to put that there.
You could have put like a firefly.
Thankfully, I got a bullet bill.
Thankfully, I can get back there every pretty much every time now.
But I don't really have very many attempts.
No, I just fucked it all up.
I got to wait till that hole goes all the way over.
Shoot it. Shoot it.
That's all right.
Nope. Oh, boy.
Yeah, I don't know.
I don't know if I'm gonna do it.
This is like 45 lives on this level.
You don't need to get, I need to get like the way you pro controller.
What if it hell it is?
Because I'm playing on the fucking brick.
That's like already like a hindrance.
I really wish I wasn't on this.
I feel like I'm holding onto a handlebars on a bicycle.
Apparently, wipe my hands down.
Get prepared.
I'm putting the other eye pad on the ground.
Let's get ready.
No, fuck. Shoot it.
Shoot another one.
Oh my god.
I didn't jump on it.
That quarter of second delay, whatever it is from this thing.
Is really, really putting a stake in my ass.
Big time.
This time.
The stuff like that should just never happen.
Because of this stupid input delay.
It's happened quite a few fucking touches.
Like, see, I should never be missing these.
But for some fucked up reason, it happens.
Where should I have like a 145 second input delay?
I'm gonna cry about it.
Let's go. Fuck it.
There we go. I wanted to do that.
That really is causing me so many problems though.
If I'm going to be totally frank.
Baby rage.
Let's see the chat fill up with baby rage.
Come on.
Stop doing that shit.
That's the type of shit that can't happen.
That gets me in a water trouble.
Okay, please. Please don't do it again.
Holy shit, it almost just happened again.
Bullapill don't even think about it.
What the fuck? What?!
Whoa! He did not do that last time.
He did not do that last time.
What on earth just happened?
I have to think about this because it's right there.
I just don't know.
Because I can't jump over that.
I can take the hit, but...
Jump over it now, maybe.
Gotta go now.
Fucking fish.
That's even more after that.
I was 100% certain that the end was going to be right there.
At least I just was thinking too much about it.
Oh man, this is very, this is very, very, very, very, very.
Because there's more for me to memorize at that.
I have to memorize that part.
Oh, that was just, that was just sloppy.
Oh yeah, we're getting real sloppy.
That came way too close.
Regardless, I'm making a level after this.
Fuck all this hard shit.
Your name of your level is this level's cheap.
How dare you?
That's okay.
Well, there he is.
There he comes.
Don't do that again.
Why did he didn't do it this time?
Of course he didn't.
And now he's up here with me.
Now he's up here with me.
Oh, damn.
No, I don't know.
I don't know if I can do it.
I don't know.
I just don't know.
Why do they have to come up and start throwing?
That guy has done something fucking weird the last two times I've gotten there.
First he stomps through the ground.
And then this guy jumps up through the little platform where he lives.
And is ready to throw an axe at him.
And I can't think.
Are you plummeting that you have?
Not at all.
Are you blending that?
No.
Get out of here.
All you fishes, please.
Please go on your Merry Way.
Get out of here.
Finally.
Please go on your merry way.
Bullet Bill is coming down here right now.
Nice.
I hope he doesn't do that.
Hope he does not do that again.
Alright, what are the weird shit that you're gonna do this time, buddy?
Good, he didn't do anything stupidly strange this time.
Okay.
Alright.
I just don't know what happens over here.
Wait for them to get by.
I have a second.
There's a thing to jump on.
Do I have an momentum?
Not sure.
Nothing else is gonna jump up at me.
I've gone past that point.
Except for those.
Mushroom.
Give it to me.
Don't know what's over here, but I have to jump off this guy.
Gotta be fucking kidding me.
That's it right there.
That's the end.
I apparently didn't have enough speed.
That's literally the end right there too.
There's a Bowser there.
Who knows what kind of fucked up Bowser's gonna be over there.
I'm like five of them.
Oh, down to the final three attempts.
I hope you're enjoying this.
I hope it's at least entertaining to watch me fail at this level.
Like literally 52 times.
Hey, I did it again.
Get back to square one.
Square one.
Easy.
Slow it down.
Oh god.
They've already moved over here.
Yeah, this is toast.
This is toast.
Unless I can come up with a miracle jump here.
That is what I would consider a miracle jump.
That was a miracle jump.
Miracles have seriously been witnessed.
I'm glad everyone said they pray as this evening.
Because that was okay.
No, he's up here again.
He can't even throw that far.
He can't.
He can do that.
He can do that though.
We're gonna go slow again.
That's the lie.
I want to try to get two hits here.
There's another big fat fish.
Alright, let's do it.
Damn it.
I got a way to use that the peak of his jump.
Oh my god.
There's a wall.
He put a fucking wall.
He put a wall.
This guy put a fucking wall up.
I just threw my app as on the ground.
I don't even know.
The guy put a wall up.
There's a wall there.
That was the end.
I beat it.
I beat the level.
That was it.
I won.
I'm trying to run by Bowser.
Everybody knows that fucking Bowser.
Bowser is like, you can do that.
Everybody knows that that's what happens.
You run by by by.
You touch the thing.
That's what every single one of these levels has been.
Every single one of these levels has, dude, puts a wall up.
Dude puts a wall up right there.
Just in case you have trouble with this level and you're trying to get, you do the big jump
and you're gonna be it.
Yeah, put a giant red wall.
So I have to jump way over it.
I don't even know.
I can't even normally jump over that wall.
I think I have to go over the top.
That's the last level.
The last life.
I've just drained my ability to even pretend to play this game.
I just want to make the end level.
I just want to relax.
I'm going to fucking Mario level.
Where's the camera?
Camera, where are you?
Stuff the camera up your ass.
Dude puts a wall up.
And now there's a bull.
I just care to take.
I couldn't get it.
I couldn't fucking.
Dude puts a fucking wall up.
It's a big red wall behind it.
No, it's just that.
It was that guy's level.
I'm gonna write something on that.
I'm gonna do it.
I'm gonna write dude puts a fucking wall up.
I don't even think I can do it.
I'm addicted.
I'm gonna like to do it again.
Yeah.
I got something for you.
How do I write something?
Zero.
That's the seventh person to play this.
How do I say something?
I'm just gonna draw.
I'm gonna draw.
I need to download that one.
What does that thing go?
I gave it an attempt.
I gave it my best effort.
Wait, nobody has beaten this.
Is that what that means?
Oh, that would have been so...
Oh, man.
That would have been cool if I was like the first dude to clear that.
I'm so depressed.
I'm just depressed right now.
Like, I beat it.
You saw me win.
The axe was right there.
I touched the axe.
I beat that level.
I mean, it'd be one thing if I kept dying at like the first part.
I got to the end, right?
Man.
I hope it was entertaining.
That's all I care about.
And writing a bunch of fucking swears on this guy's thing.
But I don't know how to do that.
Okay, like, band from Nintendo.
I was gonna like draw like a picture of you.
Like, fuck you.
You're a level of fucking sucks.
And then I'm gonna get like a permaband from Nintendo.
Let's go to the main menu.
Let's make it, I'm just gonna chill.
Just relax.
Let's make it, let's make it course.
I'm just gonna relax.
No, there's no reason to freak out about stuff like that.
Look at the mile level.
Let's go over mile level one more time.
Right here.
You start, you fall down.
Whoa, are you gonna make it or not?
Maybe you will.
Look at this, this is just good old fashioned Mario fun.
Where there's mushroom city.
Let me see, this is fun.
Let's expand on this.
I'm gonna start a new one.
Remember the time, German, was the first one to beat this level.
It was awesome.
Oh god.
No, he just, he just have no fulfillment.
I'm just, I'm just, I'm just fulfillmentless right now.
My little dog, you know what?
I don't, give me that.
Hey, good dog.
Otto will make me feel better.
So let's, I threw my stylus somewhere in that in the mayhem of me complaining about that level.
I don't know where it went.
We find this shit.
I don't really thought it was gonna be, I'm not really thought.
I haven't even eaten, I've, she's in crackers over here.
I haven't even like eaten one of them.
As far as it beat that Mario level.
We're gonna shake this up.
We're gonna make a weird level.
So.
I can find the stylus.
Is this gonna get me bangry too?
Where's the stylus?
Where's the god-have stylus?
You're gonna lose the stylus?
Really though?
Where's the, oh.
It's in my crotch.
It's in the fly of my zipper here.
Found it.
All right, let me put my feet up.
I'm gonna put my chair back a little bit in this.
Let's just hang out.
Just you, me, Mario Maker.
See Mario right there?
Gonna be making a couple of things.
You're gonna be doing an underground level tonight.
Gonna put some of these.
Put some walls up here.
This is gonna be a very linear level.
Let's go up here.
Wait, is that really my hand?
Look at, that's my hand.
I didn't even see that before.
I was so locked in.
I really thought that was my hand.
I fucking for real thought that was my hand.
It looks like my hand.
I swear to god, that's my hand on the screen.
God, what kind of like drugs am I on right now?
Let's reset them.
The one that I think about is like, why?
There's no camera pointing down from the ceiling.
Okay, she gets herself together.
She.
Looks like my fucking hand.
That's my hand.
Alright, we're gonna make this, put this here.
Why is it on the screen?
Why?
Nintendo love all things.
Why is there a fucking hand?
A human hand.
I just admit this.
Like that.
You guys have no idea how much I freak the fuck out.
Because you're my peripheral vision.
Saw that on my big screen up here.
Geez.
It's spooky.
Alright, I want this to be, I want, first of all,
I want, I want, I want, we want to be able to troll about this, you know.
I need to get the run through.
Delete some of that.
I'm strapped now, iPad.
That would be great.
Oh, I got new stuff.
Where's my new stuff?
New stuff.
Ooh, I do have new stuff.
Look at all this shit that I don't have.
Let's clean that up.
Okay, so we're gonna keep that going.
We're gonna do one, one, two.
One, two.
One, two, one.
Two, one.
Yeah.
Oh, it's sad.
It's just give-y-sac-y.
So they're gonna start the level off, and we're gonna have to run for a little bit.
We'll put, we'll make things a little bit dangerous, you know.
If you want, if you want to try to get that, you're all, you know, you're all, you can get it if you want.
Although I think I'm pretty sure that's impossible.
That's not possible to get this, right?
No, it is, it is, it's very possible.
Well, you can change the hand model in the settings, you can get it, let's take a look.
I need to see that.
Gamepad 3D Audio, notice the case course, controls.
Where is it?
That'll see it.
Whatever.
Alright, so that is getable.
Let's do it.
We'll put a mushroom in there.
It's gonna be real dangerous, but if you're able to get there, then, you know, good for you.
Press stick.
I don't fucking even know what's happening in my life.
What do I want next?
Maybe I should put something to jump over.
Yeah, you're gonna have to do some jumping here.
Maybe another, maybe like that.
Can you get over there?
Is that possible to go over there?
I like how you can just test it immediately.
That's awesome.
Oh, you mean like the thumb sticks, okay, I getcha.
Yeah, I'm dumb chump, I'm immersed in my video game.
Yeah, that's real dangerous.
Good.
I wonder if you can even get over this.
Can I even beat my own level?
Probably not.
Yeah, you can get over that.
Very nice.
Click the gamepad stick.
Hey, look at that.
Oh, what?
What else is there?
Cat ball.
Only Nintendo would do something like that.
All right, let me go back to this.
Okay, we're gonna put a secret.
Right at the, don't tell anybody.
But right at the beginning of the level.
You can go up here.
And there's gonna be a bunch of secret shit up here.
You know, you're gonna win the game if you come up here.
Yeah, like here already.
This is just gonna be a straight line to the pull.
That you'll never know unless you were watching this stream.
Yeah, that's Mario's hand.
That was in trouble right now.
So see, it's a guaranteed win.
There you go, guaranteed win.
Get rid of that.
I'm gonna put this higher.
Let's put it here.
Is that like just out of reach?
Let's find out.
It is just real average.
That's so obvious.
That is so obvious.
Looks crap in that.
That is like the easiest thing I've ever seen.
It's so obvious.
Look, keep it there.
It's right now though.
Just because it decided to go against it.
Okay.
Let's put.
I'm gonna have some coins.
Three, two, three.
What does this little shithead do again?
How bad.
How hard is this jump?
You slip around a little bit.
Yeah, you can do it.
It's doable.
No hidden blocks.
No, no hidden blocks.
I want you to think they're hidden blocks.
Okay.
Danger mushroom right there.
Dangerous.
Wait, under.
No redo.
There is no redo.
Oops.
Okay.
Now I need to have like somewhat of a normal little bit here.
Maybe one, maybe one more like jump.
That's really annoying to do.
And then we take this.
Oh, the way like that.
Up with it.
This.
I'm gonna do the thing where it's levels over, but.
That's what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna do it.
Replace these with this to make it so much more obvious that it's the end of the level.
Fix that in a second.
There we are.
Just like that.
Oh, what a doozy.
What a doozy.
Do you see this doozy?
You know what?
I'll put this one.
You can't beat my level.
This is the end.
Just kidding.
You got to break this.
Oh, wow.
What are you gonna talk about?
A crazy twist.
I'm gonna get the twist right here, guys.
Gotta get that mushroom back here.
I really think you're gonna be able to get that mushroom.
Otherwise, you're a toast.
You gonna do it again?
Got the mushroom.
Pretty hard.
Pretty difficult.
Let's try it again.
It's not quite there yet, but...
See, I know the secret to that one because I made it.
I'm the creator of this level, so I know all the secrets and nuances and how everything works.
See, you get to here.
Oh, yeah, oh, yeah.
Oh, don't worry.
You're good.
Next part of the level.
Just to be a real prick about things.
Just to make sure you don't...
You don't have chance.
I wish I had more stuff.
Okay.
Put a couple of these here.
Yeah, why not?
This is where it gets dangerous.
Oh, that's not the end.
A little bit more.
Not that much, but...
Well, he sure got me.
Didn't I do it?
So now we're gonna put the one here.
Can you mess with the timers on these things?
Can I determine when this is gonna pop up?
What the fuck just happened?
What's going on?
My battery died on my Wii U gamepad.
I can't say I don't know what's happening.
Hold on, let me plug it in.
Hold on.
This thing died.
I wonder why it died.
Maybe because I played like an hour and ten minutes on the same level.
Um.
Can I do it with a Wii U?
If I can just do it like this, I don't care.
Nope, I cannot.
I can move them around, but I can't actually use the Wii U.
Let me just plug it in.
One second, guys.
One second.
Oh.
Oh, hell.
What's that?
Wii U gamepad.
I'm not a battery life.
Oh.
Do I have an open outlet I can put this in?
Oh, so otherwise...
I might have to just play more levels because that's how I can really do.
I'm not a gamepad.
What a great stream that's going on right now.
You got a guy that doesn't even charge his batteries on his Wii U gamepad.
I'd like to punch that guy in his face.
Alright, we got some juice.
I turn it back on.
Uh, go ahead.
Hey, we have life.
Look at that.
Now I can move.
What's my question was, can you determine the timers on these guys?
Notification settings, manual.
Maybe not.
Can you?
Let me get my second iPad to see what people are saying.
Stick a fucking outlet, please.
Alright, let's do it.
A couple more of those.
I put way too much orange juice on this gamepad.
I probably shouldn't have tried to pour orange juice on my gamepad.
That probably would have helped.
I don't even win.
This one will just be sitting there.
Move this one down so you think you're safe.
But you just have no idea.
Too much.
Oh, what it could do is, you know what, you're just safe.
No, no, no, no, hold on, hold on a second.
Hold on just for one second here, man.
You think you died when you fell?
We give people second chances here.
That comes up like this.
But because you got a second chance, you're going to deal with all this shit.
You do get a second chance, but you better make a count.
How noticeable is that?
Is that really noticeable?
Let's find out.
Let's go.
I'm not going to move this.
Alright, let's do it.
Let's see what happens here.
So they are random.
Kind of, right?
Where did this one go?
Let's go with the mod.
No, you can see them.
I'm going to take away the wings.
I think if the wings are, so no.
They probably wings are.
If anybody have wings, this boom is got wings.
Okay, now you shouldn't be able to see them.
Wow, real exciting stuff.
Can you still see them?
Move those up a little.
Just in case.
Alright.
This is going to lead up to here.
There are a bunch of coins.
If you made it this far, congratulations.
Here are some coins.
You win.
And then if you can see up here, there's going to be...
Smiley stones.
Let's try it.
Let's just take a look.
Take a gander at it.
Alright.
Play.
It's kind of no reason for the mushroom.
I broke the room.
What the...oh boy.
Oh, I can't do it now.
I can't beat the level.
That's when you go, what the hell?
What a dick.
Start.
Whoops.
Knicks ago.
The reason for the coins either at this point.
And you can just walk over that.
I just realized.
Made it through Phase 1.
Oh, Phase 2.
Oh no.
I made it to the end.
I win.
Holy shit.
That was kind of a hard jump.
Let's make the mushroom impossible to get.
Let's be real mean.
Let's be real mean about it.
Maybe she should just be right there.
What does the sound effects for you?
What is going on in the background there?
How do I make that so it's harder to get?
Hmm.
Maybe.
Let's see.
That's a little bit harder.
That was a really weird mushroom.
I'm going to get rid of this too.
So you're going to get that mid jump.
Oh yeah, yeah.
Hold on a second.
Wait just a second here.
Get rid of all of this.
You're going to go mid jump.
Where do you end up?
Right there.
Actually, even further jump.
Now it comes out too fast.
Bang.
Right there.
Getting carried away.
Oh, that's cool.
That's cool.
Now, fucking fell off.
Is there a way?
I wish I had a way to mess with this guy's behavior, huh?
I guess I could just do this.
That's easy enough.
Let's try that.
Is he going to jump?
So, yeah, you missed that mushroom.
You got to start over again.
Maybe I'll do like...
Okay.
Might be a little too much.
Maybe.
And then you can use that to jump up here.
Alright.
I'm going to go to the green shell.
Make them a red shell, it's Koopa.
Shake the Koopa to make him turn right.
Usually coins do.
Guess not.
Oh, where are you going to?
You don't have to do that.
You're right.
You're right, chatter.
I don't know if I do this.
It's still possible.
It's definitely still possible.
Okay, but even higher.
That might be too high to even hit.
There we are.
No, you have to do that.
Got a time it right.
Oh, I see, I can't even time it.
I like it.
I wish I could put more things in here.
I would put this all around being able to do jumps like that.
Alright, so we can get rid of this now.
The reds walk up the edge.
Sounds like plan.
I put a couple over there.
I'm not going to put like...
You do two.
No, one.
We'll do one with one.
Let's go.
Moving backwards too much.
Not enough momentum.
I like this.
Alright, this works.
Yeah, see, and I get screwed up with those guys.
You can save, right?
Because I want to actually get items and use them.
Like a saw blade come across here.
I have just like bullet bills shooting this direction.
No, that's good enough.
Oh no, I got to the end.
I can't get out of here.
Can you get the mushroom go back and just do the jump a second time?
I don't think so.
I mean, a baby you can, but it's kind of hard.
Trying to replicate what you're asking.
Yeah, I guess you can.
Is it time to remove this?
Is that still?
Is that doable?
What the hell is this mushroom doing?
I can throw the mushroom out of it.
Shaking this doesn't do much.
Why is that?
I can't turn it into one up.
I don't even know if this is still possible.
I don't know, now that it's there, I might have to move it a little forward a little bit.
Try to a couple more times.
Yeah, I'm going to have to move it.
Not to move it.
One more block this way.
That's a month.
Put a brick over the first two open bricks so you can only run and build a momentum.
That's not a bad idea.
Oops.
Yeah, you've just barely made it.
All right, now I have to test to make sure you can't go backwards.
Can you get this and still come back?
No, not really.
Maybe you're saying like put one here.
Let's try it.
I could spend all day doing this if I had more things.
You can turn Mario into a Luigi.
You make him bigger, small.
I just wish I could put more of these things.
I can't really do much.
So I have to move my like a wee clock forward.
Is that what I have to do?
Apparently.
Maybe for next time.
I like to put much more hazards and things here, but there's not very much to start off with.
Save this though.
Wait a second.
Who's there?
If you frustrate your players and the first jump, your level is not going to rate well.
I'll tweak it.
I'll tweak this in some other day.
Make much of junk blocks.
What is this thing even do?
Random property?
Whatever.
You unlock more by beating other people's levels.
I beat a bunch earlier.
I can get some more stuff unlocked.
It's about no.
I'll play in a little string of levels.
I'm going to go to bed.
I don't want to get something interesting done with it.
I've been playing that multiple times.
But not so terrible that you end up like I was yelling at things.
To be fair though, that level of that guy made was pretty damn good.
Alright, 10 Mario Challenge.
Can I do this one on normal or expert or something?
No.
You know that I've had some time to warm up a little bit.
I want to go.
We'll try one of the good featured ones.
I was all over the place earlier this evening.
So there's only a 20 to 20.
2.37% clear.
So no, maybe I wasn't crazy.
This is just extremely difficult.
Only 15 people have beaten it at a 632 times or 632 people.
That's kind of crazy.
Let's go back.
Where's one with like a 20% or 10% or something?
Alright, one shell.
This is a 1% clear ratio.
Damn, by star ranking.
Don't press anything.
I played that one before, didn't I?
Look at how many ratings this has.
Don't press anything too.
Press right, run and enjoy.
Let's do that one.
53, you can apparently still not beat this one.
Let's go for it.
I need to.
Alright, press right.
I was holding right.
I did something wrong.
Look at all the deaths.
A ton of people died there.
It says something.
He's in a car.
I'm in a little go-cart.
Think about how long this stuff can make.
Mario in a go-cart.
I'm in a straight.
Then a bunch of cool things happen around you.
They're like I'm playing braid.
This is so cool.
Damn, man.
Some people are just super, super crazy creative.
That was awesome.
That was so cool.
What else is there?
Well, the pyro.
That was maybe the pyro.
Alright, what about...
What about don't press anything?
This is the highest rated thing.
We already saw a version of this, didn't we?
Let's check out this one.
Don't press anything.
What is even happening?
How did you even...
The program...
Look at that look at that close here.
The coolest roller coaster.
Smart.
Weee.
This is no way this person doesn't have an engineering degree.
The person that made this level has a PhD in mechanical engineering.
What else is there? How do you fail that? You just have to just move.
40% clear right? That means like 60% of the people just walking around trying to jump.
Okay this is don't press anything too. It's by the same guy.
Yeah, I think it's the same guy right? Let's see how good the sequel is.
Did I just get a cat paw?
Okay that was cool. That was really cool.
Is it good? Is it good? Is it good? I'm pretty sure that's a dick.
Otherwise he has three hands. No, that was too armed. No, that's not.
Hardy time. Bring the disco. So what do you call him?
Who was never touching him? I didn't walk right there.
Cool.
I like those. I was watching a little short. That was like watching a movie.
I watched a little TV show. Mario TV show.
What else is there? Splatoon.
This has a 60% clear right? Let's play this one. Do I get to move in this one?
Do I get to play the game in this one? We'll find out.
Your squid now. Now a little squid.
And those would like to be Mario. It's kind of like text huh?
I really am a squid.
So cute.
Hello out.
So what happens? How does so many text does?
Need to draw that?
Let's get real looking entire comic book.
Look at this. Just dude has a whole graphic novel in here.
I'm trying to know I'm going just the wrong way. I'm reading his.
I'm stuck in here. I'm stuck in here. I'm gonna lose. I'm gonna lose to the
Yura squid level.
No, not. I have the power of the cat to protect me.
There's that one up.
This one. What can I write a comment?
How do I write a comment here?
Oh no, Bowser. Oh shit.
Now there's an actual game here.
I must try. I'm like just reading what the purple is saying. Look at all those deaths.
I need to write something. I need to write like. I need to write.
I'll about.
God, I'm just gonna write in all capitals.
Cuity pot.
Makes it go.
Well, I died in that one because I'm reading all the weird text.
Don't touch the shrooms.
Sonic 1.
All right, I gotta check this one out.
This is apparently Sonic the Hedgehog.
Wait, I should probably pick. I should get that.
So hold on a second. Wait a minute. Wait a minute. Wait a minute. Go back.
I can't wait.
Sonic the Hedgehog is in the game.
Did that dude upload that or is that in this video game?
That's Sonic the fucking Hedgehog in this game.
I'm confused, but I don't know. I don't understand. That's interesting to say the least.
That's surprising.
Oh, is it a mebo? It's an amoebo.
Here it begins the memes.
You're all right about that.
I thought he was a bush. He wasn't rolling.
Yeah, what I fell to.
I hate the dude. Come on. Step it up.
It has the ring sound too.
Yikes.
Let me jump on these things.
Run.
Okay.
Did you just say Pac-Man is in this game?
Pac-Man is in the game.
Where is he?
Where is he and how do I get him?
That's unbelievable.
I tied away search for Pac-Man.
Metroid.
Donkey Kong.
No, no, no. Give me a Pac-Man level.
Featured. Search. Here we go. Pac-Man.
Pac-Man.
Okay.
Of course not.
Oh, this is...
No, that's like a code.
Like a friend code.
Top right.
Get a go get a Pac-Man of Bebo.
Look at this. Look at some popular rankings here.
Look at that. Those are the two guys that have the most popular thing, huh?
Mega Man's in it.
That's really, really, really cool.
All right. What are some of these levels?
Somebody was saying I should play a certain person's level.
And I couldn't... I don't remember who it was.
There were a lot of people.
Who's levels were you guys all saying to play?
Or somebody? So was it this guy?
Ross the suit?
Yeah, everyone was saying to play this guy's levels.
Okay.
We're gonna go with please dance.
Sure. Let's play please dance.
Not bad. Get ready to dance.
Come on. Make sure there's no secrets.
I gotta make sure there's no secrets.
That's a secret. Found it.
Found the secret I went.
So to the 5,000 other people.
All right. Let's just like actually do the level.
I can't get those pipes in.
Let's go.
Is this good?
Is this dance party with the ocean?
All right. Okay.
We did the dance party.
How do I get out?
I don't like that. I forgot Yoshi has that move.
It'd be nice if I could do it.
What you know do this?
I wouldn't.
All right. He's gonna pack my level.
Where's his pack man level?
Who's I'm gonna have to buy a pack man and me boh if that's in the game?
Ultimate life form Bowser's trap.
Pack Mario.
Yes.
Where is it?
It's even the pack man with the big nose.
But he turns into a banana.
That's so cool.
Can you do anything else?
Because I just stand there like an idiot.
All right. Let's go.
Oh, look at when he swims. He turns. That's all. That's so cool.
I lost it already. I was too busy.
I was too busy.
Fanboying over pack man.
You know what I first purchased this game.
I thought that it was going to be extremely limited and not fun.
This is pretty cool though.
Can't go down what?
What?
I don't know.
You can press up.
I just want to look at him one more time.
Let me get it.
Give me the pack man.
He'll let it fruit.
That's awesome.
Go go go go go go go.
Can I actually run into them?
Come on.
But whatever.
Easy. Easy.
I did it.
All right.
Maybe one or two more and I'm probably going to hit the head.
Tip of the hats as well.
Is tomorrow I should probably be up.
I got some work that's being done still.
But thank you guys for coming out.
Then witnessing my um
my very bad not good
playing this game.
It was fun though.
There was a couple of points that I was getting uh
getting super salty.
Oh wow.
So much so salty.
But it's fun.
This is great game.
Highly recommend if you uh
are into this kind of thing.
It's really fun.
I'll do one more.
We'll do one more hard one.
And I'll try it like five or ten times or something.
Like courses.
So I'm going to try to beat that one that was giving me trouble before.
This one.
Just the one with a two percent clear right.
All right.
Let's try to remember how this worked.
Oh yeah.
I forgot.
Mr. Chops.
At least I don't have a set amount of lives here.
So I should have done from the very beginning.
Well that's something I had to press.
We didn't get you to put a fork in the outlet.
No we didn't.
We did not.
Also this is my first time I've ever streamed on a console.
So I have to work out the bugs and all the you know
kinks and stuff because there were quite a few of them unfortunately.
I'm going to wait till they both up.
Come on jump up there join your friend.
Shit I would have gone through.
I was going to figure out that delay.
Not just like the random weird like input delay of feeling but the delay of the audio that was
happening.
Some people have said that there's been a couple of flashes like it just flashed once or twice.
Audio delay for some people.
I'll figure it out.
I hope.
I should have waited.
Ah I should have waited.
Should I I can stand right there and be totally fine.
If I stand right there they won't hit me with any of their crap.
I'm waiting too long.
I actually think I'll be able to get this.
I think I'll be able to beat this one.
I warmed up enough and I played enough of this game.
And after a few minutes I should be able to get this.
I wasn't I was looking over to the right just trying to get the opportunity to run.
I'm going to try that this time.
I'm going to try to jump and hit them underneath.
Seems like a good idea.
Oh I can't I cannot hit them but I'm going to say a spot.
Jumped down.
See that just kind of threw a cog into my brain.
When I couldn't hit them from underneath.
I just assumed I was safe for some reason.
I'm going to be one of those two percent.
I will be one of those two point seven percent people.
Come on now.
I need to do too many.
Now I'm in deep shit.
I'm in deep shit.
I'm just like locked in right now.
I didn't I was hypnotized.
I was under legit hypnosis right there.
I didn't know.
It feels like I was at a magic show.
You gotta go right.
Mmmmmm, now.
Holy dog shit, okay.
Need to wait till the end of that thing.
I will be in the 2.7%
I'm gonna do it.
I'm gonna do it!
No, I know that happens at the end. I'm gonna do it.
We are way through the one to fly up there
Shit
My god, I could have gone up. I could have gone up
I could have gone up
That's the worst part when you play through these levels there
Like kind of you have to memorize things and you see something right at the very end
I saw that right at the very end that I could have probably got a mushroom there
I don't think I have a good opportunity anymore
Maybe right now
Nope
Right
Did they just throw way more than usual?
Get out of here
You got to be shitting me right now
You've got to be absolutely shitting me
I'm very, very mad at that one
I showed a hit him right now, fucking cron of his head
That one was perfect
And then of course it all goes to hell
Like it typically does
I really want to stop this from moving
I came off further than I thought
I should have been attacked
That was just an extremely stupid move
I'm gonna get it
I have to get this before I go to bed
That's extremely important
Guys throws a perfect pitch down the middle right there
Damn, this is fucking hard as shit
I didn't mean to do that
I'm gonna get this
I should have kept running
It's actually surprising that only 3% of every person that's played this has beaten it
That's kinda funny
You think it'd be a lot more
I should have just jumped again
Should have wore a color
This one's the fireballs that just get annoying
And here comes a la key to whatever his name is
You're not dropped on
Let me get you
What the hell was that? What did they just do?
No, I got a move
It's not gonna happen
I'm just over there
I'm over complicating things when I get there
Massively just over complicating the shit out of that every time I get there
I didn't even need to jump as soon as I get over there jump jump jump and get up and kill him
Because he's such a ping in the ass at that part
Because he's throwing shit down when things are coming up
I was literally reading chat
My face is just down
Oh, it's very possible
But you just need to do everything perfect
And at least close to it
I missed it and I just bad this threw me off big time
It double teamed
You want some of this too?
No, no, no, no, what do I think?
I don't be a fucking idiot
Just watch him
Watch out for that
Here comes another one he's gonna throw it down right now
I can't even
I just, I just, I haven't gotten there in a long time
I just got, I forgot that's what, yeah I forgot
I just 100% forgot
That it was like that
I don't know why
I'm getting tired
I'm not getting fucking tired
You tell when you're getting tired when
You're forgetting things that happened like three minutes ago
That's the way you know
God, stop throwing so many, I hate when they do that shit
Yeah, you can't take the cloud but
It's getting up there is the issue
Because all the flames that are coming up and he's throwing shit down
All the while you're trying to not, you're trying to do those jumps and avoid getting hit
It's just a lot for your brain to have to do it the same time
Oh my god
Yeah, you can go the easy way but
I don't know, I feel like I've been doing it like this way so much
Somewhat reliably getting past the hammer brothers
Until very recently
I'm getting, I'm getting too sloppy
So I figured out why only three percent of people have ever beaten this level
I figured it out
Here's what it is
You do it like this many times and then you just go like this
I don't fucking care and you quit
I'm not gonna do that at all
Yeah, I have to beat this to go to bed
This is my sleep ticket
You know, because this is my sleep ticket
I'm just gonna go in this way
Forget what happened
You don't even skip the hammer brothers over here
That actually was more work to do that
Yeah
Yeah, forget that it's not easier going that way
It's just longer
I mean you get to mushroom but
I'll just try to get it over with
It's just this is like no opportunity to jump through that it
The opportunity to go through there is so small
Maybe it is, yeah, it is, I'm still dead
I'm just, I'm gonna get the mushroom too
Because like the 2% chance to get through those hammer brothers
It's seriously not fucking good
I can just go through it every time if I just take this
I just, I gotta remember when they are
When they come up, fuck
If I didn't break that, I wouldn't have freaked out about it
That he has to die
Immediately otherwise it's never gonna happen
Like right when I get down here
And I get past the hammer brothers
This dude's got to die
Like, is this second example too?
Shit
Oh, it's 3% of attempts, not 3% of people
But still that's still a fucking tiny number
That's even worse
3% of attempts means that
But just potentially like thousands of attempts at this level
That one has hit me so many times I just keep trying to get through
How did he get this level again?
I wanna beat it before I go to sleep
I'm gonna difficult at a shit head level
I'm not getting the mushroom this time, whatever
I'm gonna do it with pure luck
No, I'm in trouble now
I'm in trouble
I had to go there but those stupid flames
Ah, the flames man
All right, it's time to go
Yeah, I played the level with a 0% clear, right? That sucked
I was on it for like an hour and 12 minutes
That level fucking ate shit
All right, he's gonna
I don't know, I don't know what happened
Why did I do like a little jump there?
I just got like stuck on the pee thing? What the fuck is that?
That should not have happened
Jump it over, that shit
No, I've screwed that
Let's get it
There's not much more after this though
I mean, there's a little bit but not a whole lot
No, I was gonna go right there, that was a good opportunity
Whatever, screw it, just go
God
Those flames are in a position where they're extremely difficult to avoid because you have to land there it seems
Get over here
Fuck you
Fuck everything you stand for
I don't have to worry about that guy anymore
I just had no opportunity to go anywhere
Oh, it's again, it hit me again
Oh
I split already
I seriously didn't even do that
I looked down again
This shit is gonna try to be fucking crazy
I'm going to legit lose by fucking mind playing this game
I'm gonna wait for this dumb shithead to come back
Fuck your cloud
You could get in it but I keep telling him in the worst possible spot
Well, I didn't hold down B all enough
I'm just unraveling at this point
I got a kill him right here
Actually, wait, wait, what the fuck star?
The star in there?
Holy shit, how do I get in there?
Oh my god
Give me that thing
You serious?
I'm getting that
That's actually kinda hard to get
Oh dear, I know what to jump
It's bright
No
Close
That moment when you realize that the chat's been saying forever
Well, it's kinda hard to see chat because it's on my eye
Because I'm facing away from my computer right now
So I have my iPad sitting on my lap right now
That's how I'm reading chat
Because I'm facing away from my desk
I've gotta figure this pattern out
Thought it was like that
It is, I just have to go faster
I could, yeah, I could just get the mushroom too
I'll try that
Just jump up and get it
Let's try that
Yeah, I'm definitely getting away too tired to play this game
I was looking for the blue thing to jump on
That's like how like just tired and just done playing this game I am
I'm sleepy as all shit
Okay, we're here
I'm more excuses
Let's go
Hey, can you guys guess what happened there?
I forgot about the end again
Because I hadn't been there in so long
But that's easy enough to do it
I'm just for about six hours or something
Have a night, thank god
My brain's doing explode
I'm so fucking tired
I just wanna be done with it
I'm so sleepy
I gotta fucking long day tomorrow too
I gotta wake up, wake up at like seven o'clock in the morning
There's like a construction guy gonna be here
And then tip of the hats is all day
Why am I doing this right now?
I have like extremely important busy things to do tomorrow
And I'm playing a 3% completion rate fucking Mario Maker game
Like what the hell am I doing?
Oh god, I hit the wall
Ah
Just like one eye is closed and shit
Okay, wake up, wake the fuck up
It's time to get this like done
Get there, who cares?
Just get through that
No, I just...
I'm gonna frisbee my iPad into my wall
I'm gonna take a fucking professional frisbee
Move
And it's going straight through the drywall
I'll never find it, it's just gonna go in
I'll never find it again
I'm gonna chat
Alright, slow it down
Kill this fucking asshole, oh he flew away from me
What an iPad gamer, I've just...
Uhh...
What I was making like a level, why did I decide to do it?
I don't know why I decided to do this level
I wanted to do this for some dumb reason
And this is so easy too, it's just up so dumb
I was done like two hours ago
Fuck you, give me your cloud
Get outta here
Give me out of the cloud
Mario, please get out of the cloud
This is this, this is this, this is more to this, this is a lot more
Come on, come over here
Shouldn't have gotten that tall
Oh my god
That's the end right there, that's literally the end
That's the first time I'd ever seen that
At least I know that's the end
I have no idea what's happening there, but I know it's the end
Because it has the knife, the big knife
Here we go again
Oh what, what's this?
Ah yeah, I'll take that, absolutely
Alright, here we go again, this one wasn't terrible
Although how am I supposed to get through this without getting hit?
Besides like jumping up and jumping up
Yeah, that's how you do it
Okay, I don't know what this guy does
Wait, what?
Do I have to get him to hit into this wall?
I just need to know if that's what's happening or not
Don't worry, I died there intentionally
I was just seeing what I'm trying to figure out what the hell he does
I'm going to assume that that's what it is
Get that again
Alright, what the fuck does that guy do?
What the hell, what's this?
Oh god, that's the level being completed right there
Okay, I just didn't even realize what the hell was happening
I'm just going to push the P block
Oh, I get it, I get it
I see, alright, I understand no
I understand
There's just the P block, just keep falling
I get it
You just got to keep hitting him
Makes sense
That's the first time I've died of that guy for obvious reasons
It'd be nice to take the three hits too
I have no idea what the fuck I was doing there
Nothing smart, that's for sure
Nothing smart, that is for sure
Don't take unnecessary damage for no reason, please
Let's not mess this up
Come on
I'm waiting for the fire
Actually, I shouldn't have stepped on that, that was stupid
Well, fire, fire, fire
Ah, the fire, I forgot about the fucking fire again
I thought he was going up
I really seriously thought he was going up
And not coming straight down like that
Well, I got both their patterns
This should be over very soon
And I use that term very, very loosely
And then I can go to bed
I overshot that big time
Ah, fuck
That was very close, that was unnecessarily close
That was extremely unnecessary
Okay, wipe the hand stone
Wipe the hand stone
It's easy, there's no reason they're sprinting around all over the place
They have very, very, very manageable patterns
And this lasts a long time
Easy peasy
I didn't know when the fire was happening
Fire, fuck, no
Oh my god, damn it
It's a fucking tedious
You know, I died in the exact same spot, probably the last time
You do that like six times, that sucks
Do you look at how I've just become so like mesmerized that I'm just doing this
I'm not even playing the game right now, my muscle memories is doing this part again
I'm gonna beat this guy, don't worry
They're both a secret door
There's no secret door, that secret door is not real
It's the fire that's screwing me up
Let's keep, better remember, no these two are shit heads
Don't forget about the fire
I'm gonna get hit
Yeah, I'm gonna keep shit now
There's just a random random random random random random directions that they go
They just have to go, it's in the fire too
So close
I'm so close to defeating this
I'm so glad I didn't do this anymore
I can try to get better at the next part
I can pick the flower up, you dumbass
God, do I have to be such a dumbass sometimes, seriously
I'll get it right, well, let me screw up
I just like to know if that was it right there
Alright, I need to move, I need to put in the iPad down
Get this shit off my lap
Let me sit forward
And let's go
Fuck you game
God, that was...
You guys ready to go to bed?
Oh boy
Yay
I beat Mr. Chomsdoghouse
What do the people say?
Let's see what they say
Like I said
Um, I'm here to thank you
You just killed my Mario 100 run but in high-level
See, in 15 years, fun
Awesome, final boss
Go up if you want to have an easier time
This poor guy, this poor guy got his 100 run killed
Okay, well there is the number if you need it
That was really cool
That was really fun
If you think that a
Torture is fun
By Cuddly
Oh
Alright guys
Now, it's like funny now that I look back at this level
It's actually very, very easy once you know exactly what's happening
But that's the problem with all these levels is like
I died a million times on things that I just didn't understand
I just want to see one thing
Oh, it's a featured
One shell
Yeah, it's funny looking back like I'm like
How did I not beat that? Like I'm my first try
Which is he's
You have no idea what the hell is going on and shit is flying all over the place
This is a really fun game though look at this one
Look at this level, what is even happening here
This is not, I'm not attempting to beat this or anything, I just, I'm curious
Let's see what it is
Dude here
Okay, that leads to nothing
Probably need to jump off his head
No
I'm kind of confused by this level
I think it is
Oh shit, okay
Oh
Alright guys, I'm gonna take off
Thanks for watching
If you're new, if you just found this stream
I'm real fucking goddamn sorry
That you had to watch that
Maybe fail miserably over and over again at this game
Yeah
Hi, my name is Jeremiah
But for the rest of you
Take care of these guys
See most of you at Tip of the Hats tomorrow
I think I'll be there at
Either one or four I think is what I'm gonna be starting on it
Yeah, good night guys
Have a wonderful, wonderful evening
Rest of your night, rest of your day, whatever, wherever we are
Good night
Goodbye
Good bye