Hey, good afternoon guys. How you doing? Good afternoon.
I think we're ready to go.
Hello. So I got to apologize right off the bat. This I'm in my new office kind of area in this place.
And I'm in the process of putting up like sound panels, but it's still a little echoey in here. So I got to, uh, gotta say sorry.
Until that's all done, it's going to be a little roomy in here by you know, whatever.
My new, yeah, my this is the office where I get new it is my new office. I just get new in here.
Alright, so today, what's tonight? We're going to play a cryptarch. It's a game that came out in early access. Not that long ago a couple days ago or so.
It's a kind of rogue like space shooter sort of twin stick bullet hell type game. That's kind of a weird way to describe it. It's not really that it's more like a try to take money from spaceship game.
I actually really don't even know I have no idea. I just know what I've read about it.
But apparently very good things I've heard extremely good things about this game. And there's no reason why we'll play in this game too. This is another very specific reason why we're going to play this game.
You'll see very soon.
Do you like my hold on a second screen?
I did literally drew this in less than 15 seconds.
So we'll let some people trickle in before we do this.
Can I sell your DNA on the internet for money?
Oh, no.
No, that's it. That's pretty fucked up.
My initial question, would you get it? Where the hell did you get this?
I'm not playing sticks. No, I'm not playing sticks.
Okay, let me get this up.
I actually have heard of keep talking. Nobody explodes seems really, really fun.
Don't you need like three or four people to play that game though?
It's a game we have like at least three people, right?
Sometimes it's 1130 right now. 1126.
Only two. You only need two people? That's pretty sweet.
Maybe me and Stark have played at some point. Or somebody else who doesn't matter who it is.
007, I remember that 007 was such a good game.
First time, that was way ahead of its time.
That FPS multiplayer type game that was never, it was the first of its kind really.
It definitely matters who it is. Well, it doesn't really matter.
You don't think that would be equally as entertaining with like boo or MLC stuff?
Doesn't always have to be star guys. Plus star is in prison.
How am I going to play with them?
Pax East is not till next year, man. Not till like April or something next year.
From March or whatever.
Okay, well, I'm going to get going.
I just want to give it a minute or two so we can kind of trickle in.
We're going to open this game up. This game is apparently very hard, so please don't be mad at me if I can't do this well.
So let's do it.
Let's see if I can get the hold on the second screen off.
Hey, look at that. There's a video game on the screen now.
All right. So let's play it. I don't know a whole lot.
I know it's a shooter kind of side-scrolling top-down.
Break in, steal the stuff, take the core, get out.
I actually have played this game for like 30 seconds.
I don't really know a whole lot, but I do know this.
Let's take the last shot. Let's go ahead and do the tutorial.
You know, sometimes when you start a new game up, how are you supposed to know how to play?
You got to do the god damn tutorial.
Let's watch.
Look at those characters.
Let's go.
Yeah, we are.
I don't know nothing about this game.
I just know like the first 30 seconds.
So we're going to take over this ship.
Difficulty 1 class envoy, goal time 407.
Let's go ahead and launch.
Let's load up this first level.
Who the fuck's that?
Who's this one?
Alright, so this is what it looks like.
That's me.
Hold, eat open doors.
Easy.
The old gun handy is got four weapon hard points and four item brackets.
Yeah, yeah, move the mouse to aim.
The controls, it's pretty smooth.
That's pretty cool.
That's awkward.
Hard to even see where I'm going.
Alright, grenade is F.
I might rewind that.
And that's the shield.
Alright.
The dash, the shield.
Interesting.
Why didn't you actually learn an extra terrestrial language to prepare for your role?
Shameful display.
Okay, let's see what we're looking at here.
Now let's figure out a plan of attack.
What about the map?
This is all important information that I'm learning for the first time.
First, this active shield system will have to be taken offline.
It looks to be protective of core with some sort of energy field.
Take out the shield.
This is kind of like the swindle.
Right?
By the way, this is all procedurally generated, I believe.
We can just take a look at this shield.
It protects a single system with an impenetrable energy shield.
So this is blocking this.
Okay, so this has to go down before the core can be destroyed.
Controls the multitude of interior defense turrets.
So if I destroy this, there's turrets that are going to be here.
This is locked.
All right, let's just go.
Let's just play.
Let's do it.
There's nothing else I can really do here.
That's my shield.
I want to turn F.
I don't want to make it something else if I can.
I have a different button I'd like to do.
No, I'm apparently going to need to use my other mouse.
Let's see, mouse 4.
That works for me.
Did I do it?
Should have done it right.
I'm going to reset it.
Yeah, I don't know why that didn't do it.
Did I use all the grenades?
Maybe I don't have any grenades left.
Where's the indicator?
Because that's mouse 4.
It's not working.
Uh-oh.
Now I'll just put it back to F.
Whatever.
I'll put it down to Q.
Maybe Q is probably easier.
Oh, whoops.
Q is my like change scene button.
Oh shit.
Oh, I got to...
Well, we definitely can't make it Q.
Yeah, I don't know.
I guess I just may have to deal with it.
Because I can't get it to be mouse 4.
Alright, let's just play.
I've sit and have sat here long enough.
Pioneer away.
Hey, equipment expenses logged.
Start mission clock.
Now, I believe there's a timer, yeah.
Oh, shit.
It's going right now.
Alright, I got it.
I didn't even...
I didn't even plan my attack.
We're just going on the right in the front door.
Okay, I get...
The shield is up to the top left, right?
Repair supply.
I don't need to do that.
Whoa, okay, they can't hurt you.
These are tarots.
These tarots aren't here, for sure.
I got 1,400 of my machine gun, which is good.
Here's the shield.
Oh.
Whoa.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Oh, it's a reflector.
That's a reflector.
Okay, I got it.
You got to be real careful.
I'm going to shoot some grenades in there.
That's the way to do it.
I need to see that guy to the left.
This is pretty damn cool though.
What is that?
It's a piece of...
I got to look at the Metroid mini map.
Key terminal.
I guess I got a key.
Apparently.
Is that another key?
Let's open it up.
Ooh, I can now open that.
Okay, I got it, I get it.
Help is in the bottom.
The brain is up here, but I have like two minutes.
Hey, I should go down and...
Okay, tech advance.
What does this do?
Okay.
So I pick these up to get better shit.
Thanks me.
Thanks for telling me how to play.
I am running out of time.
No.
I don't get anymore ammo after this.
I probably should just try to do the first little tutorial area first.
Up here, right?
Yeah, there it is.
Here's the brain.
I only got a minute and 40 seconds left.
I gotta get these little shits out of their parts.
That's his port.
This is like quadrants of the brain.
That's pretty sick.
Ow.
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow.
Oh boy, not good, not good, not good.
Probably should have taken out the turret system.
Oh boy.
You're getting lit up like a white ball!
Activate one of those repair kits.
I'll get you a repair pod and patch up my shoot.
Oh shit, I'm getting yelled at.
So I gotta go to...
Okay, repair pod.
Are these things spawning from somewhere?
I thought I killed these guys.
Okay, I have one on me.
Okay, I gotta get it.
There we go.
Now I got free reign to kill the brain.
Boink.
Got the code.
Yeah, I just scoled him by self.
That's the next level scoled him.
All right.
We've got a starting budget of 500k for equipment and weapons.
But we'll pull in more funds for each boat we capture.
Just don't get sloppy.
You crash and burn out there and we'll get slapped with the expenses.
If we go into the red, our contract gets torched.
All right.
So it costs money to attack.
Difficulty one.
These are all fairly simple except for that one.
These are both harder.
No supply pods.
These are those little bonuses.
That's cool.
They use dollars instead of galactic credits.
Oh, this is unrealistic.
94,000.
I'm gonna stay with the baby ships because I'm still learning the game.
Tech advances for what was the discode that the cheapest one.
I got about five minutes to beat it.
All along don't highly guarded multiple factory systems.
All right.
Hey, look at us.
We got a bit of new equipment licenses.
We're getting a load on right here and I'll get you all cared up, Sunny.
Oh, that part was adlib.
You see there was no sunny there.
Whatever the actor over the brilliant actor was, added that little part of the end there.
Just a little bit of an insight.
All right.
Let's get down to business.
You got four weapon points.
I can carry whatever hardware we got licenses for.
I can modify the amount of whole durability your suit has as well.
Polternaut and extra plating can get pricey though.
I can't wait to see the item bracket.
It's gonna be loaded up with whatever good news you think might come in handy.
So humble.
I'm just kidding.
It's a joke.
We're just joking here.
Okay.
So what do I have here?
This is 36,000.
I can...
Where's my money?
I can also...
Can I sell it too?
I'm just gonna go with default now.
So this is what I can put here.
I got all the elements catalog by type.
Be sure to let me know how much ammo you want for each gun too.
These things get hungry out there.
I'm trying to just let you die.
So I can get keys.
I can bring a nuke.
I'm gonna keep the fix.
Two fixes.
What's the key?
So I can get through one key and it's $8,000.
I don't think I can do one fix.
I should be all right.
What else we got here?
Oh geez.
There's even more weapons.
The spike is cool, but...
Okay, shotgun.
224K.
Let me try the shotgun.
We'll go with 200.
Now we're gonna go with 100.
Just to guess I don't like it.
Yeah, 50.
Just in case I hate it.
So the machine gun that's fine, although maybe...
1500 is fine.
Shield should probably stay there.
It helps.
Bombs.
We're gonna stake the shield.
Here are the grenades.
Sticky grenades.
I was barely using these, so I'm just gonna...
I'm gonna say zero.
I'm gonna save a little more.
I'm gonna get more bang for a buck.
I'm gonna try the shotgun and I will put on another thing of health.
Maybe two more things to help.
I get $500,000.
I get $69,000 for beating this.
So maybe I shouldn't be doing that.
I'm just gonna be in the red.
Fuck it, whatever.
Who cares?
That's the way we're gonna do it.
Where did I go?
There it is.
Oh, cool.
So I can just use them.
Ooh, I like the shotgun.
Shotguns actually pretty damn cool.
I think I'm liking this.
I think I am.
I like the shotgun.
I'm gonna try shotgun shotty guy.
What the fuck is this?
How did I get connected with this game?
This is actually made by the same people that made a Pothion.
Alien trap.
And the guy that was the casting director for Pothion is a guy that I have to know from the old voice acting communities.
And he got me in touch again.
He I auditioned.
And they liked it.
So I'm in the game.
That's pretty much it.
Let's go steal some stuff.
Let's go blow up a core.
Alright, let's look at this.
I mean, this is important.
Here's the core.
Alarm system.
So that protects the core.
This is gonna be kind of harder.
Well, this is tiny.
This is a little one, huh?
This is a little baby ship.
I forgot.
So if I go in this door, no, no.
If I go in this door.
This is the thing that spawns enemies.
I'm gonna come in the back door, destroy the thing that spawns the enemies.
Then, wrap around this way, come up to destroy the alarm system.
And then, core gets taken out.
Nothing but net.
Let's go.
Okay, confirm loadout.
88,000.
I feel like this is very wasteful.
But I'll learn that as we go.
I only have four and a half minutes.
Right in the back door.
Oh, lots of people down here.
Holy shit, everybody.
This thing up above has hit me.
I'm freaking out.
I calm down.
I gotta calm down here.
I went way too fast.
I should've just slowed down.
That's a good amount of health.
Oh shit, alarm triggered.
What?
What am I?
Careful about tripping those alarm sensors.
I see multiple contacts converging on your position.
Yeah, I did all those laser effects.
Yeah, all these sound effects in here I did them with my mouth.
No, that's not true.
They're very talented sound designs on this game.
That's what they're actors.
I'm taking away too many hits here.
There goes that.
Whoa, what the fuck is happening to my character?
I'm getting pulled in and I just got sucked in.
All right, note this out.
They suck you in.
Don't turn off.
Tech.
Key.
Fuck.
Give me that heal.
Damn.
Oh, I can't hurt the brain, but it triggers the alarm.
I'm out of repairs.
So maybe I should have brought.
I thought that was five.
No, okay, I get enough.
That's five health points, not five in the slot.
I don't think there's so many enemies there are.
Quick hit, get that tech upgrade.
That's what I should have just said right there.
I think we're just gonna go for it.
Just destroy it.
Pull it out.
I'm dead.
Okay, all right, get it.
I just lost a budget.
I just lost 100 grand.
Shit.
That was cool, though.
Now that I know how that works and now we're back here,
and I believe these are all generated again.
We're gonna go with the baby one again.
This time I'm gonna put multiple heals in.
Now I know, triggering that, that the alarm switches,
it's pretty planned, didn't work.
Okay, let's go down, get another heal.
That's $10,000.
I think in an upgrade, what is this sensor?
Deepwave Red Arverse Scepter is in advance.
Mold-Bat, tunneling processor, a lot of the sensor package
to reveal a lighter area.
I don't think I need that yet.
15 grand for a nuke, I don't know.
I'd rather just get another heal just because I'm a fucking shitty.
I might as well reset.
By the way, this is kind of like a rogue like.
When you're out of money, I believe the game is over.
I'm already down 100k.
Still have the shotgun.
Still have the shield.
And we'll go with that.
This time I'm gonna be a little bit more careful.
God, that was a lot of money.
This one's the layout is a little different.
Brain is down here at this time.
Alright, I'm just gonna be more, I got way too gong-ho.
I just went straight in.
It's locked.
Just gotta be careful.
You just slow it down.
It's kind of like binding a Isaac.
You don't just run in the room and run around like a fucking psychopath.
Couple of tech upgrades here.
Key.
There you go.
Let's open his door.
This is where the turrets are being shot.
Clear out the little, clear out the trash.
Have you learned anything from World of Warcraft?
Clear out the trash.
Okay, that's gonna pully.
That's gonna be hard to do.
This is scary.
Alright, Sentry systems are now destroyed.
I can move freely without getting aggro from them.
That's tech upgrade in here.
I don't have key though.
Is it now?
Oh, no I do.
Only a minute and a half left, I gotta keep going.
I'm running out of time.
It's have and have not.
This is a game of halves and have nots.
Am I going the right way?
Nope.
Not even close.
I'm just letting go through here.
Is there a way to get in this back way?
I would pull a planning.
One minute.
No, there's no way I'm gonna do this in one minute.
Fuck it.
We gotta go.
I have 45 seconds to kill the brain.
Wow, time is not on your side in this game.
Go soundly alone, don't give a shit.
30 seconds.
45 seconds, go on.
Thank God.
Phew.
Damn.
So my revenue was 100 and how much did I spend?
100 and something thousand?
So my actual net like actual gain was like 30 thousand dollars.
This is pretty cool.
I will say I am.
Oh, would you look at that?
That's why this is cool.
So you have a choice between four ships.
You can either spend a little bit more money
do the really hard ones.
Because you have to go through these five slots.
You can do one, two, three, four, five.
And then you get to the crypt.
Let's go with the hard one.
Let's just see.
I'm just curious.
Now I'm gonna get my ass kicked.
But I'm curious to see what like a three difficulty one is like.
I'm sure they go up to 10 or something.
Think of all the slabs of granite you could have bought with that money.
Quite a few.
We're gonna do the really, really ultra super level two hard one.
This one looks pretty big too.
Six and a half minutes.
Destroy the sensor jammers for an extra 34k.
Let's just go for it.
We got another, we got another tutorial.
Oh no, we don't.
What do I have for this heavy machine gun ricochet?
Lots of recoil but they ricochet the bullets ricochet.
How much is the price difference?
The machine gun burst smart.
Ooh.
The advanced smart gun.
The zip gun?
Let's go with the zip gun.
How much money is the zip gun comparison?
No, if I have much more zip gun.
3000 bolts.
Am I gonna stay with the shotgun?
Yeah, it's kind of tried and true, right?
Probably bolts 50, 50's been working pretty well.
You could probably even go lower.
No, you can only go 50.
Actually, I wanna put this on.
Okay, let's do 10 grenades on mouse three.
Most two, no, no, no, no, no, no.
That shield is too good.
You can't take this off.
What does this do?
Blaster?
If the zip gun isn't voice acted by Jermami, I'm gonna stay with the shield for now.
I should take grenades but I wish I could just change the key bind.
F is kind of awkward to press when most 90% of the stuff you're doing is on the mouse.
But whatever.
Didn't I find something else here?
No.
Now that I know what the hell's going on, I think I'm okay with having one of these fixers.
I barely took any damage that last run.
Now that I know, not to be a psychopath about everything.
You can even take this down.
Okay, so if you were confident enough, you could save yourself like $40,000 if you knew you were gonna hit more than one time.
Or two times.
Where's it gonna go with, you know what I'm gonna go with eight?
This is a $74,000 mission.
I get 141 if I beat it and the bonuses.
Let's just get our asses kicked, why not?
Let's take a look at what we're dealing with.
Oh fuck.
Oh, that's evil.
So I guess I could take one of those sensors, right?
I don't have those things.
I gotta do.
$8,000 to be able to see not that far in front of me.
Let's try it.
We'll go for it.
I think does that mean I can see things now?
Okay, so this thing will repair other things that I destroyed.
So that thing's gotta go.
What is this? That's the jammer.
If there's a way to get in right here, or like here, I can grab the intel, take out the drone factory, repair system, come around.
Poke the thing in the eye.
Rip around, get rid of the turret system, swoop, shoot, bang, shield, generate it down, and the alarm system down.
Thank you very much. I'll take my 200 rent.
You heard it here first.
So that's what that does.
Is it door right here? What do you know?
We're gonna be good to go.
At least that's loud.
I'm sorry, everybody. That's very loud.
Say it's the dip gun.
Oh god, forgot. I forgot where am I.
Oh, that just totally ruined my whole plan.
Get me out of here.
Fuck that.
Bye. I'm going back to my original plan.
Can I?
Shit. Come on. There's got to be like a secret entrance up here I can break through, right?
There it is.
Ow!
This is dip gun is sick.
We're going for speed.
French gun.
Hard to shoot the zip gun in here because it's so inaccurate.
There it goes. Where's the brain?
Okay, brain.
Fuck.
Easy, easy careful.
I got five minutes to do this.
I can probably...
I might not... I don't think I'm going to get the brain just yet.
I got... I went through the secret entrance.
Throwing factory... oh shit.
No, we're gonna go.
Is that gonna shield me?
Hope not.
I think I can hurt you this side yet.
That's not good.
No, now it's good.
All right.
No, I got three health.
Three HP in no way.
Yeah, I didn't take out the repair thing because my everything got all screwed up.
Look at that money.
No supply pods. I didn't destroy the jammers.
297K.
I'll take it.
Attention crew. We're moving deeper into the flotilla and getting closer to the cryptarch.
Expect higher resistance.
All right, I'm messing around.
I'm pretty sure the only reason why I'm alive is he probably dude.
That's probably true.
These are bigger.
I don't know man.
What's the difference between these?
These ones more money but...
There must just be more stuff.
See, all those icons in the lower right, I don't even know what the hell any of those mean.
We'll play this one a little bit safer.
Three, five, five.
Would Benjamin Franklin have taken this like a safe the safe way?
No, he would have people to start off the fucking goddamn revolution and been like the best president we've ever had.
We're going with the danger of five.
How do you think he got on that hundred?
Did he get got on that hundred by like taking a bath?
No, he was the best electric president we've ever had.
Benjamin Franklin wasn't a president.
He, but who cares?
Only damn president on the money that's not on the money, you know, that's all the money.
Yeah.
I got a new weapon. Let's take a look at what it is.
I do like the zip gun.
Trench gun.
Sawed off double-barrowed shotgun.
Slowed or reload?
Nothing compares to a brutal one-two punch.
What if I do double shotgun?
That sounds kind of fun, right?
If we're doing a hard one, no, I don't know.
That doesn't seem like a good idea.
Try the other guns. Advanced smart gun.
It's too expensive.
Is it really worth it to have like a home, this one's homing.
And it's almost fifteen thousand twelve thousand dollars less expensive for more bullets.
We'll get a try.
I feel like that's not enough though.
We'll go with the default.
And we'll do the shot off shotgun.
Can't take the shield off. It's too good.
I don't even care. I don't even like the sensor.
That's eight thousand dollars I don't need to spend.
At least not now.
Should I do it?
I could have double zipped on.
And blow everybody's eardrums out.
I'll keep it on. This is a big job.
I like the key.
I don't care about the grenades.
It's money I don't have to spend.
I feel like I'm gonna run out of ammo.
But it cares.
I'm gonna be a millionaire after this one anyways.
Uh oh.
I'm really what does that mean?
Okay this gun is pretty amazing.
You can just go like this and shoot around corners.
I'm blotting. Look at how much ammo I'm blowing though.
Whoa.
That's gone in the game.
So out off shotgun is probably the best.
Look at this thing. Look at the spread.
I like this loadout.
Oh it's stealthy. You like the voice?
Let's go.
There's a lot of enemies here.
Look at that.
It's tiny.
This one is so small.
There's a ton of enemies but it's tiny.
Provides all drones aboard this ship with additional 25% health.
Shit.
There's the point of entry.
Ooh.
This one's multiple ships connected together.
How much time do I have seven and a half minutes?
Take it slow.
I got a key. I can go right in here.
Let's go.
Actually, hold on.
I can't get it. Yeah, I can.
I have a key.
Is this scary?
I'm scared of opening this door.
Yeah, there's their shield.
Wow.
Oh, it's in every direction.
Why did I do this one?
Why did I do this to this hard one?
I should have taken like the fucking Alexander fan grant.
What her first name was.
What was the name?
Anthony Grant.
What was that president?
Oh my god.
Get me out of here.
Oh my god, my game is crashing.
They're following me out of the ship.
Oh, wow.
That was not prepared for that one.
Ulysses S. Grant.
That was like a general.
That wasn't even a president.
They can't hurt me if I'm out here.
Not like that.
Just get away from these guys.
Jesus.
Tech, tech, tech, tech, tech, tech, tech uppers.
Chain gun.
This thing has a shield.
This is bad.
Are those green bubbles?
What's next?
Huge knockback.
Why do I...
All right, their armor is down.
Those turrets are unbearable.
Oh boy.
That's it.
Wait, is it not in?
Is that not it?
That's not it.
So there's like a left for dead style.
One last chance playing in this game.
I can't tell any of his health whenever this is bad.
I'm dead.
How much money did I just lose?
That hurts.
I was going to get a poster of Benjamin Franklin
and put him up on this wall back here.
Now I'm going to get a poster of Dan Bush.
Like George Bush is like seventh cousin.
Or like Bill Clinton.
You know what?
I think I'm going to get a Bill Clinton poster.
Is it like a Bill Clinton poster with a cigar in his hand?
Probably.
Is it like just like leaning back like smiling with a cigar?
Benjamin fucking Franklin.
Unbelievable.
Well, we lost a bunch of money.
That one was very, very, very, very hard.
Is there four or is it just three in five?
I'll do it three.
I'm not quite there yet to do the advanced level five ones.
I don't think the uh...
That Tracer Gundon shoot really fast enough for me.
Oh, I got into weapon.
I got a chain gun, right?
Let's try that one.
You lost 100,000 Berger boys, not Bugafot.
I don't know why that's so funny to me.
Bugafot, not Bugafot.
That's great.
One spinning, they deliver a hurricane of weathering fire.
Let's try it.
I still like this shotgun, the uh...
The Tracer Gundon.
Do they make something else?
I'm saying like something else could be here that I'm just not missing.
The zip gun was a good choice too.
Let's try the chain gun.
No, but this is level three.
This is not level five.
Keep these.
I'm going to take another key.
Just because how much are the keys?
Whatever.
One, two, three.
One, two, three, four, five.
I'm going to do seven strength.
That's a bad idea.
Bad idea, but you know, I'm going to do it anyways.
Yeah!
It starts off slow.
Then you get into face melting category in like two seconds.
I like it.
We're staying with it.
This one, I didn't even look at it.
I was pretty dumb.
I'm going to go in this door over here.
Go in this door, grab the key, make my way up, try to destroy the shield and the alarm.
Because that also requires a key to get in there.
Get a couple of these tech upgrades to go down, swing all the way down inside the puzzle piece into the core.
Let's go.
It's going to be a long trip to go all the way around.
But it's worth it.
At least I think.
I hope.
How many lines did I record for this game?
I think like 40, 50, 30, something like that.
More than a handful, I would say.
Things get kind of like unwieldy.
Take the key, let's go up.
I don't need to be bringing that many keys.
I already have three.
Here we go.
This is going to set off the alarm.
Having the double barrel shotgun shoot twice is going to kill me.
And.
Get in there.
Shit, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit.
I'm going to have to hang out in there.
I'm going to have to hang out there.
I'll scramble into this one room.
Is corpsman going to dissipate if I don't touch them for a while?
Where's the repair drone?
No.
I forgot that this thing existed.
Where is it?
Is it this far down?
It's that far down.
Should have done this first.
Look back planning.
It's okay.
How much time do I got?
Three minutes.
It's alright.
I just worked myself.
Shit.
Shithead, put your shield down.
Can I not kill these things?
Oh
Not a bad one
Oh, no
Get these like snakes these little sperms get out of here
I'm out of ammo on every gun
You
You got yet you called it not in a famo I heard it I didn't I didn't I should have I
Really liked this game
This is this is really really cool
Well we're officially lost almost all the money that I have in my bank
Chain gun I I'm gonna have to go back to tried and true zip gun man
Let's go
Am I not I got a couple of new things but
Could do double zip gun. Let's you know we're gonna try it. We'll try double zip gun
Wonder if it's even possible
Yes, you the chip look at how much money that is no wonder it's that much money because you can just spam it
Okay, heavy machine gun piercing
High fire that's a piercing ammunition auto stabilizer
He brings suit so this is slows you down a lot
Yeah, do we even need to read that or we just get in two zip guns
You know what I mean actually we really need to like read any of that shit
That's awesome. Oh, that's so cool
That's enough ammo too, I think
All right
That is gonna be enough ammo I hope
Don't need two keys you get keys pretty easily sensors. Okay to stay
I'll keep the one key the one healer and now we've got double zip gun
So the game's pretty much over you know
Then many things are gonna get now way now there and they're insane
Now let me think about this for a second rather than just
Be a moron and say oh, yes, it's connected to this and now I go
This is repair system
This has to go this thing has to go first
Otherwise if I destroy this it doesn't matter
Although yeah, if I destroy this it won't matter like all those repair facilities these things have to go
So there's one in here there's only one
So we got to go down and then we got to go all the way back up again up to here or even right over to here
So this is the point of entry actually this is good because the turrets thing is right here
We got double zip gun. We're going in that spot right there to the lower right
Let's go
We're almost out of money so this is our last chance to pull this out of the fire oh shit. We're out of money
If we don't deliver the ship to the contractors we'll be out of a job and that's where the game ends
All right, I can't lose this one. I physically cannot lose this otherwise the game's over
So you know what they say
Oh
Move move move
I got places to be places to be
I got a key I can open the store good
Fuck you
All right
All right keep moving we have this is a must win this is a must win situation
We're only gonna do one zip on trigger a cheap forgetting about that
Don't want to run out of the ammo
I got plenty of time show
What's happening what happened would I go
How do you not get by those
Let's go
I got I got yeah, I got like a thousand rounds
Fuckin hard to blow in this whole thing
Like a wagon
Is the brain
Is this shield all right, I get a chill for a second. I'm rolling out of ammo. Is there any able to you guys see an ammo pod me work?
I can't really look in the map
Shit
Is it gonna be so hard to hit this and not get hit I get up to stand so close and just go like this
It's cuz it's gonna reflect it right in my face
Brain I got a full minute and a half
Slow down slow down
Each shit down to one down to one zip gun
I can't even tell I can't even tell this stupid motherfucker right here
Oh
Oh wow, I thought I lost it right at the end we live another day
You know what I bet you after a couple more seconds of that it would have lost I would have lost again
Nice
Okay, well there's that
Double zip gun all the way it was all double zip gun
For zip gun, it's probably possible. I don't know if I have the money
Class five class to work to six now
I'm gonna be able to beat that with the amount of money that I need to save
You know
Many multiple heals a key
Now you know, let's try it. I'm gonna spend my entire bank account
This is a huge payout if I can beat this though
I
Can actually beat this it's a pretty large pal
So you know, we're just gonna we're just
Can I do this
Oh
Alright guys got to say
that
This is really really really cool
This is great um, so this is uh being able to do something like this people can just do whatever the hell they want
to the detriment of your
We're doing four zip-gun
We're gonna do here's what we're gonna do
We're gonna do four zip-guns
With as much ammo as I can put in them all
What about chain-dons? Let's try that
I'm just curious to see how much more outrageous the chain guns are with four of them
I
Yeah, that one's too dangerous because I can't even move so we're not doing that we're doing zip-guns
Four zip guns and four heels. What's knock?
So this is could you kind of blocks projectiles?
Oh
I wasn't even firing the fourth one was I
Let's just do it who cares let's do fucking five chain guns
Look at how much money this is I'm not even gonna build a fort
How much money do I have
Total bang okay, I'm out of money
Let's go you guys ready to lose the game I'm about ready to lose the game
I'm out of money game over I have to win the search game over and I have four I can't even control the character with W a.c
I'm just gonna there's no way I can't do that at w a.c
F I have my my hand on my mouse too
But you know with that with a little luck we could just spare myself to victory
We'll take it easy at first there's new hazards, okay
Okay
Oh
Why is this working why is this working
It's like super no brain
That's gonna take over this whole place ain't it
Oh
I have so sweet color
This is gonna reflect the
Let's get the brain give me the brain
Where's the brain was brain quick?
Try this
Dead
Well, hell is the brain
It's all the way over here that that's
I died
I died I blew up
If I were to wait if I went the right way it would have worked
I'm okay with just losing all my money in the game being over let's see what happens
Oh, this guy gonna kill me
Okay, it's fun being bankrupt I guess
Out of funs game over total score
Revenue that's so cool it gives you like a graph look at the kills near the end
You show that bank account statement like that to a guy in Wall Street will probably throw up
That's there it is that's the game cryptark
We give you a million dollars and you spent it all on chaingums
Why did we hire you in the first place you're a fucking idiot
All right, well, I'm gonna do another run this time I'm gonna this this this one will be a little bit more legit
Because the first couple times that no idea what the hell I was doing and then the last few were more kind of joking around and messing around with the loadouts
But this is cryptark
From what I just played this like 40 minutes session so far this is really really really cool
Highly recommended so far, so I'm gonna pee I
Will back in like two minutes
The first of many pisses by the way
Like if you didn't think there was gonna be at least like four pisses this stream I just really don't know what's tight
Be right back I'm gonna go pee
You
Hello
So what am I gonna do game where can I just continue?
Now that's from the previous one
New game right
Yeah, wait one yeah, okay, so you game
slot two hey, you know, we should look at this tutorial
Check list cleared pines bitch on weapons free. I'll get the angle grinder up when you get back
To it's a leg right off the bat. I guess this is giving it look off. You know, we're gonna go to
This one seems pretty good
Let's actually try to beat this
I like the way the character looks we've got his face
Looks like a shark that like shark red shark face
It's pretty damn cool
Let's conserve money
We'll go with the ramp spike
Don't need two of these at the first level might not even need one. I don't need the grenades
You do two shields no
Save money in the first few levels for sure
I
Think that's pretty bear bones. That's fine. This shouldn't be that difficult
You know save even more money. I'm doing pick that down. I think this not too
I'm seeing a repair system on board this vessel is
Scrolls will attempt to fix other systems. We have already destroyed
There's a repair that goes down first
Yeah, that that has to go down first because the alarm system and the shield generator will both be repaired
By the time I try to come back down. So we have to go I guess kind of just right in the front
This is not really this is a terrible entry point
Along do I have five minutes I
Hold on I've five minutes to go from here all the way down here all the way up and then all the way down again
Might just bypass the alarm come over here and get rid of the arm ring system. Oh, this is a this is a really tough
Generated level
You can come down here and I still have to go up
You know what we'll go. Yeah, we'll go there
Let's go
54,000 dollars. That's nothing. That's peanuts
Oh
I know I know I know knock out the arm ring system. Where am I going? Where am I?
Fuck
I
Thought it was like down to the left. It's right above me. I just lost like a full their 20 seconds
This isn't even the right area to go in. No, I guess it is I'm going the way
I
Stinger pod cool
Brain
I
Second man's heavy machine gun burst I
Didn't even see what the hell does hit me
What the fuck just hit me is like these bomb things that are floating around
You
Walk in my view
All right now we're gonna go
Destroyed the shield
Here
Back upgrade got free minutes like a time
I gotta go down because I can't go through it's yeah down around
You
That
Never seen this enemy yet this thing takes a ton of hits
It was actually pretty hard for some reason
Open up
Open your face please
That another shield up here
These and I hate these
Expending wheel of death enemy to the world
You
Out of here I want any of this
These guys sneak up on you they blend in with the environment pretty well
Brain
Not sure
Shield isn't
Yeah, that's just the alarm system I can't hurt it
Huh
What's going on here
Does that protect this as well I thought that was just an alarm
Guess not well already then
I
Can't go around this either this is a
You're trying to look yeah, I can't hit the glowing side I guess okay
Yeah, there was no way to go around
Was that just like locked in there that was that that side was locked in
Unless I like went through that was weird
Yeah, I don't think there was any there was no way for me to go to the other side of that brain I
Think I think I may have just gotten procedurally generated screwed
Because if I went if I had to go all the way around I don't hit like 30 seconds
Damn it
Okay
You'd have to go around the whole ship I only had like 45 seconds
Whatever
I could I could be I could be upset or I can you know just get get myself going do it again
Well, I'm not happy that I just blew that money I
Don't like this bike
That one seems kind of cool, but let's look at the
Cluster grenades stinger to pod
No, I want to bet here. I don't think I need that money
Try these for fun stinger misses not that many
This is new
That seems pretty damn cool you can teleport to it
I like that I kind of want to try it
Take a look
So there are two places to go to the brain
Shield
If I go in this way I can destroy the shield here
I don't think there's a reason to destroy the door lock
Don't really need to care about the alarm here just bang around here
There is a repair station there
And I come up get rid of that
If I can destroy this and then come around quickly enough to destroy this
It's risky, but I'm thinking might try it
I'm gonna try that I should be able to go from here to there in less than a couple like a minute or two right
Worst comes to worse that is have to go back around
I'm gonna go straight down to the top
Let's go
So I got to go from here. I got that's actually pretty long way to go
I'm gonna go all the way around the ship
Move
Yeah
Yeah, the teleport it can go down I'm gonna put the teleporter right up here
Is it sad?
Oh god
Okay, so you just hit two and then you hit two again
What the fuck?
Well back to the original plan oh
My god, what a fucking disaster this one is
This one is a total fucking disaster because I was too busy figuring out how the teleporter worked
I thought it was gonna like shoot out of the device
No, I guess it's just like remembers where you are at the time
What the fuck
I can do this in time for sure
Just a little bit there was slow
Oh
16,000
Wish I had the teleport now
Really wish I had the teleport
Yeah
Run in ammo
Yeah, right on that
Running out of ammo
I got oh that could have been a lot later
I'm so upset right now
I
Wanted how much money I'm not going to get for getting actually
I took the the help which I absolutely needed to do otherwise I would have lost
Load out max 100k
Does that mean that I
Spent more than a hundred thousand dollars to be able to do that mission
Apparently
Is there a story in this game? I think it's pretty open ended. You're like a crew
That's doing these like salvaging mr. Salva-ging missions for this weird snake person company
I don't know like all the lore. I don't think there's very much. I mean this is a member this is a this game is early access
Just remember that that's kind of this is a very very
Complete feeling game for it being early access
Okay
Do I just play I might just play it say if you're into one of the ones I
Need to do something simple to not because that first one really does got screwed. I'll do the two
Tech advances six one tail station that's just two I want to try to get to the end
One is too easy two is like okay three is like a little bit more difficult
Small to that's good
Larm down there
No supply pods in the lowdown needs to be more than 60k I
Could probably get all three
I'm gonna go for all three bonuses, which shouldn't be that hard
Considering I can just walk right in the store two tech pods
There's the shield going with the key destroy the brain
Pretty self-explanatory Terry
So bang bang is a key right. Oh, yeah, this is this is this is Kate as you spend 60 grand
How much is the loadout worth right now 79
Get rid of these that wasn't a fan of those
Hmm, I don't need this
60k right okay, I think that's good to go
Oh the max okay, I get I get it I get it
So I'm just gonna go with nothing at all
Maybe a little bit more ammo with the zip gun that'll do it
That'll do it
All right guys, let's do it right in the front door should be easy
To check out variants right off the bat
I need to have six oh
That I thought that was an enemy
I'm gonna watch out for the alarm
I thought it's gonna be hard to shoot through here
I need to get close
These are the worst ones I hate those ones
Oh
Come off whoa that was black
Oh my god my game is lagging
Okay, well that didn't really go to swim
Oh
The shield we're charging shield we're charging together. Thank God
Bye-bye I didn't I didn't get the first bonus, but whatever
When in doubt blame lag well the lag's not the right word like
Hardware lag like in everything like you know your computer freezes for like a second
Not like internet lag
Grades don't reflect like bullets the shield killer is basically oh okay, that's good to know
I just wish I could rebind the button to be something of my mouth
Got least the two
bonuses I got plenty of money now
My reki probes are showing several new types of defensive systems and morphons aboard the target vessels
Compiling this new information to the taknav now even more stuff to worry about great
Two fives or two threes this one is the more expensive three
Do that
I have a lot of money
I'm going to get a little bit more health because I have more money I
Know that load up max 60k is a thing, but I would like to complete this game at least you know do a run of this game
I guess
Drown factories how many drone factories are there?
Okay, this except oh, what's this one EMP shotgun?
Oh
Let's try that
I'll get him it's just hard to use I just hitting F is awkward for me
We got a hedge I said EMP weaponry this game will scramble us credit's good
Good enough
F I want that to be mouse for
Now should still be most for mouse for
Damn it
That's too bad it's not F now it's not
Well
Can you make it most now I can't do most five
Something that's less
Hmm F is really the only thing I guess it's I guess
Shift maybe shift yeah actually shift is probably better
Then that takes away that I'll do this as alt maybe
See if that's better
Yeah, it's better not ideal, but
So this is an EMP shotgun which disables electronics
So assuming I can go bang they shut down for a second like you can destroy it
All right, let's take a look at the area
Tons of these repair systems
Too many of them might with some one might say
I
Think I'm gonna get rid of the alarm system this time I'm gonna start with the alarm system
I'm going right in here and destroy the alarm system that really does just kill you every time
When you trip that every you're gonna lose like 4 HP from the sheer amount of people that are running around
I
Mean this you can do twin stick. I mean you're talking about mouse control you twins
I believe you can plug it. There's a gamepad mode. It probably works. Okay. It's like kind of like geometry wars
Unlike the Xbox
Course of action in here. No, I can't do that because the prepare stations
Well, these are the only two repair stations
One two get rid of those
Okay, here's the plan I'm gonna get rid of both of these through here. I'm gonna bring a key with me
And then I'm gonna go down here. I'm gonna place the teleporter right there
Okay
Teleporter goes there
Then we go over here take out the alarm
Teleport take out the shield and then make our way up in a round actually yeah up and around to the core
Okay, so that means I need a couple things I need a key and I need a teleport
Okay
And I start here which means I have to go up around this way through here. Let's give it a go
On which ameldo I have enough
That was a lot of money
Yeah, I personally wouldn't be able to play this game on anything but a mouse
Although like a twin stick shooters usually they're pretty they're okay. They're not terrible
Because it's just like you're right thumb to do the same thing right
Those in the spin guys
You
of
Oh, those things can't hurt.
I just realized that.
Those cannot hurt you.
I guess they can.
Oh god.
Just being repaired by the other one, isn't it?
Oh, so much ammo.
He's been lost.
I know. Gotta go. Gotta go.
Okay, they're both dead.
Let's go back around.
Who?
Fun.
What the fuck?
I need a- I need- I'm gonna need up an ammo station here.
For sure.
Gotta keep it right.
I'm gonna need going at them.
All right, let's put down.
There's the teleporter.
Well, I have a second here.
Looking for an ammo station.
Down here.
Okay.
Where am I right now?
That's far.
Ugh.
Going to the right is too far to go.
I'm gonna have to just do it.
I'm gonna have to just bite the bullet and go down.
To the left and down.
I need to take out that one down there.
Okay, let's go.
I don't have to attack anybody.
I won't.
Fucking hate those enemies.
These guys have put up the shield.
The thing is that repaired you.
Holy dog shit.
There's so many things flying around.
Ugh.
What the?
Quick left for dead.
Come on.
Come on left for dead.
I'm gonna have to go back to the right.
What the?
Quick left for dead.
Come on.
Left for dead.
Bring me back.
Come back.
Quickly, quickly, quickly.
Yes, I will.
That was a lot of money.
That was a huge amount of money.
That on the time for this.
I'm blowing through so much money.
It's crazy.
What?
You fucker.
That's that's game over.
We're gonna go teleport.
See you later.
I triggered the alarm, but guess what?
It didn't even matter.
What the hell is shooting me from across the map?
Should've got grenades.
I'm gonna have to go back to the map.
That's not the right way.
60 seconds.
Franchise fingers.
Oh, I don't think so.
I don't think it's gonna add...
It's gonna be a fucking Christmas miracle if I can do this.
Jesus!
No way.
Game over.
I can't.
I'm not gonna left for dead my way out of this one.
No way.
Holy shit.
Fuck.
The EMP was the shotgun that I had.
It's okay.
I still got money.
I still got cash.
Oh my god.
It's because I bounded to shift.
That was...
Oh my god.
You see, if I could just put my fucking keybinding on the thing I wanted,
I wouldn't have forgotten that I had bombs because I pressed F.
And I was like, I don't have bombs.
Of course I don't.
No, it's because I had it on...
Fuckin' shit!
It should be on this button.
I don't think it would have mattered though, honestly.
I'm pretty sure I still was gonna lose that.
Fuck.
I'm gonna crack this shit.
Oh, spam.
Spam the salty, but this streamer's getting fucking salty.
Now, I just didn't think I had them for some reason because I just rebounded the key.
And I like forgot that the key was bound there.
That was the problem.
Won't forget this time.
I love a god.
I actually don't like this shotgun either.
What is this?
Now they're licensing us industrial equipment and standard weapons.
Comotive, ungrin projector.
Some sort of cool gun for disarboned scrap metal.
What does it do?
I don't know what it does.
You can also cook the grenades too.
We'll get as good as we're gonna have to find out.
Slime mortar cannons.
Let's slow them down.
Let's go looking.
I think it's time to buy more ammo for the Zip Gun.
Another expensive trip.
Not gonna not factory.
Okay.
Drawing factory.
It's another one of these spread out ones.
The brain is here.
The brain is making me dehydrated.
Go drink some water.
Go drink a gatorade.
I don't know about this one.
This one's really spread out.
Technically I can just go in there.
Even if the alarm does sound, let's say I just go in here.
And come right back in here.
Even if the alarm sounds where they're gonna come from.
They're gonna have to come a long way.
That's a very far way to go.
I'm gonna try that.
I got my Goo Gun.
I can try that.
We'll do it.
So where's the ship?
And in there.
I'm gonna also put a... yeah!
Let's do this.
I'm going here first.
I'm gonna...
That's probably a bad idea.
I'm gonna say put a teleporter in here, but I'm gonna trip the alarm and that'll screw me.
I'm gonna get rid of the teleporter.
I don't want to use it.
Whoa!
Can you guys hear that?
Holy shit!
Hold on.
Wow!
Those are coyotes.
What the fuck is going on out here?
I don't know if you guys could hear that.
Those are coyotes, man.
Just looking out the window, trying to see.
My dog just jumped up.
He's like, what the hell is out there?
That was right.
I've heard them before.
I've heard coyotes before.
Down here, but...
Oh, that was right outside my window.
Alright!
Well, you guys can hear the coyotes.
That's cool.
Well, if those are coyotes, I don't know what they would be considering there's no dogs over there.
That is woods.
Alright, we'll back to reality here.
Alright, let's go.
I'm gonna stick with the plan.
So expensive.
The plan is go all the way up and just go and just shoot the go everywhere.
Such a stupid plan.
What an awful idea.
I wish I was better at playing difficult video games.
Because I could have planned that out.
I'm just gonna go here.
Chalapura is gonna go over there.
That's not a place to go.
What's the good thing?
I'm totally sure.
Flame thrower.
Now that's what I want to see.
Get out of here.
Worst enemy in game.
Health that I'll meet at the moment.
Wait a second.
Oh shit in my pants.
Come on now.
Wonderful.
I don't want to use grenades.
What a dumb mistake that was.
Is there a unbelievable?
Oh come.
Go go go go go go go go go go go go.
Go.
Guys just make swimming out here.
How far away is it right there?
Straight up.
Take the heal.
I was blow this thing to health.
Oh that lag.
Very quick.
Very quick indeed.
My apprentices.
Look at that bonus.
Look at that bonus for beating that in that amount of time.
I think we made back a couple of our awful mistakes that I made.
I would say so.
This is where I lost last time.
So for the purposes of me trying not to lose again.
Last time I did a six and did all chain guns.
This time we're going to stay with the baby three.
So I can try to get to the end of this game.
And I might not even get to the end of the game.
That's two expensive.
I think we do like a melee only build.
That's pretty awesome.
Where's the flamethrower?
Flamethrower.
Simple but undeniably potent in tight spaces.
This brutish weapon sprays pressurized gouts of highly flammable liquid.
We're going to need a lot more than that.
I would say we're going to need like that.
And you know I'm going to stay trumble.
No.
I'm just lying moderate.
You know, I'm not really wasn't really feeling it.
So we're going to have a backup here.
Back up.
This is the upgun.
Maximum 100,000.
What am I at right now?
That's way more than 100,000.
It's double 100,000 in fact.
Alright, we got our 200,000 dollar loadout just in case the flamethrower sucks.
We're going to try it.
Flamethrower always seemed to be amazing or terrible.
That's very true.
Let's hope it is the former.
Let's take a look.
That's not really even a flamethrower, man.
I guess it is.
That's very, very dangerous.
One problem I see with this weapon.
It's very blinding.
It's going to be hard for me to see incoming projectiles.
But we'll give it a go.
Another two repair.
This one sucks.
Again, we can go for speed.
Two repairs.
Wrap around right to the shield.
There's a couple of tech on the way.
How is this core surrounding?
Let me see this core.
There's one tiny little slot to get into this core room.
That's it.
It's right in the corner here.
That's a really awkward spot.
I don't know if it will find out.
Maybe it can reflect it.
We'll see.
Up here.
And then if I go down through here in there.
I actually might have enough time to take the alarm out.
And save myself a little bit of potential embarrassment.
We're using the flamethrower.
I've never used it before.
Probably a bad idea, but it's too late.
I just dropped $200,000.
Let's go ahead and go right.
I have the key.
For this purpose, let's go right in.
No, I don't have the key.
I don't have the key.
I'd say I'm going to go down.
Let's go down this way.
All right.
Boys and girls.
Flamethrower time.
Let's turn on flames.
I knew it was going to blind me, but it's very, very powerful.
In fact, it's so powerful.
It's still making the noise like I'm shooting it when I'm not.
Oh, what is hitting the fuck here?
God.
I don't like it.
It's too hard to see.
Oh, boy.
That's a guy.
This is still building.
Oh, boy.
Oh, I kind of can't reflect.
Yes, it can.
Oh, I can't.
I can absolutely reflect it.
Laser.
I like the sound of that.
All right.
Come on.
Right when I hit tab.
I wish I got plenty of time.
Let's just take a slow.
Hey, get slow.
I got a full six.
Oh, my God.
Surrounded down.
What the fuck did you come from?
I'm not going to be so hot.
Oh, my Lord.
Those things do so much damage.
They're so hard to kill.
Surprise.
I didn't get my life back.
All right.
We need to see.
Okay, straight up.
Straight up.
Literally straight up.
See you later.
No, no, no, no, no.
I'll go that way.
Let's do this right.
Let's do it right.
Oh, come on.
Come on.
Really?
No way.
Fuck.
This ain't happening.
Damn.
I just didn't like it a life here.
There's so many enemies here.
It's a left or dead.
Yeah, I got it, but I immediately died.
Oh, God.
Yeah, Flamethrower.
I think Flamethrower kind of stuck a fork in that one, unfortunately.
And I had a money.
And now I still have a little bit of money.
Flamethrower too short and blinds you, unfortunately.
I tried this one.
This game seems tough.
It is very tough.
But it's very fun.
It's very fun.
I got to try to salvage as much money as I can.
Well, and by salvage money, I mean the game is the game crashed.
No, what?
Yeah, I don't know how this still audio playing.
I'm not sure how this still audio playing.
Yeah, the game crashed.
That's too bad.
So where is it?
It's not on my taskbar.
Sounds like it's on the menu screen.
Oh.
It's still running.
But where is that running?
Well, there's that.
Well, we can just start it again.
Hold on a second.
I probably could salvage that too.
Unfortunately.
I'll try. I'll give it one more go.
I'm going to give it one more.
Start to finish.
Try to run through it.
I may or may not get to the last couple of places.
This is a very, very hard game.
But that's good.
That's like a good thing.
Can I continue?
Wait for.
I think so, alright.
Yeah, this is the same.
No, okay, we can keep going.
I guess it just crashed out and saved them.
There was a tutorial.
It was a pretty short one.
This is a very dark level.
I might have to rethink my entire strategy.
Going quick and trying to blow through.
I just get so scared of the time.
But I can't afford anything.
I have $133,000.
Highly recommend this though, guys.
Honestly, this is one of the more fun games in this category
that I've played since like Binding Vizek.
There's a lot of different loadout options.
There's a lot of very, very difficult things in the game.
But I don't understand what this is.
Does that mean it cuts through doors?
I don't know what that means.
See, the problem with playing through one of these games for the first time
and trying to figure out that last run
by using a flamethrower?
I blew $100,000 and lost the mission.
I had to figure out that I didn't like it.
But that's why it's cool.
Because you're going to play with all these items
and all these things,
and you're going to lose a shitload of times.
And you'll find the thing that you like.
And you'll do all your runs like that.
Oh no, what's the matter?
What are you doing?
True dead bone.
Just looking at me and just making like a...
Saw.
I just saw a saw.
Why do I feel like I'm going to make like a star comment?
Like the relatable gamer star?
I feel like if star played this game, he would just do all melee.
And he would beat the game in like 20 minutes
and be like, oh no, I didn't all melee run.
He'd show me.
And I'd be like, cool, whatever, dude.
Why does like melee...
I feel like melee guy is something that like star would do.
If you're watching right now star.
Do it.
Let's see it, you know?
Let's see it.
I don't know, maybe I think I'm going to change up my whole...
my whole scheme here.
I can't do that.
I don't have enough money.
Well, I'm absolutely not going to beat this one
because I have like no money.
132?
Are the key?
I'm... I'm...
I want to do the double spread shotgun.
Okay, let's try it.
Alright, I got nothing to lose really at this point.
Let's just see how that works.
That's a lot of recoil.
I'm like flying too far back.
I think that's going to screw with me.
To do the double spread.
Dangerous though.
I can spread him out.
I don't have to do it at the same time.
And that's probably not enough ammo.
How do you weigh more ammo than that?
Yeah, that's not going to work.
Oh.
Short wave scanners are getting interference.
It looks like there's an active jammersystem in this hole.
Great.
Now I'm definitely going to lose.
I'm going to give you a laser gintel on the rest of the ship.
Though I'm absolutely losing this one.
You guys want to see the end of this run?
It's going to happen right now.
You know what's even in there?
What is even in here?
Shield.
Jammer.
Cool, cool-aid jammer.
Let's go.
Get this shit, go.
Where's the shield up there?
Go.
There you go.
I don't even care.
Okay.
I can give a shit.
Let's go.
I can't fit down the little bot crack.
What the hell?
What the way?
No way.
That was dog shit.
I got stuck in the corner over there.
Oh my god.
I can't go.
Let's do it.
Where's the core?
Right down here.
We got technology.
I ain't even messing around right now.
I'm here for one purpose.
Where the brain?
Oh, get up.
Just die.
Huh?
I'm just gonna lock me out.
This guy's like locking me out.
Get out of the way.
Start praying.
Look, blow it up, blow it up, do it!
What did the explosion, did the explosion kill me?
What's going on?
It's a banana wave, skilled you.
All right, time for a fucking dog camp.
I'm just gonna lock you out.
You know what?
Time for a fucking dog camp.
When life's got you down, then you're getting your ass kicked in a video game.
It's just time for a fucking dog camp.
He's locking his ass.
Hey, hey, hey, you're on dog camp.
Don't you know that, buddy?
Hey, auto.
Got you.
You're on candid dog camp.