Ladies and gentlemen we are now live hello ladies and gentlemen welcome to the
stream where Star just writes countless things in the chat that she should
never have written and she's just being annoying good for him
oh my god that's a bad hold on a sex screen
what I just I had to do it quick oh my god you are such a professional
streamer boy I'm glad like oh I've been planning for weeks and weeks to stream
on a crack got you a month ahead even more time to prepare here is my like happy
meal BRB look I don't I don't have all that stuff I just barely got night bought to
work did you go to the night bought website and click a join chat yeah I couldn't
I'm sorry I'm moving in sorry I didn't have like I'm not I don't have like
city skylines and like cool lighting effects on all my stuff oh sorry you
don't have any talent wow can you believe this guy sometimes it's hard to
believe the things that come out of his mouth yeah like but whatever all right
let's switch over to Armacrow let me get my chat popped out so actually I
should probably should probably say I'm streaming this game right that's
probably should be you should and you should give people a second to join so
they don't miss the opening cut scenes don't worry I'm gonna make sure we're
gonna sit here and chat about this for a few minutes okay so don't worry about
it you should color in the face while we wait I can't do that you just
in you you're in the planet I'm done I'm doing I'm doing a little bit of a
tweet here I'm doing I'm using Twitter it's your favorite thing about Twitter
very quick thoughts very quick you know you can get your mind out there as soon as
you want you know you can get your brain to do things you normally don't do do
the government spying on Twitter I don't fucking know I'm hearing that I'm
way louder than you are you yeah when you look at OBS you can see the
speaking volume and your mic you know they're separate I use those to line up
which like the equalize them a bit better some pro streamer tips because I know
you've never done it is that better I don't know you're gonna have to ask you tell
me I just I think I just load your little worry about your tweets dude not
worry about the tweets just tell tell a story that but while we get started here
guys listen here's the story all about how I bel air
you're so suck so bad like if it was me if like you brought me into your
stream you like I'm gonna get some stuff set up like tell a story I'd be like
listen ladies gentlemen let's talk about what's all a story here yeah
oh let me tell you all the guys about my favorite cartoon character that appears
on branded material good go go for it let's hear it
on on jimima is she really nobody's on is that what she was known for what's her
deal does she really make that syrup drama did she really make that syrup I
I'm not even listening to a single word you're saying all right that that should uh
okay did that work all right I get I tweeted I use I use I use that the
the the Twitter function so we're gonna wait a minute here
um gays up snack find yourself a a nice place to sit because I don't want
people to miss the uh because this this is a let's play of I was just
threw up in my mouth what the hell was that my god I was like sick earlier
what's wrong with you like let's start the stream oh god
hey man just just let out all the voices in your head I don't have very many
a lot of all out all right
so how loud is this
okay guys how loud is this I want I wonder how loud this is I hope it's not too
loud I wonder how loud this is wonder if I want to mind or really made that
hey look it there we are
all right so what's the reason that I'm wondering what this is we're gonna just
just just sit here and enjoy this song I'm gonna enjoy this music is this the
like a rory music let me try it a little bit more you're about to play sport all right
well you can you listen to this how does this sound I thought you did the
I thought you could have played mobile games no not today not it sounds it sounds
better now okay okay so Armour Crog if you don't know what what this is we'll
give a brief synopsis of this before we actually start playing the game this is
one of my favorite games of all time was a neverhood came out like 20 years
ago it's a claymation game it's a point and click you walk around you interact with
stuff is a lot of dialogue and this is the the guys it made Armour Crog I mean
the guy that made neverhood made this game this was a kickstarter game and it's
really awesome because the guys that made the original game came together finally
after a long time to make a new one so hopefully they still have like every
they still have the passion and they still have the creativity like they did 20
years ago so we're gonna sit here for another five minutes maybe I'll turn up
the sound like during the cutscene maybe that should be better yeah yeah I was
listening to the volume yeah everything in general seems fine it's all a little
low people say I could barely hear but they don't understand that there's a
volume slider on the website twitch that television I'd look on the lower left
hand side of your screen you're gonna see a thing that looks like an old
tiny old-fashioned speaker that's not actually what speakers are really looking
like nowadays anymore but they still use that to help people understand you know
the same way there's a telephone all right so let's to cut you off this game
requires a pen and paper and I'm gonna say this right now I ain't speed running
this game I'm not going through this fast I want to enjoy this because I've been
waiting for like 20 years for this game to come up so I I might take a little
while in some places I might want to listen to songs and stuff like that so if
you're one of those people that's just like get on with it and do the puzzle
what are you doing you're probably not gonna you're probably gonna want to
just hang tight because this game is going to be like a chill I'm just gonna
play and run and hack up my little note pad here I could have scribbled some notes
on it and stuff you know how it is
yeah how many people are here like four like showed up I think you turned the
volume up by maybe just like the in-game volume you know like 10% boost then
no there's there's there's 10%
we're looking we're looking quite keen you know oh but you better not talk to
any cutscenes if you speak during a cutscene I am just going to end I'm gonna
end the call I'm I'm just gonna get out of here the only thing I'm gonna say
during a cutscene that I'm not saying anything
all right so here we go that's your answer yeah I got my pen I got my paper I
got my coffee I got my little dog to the right we're gonna play on the
Crock so here we go
okay okay beakeake I'm just glad we're still alive yeah me too now let's get a
look at the hole yeah this does not look good I don't think our pot insurance is
gonna cover this the doctorable is nuts too beakeake look at that what do you
make of this guy oh and I'm like
beakeake
baby well
little wing buddy hey that's what I'm here for
look good enough for me let's go in hold on hold on we don't know what's inside
there could be Carpacian rain stuckers
here we are beakeake what is this place got me I know this looks too hard I think I'd
stop here actually but I'm gonna do this because it probably would be a good idea
let's turn on some subtitles that probably helped all right so this is me there's
Tommy not there's little dog okay I can click on the dog and move the dog around so you
control two characters in this game all right interesting well let's go pick up this
take a look outside yeah I am a little louder no no whatever I don't worry about it man
what the hell was that
haha all right I got I got to pay attention because the these guys the neverhood guys they put
random weird clues that you'll need like four hours from now in these rooms in these first
rooms if I remember from the last game there's a lot of wacky shit so
just take a look at some of the stuff over here I mean that was that was 20 years ago do you
think you're gonna need to know the information from 20 years ago that'd be cool if you did
and I can't click on this from the back of the box the cell number that looks like that looks
like a dog hole but you know okay I just bought here there we go okay easiest pie
this room is so cool I am gonna apologize in advance like I'm gonna take in every single room
what is that is that a piece of cheese it's like a fuzzy piece of cheese
I knew you'd come you've traveled far yet your true journey begins through the exit unseen
okay anything else know this to open one door you must block another
as the beast blocks your entrance your exit shall appear okay can I do anything over here
the spot up there it looks like let's go touch let's go touch this guy
okay
now that looks important the light bulb up there I can I jump can I touch it
no I can't I can go over it can I yeah I can go down button press symbol right it down
right this down they don't put random symbols like this in the game I'm telling you right now guys
get your notebooks ready what would you call this room light bulb room right
I would call it spaghetti that's not that good I why you see no you see the big spaghetti in the background
tell me that's not some pasta wall kind of is yeah that's yeah my way this down okay light bulb room
we're gonna call this I don't know what you call that like a super Mario ship right
I spaghetti room with a crouton
all right well the dog looks like you can fit down here
I wonder what the light on whoa whoa this is oh god this is trippy
what's that what did I just eat
shit I should have paid attention with the way I just ate something I don't know what the hell it was
I'm gonna come out the doggy door right yeah first control I there's another symbol right
this one down there's another symbol what I wait a hold on a second
uh it's a box
all right a little swirly in the middle and then two squares next to it
can you do it can you do anything else can I go walk in now this door is closed
jelly roll that's a good day for it yeah jelly roll looks like the end of an arm chair
yes me dude kind of does he's not tall enough to grab that but
okay I got another symbol though so that's good to know now is this because the light is on
what are the lights off because I don't think I can switch back to Tommy not
what happens if I turn let's put the light on and try that again but
oh he just puked up a lever oh shit
uh I just ate it again
what does the second lever go oh no this you okay there's a lever in this next room
over here I remember I remember there it is
so that opens that door that door I couldn't open before I can push this fuzzy guy I love this character by the way
the fuzzy guy yeah well what what the fuck
fuzzy guy has no emotions he's your character
okay well whatever you want him is a symbol okay it can go up I'm leaving beak beak behind though
whoo smells like bacon in here
I kind of feel like I need to click this greetings friend I am Abraham Lincoln
one two
there was one two one two three one I'm gonna see that again hold on
Ant Lincoln
two three one okay Ant Lincoln
two three one was there anything else in there what what what what what what what what should
what one two three four five lines I have no idea what this means I'm sure maybe the
later I'll figure it out what's the significance you think of him being the tallest American
president um white quite the stature even without the other top idol for James Madison
James Madison five four really didn't stand up to anything Abraham Lincoln had accomplished
I say politicians have to be tall I think you're gonna have to be tall to do one of these puzzles
yeah yeah I'm not I don't think I'm tall enough to do this puzzle
well this obviously correlates to the ant guy so I mean I see a couple top charts on that top
row you're scrolling by any of these symbols guard chair was on the top row yeah I thought it
was two but does that mean anything this is the only role that's lit up
well can't you push them down who's the ups and the downs yeah I guess oh yeah I can
shell okay yeah cool geez I guess I guess I have to make what you do without me so let's let's
try to make the uh the jelly roll right well can I do I don't think I even will hold on
there any more swords too
I'm gonna come back to this in a second I want to go down to
I want to look at this one more thing because I want to turn the light on and let him go down
go down there can you not go down there whoa well let's head back down
oh boy wow look at this look at this feel like this has something to do with it
oh does it yeah it does right I mean it black why wouldn't it
oh man I can remember so this is obviously the top row right
okay I'm gonna I'm gonna come back to this room but I do want to turn that light on
so you go in there now that it's on because there might be something else in here I didn't see
can I hear your dog rising up well I can hear it hold on it's very faint
just had to point out um you had a real horn dog
why did you have to find that out you would only know what it was if you were listening for it
yeah okay well obviously that's the same so let's go back in this room can I what does the light
have to be on all right please thank you again a loose bike of closure
so I should probably write some of these down all right let's make this let's make this circle
here what I don't with these symbols even up there
can I get a look at these let's see this guy can just tell me anything
okay in turn you shall find two rooms in the round
hmm in turn you shall find two rooms in the round interesting I'm gonna go look and see if those
symbols are up there if these symbols are up there then obviously that's the first second
thread bro
Ant Lincoln does this again greetings friend I am Abraham Lincoln I could just take
pictures with my phone you're right why does he take so long to do the third one
okay where are those
not noticing any really
that's like astronauts and
I bet I get maybe there's one picture in here that I can even make
can you reset that thing to default I wonder maybe it'll just go to default no
I feel like there's just one picture in here that you can actually make
you know I mean like why would this line be here it's it's obviously telling me that
there's something has to be in these three lines right so what can be right moving them each
in the number of clicks that he did possibly but I mean there's got to be one picture I can make here
well that's that guy's face downstairs
yeah the yellow button is to say hey I did it
well it just for fun let's do it was two three one right yeah but that doesn't
doesn't that that doesn't determine up or down no
it's definitely a picture you have to make in this row but what is the picture
I'll check Instagram check Instagram
scales
there's anything else I can click on here no
who's that it's got to put the glasses on
it has to involve the jelly roll right that's the thing that's been
well
hold on I want to go back to the first room because remember I don't think I pushed
I didn't push that thing all the way forward can I keep pushing this I think I can right yeah
should be able to no I guess not
not I guess not
what about this this is the only row that like is full
in turn you shall find two rooms in the round
now that just opens the door
yeah I'm gonna send the dog back in
well go and go in I think he actually used to be in the room
symbols of this show have to mean something
me
all right look that okay all right all right all right all right all right that jelly roll is
in that spot look at one two three jelly rolled absolutely goes in the left spot
but apps are positive a little why would they have these three squares so if that's the first one
what determines the second and third slot
is it the two things the two things I broke down but were those even pictures I don't remember
let's go find out
but yeah the jelly roll app is in the first spot
let's just let's go back to that room when do you get it gone
hmm I want to look at the symbols again that were on this thing
I love it this is a heart it's like beating okay let's get the jelly roll here
there is all right this has to be in this spot I can't put this anywhere else it has to be here
now where is
anything else all right
is there a spike that kind of looks like it right not really though
oh
well can I maybe I can see oh geez Louise you can fucking go higher whatever happened here
it was not good all right well we figured it out we could go up a rub look at this guy
can you go any higher yes there's even more all right there's a whole lot going on here let's
holy shit that's gross can I talk to this guy yeah you're gonna want to write that down
term and there were a lot of people saying they salted it already even without knowing you could
go up this isn't really doing anything sure you this is going to walk over here
okay another piece to pick up I should probably take this
can't put anything in here
I guess I can't walk over here yet can the dog go over there no I like did get another lever
this looks very important look at that mess I'm gonna have to figure that out eventually
this remind I believe is the important room
anything I can do in here well this is where the lever goes
okay
there's two rooms in the ground I guess I had to just keep going what about that can you do
anything with that dog yes you can nice work peak peak this is a cool room
oh
hopefully oh I've seen these symbols too
yep this square was on top of the octopus I don't I gotta turn the machine on though
right I think I do
I
turns on a vacuum he has to go up there
do I have enough time to get there
I'm not sure right that down maybe I should write that part down
so one thing I have noticed is yes these correspond to certain rooms right that down
I don't need to write down yet I must get a remember
can the dog come in the dog can't come in here no right that dog
can I make it before this now I can't
anything else in here that I need to
is there a crystal floating up there
but we talked about the notebook this is why you have the notebook
now I'm gonna go back to the other room let's figure out the first thing first
because these things might not all be in the same order
is there still another room to go into
so see here I want to I want to just remember this because look up here
that rectangle right here
corresponds to the octopus these three prongs
was this game handmade yes it was this whole game is made out of clay and stuff and blocks and
word and all kinds of cool things
there's a button press the button
move the dog has to press it
can why don't you press the button please
touch it it's got a lightning bolt on it I need to write that down
lightning bolt over button
there a lightning bolt was also over the car the top right oh it was
I don't need more that's down maybe that's how you power the that's probably how you power the car
so I guess you go
you know I'm gonna put the dog in here obviously another trippy freaky ass room
feel like we're getting closer to solving the first Abraham Lincoln puzzle
oh there it is there's the second symbol there's the second symbol
I'd call that I'd call that
Pac-Man's cousin eating a lightning bolt
now theoretically the here's like the theoretical right we could go do that and then just
wild guess on the third one and get it eventually uh germa
that is actually baby carriage can struck by lightning I don't want to make sure you got that
that symbol right no it's Pac-Man's super cool sideburn brother
eating a lightning power up in the new Pac-Man's cousin game it's a different power up
oh okay I still haven't played that one yeah remember that though okay let's go back
this is armacrog it's currently oh I just clicked out of the window whoops
let's see if we can actually finish that puzzle
go back down
Pac-Man Elvis impersonator that there there you go there it is
okay where is it
hmm this is not lined up correctly is it
there's that one can I get the jelly back here though
where's the jelly I gotta get it in the right spot
oh this is tough this is like a puzzle within a puzzle
no is there only one it must have to be like perfectly lined up
what the hell is the jelly
there it is oh oh okay I get it okay let's see if that's the one
yeah but I don't know what the last symbol is there's no way to tell
you just have to spam it see which the last one I gotta get it video no I didn't
always it just no it's just different every time I thought I had it all right well there's
no way to determine that because I might have to move these around too like this so we need to find
that last symbol it's only like 50 other possibilities
one thing that's been a common factor here is the dog is the one that sees them so
did I miss an area where he can go I don't think I did
go back in here
I touch anything in this room
don't think so
I feel like I should be able to press this button
for some reason I can't I don't know
I know
bohoo ok that is symbol is in this room
Star pay attention that symbols in this room. Oh, thanks little buddy. Oh
That lowered it I still can't operate this though
Okay, right that down
Yeah, the right it down
down
So for that to activate that has to be there so I can't do that puzzle until that room is in the right spot
That's different
Oh, wait, what the fuck is this thing?
I'm like scared to go in this room. I feel like he's gonna eat me
Oh boy
What was that
It's a it's baby
Can you imagine the wandering monsters this thing is attracting I'm just saying
Tommy Tommy don't touch that thing you don't know where it's fun
Oh
P
Okay
There you go Tommy not has you now I'll take care of you and I'll just strike that baby with lighting figure out how to get you back to where you belong
So I hold I have there's put the baby in my wife when I just put that baby
I'm gonna deliver
A little weird look at this thing
Something else has to be in this room. This is a weird pattern for the cracks
Was that a symbol I don't remember
Well, just remember that's a good square with the
I got what what can I do with that lever
Can't grab any of this stuff can I
Cracks weird pattern right that down
Yeah, that lever has to go somewhere so let's find out where I was gonna remember that weird crack symbol looking thing
Please cry wait what I'm like pulling up oh boy
Um, so I can't leave oh
Shit
Did I get it
Oh
It's a song
It's not right
That goes there right
Okay, that's in the right spot. So yeah, these two just need to be flipped
This is the one
Write that down write that song down didn't even need to write it down
I get blow it
Oh
I can take the other ones off oh
I hope that doesn't mean I have to take off the punch of these
So the back ones are the ones that are correct
Oh
Yeah
Just wrap them all off
All right, so it goes
No, no, I've worked I got it
You threw up a well that was interesting
So there's one of these crystals pick it up please
There was another crystal in the other one back here, but I got a lever right
Let's find where that lever needs to go I think it's up here
No
Go back up there to me
I
Can probably now use this to repress the button
Thank good thing star was there to contribute and tell me what I needed to do
Pull it
Huh the hell's he doing?
Is he all right, who's this freaking out?
So I have to power it on but I couldn't press that button before
Maybe was can he just go no
There's no power here the power needs to be turned on in this room
I am going to piss my pants by the way I
Can't I got it I got to get this first like area done
Before I piss my pants
It's really important
Now we're gonna turn the room back to where it was
Now what is what is
This means that there's power when I turn it to the right spot
You know what I mean I mean I know I have to like oh turn the power on but that light turned on
Because there's some connection that has to be made to this button
I'm I'm just gonna say that I'm gonna try that I'm gonna make I'm gonna turn this so the light turns on because then there's
Maybe germ hour
And regards to the power if I assume you do with the green Nickelodeon sludge in the pipes in the room below that is the room you can't get into
Maybe I want to try this first. That's my vibe I'm getting I just want to see because that like the light is on now
I wonder if that does anything
Okay, germa
If you say boss
Okay
The dial upstairs can be used
This turning this
All right, so that turns remember where that is so see what happens when I spin stuff
Wow spin the wind
Because this there are things all over this
All right, yeah, so that's changing
Do it again this is a speedrun
Well, that was kind of that was buggy
One more time maybe
I
Got a quiz have you been writing these things down star I've written everything down that has happened I am the cartographer good
What's the quiz
The quizzes just did that there was no quiz
It's gonna be on a test
You know it might just be can I just not press the button? I feel like it's not I feel like it's gonna be lined up when that room is
Connected I
Really do I feel like when that room is connected to the one with the button and it'll be lined up, but I can't press the button
Hope that's not a bug. I
Hope that isn't a bug
You can hear what I said you moron
Too busy paying attention to the video game
Go look in the power room again
You're gonna agree with you once you see it
You talk about the green slime. Yeah, and they glow to in goo. Yeah
You need to amp up that goo way before you can power
There's no way to work. I want to just get this in the right spot. I
Never gonna do it dude
Shit
Can those even line up I feel like it
All right, let's see. It's probably gonna be lined up
With thank right
No, it isn't
I don't even feel like
Be worried about this right now. No, but I just wanted to make sure I wanted to get it in the right spot that power
So you're saying in this room you're talking about in here, right?
like this
Green go shit. Yeah, it's a very low and the room below that the where you didn't imagine the green
Group is coming from you can't get into yet. So I'd leave this until you figure that out. Yeah
I just wish I could press the button. I
Just love pressing buttons. I know I do
Every time I press button I write it down
Yeah, the squiggles are aligned now
Right no
Dude, I'm gonna buy the game and raise you raise me
Those other one I didn't do on I want to do this
It's a lot of trial and error to see if this works
I did skip one although you're getting the error heart down right
What is on it? Let's go look under there
Yeah, cuz I can't get in this room
Man, I wish I could just like accidentally get this
And let's wait a second wait a second wait a second wait just a second
Like maybe this is like a go symbol, right? Maybe it's like a green go symbol
The third and most important symbol has been that lightning bolt. Is there a lightning bolt symbol?
Let's find out that's true. The lightning bolt is on the baby carriage, so maybe not
Is there a baby maybe that's a baby?
oh
As this calls these collete's a baby
No.
All right, well, I think we could sit here and wild guess as much as we want.
But that's not going to work.
So I can't get in this room, have to get in this room to figure out the power, so maybe
we go down.
Can I touch this?
Can I do anything here?
Greetings, friend.
I am Abraham Hantling.
Let's take a look at the...
Nothing in the middle row, at least speaks to me.
Try it, though.
Got it.
Oh boy, this is not good.
What does that do?
Oh Jesus.
Are you serious?
I got to like freeze the room.
I got to line this up.
Uh.
Let's go all the way to the left.
You can only go a certain amount of ways, right?
What does that mean?
Slow down.
Oh, okay, so one, two, two.
I guess I have to make it hit it twice.
There needs to be two in the middle.
Yeah, I think that's what you have to do.
Oh shit, no, it's doing, okay, see what it's doing?
It's doing each part of you.
Oh, yeah, man, dude, come on, man.
I really do think of it as part of the scene.
So it's gotta go over here.
It's like a, it's a safe.
It's a lock.
So let's try this.
Let's get this one here.
So that one is not frozen.
Let's see.
That one will start to move.
I'm assuming this is the answer, right?
Let's try and do that again.
Let me go to the right.
I'm going to assume this is correct.
There it is.
All right, so this is the line, power, check, and I should be able to press the button now.
Should I pull this?
No.
I'm scared to pull that.
I don't want to let you reset it.
So let's go back up.
Now go back in this room.
I wonder if we have a thing I can do if I can press the button.
One more.
We all doubted him.
He's a genius.
Nothing, not really.
Ah.
Well, shit.
The camera didn't solve it the way that I wanted.
This is connected now.
So now, okay, now, this should be power to it.
If I get to the power side.
All right.
I'm going to go up there first just to make sure.
I don't want to spin the, I can't press that button.
I love this song, by the way.
I want to listen to it for a second.
Look at this complete.
Shit.
There's one of the tubes.
Now, the real question is, is this going to be lined up?
If the power turns on here.
So now, okay, we got power.
I wonder if this is going to be out of alignment now.
Not still in alignment.
But I don't think there's any power.
No, there's not.
Gotta hit that button.
I have to activate that button.
I got to suck up the dog in that vacuum.
I'm going to go back down here.
I'm going to look in here one more time.
No, I don't want to change that.
What does he have to say anything?
Nothing.
All is in your hands now.
The threshold has been crossed.
Who is this by the way?
Is that like Noah?
I don't think there's anything I'm doing here.
I'm going to go to the vacuum room.
I'm definitely going to pee though.
I'll let you guys enjoy this while I go pee.
I'll be back in like two minutes.
Quick bathroom break.
I'm going to go over this in my head.
Somebody's just making like what's your fart noises?
All right, I'll be right back.
I'm going to just pee.
Here's my professional hold on screen.
I'll be right back.
Start.
Tell them a funny story.
I want to be your funny story.
Once upon a time,
Jerma played our frog.
He was um...
One spawn time.
I was never been writing down any jokes.
I really haven't been paying that much attention.
It's really hard to follow what's been going on on screen
because he's saying everything like 15 seconds ahead of me seeing it.
That's typical streamer boy stuff.
Yeah, the stream was really dead without you.
Where are you dude?
I thought I heard a door.
Maybe that was a door in real life.
Yeah.
Just sitting here at the Elmo screen.
Here you come out.
I hope the story was good.
I think people are still laughing about it.
It was awesome.
Okay, let's go over a couple things in my brain here.
I have a crystal.
I have the power turned on.
What was the power run?
I actually had the power in it.
Now the stream is boring again.
That turned us back.
You know what you can do.
You can suck an egg.
What a weird insult that is.
Thanks little buddy.
That's pretty weird.
Can this be activated now?
Maybe if I put something up here.
I feel like the dog has to be in here with me.
Can I weigh that down?
Maybe I can put the baby on the green thing?
Maybe too.
Obviously the dog has to go up there.
But how do I get...
I might have to actually put the baby on that.
Kill the baby.
Because this doesn't really seem to do anything yet, at least.
You know that baby vomited it?
I get threw up and gave it that green crystal.
And then you suck it to vomit back in your stomach with it.
So?
I can't go on here.
Can't interact with that.
Alright, let's go over a couple of things.
I have a crystal.
I need to turn the power on so I can use the roller coaster.
And then there's the vacuum there that he sucked the dog up.
And the dog ends up up here.
I'm assuming, right?
He comes out of one of these tubes.
Whatever.
I can't really keep him there either.
I'm gonna go back in the room.
There's nothing else in there besides the dog.
That's just free.
He's going up.
He goes in here and he comes up the other side.
Let's want to look at this again.
Can he go anywhere?
I don't think he can go anywhere else.
Alright.
He can't do this either.
And click every single inch of this.
Because that is right in his wheelhouse.
He's ready to press this button.
Look at how ready he is just to put his face in the button.
At least you should be able to press it, right?
Even if it doesn't do anything.
Maybe it's just an indicator.
Otto, what are you doing?
I'm going to go down.
I'm going to look at the orange thing.
This can't be interacted with.
These don't mean anything yet.
Oh, hold on.
Hold on a second.
Wait a second.
That's the same type of button that's up there.
Where if we just turning the power off down here means the power on upstairs can be turned on.
That would be crazy if that's what this was.
That is a very never-hoot thing if that's what the problem is.
Like, oh, you can't.
You've got to use the power upstairs.
I guess not.
Should have wrote that down.
Does the octopus talk?
No, he doesn't.
I wonder if you can make him like stay.
Trying to think about what hasn't been done.
The only thing I can think of is trying to get into the crystal room, but that power is not like on.
Maybe the power has to be on here.
Then I can put the dog on here and then go in and do that.
Try that. Maybe this works.
See what that does.
Nice work, beak, beak.
You know what I mean?
Now is this turned on?
No, the dog come with me.
Fucking stopped.
I'm stopped.
Let's take the dog back through here.
Try to have the dog talk to the octopus and the weird.
That's a good idea.
That's a very good idea.
I'm going to do that.
Maybe he'll tell me something like,
you need to turn the power on, press the button.
That's not the right room.
I hope that works.
Otherwise, I'm not entirely sure what else to do.
Any thoughts?
Start.
Tell me on the loud paper.
I really forgot that people could even hear.
I would have just been spacing out.
Yeah, you've been totally spaced out.
Oh fuck.
No, I wanted to click on...
Damn it, come on.
Can I hold this?
No.
Yes, I can.
Hey, move on to click on that again.
You hit the baby with lightning yet.
No.
I have not.
You can't do that.
Yeah, I mean, this is a game by the guys that made the neighborhood.
So there are...
It's very, very much.
You have to remember a lot of things.
I'm in it for the long haul though.
It might take me a little while, but I'm in it for the long haul.
I'll be back in three weeks.
Yeah, see you in like six months.
You're just turning this lever.
What do I do?
Alright, please let me talk to the octopus as the dog in the secret world.
That's an MMO.
There we go.
Hey you.
Oh, it worked.
I don't speak this language.
Can't write this all down.
Yeah, I don't speak this language.
I don't speak this language.
Can't write this all down.
I need a good job.
I'm a man.
You are a man.
Another new entertainer,
Hasan Feed.
O God.
The city right,
Gujaba Ra,
Hasan Feed.
Deray Aftal Ojaba.
O God.
I'm a man.
So these people were all killed?
O lasyenas,
the crew lay.
Deravasi,
in Nakh,
the sea.
Ua,
Uas,
a Ua,
a Ura,
a sun,
a Miqas,
a Ederdab.
Yasi,
his
Mom
and
dead
I'd like to hear the transcript. What is it?
Trava Nevi, Bobby, dad, Trava Vichara, Trava, Flafi, Flafla, Trava, Flafla, Flafla, Flafla.
Yeah, I just-
That was just by this first part.
Just in case I'm gonna see if-
Why do I feel like this game would be trivial and really easy if you spoke galactic space octopus?
I picked up a thing, right?
Yeah, what if that entire thing just told you every single puzzle?
It sounded like it was telling you at least two or three of them.
I think- it probably was.
It probably was-
At least at the beginning it was like, okay, you use this one, this one you go here and you're gonna need that.
Oh, it puked.
I think my audio may have gotten screwed up.
Yeah, I have no- the game is not making any more like sounds.
Wow, quiet world, dude.
Let me save it and restart it.
I think that's-
Yeah.
You'll find a Cooper.
Okay, hold on.
Yeah, I've lost audio.
We ran into a bug.
There's a bug after that cutscene sometimes, maybe you lose all audio.
Save the game.
Audio.
Ha, ha, ha.
Well, it sounds back now.
Is it just not in some places?
Yeah, it killed the audio in random places.
That's where that fits.
Now I can probably press the button.
Yeah, I want to-
I want to-
Hold on a second.
Hold on, just one second.
Should lower my volume to a little bit.
I- I kind of can't because you're coming through the same line as the game.
Can't you lower Skype's volume in Windows?
I've done it.
That is what I have done.
Do it a little more.
Okay, it's like-
Shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up.
Oh my god.
Really, why did you draw Elmo on the screen?
That's not Elmo.
Is it you?
Is it supposed to be you?
You're not that handsome.
Hey, I am that handsome.
I am that handsome with my funny eyes and funny nose and big mouth.
It's kind of a llama mouth.
I've turned you down to like 10%.
And the next one, I don't know if it's going to help.
Should have done zero.
Zero.
All right, let me reload again.
Let's hope we have-
Hey, look at that.
We got audio again.
What is switch event away that like if you clap or laugh, like you can hear the laugh track.
You can hear everyone's laughs.
But if they say words, it like you can't get them through.
It's only claps and laughs.
Now I can press the buttons.
See, I couldn't- there we are.
All right.
We did it.
I didn't do anything.
That's really cool looking.
That's so cool.
Now I can use the thing and fly around.
And fly around on the go kart.
Oh, wait a minute.
There we go.
We're both in here.
Wow, yeah, this is great.
I'm going to go to the back.
Let's move.
I remember this was in the neighborhood.
This is so cool.
I'm going to go to the back.
It looks like there's a little spot to go in.
Hey, look, remember that thing that I already got?
I already guessed it.
So that's a- I like was a step ahead.
This is where I go that way, though.
How do I get up there?
Well, we're going to go all the way around.
Wee!
Hopefully this weird octopus lady doesn't say anything strange to me.
She's going to go like,
what the hell that means?
Let's keep going.
Ah.
Oh, do it again.
I'm going to go down first.
Just in case it's something down here.
Shit.
Nevermind.
I'm going to go up.
Go on.
Those are symbols from these.
I remember the bush.
Let's speed through this.
Can I go down?
Maybe?
I wonder.
Nope.
I'm going to keep going to the right.
New area.
Because of that's how you go in here.
So we're not going to do that yet.
Uh.
Well, here we go.
I obviously have to put this down there.
Okay, this is going to take me a minute.
I only have one going at a time.
Only one can fit in at a time.
You definitely have to clear out the bottom.
This one's going to be tough.
I'm going to get them all over on one side, I think.
For instance, this is going to go all down here first, maybe.
Shit.
All three of those can go up here now, right?
I don't know.
Where's the bottom?
Bottom's over there.
Let's get the bottom out.
Get the bottom out first.
Let me talk to them.
You're having trouble.
Hey, you're the one having trouble.
Oh, shit.
I think I actually can move this one here.
Want to talk about a German?
I did kind of screw myself with that.
Actually, no, not really.
Now I can just do that.
I bet if you used the baby, you could just skip this.
Maybe.
Maybe, maybe.
Complete.
Hey, you having some trouble, star?
Me?
No, I did it.
Why would I be having trouble?
I don't know.
Is there a trouble, some per- another one of these octopus people?
Is it a dog?
Food bowl?
Is it dog bowl?
Eat out of that dog bowl.
I command you.
Up here looks like a haunted house.
Grass coming over here.
I'm assuming something's going to come out of there in land and he's going to eat it.
Just how do you want to take a look at the rooms?
Hmm.
Interesting.
Doesn't seem to be doing anything at the moment.
You have to turn it on.
Can you grab that dude?
Do you want to pull the lever?
Is there a reason why you don't want to do that?
Okay.
Let's see what's in this room.
Yeah, looks kind of familiar.
Here's this guy again.
Okay, inspire others to great heights and your objectives shall be reached.
You didn't say it again.
Totally shit.
You want to read a whole book?
Oh man, this is a long.
This is a lot of lore.
What if I had to read this whole thing to figure out a certain puzzle?
I probably will.
Knowing these guys, I probably will have to read this whole thing.
Well, we'll find out if I need to or not.
Write it down.
Write down that entire script.
Well, let's just have him stand on that and see what happens.
Maybe I can just stand on it.
Turn the lights off.
I'm just going to keep him there.
Maybe he can stay there.
Alright.
I pull the lever now.
Jesus.
I'm not even sure where to start here.
Is there some color coding that needs to be thought of here?
Let's go from room to room to see.
Well, these are symbols.
I don't know if these mean anything, but they probably do.
And they're wearing things too.
It needs astronaut has to be the right.
Let's pull this again.
Let's see what happens.
Kind of scrambles it a little bit.
I'm going to go outside here because I haven't been out here since the...
It's been dark.
I guess it doesn't really affect out here that much.
I'm going to turn the lights back on because they had badges.
Turn the lights back on.
Okay.
Big peak.
Green.
Guess what, guys?
Hey, guess what?
Write it down.
Green.
Red.
Purple.
Blue.
Yellow.
Orange-ish.
Line those up.
Somehow by using your skills of deduction.
Still don't know what this does.
Star, are you going to contribute or what?
I don't think he's even here.
I don't think he's here.
Let's just see what happens.
Wait a second.
Is it combining the colors?
I think it's combining them to make these colors.
Let's see.
This is correct.
I didn't think it couldn't buy.
Are you leaving?
I'm going to go tell Ash.
Green.
Okay, got that one.
Look, you haven't even said all you told me to do was strike the baby with lightning.
Oh, good.
That was great advice.
These are color coded and then some way you're going to have to line them up.
What do you think I'm doing?
What do you want me to tell you?
I didn't even need star's help.
Get out of here.
Can I have you listen to this?
I can have a story on the top of one.
I didn't think you were going to get by.
Waiting for a story.
If you want a story, read the one on the wall.
Oh, do it.
Everyone wants to hear it.
No, no, no, it's a lot.
It's a long, long, long.
You're like not going to want to talk again after you do it.
Another one of these guys.
Hold on, we get a great song.
Hold on.
I need to listen to this.
It's got an accordion.
This music is so great.
Terry Scott Taylor, you are genius.
I'm going to push this in the other room.
Can I look out here?
I can't look out the window.
I want to get down.
I can't push him.
I like to go down here.
I guess not.
I can't even push him.
I really want, somebody saying I want one of these.
It'd be cool to have one of these.
Something to put on your desk.
A paperweight.
What did that, I got a lever.
A lever in the first room.
That allowed me to get the lever to put into something here.
Maybe.
No, no.
I just want to make sure there's nothing out here that I missed.
Besides the weird birds.
I actually am going to write this down.
See this octopus?
This purple octopus has this symbol.
We're going to say P-Octo.
I'm going to draw that.
P-Octo.
This first symbol.
The other one was orange, right?
It was an orange octo.
It orange lives.
He had the rectangle.
Oh, octo.
I had the rectangle.
Okay, let's go down.
Just make sure I can't go any further.
There is another area.
Another power symbol.
Let's start at the bottom.
And there's a lever.
What?
The lever doesn't go here.
Are you kidding me?
The lever doesn't go there.
I can't do anything here.
I need another lever.
You're progressing too far.
There were things I didn't do in the other room.
You got backtracking.
You got to go backwards at some point.
This is so cool.
This is bird shit.
I love stuff like this.
This is probably real bird shit.
That's a place for a lever.
Whoa.
That was cool.
That was really cool.
It just stretched out the accordion room.
Hey, I remember this.
We wrote it down.
And what was it?
Oh, fuck.
What are you?
Come on.
Two, three, one.
What?
Oh.
It's got to be the right color too.
It's got to be the right colors.
Okay.
I actually don't know.
This has been just shown up a couple times, I think.
Well, we can't do this one yet.
I need to know what the colors are.
Can I do anything with these birds?
Let me save it.
I want to make sure I save the game often.
There is an auto save.
I never know.
It could run into like a crash.
The colors.
Actually, I'm going to write the symbols down to.
Because that would make sense, right?
My notebook is all screwed up.
I got scribbles everywhere.
This is not right.
The colors.
I'm going to write it all.
This is just incorrect.
Squirrely symbol with the crown.
Then we got giant mustache.
And then we got the shoe.
That looks like a shoe kind of like a Yoshi foot.
Okay.
Let's go back.
Everything in here might have changed as well.
It did.
Look at the color.
Dude.
Here is another power machine.
I'm assuming I have to get it from the octopus.
Yeah, check out the color.
That's blue.
That's blue button, ain't it?
A lot of rooms here.
I'm almost Jefferson.
I have to sign the declaration of independence.
I need it to be my quill.
There they are.
Oh, it's like doing the subtitles now.
Okay, it was purple green.
Purple green yellow.
Got the colors.
We got the colors boys and girls.
Thomas Jefferson.
Now what the hell does that do?
Hey, remember what the colors were.
I'm assuming that turns on this vacuum.
That can't be turned on because there's no power.
Stretching.
Yeah, I was remembering the colors.
Yeah, what the hell?
You're just like saying you're repeating yourself very slowly.
Purple green and yellow.
Oh, shit.
No, purple.
You messed it up and that's all I've been talking about.
Well, I'm trying to concentrate.
And there's a guy just like going.
Green yellow.
Do I vote him?
What do you guys think?
Should I?
I vote him before I like I already clicked it.
But I mean, do you want to get voted?
Oh, what?
I don't deserve that kind of truth.
There's the quill.
Let's go back to Thomas Jefferson.
Give Thomas Jefferson the quill.
I'm seeing a lot of yeses.
I'm seeing a lot of yes, boedal.
What does he do with the quill?
Is he going to write me a parchment?
You say the colors one more time like that.
And you're gone.
You're out of here.
I have to go to the bathroom.
You're such a lame.
We're gonna miss you.
Let's go.
Quill to pay for.
Send to Tennany.
What does that mean?
I guess we're gonna murder them.
I don't know what it means, but it's like a constellation kind of.
You talk to the ant president so you could get it.
There's definitely going to be like a George Washington or something like George Washington ant.
Is that it?
Actually, I want to see what the colors on that.
Yeah, I wish I could vote you, but I can't.
I guess the colors don't matter here.
In Congress today.
Okay.
Yes, this is made.
The creator of Earthworm Jim did make all these characters and he's like the creator.
Co-creator, I guess.
There's another bunch of people that worked on it.
What does that do for me?
There's a bunch of rooms I still haven't gone in.
Wasn't there something?
Oh, shit.
That's a symbol.
Write it down.
What color is it?
Well, I, uh, something I, uh, something is a speaking of ants.
There's, there's an ant that's bothering me right now and he's about to get booted.
So, you know, let's give him a countdown.
Oh my god.
If you'd end up needing to know what color that symbol was, you're gonna, you're really gonna regret this.
Wait, what?
It's just like a Soviet.
He's God, baby.
Let me write this down.
He really wanted to get that last word too.
It's just like a ship.
Yeah, poor, poor drunk star.
He had the kid somewhere to go anyways.
He needs to go eat food.
Yeah, get, why don't you get shocked, jocked.
Climb back up.
Oh, damn.
Can we go par?
How does he get up there?
He told me to be, to be fair, right?
To be fair.
He was just typing very loudly and then would just say the colors.
Maybe what am I supposed to, what am I supposed to say?
You get booted.
That is that, that, okay, so that's where the dog comes out.
You talk to the person.
Is there a dog hole I didn't go into?
Go back up here.
He was writing things down.
No dog hole here.
That doesn't bring it back up.
I need to see what I can do.
Can you go in the sewer?
Yeah, we need a dog hole.
Maybe did I miss one that was done here?
There was a button to press.
I'm gonna get that from that lady.
I'm gonna get...
Shit.
Where is there another dog hole?
Maybe...
Hey, Sean, what's going on, dude?
Did anybody see a dog hole?
There was the exit from the dog hole.
Maybe I can't climb it and put them through.
And there's no power.
There won't be power until I talk to the octopus person.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, hold on just a second here.
Oh, I got it.
Hold on.
Whoa, no, no, no, no.
I gotta make that symbol.
The symbol is from here.
I need to determine where these guys are moving
because I wrote that symbol down.
That's the first one, right?
No, it goes down to the right.
No, that's not it.
Hmm.
I had him in the right spot.
Well, what determines where they move?
Is that just the empty spot?
Because it goes right, left, right up.
So it would go bang, bang, bang, bang, right?
Oh, this can move too, shit.
Maybe it's the laser has to come out.
Okay.
Just to go right.
That?
No.
I'm trying to determine, is the white line the one that's active or the black line?
That's almost there.
This has to go down this way.
Right now it was going like that instead.
You know what I mean?
Like this way, this way, that way, that way.
It determines if they connect.
So maybe his mouth.
Yeah, every time it's from his mouth.
That's like it, but it's not the right way.
It's like upside down.
I'm assuming I have to shoot the laser into the mouth.
I just don't know how to get it the way I want it.
Am I trying to make it shoot into his mouth or have him go backwards?
Hold on.
I just do that.
I feel like there's some connection there.
I can't move this one now.
I feel like I have to get this one up there.
Then he has to be over here.
So once he's here, that's the end.
This is the end right here.
So then I need to go down this way.
No, smooth him over here.
Oh, that's so close, but it's not right.
It's so close.
One, two, three, four.
That's so close, but it's not right.
Nope, hold on.
Nope.
This needs to be that way.
Cannon joins the dark lines.
The cannon's definitely in the right spot.
I had it close before.
I got to move him back out of the way.
So it has to go to here to...
Laser should be in the right spot, right?
Because wouldn't it come down like this?
Put the laser here.
Because then it would be...
Oh.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
It's just close.
So this is really close.
I'm just trying to think about it before I move anything.
These have to be swapped, right?
Hold on.
Nope, put him back.
One, two, three, four.
All right.
This is always going to come out like this, right?
See where it pops out from.
Bottom here.
No.
It's the way that it connects.
Okay, hold on.
Yeah, this kind of like has to go here, right?
That has to go there.
Because now I need it to come down and over.
Done.
Hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on.
Ah.
Shit.
Oh, it's so close.
It's close.
I'm looking at the symbol from this perspective.
I'm going to move this one over here for a second.
No, these can be moved over here, but that doesn't help me at all.
I'm going to put him back.
Everyone go back.
It needs to be a line here.
You need to switch.
I like it this kind of get down here.
You go down here and it's over.
I wonder if he can't be connected to something.
He has to go like a round.
He's down there now.
Hold on.
No, no, no.
Come back here.
Oh, it's just the connections that just confuse the hell out of me.
There.
Shit.
Okay, I need to go.
He needs to go down here.
Oh, shit.
Just for fun, I'm going to move the cannon around a little more.
I need to see it from like every angle.
Hold on.
Hold on a second.
He's almost down there.
Hold on.
It's just the wrong way.
One, two.
It's all twisted.
There needs to be a connection here.
But there's only two lines.
You know what I mean?
I'm trying to, because it has to be like this.
One, two, three, four.
Bang, bang, bang, bang, bang.
There's five pieces.
They only connect a certain way like this, like with diagonals.
And I had it the right way before.
What was my wish for last appointing a job?
I can start at Sunday at least seven weeks after I graduate.
I'm trying to get the cannon to go down there.
I don't know. This one's just like, I just keep getting confused.
I can't bring this guy back down.
I'm trying to get the cannon to go down there.
I was so close before.
Hold on a second.
I'm trying to get the cannon to go down there.
Hold on a minute.
I need...oh, shit.
I'm trying to get the cannon to go down there.
I just got to do some moving around.
He has to be there.
I'm trying to get the cannon to go down there.
That's it.
I did it, mom.
I did it.
Hey.
I'm trying to get the cannon to go down there.
That was all I had to do.
Okay.
See what's in the next room.
Same thing except it's a way to block.
Let's just go all the way through and take a look at everything.
What the hell is wrong with this guy?
Can I get up there?
I guess I can't climb up that.
I know what I can do though.
Where's the dog?
Where the hell is the dog?
I don't know where the dog is.
Let me go.
You're just sitting on the button.
Get over here.
I forgot I had you sitting on that button.
Yeah, a big beak.
I've got a new button for you to step on.
Step on this one.
You're my button pressing dog.
Thanks, little buddy.
Did I screw myself here?
All right.
Kind of scared that I might have just accidentally screwed that whole thing up.
I can push this now.
Okay.
Go all the way back.
Him stepping on that drops the block.
I'm going to jump on this and then jump on him and then jump on his head.
I look at his face.
He's like, yes.
I'm helping.
He reminds me of little Otto.
Go on and keep pushing.
I'm going to jump on him.
Okay.
Hold on.
You go ahead and stand on that, buddy.
There we go.
Let's see what's up here.
I don't know how they just stretched this out.
That's a little bug.
That's it.
A fly.
Save it.
Can that fly be put somewhere?
I think so.
Got a half-due.
Where was there a spot for a fly?
It was a by-question.
I can suck up something here too.
I'm going to remember that.
Can we fit in here?
No.
Can I put him in the dog bowl?
Oh no.
The baby's crying again.
Oh, shit.
Okay.
There we go.
Go on the right way.
That one's all screwed up.
I'm pretty sure this is right.
I'm going to have to push.
I'm going to listen.
I think that's right.
No.
This goes here.
There.
Did I swap this the wrong way?
I don't know.
I wish there was a speed up button.
I hope I didn't do this wrong.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Where's it going?
Okay.
I'm going to have to do this.
I see the worst part about this.
This is obviously a staple of this game.
I'm going to have to do this.
That is crystal number three.
I put the fly in here maybe?
What does that do?
He just like died.
Does he eat that?
It is a dog bowl, right?
Doesn't Big Big fly when he eats a fly?
Didn't that happen?
He ate it.
I can't get it back.
Do I fly out here?
Maybe I take him up to the area where I found the fly.
I got a pee again.
I'm drinking a bunch of coffee.
I'm going to have to go out and have a drink.
I know the way that thing was above the octopus.
I can't even come down.
He can't even walk up it.
I'm seeing it.
I love these rooms.
These are also interesting.
Interesting.
Let me guess.
I'm going to fly up there.
Come on.
Big, big.
What's going on here?
If you're real nice, if you could fly up there, buddy.
If you're really, really great.
If you could get up there, man.
How do I get in the fly?
Is there something I'm missing here?
Is he not ready to fly yet?
I don't think I can flatten the room.
There's nothing in here.
This is where the spinning wheel was.
Over here.
About this way.
I wish I had a m-
Because he ate it.
I can't get it back.
Let's go.
I can't go anywhere here.
There was like a place in the area.
Backtrack to the first room.
Oh, God.
That might be a thing.
Wasn't there something in this room that I missed?
I feel like there was something else that I didn't do over here.
Can you fly up there?
Can you go up there, big, big?
I can't go up there.
Huh.
So, this seems to be a little bit of a problem.
There are no more flies to feed him.
There's a button right here, though.
I feel like I need to move this out of the way.
But I can't.
There's a big red button here, but I can't move this guy.
Backtrack.
Backtrack time.
What?
He already ate this.
Oh, my God.
What?
What the hell?
You have to do it in the same room.
Okay, well, let's talk.
Let's see another cutscene with a bunch of Jebarras.
In Rotavoko, on another day, I said it to E.A.K.A.
I'll ask you a sneak or an impulse.
Rush in a red.
It's in Sanatura.
The red or the other chronic does seem like Nuku.
I said feed.
I already did that, though.
I think I'll have to do a quick.
Okay.
Cool.
Eat it.
Eat the...
Thank you.
What's going here?
This is going to take me, uh, not entirely sure.
Is it a lever for the sewer?
He sure can fit a lot of things in his stomach.
You're the song that I'm trying to make.
It's the song that you're making.
I just said my name.
I just said my fucking name.
Oh, he's kidding me.
That's so cool.
That was just German 985.
I think this is showing some of the backers.
I better write that down.
Okay.
That's cool.
I got to see my...
I got to write all these names now.
Yeah.
This is probably one of the Kickstarter, like credit roll things.
That was very surprising.
I did not expect to go into this room and then see my name on the screen.
Oh, this is not the end of the game by any means.
Let's think about this.
Is this actually doing this room?
Or is this like a bonus Kickstarter room?
There it was again.
All right, well, I guess let's...
Let's leave.
Well, we found the...
Found that.
I have a few things to give my friend down here.
Oh, shit.
Oh, there, there.
Is this one running out?
No, that's the one running out.
Can't remember, oh no, oh, no!
No one's crypto dormitles this room.
Only one left.
special
I
like it out of the
oh god i can skip it
hey give me that stuff you just got
i can't even tell what that was
that's the lever for downstairs and then that's also the thing to turn the power on i don't know what i should do first but i do know actually i do know what i should do first
it's p
so i break back i've been drinking coffee so you know it makes me know it just hold on a sec
i break back
you
right it down it could be a clue yeah this this could be a clue
all right i just peed and forgot the entire game what was happening
what was happening
i got the piece i got a couple pieces let's go down let's go down first
down
this is not the lever for right here
dead all right call me stupid i really thought that was gonna be it
okay well let's go put the bug in the machine
and don't
know whoops
who was the power button yellow room over here
there it is except it's currently functioning now it is
okay well let me go out back again
this should be functioning
it is functioning
so now does that allow me to use the
shick downstairs
i can press this button no is that open the door i hope so please open the door
well i press the button i can press it
big big it's time for you to take another trip
why
a couple different ways to go here i just saw that up here let's go here first
this is gonna be confusing oh boy
oh shit i accidentally clicked out of the window
i always do that
i wish me luck as i have no idea where the hell i'm going
i found a button
that sounds like suction
okay so there's one of two things that are gonna happen here
i suck up the cheese guy from the pipe that's in that room
i can push that block back and it sucks up and it's probably gonna go back to that other room
let's go down here
it's not a lever
go on go down there
let me just make sure i didn't miss anything that's all i could do up there right
let's go left just to make sure i didn't miss anything
no i didn't because this takes you all the way around right
just to be clear i'm just gonna look up here and make sure yes okay let's leave
he's flapping odd he's flapping so hard that's if he stopped doing what he was doing he was gonna hit the ground like brick
that's a lot better all right i'm gonna move the cheese cheetos block
now i can open the other door let's just see what's in that other room cars before i do anything else
thank you very much
has to go right here right
let's go
well there's the other lever
no fuck
didn't want to do that
well i did it so let's just see what's over here
i can't go that way
we can keep going look at this look at how crazy this is
what is that say of 5% 5 over 50 right at time
5% 50 is that 5% 50 or is that 5% what the hell is that symbol
50 50
whatever
the zero that zero is really small
damn okay this is gonna take a minute
let's see how much that moves and then i can determine how many more times i have to do it
move one more but i still can't go over there maybe this one moves that
i'm gonna yeah i'm gonna assume doing that is gonna move this so let's go and move the second one once more
yeah
thanks
wait a second
was that not moving that other one this this one here
right that should be moving which one isn't moving
it's moving the green one
one more
one more or two more one more then i have to bring this one all the way around again so that's one two so one over here and then two over there
one then one two
do i reach out at all of course i do but i am trying to focus on the game because this requires a fuck i did it too many times
the game like this where you have to like remember a lot of things and focus on like a puzzle it's hard to
i need to focus
but can i only do it once per screen or something no let's go
hello screen i've seen a million times
a lot of things remember i'm going back to the original area
is that like dancing
what are these guys doing
there's something here i need to remember
you know what i mean like this is it in the order they do this or the colors
i have no idea
well it's three pinks and two grades
maybe when you looked out the window yeah they were
well i'm just going to pink gray pink pink
pink gray pink
gray just i don't i feel like they're going to need to it's probably the order they're chirping too
one pink gray gray
okay
oh five no idea we need to come back we come back
you're out here but thanks a lot thanks for coming take it easy to you
whole another room whole another area
this one has a gigantic scratch on it looks like someone tried to break in
another one of these oh shit
this is this is not fair that's not fair at all
which one goes on the bottom let's just i need to look at the bottom first
so it's a swirl this one right it's the only one that exists
holy shit this is going to be difficult because i need to know exactly which one
so that's that so it comes up and around the left
so that one or that oh my god it could be any where could be land in one of these
i think it's this one right
you look at it the way it's supposed to be looked at
comes up around her left her right thigh
is it that one
first that's obviously the top piece
that one it got has a little bit of a bump to it though
could be that one well let me just let me get some of these out
I need to get obviously the bottom one out so i can't bring more than one they're
different colored ones maybe it's the ones that are colored differently
so
at least i have to go down
am i turning my head sideways
this is the list this one right let's take a look
oh yeah definitely definitely that one
i just want to make sure it was out
it's turning my head from side to side
if
these are the cem hundred
No, I'm going to be doing it backwards.
This needs to be right.
That one has to switch with this one.
We're ready to come out.
Come on out, all you.
That one's next, right?
Go that way.
Get out of my way, block.
Is that the one?
That is the one.
Open the door.
Oh, I got it, I got it.
I just, I just want to chill out.
Hang on a second.
I'm just calm down.
I got it.
Is that all right?
Don't worry about it.
Okay, I'm in another area with another pump.
I feel like the pumps matter, the colors of the pumps.
Because this is a blue one.
Time before this was purple, then before it was red, right?
This is a really cool looking run, by the way.
Anything to tell me, Mr.
I'm going to use that.
Perhaps the answer is daring right back at you.
Outside solutions, huh?
Beware the intruder, he claims to share your goals, yet seeks to destroy what you protect.
Okay.
A generous meal can often weigh heavily in your favor.
Let's go.
Come on, Big, Big.
So there's a monster in here, apparently, where somebody else is in here.
Now they're octopus to tell us more of a story.
Eggs?
You can't go wrong with eggs.
Just keep going.
We're gonna get to see another president. There's gonna be another president ant in here.
Hope you guys are ready.
Mully!
Yeah, ha, ha!
What?
That's all you got, bruise, bruise, bruise, and veils?
Mully!
Yeah, ha, ha!
Bully!
So that's all I'm gonna get from him is Bully.
Pink, gray, pink, pink, gray.
I'm just making sure I, cause it's showing me these this again.
Big, big, big, can fly.
Pot, we're not gonna do that yet. I'm gonna look, see what this is on the wall.
Okay, so you have to make one of the robot.
Well, let's simply look at what they look like.
Let's try this one.
This one has the thing in the top left.
Guess I can't make that one.
What about this one?
Top left, bottom right.
That's the right one, isn't it?
What about the middle?
Three on this and then that.
Wait, hold on, no.
This one didn't have that right.
Here we go.
He's gonna always get a claw for a hand.
Yep.
The body is that.
Triangle with this, where on the right?
I think that's the right one, right?
Yeah, that's the right one.
And then the head is the knife sticking out of his neck.
And the pretzel on the left, okay.
No, there's no hole on the right.
Like that.
Okay, let's try this one.
Nope.
The side is the saw.
Oh, that's right.
Is the bottom one wrong?
Oh, the bottom one has the three.
Yeah, this one is wrong.
Is this one?
One, two, two.
Unless it's another right.
No, it is.
Right one's more curvy.
Let's just take a look through this one.
Oh, is it a fist?
No, it's like the glove.
Yeah, it's that.
No, it's not that one.
Okay, so it is not this robot.
Is that one way over?
More about?
So we just did this one.
No, it didn't.
There's one line on his chest.
Yeah, it's the one.
Is the head correct?
Is the head of a head does?
So that's the head is correct.
The upper body has the line, the circle here, and then it's filled.
Line, circle here, and it's filled.
Yeah, that's right.
That's right.
One line, one line.
One line, one line, just make sure.
Hold on.
Here it is.
Drop the egg please.
Hey, it landed.
Oh!
Okay.
You know, it's good that I picked to do this one, because otherwise I would have been here a long time, huh?
This is the correct one.
If I started, like, I also start over here.
I would have been here a while.
Yeah!
Now, why should he be able to eat this?
Should he fly out there?
I mean, he can go in here, but I guess he's gonna go in there.
Octopus.
Hey, look at that.
Time for an octopus story, guys.
I can't wait.
That's a reverse.
I'll cut a rocket in my racing.
That's what the arena makes.
For the market, the arena goes down.
That's the ultra.
The concept may be a structure that's okay.
Or a product that's a new one.
Ovi, may new arena.
A lot of the rassul, online trend,
a lot of the arena, and a lot of the slok.
Now, remember to subscribe to our channel.
Like our reviewer, editor, and most of the time.
If you like the arena, play our talk at the press.
Get a bucket of milk.
Or a belt.
Or a tray of chocolate.
I say, through racing.
Primest, the end part of the Hitler-Oternav.
Hit or a prop.
I'll let it grow.
Or the kid that say, wrap it up our rassul.
Hello, my friend, or a wrap up our rap.
Or a wrap up our rap.
Or a wrap.
Or a wraps up our tough tone.
Sorry my friend.
Sorry it's not a wrap.
Oh, sorry my friend.
Forget it if by today mood.
But thank you for this review, guys, for being with us today.
Say ddas  aust j sejo jaa.
Cagus!
Esse Berlao!
Ellis, meanings, kyban and Say ddas.
Amy Gaesha from comment arena.
I amunto there and it is not the same thing as what words tree are kans along with the
Russian Shanse language stop.
Such As I was so bleak that sometimes the harsh words means words dictate our
mind.
This game is pure disruptive and not necessarylight.
Everything we need to learn is, Germany very much access to both areas.
In the last few script, we've met many questions Regierung and actions, from our
That'd be funny
This one is I don't know what color this octopus was but
But we'll color with the octopus as lips because to see the simple above his head
That's a symbol that we need to write down
What would you do if someone gave you a million dollar donation on stream? I would immediately refund it
That's like a sclery amount of money
Get down here
Give me what you picked up please
Take that
And the lever
Thank you that's it. Oh, let's go
No
Now is theater Roosevelt gonna tell me something
Nope, he's still gonna say bully
Oh shit
Not this again
Oh, no
Tell me to remember this it was I really should have written it down
You know what I mean like I should have written down the pattern because I have to do like the whole thing
No, it was this was here
This was maybe the hell is this fuzzy son of a bitch
I don't know I don't like no, I don't remember I thought that this was this is kind of closed
Now I didn't you know I'm gonna write this down
Oh shit, I think that's right
I
When I get this right I'm writing this whole thing down because I'm gonna have to do the whole thing probably eventually
Every watch the broadcast
Oh
Don't fall off
Okay, got it I want to write this down
It's gone it's gone
Can't write it down it's gone
Oh
Creepy
It's okay
P
Still the baby
We're gonna do now we're going to get pee back
All right, I'm kind of glad that I don't have the baby anymore because it means I don't have to do the song thing anymore
All right, what we doing something before the other guy takes stole my baby
I
Can power this up
Please plug it into the device
Power button was back here I believe I remember correctly
This is the neverhood
Spiritual successor
This is not a sequel to the never same style same people that worked on it, but not a direct sequel
All right, do you have anything new to tell me now?
Oh
Let's go upstairs or downstairs
I
Purple face i'm not sure it matters
But you know it might
Don't get any day miss anything here
Well now I can go across because the uh
I did the egg things and I can go this way
One of these is definitely bill from the neverhood by the way
Me too
Right it down
Nice plus
You
Square
And what about your odd symbols
With the box within a box or now more like a
Two lines
Done
Okay
Um try this down to right
Shit more symbols
Oh
Hey, there's the music kicking in for me. Thanks music
I want to go back for a second because I think one of these wasn't filled in over here
It's more fun to write it down though. Oh, okay, click out
That way okay, make sure I remember that
I like I like keeping a notebook. It's fun
I could like take a picture with my iPhone, but then I thought about it. I was like you know
I want to like write it down. I want to keep my like like detective notebook bed
Okay, no, we teleported
That's the solution
Like I told you that was such a good lucky guest to do that one first because if you came over here first
You would have seen that that was the correct one
Now we have another one of these oh boy
I'm not even sure there's a way to tell
Let's move all this out of the way to see
Is it baby
What did he scratch there was something scratched off
I
Didn't he scratch off the part of the door maybe it's there on the door
So I'll check behind all these make sure it's not listed here somewhere
And that's not behind this
Oh
No
Well, it's somewhere
It's definitely the guy holding or it's definitely the guy that took the baby, but I mean there's a bunch of different faces here
It could be any one of these
There's like two or three versions of the same face and yeah, you gotta get it exact. I don't want to just yeah, I could have to figure it out
It looks like dark wing duck
Ah
Yeah, I'm gonna have to come back to this I think
There's no way I can do that without knowing what the right picture is
He can go in here
Maybe the pictures in here
That would sure be swell
You
There's the p-ha
Gotta write that down I have to draw this correctly
No, you know what fucking
This is what I'm going to take a picture of this is the one I'm gonna take the picture of
Haha
I went through all that trouble of describing the notebook. No, no, no, I gotta use like the notebook
The notebook is like it's so key. It's gotta be the notebook
I just went back on my word and I'm not using the notebook now
I just took a picture with my eye
Cheater
Wait, was there anything else in this room?
You want me to do if I draw this? Are you kidding me?
What was this?
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, hold on, I wrote all this down
Uh
So it was the this one
When it was filled in
With a plus and minus there
I could think I wrote it down
And then where is it?
The box in the middle this one
Okay, filled in is there another one that's not filled in?
That's that's all correct
What does that do?
I
Shouldn't this do something?
Their indication about it is did this?
Um
It was already on the second sequence. That's the thing
That's the way that I raised that obvious of gel
Our
You
What was that?
I can't move this anymore.
Well, there we go.
I don't know, I mean, I guess um...
Just for fun, I'm gonna put it back.
I'm gonna try the other one, just for fun.
Just make sure I didn't miss anything.
That's the other one.
So we're gonna put it on the one now, I guess, maybe I think it was on this one to begin with.
Black-Blank-Blank.
And this is right there.
I can't remember where that is right now.
Let's see, October.
Everyone's doing like the triangles.
Maybe that did change the path.
We'll find out.
So I am getting very hungry.
So I'm going to potentially do this.
I'm going to go get some food.
Oh, he's spitting something out.
That's right.
He's got this.
Maybe that.
Okay, let me look at this picture of Darkwing Duck.
The eyes, the head has, oh god, I can't even see.
I think this is the right head, right here.
I think.
Is that the right head?
Yes.
That is the right head.
So, I'm just going to go over here for now.
Where's the eyes?
Oh, this is going to be so hard for me to figure this shit out.
No, those are not right.
Where are the right eyes?
He's looking to the left kind of.
So I think it's down here.
I need to make sure I don't want to screw this one up.
So let's put it around.
Could be.
It could be.
Wait, what?
Hold on.
So it has to.
So it needs to go up because this doesn't fit down here.
God, this is making my head hurt.
Only three eyes and one of them.
Where's the helmet?
Where's the head?
Where's the right head?
I think so.
Let me get that over there.
This is going to be very slow because I need to make sure I'm doing this correctly.
Oh, shit.
Is that the right body?
I can't even.
I don't even know what piece of the body that is.
That is hands.
No, this has got to go up this way.
That's the right head for sure.
That is not the right eyes because look, it's in the right.
It's the wrong way.
So it really just determines how to match it up the right way.
So the right eyes are the ones that are down here.
Let's just see, I don't know.
So I flip this upside down.
Yep, those are the right ones.
I got to get those back up, shit.
Seeing all these pieces of really messing with my brain.
So these have to come back down.
I got to get that one out of the bottom though.
I'm just going to do this piece by piece.
Like, I'll figure it out later.
I think, hold on, what's that one?
Oh, shit, I lost the picture.
There it is.
Okay, so the body's hand comes across.
This is going to be very, very annoying.
I need the mouth.
This mouth has this leg.
That's it right there, right?
I think.
Pretty sure that's the right mouth.
Let's see.
Yep, that's correct.
Getting there, we're getting there.
We're getting closer.
Now I need to go down to his hand.
Which is the right way this way?
Nope.
It's hard to tell what the hand has even gone the right way here.
I think it's the one down the bottom.
This one.
Yes, it is.
Alright, what's the last one?
The hand coming down on the right.
It's like a bit, it's like fingers and shit.
Is it this one?
Is it the one that I just had?
Nope.
I'm not this one.
There it is.
Woo!
Okay, that was kind of strange.
No power.
I did pick up a power thing though.
I want to see what that potentially changed when I move to the blocks.
Because I didn't change all those blocks that were over here.
And boom.
Bottom boom.
Hey, look, power.
I'm assuming I can put this in here and then there'll be power.
And then this thing up to stairs that goes that way.
It's just positive figure out the game and went again.
This is the octopus part.
Remember I told you about the octopus?
I'm assuming I can put this in here.
Okay, well, the first octopus was the one with the rectangle.
So it's in the second one we saw was the, let me see, so servitude, family, hope, honor.
I'm just going to write underneath them, servitude, family.
This one is hope, servitude, honor.
Okay, bye-bye.
That should allow us to get in the door that we just had.
I'm actually curious about something.
I'm going to go up.
I'm going to go back down there, but I want to see what's in this room over here.
Because I can turn the power on now.
Oh, damn.
I just looked at the chat.
Now maybe they're speaking English now instead of, okay, that's kind of cool if that's what that did.
Yeah, yep, I can, I'm going to be able to understand them now.
So this is, this is cool.
This is cool.
This is going to tell the whole story.
We need to do it in order.
This is not the right order.
But I mean, this right here is the last part of the story right here.
You have made it far.
Mother and Father must be pleased with your courage and honor.
Yet always for not without saving the child.
And it's building a machine to extract her power of a process she will never survive.
It's the final piece you will need.
Just spit it down on me.
So what is it now?
I got to go listen to the other part of the story.
I got to go all the way back.
I'm going to talk about backtrack.
You think, you didn't think we were going to backtrack to the very beginning?
That's exactly what we're going to do.
We're going all the way back.
Does that want to see, I want to see it from the beginning.
You guys are ready.
Hope you guys are ready to go all the way back.
If I hadn't remembered how to get there.
This is going to take a long time.
Okay, no, I didn't do anything there.
So where is the last?
I don't know.
Big, big, say, I'll go back.
Can we even go all the way back?
I think we can.
I'm pretty sure we can.
Good luck.
Big, big change it back to normal and you.
Oh, good dog.
Can I get over on the other side?
There was a little like a...
I can go down.
I can do this.
Oh no.
Guys.
Please stop him.
I'll not...
Just through here.
This symbol was on the wall a while back.
This was somewhere too.
I didn't write him down.
That's my downfall.
That didn't do it.
I didn't write these ones down.
Let's just go in and see what's going on here.
This is the baby.
Can I?
P, not so fast, brother of mine.
Vognon, come on.
Let's be reasonable.
You've got to let me get her out of that thing.
I'm not a pal.
I'm wasted on her anyhow.
I'll put it to real use.
Vognon, don't.
Sorry.
Too late.
What the?
Well, that was easy.
Oh shit.
Please kill my dog.
Don't worry.
I've got you.
I feel like we're not focusing on the fact that my dog is just instant.
The dog that's been with me the whole game is dead.
What the hell?
What?
Okay.
Big, big rest in peace.
Here are the less piece of power.
I can actually turn this on now.
Huh?
How do I even fill the...
I'm going to hope, servitude, honor, mustache guy.
I have the mustache.
Oh, okay.
Drag it.
Yeah, the symbol.
I feel like I need to watch the cutscenes again.
Let's go back to the first octopus.
That's what we're going to do to begin with.
Is this the first octopus?
So this is octopus number one.
This is octopus number one.
Let's see what he has to say.
Welcome.
I must tell you.
In service to father, my obligator kin and I have seen much underneath Grand Wall.
Most of it, Gloria, yet some tragic as well.
It is the planet's zero fly, where you now find yourself.
Intuned in the foreshared, on the cross.
I'm home, or science magic, pretty well.
And servitude.
That's serv- fuck.
I got it.
And other dangers and indigenous to zero five.
Then one day without warning, how do you come up?
You're attacked by a fierce warrior who while lighting ultimate power, possess intelligence,
intelligence, knowledge, and spiritual and religion's defense.
Father and mother.
All I need is hope, servitude.
A lost soul, just taken by ego and envy.
So the power of our God for his own gain and song hyalurant, execute to this power.
And before the greatest end, the last step is struck down by his foe.
Struck down by his essence, his own hearing arm power.
Okay.
Bad guy comes, wants the power of the armor-crogged fortress.
Servitude is the X with the square with little lines on it.
Each one of these sentient octopi are going to give me one of those.
So that's the first one.
We're going to go to the second one.
So that this is the servitude.
And I got servitude from the rectangle.
I remember that.
There's no one can stop you fucking meds.
Seriously.
Okay. So now what was the second one?
Second octopus is this way?
I got a pee again.
What?
I just heard, did he just...
Did it just hear the dog?
That's what I got.
Oh yeah, I have multiple pieces of paper.
Which is all over the place.
I'm hungry too.
I feel like I'm pretty close to the end though.
In the next maybe half hour 45.
I'm at the wrong way.
What was the second octopus?
Down around this way, right?
This is the second area to go to.
Beak, beak.
How many bugs have I've actually seen?
Believe it or not, I heard this game had a lot of technical problems with it.
I don't think I've seen any.
I don't think I've seen one technical bug with this game.
Why is this blocked?
Is the store's locked now?
Okay.
Why is this store blocked?
That's unfortunate.
Yeah, the only bug I've seen was with audio.
There was one bug in like the four hours or whatever I've been playing this game.
I have to go down.
Have I even gone this way?
I don't even remember.
Here we are.
Which one is this?
Is an octopus in here?
This is the third one or the fourth one?
This is the second octopus.
I believe.
Let's get it.
I got my hands ready.
My activator, Sivlin, told you of the attack upon Spur of Five I presume.
Allow me to continue.
Our fortress had been breached.
The father was prepared.
Designed with an unlock was a hidden defense mechanism father added to ensure the safety of his planet.
His people, his family.
The children had attacked, believing he was not a father who was key to the power he desired.
But she knew the truth.
The power resides in their infant daughter, Peele.
Hiding Pee from sight.
Mother hurry to initiate father's plan.
But was interrupted just as she began the activation procedure.
The attruder called Vognant.
Some others empty shell and realized his mistake.
She did not hold the power after all.
There must be another.
The child.
Okay.
Family is the circle with the three circles on it.
All right.
We have a servitude family.
We need hope.
What was the other one?
Hope.
Shit.
It's not the right way.
Hope and honor of the last two.
I feel like I need to suck something up this time.
Wasn't there a couple of the button I pressed.
And it made the vacuum sound.
Am I crazy?
Remember when peak peak was up there and there was a button to press and it made the vacuum sound?
I don't know.
Where's the dog?
I think you might have missed what happened earlier.
I'm going to go down the vine.
Down the vine.
What was out here?
I forget whether it was a tree.
I'm going to go down the vine.
What was out here?
I forget what it all was.
Because through this door is where he flies up and hits the button.
So we get to go down here.
Let's continue.
Did I miss one of the sentient octopus people?
I feel like I missed somebody.
I forget which way to go.
That's not that way.
There's the 50-50.
There's the 5% 50.
I'm going to go down there.
Go on, get on there, get up.
Speed it up, speed it up.
Anything change up here with these weird birds?
I swear it's going to be like...
And remember the 5 birds of our ancestors.
Pinky, Grayson, Pink Mondo, Pink Mordel and Gray Sanibi.
Remember their names?
I swear it's going to be something like that.
Whatever.
Let's go!
Derma is auto-okay.
I had a dream where you left him outside and he had to eat his own poop.
He's right here and he's well fed, don't worry.
That's an odd dream to have.
Derma is your dog all right.
What are you doing man?
Let's activate it again.
Let's see what you have to say.
Did I already do this one?
No, I didn't.
I missed one, but we'll get it though.
You know a lot of not.
You know the attack.
A lot of not believing mother was dead.
But mother was still alive in a patch.
She had used the soul transfer device to insert her being into the fortress.
The first of a two step process which would activate father's defense mechanism.
Yes, she had narrowly escaped while not splashed.
But the soul transfer device was destroyed forever trapping her within the wall of the armcrab.
The original plan was for father to use the soul transfer device to complete the first step.
The soul would insert herself into armcrab while mother would perform the second step.
How rough the machinery, the control panel located it in the ample room.
However, with father killed by father not, mother's only option was to inhabit the fortress herself.
And hope that father's spirit could somehow find a way to activate the console.
Unlikely, yes, but this was her only hope.
Thankfully father's spirit appeared to have found a way.
You know what's really funny about this?
Star was in this call like four hours ago.
And he said, wouldn't it be funny if all the things that these octopus were saying was just how to beat the game?
And he called it.
Good job. Good for you.
Now all we're missing is honor.
Honor and then we can pull the thing off the crystal.
That one was the, you know what I haven't been doing.
Shit, I haven't been, oh no, hold on.
I gotta go back.
I need to write down what the symbol was above that octopi head.
Because I feel like I'm gonna need to know that.
So that was the piece facing this way.
Isn't that was hope?
I didn't write down which one was above the one that was family, unfortunately.
Chopper!
Keep going.
Didn't I already see this one though?
Did I, I must have missed one.
No, ah, come on.
That's annoying.
Hold me up.
Sorry, this is the one, was this servitude?
No, this, okay, so this one is, what was this one?
Is this family?
Mother and father must be pleased with your courage and honor.
There it is, there it is.
Vognoth has her and is building a machine to extract her power.
Of a process she will never survive.
Takes us, it's the final piece you want me to do.
So make sure I got it, the right.
Mother and father must be pleased with your courage and honor.
The square with the, all try not without seeing the child.
Vognoth has her.
Alright.
Sad square.
I can now do that puzzle.
Let's go.
Baby back.
Let's do it.
Let's finish this up, huh?
Alright.
Servitude goes here.
Servitude was the circle of the X.
Where is it?
Is that it now?
Which one is servitude?
Where is it going with the circles, right?
Was it that one I was just on?
Because that one, that's family.
That's honor.
That's hope.
This one was servitude, right?
I've wrote it down with like, I've wrote it down like crazy.
I'm going to, which one does it match up with?
That one is hope.
So that goes over here.
There.
Where is family?
Family goes.
There.
No, wait.
Yeah, the honor goes there.
Alright, my servitude is like, I don't even know which one it is.
Is it this one?
And then we go back into this room.
We pull the thing down so it gets down here so we get the power away.
Where the fuck is Big Big?
Okay, thank God.
I don't even need him.
Or do I?
Alrighty.
Whoa.
That, alright.
Press the button.
Oh, this is the...
I wrote this down a long time ago.
This is a short, it's shortest one.
I'm going to need to be short.
Oh no, I got to go look at it again.
It's like a weird accordion.
That's not it.
Didn't write this down good enough.
Mine is just like teeth.
Is it the other way or the other way?
Let's see how big they are.
It's all gets deeper though.
I think I can still look at it.
I'm pretty sure I can still look at it.
Isn't it down?
It was a super Mario ship I remember, but...
Is there a way I can still see it?
Isn't the room with the light bulb?
There it is.
The fat one goes at the end.
And then it's just a nice straight line.
Fat one goes at the end.
At least I know that.
I can get it done.
Fat one at the end.
Let's get them in there and take a look.
Which one is the smallest one?
This one right?
The one that's in here, the little list.
Not quite.
Oh, that's in there deep, huh?
You stay there.
That's not small enough.
That's too small.
That's not it either.
I guess it was that one.
I guess.
Interesting.
Okay, hold on, hold on.
Hmm, why?
This one has to be the smallest one.
I can't see that that one or that one.
That has to be one of these two.
Which one is smaller to those?
I can't tell if those are exactly the same.
I'm going to line this up.
That one looks like a little bit lower.
Huh.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Am I fizzled? Did I flippet?
Oh, shit.
Whoa, okay.
All right.
Well, that's a thing that exists.
Now to get this right.
Oh, boy.
Let's just through a bunch.
This is going to be annoying.
That one's...
Whatever one is the lowest here.
So it looks like it's there.
There, there, there, and there.
Tommy Knot, you have saved my daughter with your acts of servitude and honor.
He has given you her plutonium crystals, which will provide your planet with power for eternity.
Because you have shown yourself to be a true hero.
I can now give you what you need to complete your journey.
Away home.
Activate tower transformation.
Tower transformation.
Complete.
Giant robot mob lives and ready for takeoff.
Give it a count of words.
Count of me, birds are there.
Thank you.
Ah ha, Tommy Knot.
Do you think you're a hero?
Just wait, thy blessed human and baby back to fiber's hand.
What the?
Oh.
Get destroyed.
Down vote, Tommy.
Bikki.
No, the dog.
Hey Tommy.
I feel kind of funny.
Bikki?
You're alive.
I'm alive.
I feel kind of funny.
Bikki?
You're alive.
If by alive you mean hungry, then yeah.
Sure, I'm alive.
Come on little buddy.
We're heading home.
Maybe, maybe.
Step into seven.
Outside darshan's wall.
Maybe, maybe.
What do you know?
It's numb not.
Maybe, maybe.
Bikki?
Change coordinates to Darshan's orb.
Aye aye, captain.
I always wanted to say that.
Look at that like big practical effect.
I'm alive.
Did I win?
Darshan's orb.
Yeah!
No, that's not it.
Don't forget about the secret at the end.
I'm hearing like two songs at the same time here.
Options.
Same the game.
All right, well.
Listen to all the music.
The sad music and the title theme of the same time.
Yeah.
Okay, let me go back to the hold on a second.
All right.
Well.
So that was the game.
Pretty short.
It was about four hours or so to beat the game.
It was, uh, it was good.
That was fun.
That was interesting.
I enjoyed that four hours.
I wish it was a little longer.
Maybe like a part two kind of where you go to like a different planet or something.
But that was cool.
I don't know what I did here.
I was like, I scribbled on this.
Now we want to see the notebook out.
Um, I'll tell you know what, let's see.
Can I take a couple pictures of this?
I don't even know what I did here.
I was like, I scribbled on this.
Now these are my notes.
These will stay my notes forever.
Yeah, what did the ant, the theater Roosevelt ant, he didn't do anything, did he?
I feel like there are some things that I missed.
Right.
Like I feel like there are a couple things that I didn't do that could have added some time.
Shit, that was um, that was armacrog.
Time is it 10.30.
Four hours.
I really would have liked to have seen it be like six.
I thought I said, all right.
Like 10 would be like, well, that's what that's way up there.
Because it neverhood wasn't even that long.
The neverhood was like maybe five or six, maybe total.
It might have even been like the same and I just don't remember.
But I mean, they did what they could.
It was only a team of like three or four people I think that put almost 90% of that game together.
So it's pretty impressive because it was just a Kickstarter kind of game.
That's off to the guys that could put all that animation work and all that design work together.
And a little under a year, I think.
Year in like some odd months.
And what I've liked to have seen it go on for like another hour or two, yes, absolutely.
But it was what it was.
And I thought it was fun.
So two hours if we try to explain the notebook.
Yeah, they did.
I'll give them.
I'll give them a round of applause for their accomplishment because that was pretty damn cool.
Am I going to make any YouTube videos out of these streams?
Probably not.
Maybe I would make eventually like a playlist and upload highlights of or something.
Oh boy, I'm starving though.
And credit.
Probably was something of the end.
I probably should have watched the whole thing.
But for any that was an end of game.
I think that it was just over just under I think a million dollars.
And for what the game actually was for all that work and all that shit that had to go into it.
Like $900,000 is not a lot of money when you're making an entire game in claymation.
So that was cool.
Considering the fact that I played broken age.
And broken age was just about like three hours long.
And that game took in like millions of dollars, didn't it?
And that game was like a 2D hand drawn game.
So all the guys at pencil test and like Doug to Naples and you know,
all the guys that worked on the game.
Very, very nice job.
I much enjoyed that.
And with that.
That's gonna wrap it up.
I'm actually kind of glad I got the whole thing done on one stream.
That's kind of cool.
When my name just like popped up that I know where that was crazy.
I'm actually surprised that that was just in there.
I know that because I because obviously I was a huge never heard fan and a huge like earthworm gym fan.
So I gave enough money I think to be put somewhere in a game somewhere.
And that took me off card and that was funny.
But yeah, games are very expensive.
Very, very expensive.
Now if this if pencil test got like 10 million dollars or like 30,
you know, 20, 30 million dollars from a studio.
Yeah, that probably would have been like an eight hour long game with a bunch more stuff going on.
But that was an independent game.
Yeah, I think I'm going to I'm going to take off.
I'm starving.
I was hungry when I started the stream even like two or three hours into the stream.
I'm like, I'm like, I'm like really, really, really, really,
let me just get to the right page here.
I'm going to see I'm going to tear out some of these pages.
Yes, you guys want to like see here's like one of the pages.
Actually, can we see if I can even turn on my webcam?
Is it even connected?
Let's see.
Okay, did it work?
So here's the page.
Here's a page you want to see.
Can we over here?
Hey, look at server to family hope.
I remember these symbols.
If we're going to write those down.
There you go.
This is one of my notebook pages.
It was before that anyway.
There's all this stuff.
All right, guys.
Well, that's just one of the, I there was like five or four of the pages,
but we don't need to see those.
We're going to see my awful, awful handwriting.
But yeah, I'll talk to you guys later.
Take care.
Hope you enjoyed the stream.
I will be around probably the next couple days.
I'll probably stream something.
But yeah, I'm off.
Take it easy, guys.
Good night.
Thanks for stuck around the whole time.
Thanks.
Cool.
Yeah, I'm a crox on steam.
You can get it right now.
I believe it's 1999 or 2025.
I don't know.
It's something like that.
But yeah.
Take it easy, guys.
Thanks for coming.
Bye.
Bye, bye.
Good night.