The critic song.
So, dudes.
Oh, he's close out some of the windows.
Okay.
Whoa.
Whoa. All right.
Important, very, very important for the stream starts.
I set up a new virtual audio cables thing.
And I want you guys to tell me if you can hear the music that is about to start playing.
So let me know because otherwise it will be no sound.
So ready?
Let me know if you can hear the medic music.
Oh yeah.
Can you guys hear that?
Okay.
Good to know because that means I set the audio cable thing up correctly.
So that's good to know.
Loud and clear, Burger Boy.
All right.
So tonight, first of all, happy Saturday.
Hope you guys are having a fantastic Saturday.
Second of all, of course, grandpa is tonight.
There's a lot of things going on tonight.
There's a lot of things going on in the world of Jeremy.
Did a video, doing a live stream.
Grandpa is tonight on Machinima.
A lot of crazy stuff.
So I've been all over the place today.
Flow me.
Do it.
All right.
Let him explain himself.
All right, Flow me.
You have 10 words to explain yourself.
10 words.
In 10 words or less.
All right.
I'm going to get rid of that.
Two plus two is four.
All right.
So let me just, where's my phone?
Oh, I always am losing my damn phone.
It always happens.
Oh, down.
I think it's across the road.
There it is.
Hello, phone.
All right.
Oh, if you're watching this on YouTube,
like eventually when I upload this tomorrow,
if you're watching this on YouTube,
you go ahead and you can skip two or three minutes
while I set this up.
I know I put an annotation there,
but sometimes people go,
whoa, when do you start?
So go ahead and skip a couple minutes
if you're watching this on the YouTube's.
Okay.
Twitter.
Hello, Twitter.
So yeah, Team Fortress 2 and Binding of Isaac.
And you're probably wondering,
why am I playing that crazy ridiculous disturbing game?
Well, because this DLC for coming out in like a couple days.
So I want to get back into it,
because I love back in.
So let's see.
Let's see.
Streaming.
G.
F.
Two.
And Binding of Isaac.
Oh, come here.
H.T.T.P.
Clones.
Lash.
W.W.
Yes.
Twitch.
Twitch TV.
Fun.
I'm not gonna run on it, but.
Don't ask me why I always do this on my phone.
I just like don't feel like opening up another tab.
Like it's probably faster if I did it on my Dan computer.
There's that.
Is that all right.
Ready to go here in a second.
Just gonna put a steam message out to the steam community.
I have to be, oh my.
Oh, what?
New name apparently.
Massive bus accident.
Is my name on here.
Well, that's one way to do have your name B.
Whatever.
Massive bus accident.
Oh, weird.
Streaming.
Yes.
Oh, I don't think that's so funny.
Oh, screaming now.
Oh.
Colin's last night.
Streaming.
I actually put this here.
Oh, man.
Do you have to do a body of my.
Just waiting.
I'll change that.
Open my face.
This party.
15 minutes.
All right.
Oh, God.
Oh, no.
It is like duped and drank on my floor.
Oh, God.
Oh, you know what?
I'm going to stay in there.
This is staying there.
I'll deal with it later.
God.
What a pro.
Oh, okay.
It's like a cup of milk on my floor right now.
That is not cool.
Whatever.
The show must go on.
Let's do it.
That's that.
And here's the tweet.
I can't believe that.
Milk does a body good unless you dump it on your floor.
I don't know.
Geez, Louise.
Is that work?
It was fun though.
Nice like avatar.
All right.
We're good to go.
Oh.
Okay.
Now I'm going to make the chat so I can see it.
Good Lord.
Well, that was not cool.
It's good to server with zero people in it.
And my T-F2 server is coming along.
I know I said last week it was going to be done this week but it's not.
It's close though.
I have to talk to the guys at game servers.com.
We have to have a meeting.
Some type of meeting.
What's up, dudes?
If you're just joining us.
I'm just going to spend a couple of milk on my floor.
And it's going to stay there until I'm done screaming.
I hope I don't ruin anything.
If it like seeps over near my computer, that's going to be really bad.
That might as well be like an emergency stop.
All right.
Let's go to...
No, no toot forward.
No, dust bowl.
We play dust bowl too much.
How about...
A gravel pit.
I'm okay with gravel pit.
Let's do gravel pit.
This is the server.
Ladies and gents.
Head there.
Gravel pit.
Yeah, dust bowl is a little overplayed.
But I love it though.
I love dust bowl.
That's because I'm an old school TF2 player.
I mean, I haven't played since 2007.
And I remember that.
It used to only be dust bowl, two fort, turbine.
Gravel pit.
What would the...
There was only like two more...
There was only six maps when TF2 launched.
Two fort, dust bowl, gravel pit, turbine.
What would the other two maps?
What the hell would the other two maps?
Can somebody in the chat throw that out there?
Well and...
Granary.
Right?
Those are the only...
There was only six that came out at release.
Let's go below.
Let's go attack eight tonight.
I feel like being an attacker.
Hmm.
No, we're gonna stop with medic.
I'm starting with the medic.
Alright, let's get the audio good here.
Game audio good?
Voice audio, is it?
We getting up a pod?
I'm gonna have to tell.
We should begin.
Dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun.
Oh yeah.
High five, baby.
Excellent.
Alright, let's push this point, voice.
Yeah, if anyone wants to do me, I will accept it.
I'm not gonna promise I will win the duel.
It's anyone watching the stream, but I will try my best.
I got you, I got you, I got you.
Follow me, doctor!
I'm gonna cover the house, I'm gonna push the cover.
We got, we need to...
We need this over or what?
Are we good?
We're good to go?
I think we're gonna get this.
You know what?
I'm gonna go.
Not that way.
I had to use it.
Oh no.
Oh, I shouldn't have left.
That was my bad.
I should have ice creamed that up.
Oh boy, I'm gonna die, I'm gonna die, I'm gonna die.
J.M.Z.
Hole.
We're okay.
That guy's gonna try and shoot the window.
We got it, we got it, we got it.
Oh, even that sandwich.
Spy, where are you?
Bastard, there you are.
We gotta get out of here, we gotta get out of here, we gotta get destroyed.
Thank you for saving my life.
S, I don't wanna say your name, Holland.
You're very quiet, you're very quiet.
What?
They knew I got him.
Alright, let's push it.
I love your outfit man.
I think I said this before last stream, but your outfit is unbelievable.
And this is when we...
I'm using it.
You know, I'm gonna protect this guy too.
Just because, for fun.
Oh, a Turk!
Oh, it's the guy I'm doing!
Oh my god!
That's just fine, that's fine.
Oh, get away!
Oh, damn it.
I didn't even know that was the guy I was doing.
I just walked up and function in the face.
Yeah, if you gotta do it, throw up my way, dude.
I will do you.
Absent positive, I'll do it.
I'm gonna get a...
Let's get a...
Oh, I have to do it with you.
I don't even know if I have any tools.
I think I gave them all away.
Oh, shh, there we go again.
Oh, give me that Uber.
We're gonna be able to push this...
Right crowbar.
See what you got, baby.
No, no, no, where are you?
Oh, no.
Get out of my way!
Okay, hi guys, hello!
Get away!
Damn it!
Oh, damn it.
Do you see that whole group of people that were running off the stairs?
That was terrifying.
Good morning, good morning.
Dun-dun-dun-dun-dun-dun, good morning.
Good morning!
People need heels.
Oh, Burger Boy, the DUP machine.
Oh no, oh no.
Two of the people that healed, I need the quick fix.
Oh my god, he's coming after me still.
Oh my god, how did he get me?
Dude, that guy was like in a bubble.
He was in a bubble of invincibility right there.
You know, I'm going quick fix.
After my backpack, if we- oh no, that's right, I unboxed this strange one.
Oh god, I unboxed this.
I just will put it to the use, right?
Let's go scout, I want to be able to run fast.
Run, run, run, run, run.
Quick fix!
Oh yeah, quick fix!
Oh you want to get him?
No, no, no kill the medic.
Come here, run to me.
Oh my god, die you bastard.
Oh my god dude.
How many hits did that take?
Alright, I got a new one.
Let's push through this.
I'm not going to push through this nonsense of the equation.
Quick fix, oh what you know about the quick fix, oh my god.
Come here, come here.
Oh you jumped away from me.
What the hell?
Holy one.
Cool, nice job guys, good game.
Good game.
I really like the Yogs cast.
I don't really watch it to be honest.
Yogs cast is kind of like a Minecraft thing, isn't it?
Or at least a predominantly Minecraft?
See, I have no idea.
This is me, I have absolutely no idea.
They seem like nice guys, they seem like cool guys.
You know, I don't, I'm changing.
I want the crit screw.
Can I get it charged before?
Well, I really, I don't have an affinity on them to be honest.
Oh, I can't have vibing.
Let's go Virgo boy.
Optimus Brogues like Stadda then, like a statue.
Mission begins in 10 seconds.
All right Virgo boy, you better be ready to unleash hell on the world.
After this crit screw, I'm gonna, he's dying over here.
All right Virgo boy.
Watch out for Virgo boy.
I'm holding onto this.
I'll come back to you.
Over here Virgo.
Oh there's Spy here.
Spy here, what do you think down?
Am I a fan of Shibuya 142?
I love Shibuya 142, he's like a friend of mine.
He's like a good bottomine.
You are not real.
He's still here.
Me and I Shibuya 2142 are a roasties.
I'm gonna get this.
Just shoot a bunch over there.
Oh my god, never mind.
I do know Star as well.
I'm not as close to Star as I am with Shibuya, but I know Star.
Speaking of Star, we may actually be doing videos together sometime soon.
Sometime very soon.
He's a cool guy though.
Stimid.
Yes, I know Stimid.
I know.
Pretty much if you can name me like a team portrait through Channel, I probably know them.
I probably know who they are and I've probably spoken to them.
At least once or twice.
Stay alive, Derp.
Do you know German 985?
No, who's that?
He sounds like a real looser.
Oh Virgo boy.
Get rid of this guy.
He's a pretty cool guy.
For its great.
Blodges.
Do you know.
Is that a spy?
Probably not.
That's a spy.
What?
Alright, so my brain just exploded.
I walked towards that engineer, the real one, and then I turned around.
I thought it was him again and I thought it was real, so I got fouled.
That was a good spy.
Why are we screaming?
I don't know.
I don't know all of them.
There are probably a few that I've never had a conversation with.
But for the most part, I had a conversation with all of them.
I think there's a little murder.
Alright, that's a spy.
Nope, it's just a dump machine, Bird of Boy.
I don't stay alive dude.
I got you.
Oh, the medic chain.
Oh my word.
I'm getting a little bit of trouble here.
Shouldn't be walking out that far.
Oh, just give me one more.
And...
Should I use it?
Yes.
Oh, everyone died.
Oh, crit rockets everywhere.
Spiders.
Oh, I hate spiders.
They scare me.
Alright, I'm gonna go to...
Do I even...
I don't think I even have a huntsman.
No, I don't.
My huntsman's gone.
Oh, forget it.
Then wait, wait, wait.
What the hell was that?
What?
Oh, hey, I'm just the floating sniper hand.
There we go.
That was weird.
Let's go scout.
All defaults.
Uh, no, I'm alright.
Optimus Brent, I'm cool.
Not right this second.
Maybe after when it's all said and done.
But for now, I want to focus on the Zistream.
Let's give you a straight-up.
Yeah, we'll do it, thanks.
You know what I want?
I want a strange huntsman.
Oh crap.
You are still alive.
Is there even a strange huntsman?
Can you even get that?
Ah, damn it.
How much is a strange huntsman?
40 keys.
It's 40 keys for a strange huntsman.
What?
Oh my god.
What crate do you get it in?
What, do you crate number 40?
What?
Wow, man.
Wow, the salvage crate.
Oh, it's just a salvage crate.
It's one of the rare ones.
That's insane.
40 keys.
If I get a strange huntsman, I know I'm going to keep it.
That's crazy.
Anybody up here?
Now, what's up?
Millennium boy, exoskeleton bug body.
I just landed on his head.
No.
I got flowed up.
I got flowed it up.
Sorry, Millennium man.
Yeah, it's going to be fun.
Well, after this round, we'll change servers.
I don't want to use the pistol.
Oh, I still have it.
I have the critical.
Let's put it on.
Yeah, I love all the scatterguns.
Except for the force of nature.
It's not my forte.
I'm not a big fan of it.
See if we can't crit some people.
Oh, my god.
That was a deathmish.
I just wanted to see how many hit markers would just pop up.
My name's like, yeah, I don't have my giveaway.
My backpack.
I feel the option I have right now.
What happened to my mad bill?
Oh, right.
I probably gave that away.
Yeah, I gave that away as well.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
All right, let's close this out, boys.
End girls, potentially.
All right, I want to get that good couple kills.
This thing, Jake.
Thank you for Jake.
No, that's a death wish.
I'll go the other way.
I'm going over here.
I'm not that I can see.
Anyone going to come out of this way?
Oh, god.
I don't think that guy.
I didn't even see him.
Run away.
Oh, my god.
See, getting stuck just like saved my life right there.
I'm going to get shot right in the back.
Oh, my god.
See, getting stuck just like saved my life right there.
I'm going to get shot right in the back.
I want to go shot right in my vinkine.
Oh, crap.
I'm bumping into somebody.
Yep, there he is.
Help me.
Ends in 30 seconds.
Shit, wow.
The dead ringer.
Anybody, anybody?
Oh, nine damage.
Thank god I did nine damage.
Oh, man.
This is bad news.
Bad news right now.
What am I thinking?
Oh, god.
I tied it up at the very end.
Oh, my god.
Right at the very end, I tied it.
Holy crap.
All right, we did, guys.
We are going to change servers now.
So thanks, guys, jumping in this one.
It's going to be one.
Damn, damn, damn, damn, damn, damn.
This, I got to clean this milk up.
I got to clean this mad milk up.
I got to clean this.
I got to clean оргan.
I got to clean it.
Vyaduct.
No, that's, I don't know where that is.
Five gorge could be cool.
What else we got?
Granery.
I might be feeling granery right now.
Granery is, we're doing granery.
In the Reddit server apparently.
I'll be that.
Here you go.
There's the new server.
Granery is one of those maps that you never feel like playing on it.
But once you're actually playing,
you're going to be able to play on it.
You never feel like playing on it.
But once you're actually playing on it, you have a good time.
I don't know why.
Every single time I play granery, it's like, oh,
do I want to play granery?
I don't think so.
But then when I actually get on it, it's like, oh, this is fun.
Oh, it just changed a well.
Well, that's cool.
I feel the same way about well, though, to be honest.
All right, let's go.
Let's go.
Here we go.
I'll go red because I was on blue last time.
Maybe not.
Maybe so.
Nope.
Let me join red.
This time we're going to play demo.
Default demo, man.
Okay, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, strange lock and load.
Almost forgot.
I almost forgot.
Mission begins and 30 seconds.
Mission begins.
One second.
One.
Go.
I don't know.
But let any of the men get a better internet.
No, let's see.
Can I kill somebody?
Come on.
Are you happy?
I'm happy.
Thank you.
Oh, man.
Shout out to the men.
One.
The belt machine.
Millennium man.
Will I be selling admin on my server?
No.
I plan on just having people be able to play.
And I'm sure that's, you know, if you play there for long enough and you're, you know, a good supporter of the server, I would just give it to you.
You wouldn't have to pay for it.
Save your money.
That was a bad jump.
Now I'm going to die like instantly.
No, no, not OK.
Where is everybody?
Nothing in there.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
He's behind us.
He's dead now.
What is that?
Wow.
Oh, I thought he was going to walk out the door.
It's all right.
Man, here.
Oh, no.
Oh, no, what's going on?
No, I'm going to drown.
Oh, my God.
I really thought I was going to drown right there, guys.
Oh, come on.
Oh, die.
There we go.
Watch out behind us.
Behind us.
See, guys.
Oh, God, I got wrecked.
Right when I got over here.
Oh, my God.
I didn't expect this.
Oh, I didn't even look.
I should have been looking.
I'm going to die.
It's up top, isn't it?
Nice job, guys.
Nice job.
You have a little lady.
Cool.
Good job, gentle ladies and gentlemen.
Who's that?
Who is that?
Who am I doing a refreshing up?
Oh, jump.
Mission begins in 30 seconds.
We're going across the top.
Oh, my God.
Look who it is, ladies and gentlemen.
Burger boy with like a chocolate melted in his mouth.
Oh, what am I doing?
I shouldn't have came this way.
Why is that up here?
Who got up here?
How did that happen to someone from the last round?
Three, two, one.
Come here.
Oh, I'm never going to hit him.
Oh, he just jumped into that.
Where's my spray?
I want to spray.
Oh, come on, walk all over this.
Come on, come on.
Oh, let me get it up there.
Oh, well, at least we got it.
That's Pally.
Oh, this way, go, this way, go, this way.
Careful with the spies.
That might be a spy.
I think it was.
Yes, it was.
Cartoons.
These two.
Be careful.
We're entering the enemy base.
Oh, man.
We might be like a team scramble.
Oh.
Oh boy.
Oh, get out of town.
No, we're damaged.
I thought if I would just be in try-hard mode right there, I could just be quiet.
Bad.
Oh, the teams I guess aren't that bad.
We could probably use the scramble.
Maybe not.
We'll find out.
Oh boy.
That's up.
Heavy.
Really not anymore.
I thought I was going to hit him.
It's all about that little area, little corridor.
He didn't get hit by that.
What is up with that?
How can we, we're defending this point right?
Oh my god, we're going to get like four here.
I'm going to die.
Help me.
Somebody help me.
Oh, suicide.
I'm going to die.
Damn.
The heavy, baby.
I talked to DJ last night.
He's working on more stuff.
He's a hard work, man.
He's got a lot of cool ideas.
He's working on a lot of stuff.
It's coming.
You're just kidding me.
I thought you were an enemy.
Oh, wow.
Oh no.
Why did I do that?
I got behind everybody.
And no one knew I was there.
What is wrong with me?
What does the matter with me?
If I had just like not been a freak show,
I'd probably would have had a couple of kills right there.
I made it.
Whoa.
Oh, come on.
We're going viral.
Fire with the flare gun.
I have a degree.
You got to use the console to enter the Serb rip.
I think it's the till day key.
You have to enable it.
Hold on a second.
I've got a Pia offline.
Just so I have those notifications.
Stop popping up.
There's nobody wants to see the notifications.
They want to see Team Fortress 2.
I don't know.
I don't know what's going on.
Oh, God.
So much stuff going on.
No, don't die.
I'm trying to save the heavy.
Who got to buy the bus?
Somebody got to get by the bus, I think.
Yeah, this is the till day key.
You want to enable it.
You've got to options.
Go to advanced.
And then enable developer console.
I want that checked.
And once that is checked by default, it is the till day key.
The thing under escape.
And it looks like this.
Then you type in connect space.
Then the IP.
And then enter.
And that's it.
And that's all she wrote.
Massive bus accident.
Got hit by a train.
Oh, my God.
Oh, boy, you're being captured.
This way.
Oh.
No.
Damn it.
I'm going to spell it out.
D-A-M-N-I-T-E.
I have never played TF2 where.
I've heard it is hysterical though.
And I am absolutely willing to try.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
They're pushing us back.
They have pushed us all the way back.
This is not good.
I'm hanging out here.
Time has been added.
TF2 where is like a Wario where mod for team fortress where you get like five seconds to do like a little midi game.
It's very funny.
I've seen videos on it.
It looks really entertaining.
I'll check with them.
Oh, damn it.
Oh, God, it's chaos.
Shoot at me.
Somebody shoot at me with something.
Oh, that was just chaos.
I'm not sure.
I'll at control point is being captured.
Got to move that gear up.
Yeah, I actually own Gary's mod.
I'm not very good at it though.
I know a lot of people in Gary's mod can make ridiculous things.
I'm not one of those people.
Like, oh, I made this boat.
That's actually a car.
That's actually a house.
And it moves.
And these mouths are animated.
I can't do anything like that.
I wish I could.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, retreat.
Wow.
No, no, no.
Oh, there's nothing I can do about that.
Damn it.
New server, guys.
We'll do one more new server and then we're going to hop over to Binding of Isaac probably.
Last empty server.
Where can we find you?
Auxiliary operation.
What the hell is that?
1 to 32.
Actually, this one's 1 to 28.
Bad water.
We can end it on bad water.
There you go.
Join that server right now, ladies and gentlemen.
That's the new IP.
I'll post it again.
And there it is again.
Oh, man.
I'll go defense again.
I'm going to go big century engineer.
Oh, man.
This is depressing.
Where's all my stuff?
Where's all my hats?
I can't do this.
I said I have this.
I can look like I can put this on.
Oh, cool.
I don't know I can wear that.
That's awesome.
Hell yeah, I'll wear that.
I'll wear my ring.
Do well, do well.
Let's do it.
Big century engineer.
That built.
Get it to, you know what, just do an intro.
I'm good.
I'd rather have like the Return to Glory.
Appreciate it.
But thank you, though, Brian.
Appreciate that.
Where's it going?
Let's go right here.
It's a pretty safe place usually.
That way.
Now you know what this is going over here.
That's going to be sure.
Oh, yeah, we're on fire.
Hey, Nuckleheads, I'm talking to you.
Oh, what?
That just scared the crap out of me.
I just scared me.
Like I've really got scared by that.
Like it was like, oh, man, I'm sorry, you guys.
If you were in that server and you just got in and you, I really am sorry.
Okay, well, let's do this again.
This one is not.
No, I don't know about there.
Damn, that was dumb.
All right.
Dustball.
No, this one's bad.
What is it?
This bot's here.
So if we start to join this, it'll get rid of the bots, right?
That's usually what happens.
I'm pretty sure that's what happens.
So let's try this one.
Bad water basin.
Hopefully this one doesn't just turn off, instant turn off.
I hope you're enjoying your time because it's about to instant turn off.
All right, I'll stick with this.
I'll stick with this.
Going over here, no.
Oh, you're already over there.
All right, you got that coming.
I'm cool.
I'll stick right there.
Jeremy, why is Burger Boy so fat?
Hey, that's not nice.
That's not a nice thing to say about Burger Boy.
I'll just get the thing again.
This is a bad spot for that.
I don't know why I put that there.
I need to move that eventually.
Somebody's right there, and it's shoot at it.
You know what?
I might move my...
I'm going to move it.
I'm going up here.
I'm going to go over here.
Looks like they're not capping.
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
Oh, dammit, dammit, dammit.
He doesn't have a sapper.
He doesn't have sapper.
Somebody take care of that.
You know what?
I'm going to go up Gonslinger.
You have a feeling that's going to happen a thousand more times.
Man, did you...
And give my dispenser to this guy.
You got to put it over here.
Somebody comes in Hoover Chargers and kills that.
They'll have this backup one.
In case he needs it.
There you go, sir.
Let's go and get some more.
No, I'll be out of that field yet.
I'm going to leave.
Whoops, didn't mean to click.
Oh, what's going on?
What the hell?
I'm going to build it up.
Run away.
Build in the center.
Two mini-centre in the same spot.
That's a double mini-centre.
You're still alive.
Oh, no.
Dammit, I got too many spies.
Too many spies.
Oh, engineer.
I'm not going to play with you.
How about a soldier?
Soldier with the strange Liberty Launcher and the...
Talon's backup.
Why not?
Might as well.
And the strange hats are touching.
Do I want a vintage husband?
I'm all good.
I'll be okay.
Thank you, though.
And rather, like I said before,
rather you guys keep your stuff.
Thanks for the aid.
Because you could use it, too.
What?
Oh my god.
This is fantastic.
I'm dead instantly.
Didn't even see that.
Oh, they're going to win.
No, I don't know.
I want the...
Let's go to shotgun.
Just walk into that.
If I were to have needed any weapon of my choice,
if I would have wanted,
strange huntsmen.
Everyone was just talking about it.
Oh my god.
It's worth like 50 million dollars or something.
For a 500,000 million trillion dollars.
Let's get on a streak here.
What do you say?
What do you say, Jeremy?
Let's get on a streak.
The reserve shooter would have been like a better option.
Be careful.
Be careful here.
Oh boy.
He's in trouble.
Watch out there.
He's trying to fool us.
Oh, it's a losing fight.
It's a losing fight.
Gotta get away.
Oh, come on.
Look at this health.
Should you use your three refined to craft a hat or should you trade it?
It depends on what hat you want.
Because if you go into a trading server,
you can...
For a lot of...
A lot of the time, you can get one hat for one refined.
Like one of those craftable hats.
It really depends on if you want a just a hat.
Because you can potentially get like three hats with three refined.
Or if you want to just make a random one and potentially get one of the new ones.
I got an email apparently.
No idea what that is about.
Can I check that after I die?
Well...
He's going up here.
Oh, that was lucky.
Anybody in here?
You're not a spy.
Oh, my God, there's a sentry.
Damn it.
Oh, they're going to get it.
Gotta get rid of that sentry.
Even if I die, damn it, damn it, damn it.
I was standing right there.
Damn it.
The difference between dirty and clean items, I really don't know.
I'm not a real big trader.
So I'm not really sure how the link goes.
I think clean is when it doesn't say who crafted it.
Isn't that what it means?
Oh, uncraftable, okay.
Wow.
I think we're good.
I think we got it.
Oh, run.
I don't have an equalizer.
I'm a trouble, I need help.
I'm bumping into a spy too.
They're going to get it.
I don't even see what I'm looking back and forth of the chat in the game.
What had you talked about?
Did you want to have a German?
Just read.
I'm like, wait, what happened?
I would like it if you guys don't have to give me anything.
I got plenty of stuff.
I got plenty of options where I can get things.
You guys hold on to your items.
They're your harder items.
You guys deserve them not being.
There's a lot of people right there.
I'm dead.
I got the help.
Oh, crit.
Oh.
Outside 100, I have a setup video.
If you go to my YouTube channel and you type in 4,000 subs, I did like a 4,000 subscriber
thing a long, long time ago.
And it's a setup video.
And it's got the same, I got the same computer.
So I'm probably going to get a new computer at some point in the near future.
I would assume probably the next couple of months I will get a new computer.
Well, that's over.
You failed.
Alright.
So I think I'm going to transition open to binding a bison for one life or two lives or something like that.
We'll see what I do.
Broom.
Binding of Isaac is a really weird, really disturbing kind of...
It's made in Flash, I think.
But it's a steam game to get its five bucks.
It's very, very disturbing and very screwed up.
So I will put that disclaimer out there before I stream it.
But yeah, thank you guys if you would see her for the TF2.
Then thank you so much for coming to watching.
You guys rock and roll.
And I'll catch you guys probably next time.
And I'll be getting a face by frying pan.
Oh.
No one come over to where I'm at.
Alright.
Let's do some binding of Isaac.
Now hold on to your hats.
Hold on to your hats.
Hold on to your seats.
Let me see if I can stream this.
Bamp bamp.
And here are two.
On the dash, the dashboard.
Dashboard.
Playing.
Binding of Isaac.
Update.
Yeah, I got to change my background.
Actually, let's change my background.
Because this has been my background for a very long time.
Let's change the background.
Alright, so let's do personalize.
Desktop backgrounds.
Alright, so do I want like the space needle?
Oh god, am I breaking the stream?
Maybe not.
I think I like the space needle.
What about the ice one?
Oh, sweet.
Oh, what about this one?
Oh man, this is the one.
This is the one I'm keeping.
Look at this thing.
That thing is beautiful.
Save changes.
Gorgeous.
Gorgeous screen.
It's like a painting.
So disclaimer, finding a Isaac is an incredibly messed up, disturbing, crazy, insane game.
So viewer discretion is advised.
I'm going to say that before playing, because obviously this game is ridiculous.
Probably the stream doesn't die.
I don't think it will.
Take a look.
The audio is going to have to come down a little bit.
It's okay.
The finding of Isaac.
Isaac.
Okay.
Change this.
Screen's going to go black.
Black screen.
That's screen region.
Take this.
And stretch it out.
Not ready.
Finding of Isaac.
So I'm pretty good at this game.
I've become pretty good at this game.
I love this game.
It is so much fun.
It's just so addicting.
Go with the cane.
Cane.
Got the eye patch.
Alright.
Let's do it.
The reason why I'm playing this again is because the DLC is coming out in the next couple of days, I think.
Finding of Isaac DLC should be out soon.
I'll get that bomb.
For the meantime, I'm going to run around like a psycho.
So if you like games that are...
They call these rogue likes.
Don't they have rogue like dungeon crawlers?
The real Blizzard 10121.
How do you become a mod on the stream?
Usually the mods are people that I...
That I'm like friends with that I talk to all the time and stuff like that.
But yeah, I mean, if you've been coming for that long and you know...
I'll probably set up some type of way to get a mod.
A way for you to get mod or wait for people to get mod if they want it.
But it's hard to give mods to people because there's just so many people that would want it.
So it's very very difficult to say, oh yeah, you can be a mod.
Sure.
Oh, triple shot. This is going to be a good game.
This is going to be a good game.
It's hard to give up mod specifically because it's just so many people want it.
So if I were to give it to one person and you know somebody else would be like, well I want mod too.
And it's like, it's a very tough decision to make.
So, but eventually I will probably do...
I will probably do a...
some type of way to get it. I don't know how though.
Triple shot is incredible.
Did triple shot extra damage more tears?
You're talking about absolute chaos.
Let me get that bomb and open up the secret room for crying out loud.
Spreadgun.
Oh, and now it's the troll bomb.
That's not cool.
For fly contest, mod giveaway.
You know what? I probably...
You know what? We're going to have to build it.
I'll do some type of...
I don't know.
It's hard.
I'll tell you one thing, but those of you that better hang out here.
I'm going to do...
I'm going to make a video and move this mouse.
I'm going to do a video on this in the next couple of days.
Next week's stream.
It's going to be very, very interesting.
Because I'm going to do a game show.
I'm going to...
I'm going to try and explain this.
I'm going to buy another 30 or 40 keys
and get a bunch of crates.
And what we're going to do is we're going to do a trivia night
where I have the screen opens on Team Fortress 2
and hold on, I'm going to die.
So the screen's open on Team Fortress 2
like 40 crates with 40 keys.
And I'm going to ask trivia questions.
Like, basically, gaming trivia questions.
It's not going to be all totally Team Fortress though.
So it might be some other general gaming questions.
And if you get it right, if you're the first person to get it in the chat,
then you get to pick which crate you want online.
And I just thought about that the other day.
I was like, you know, that would be actually really cool.
It would be fun.
So that's the plan for next.
And I'm going to make a video on this.
If you're watching this on YouTube and you're like,
oh, wait, wait, wait, what? I want more details.
This is going to be a video made about that very, very soon.
Do, do, do, do, all right? Let's get some more help.
Yes, you will get what's inside.
If you get the trivia question correct,
you can open up whatever's in whatever crate you want.
You get whatever's in there.
It doesn't matter if it's a $5 million unusual or paint.
You're going to get it.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, get out of my way.
I don't want to tie this early.
Trouble shot.
Yeah, if you want, if you guys have crates,
I mean, I know I did a crate.
People donated a lot to the last one.
But if you have crates, if you have, you know,
I'd series 20 and above anything lower than series 20.
I don't think I would want to leave that alone for now.
But yeah, it's just a way to involve everybody.
Because I think that would just be fun, like a trivia night.
You know what I mean? Like, all right.
In what level of, like, legend is Zelda.
Do you like just anything like that?
Do you find the master saw and just general basic.
A lot of people would get involved if they're really fun.
And hopefully somebody gets something cool.
Oh, it's a lot of what you got.
Nothing on me.
You got nothing on me in my triple shot, baby.
There would be a lot of team fortress questions though.
Like, oh, I'm going to get a lot of people.
I'm going to get a lot of people.
There would be a lot of team fortress questions though.
Like, oh, in what crate can you get a strange Gerradi?
Oh, I'm going to die.
I'm like, too busy talking about what I'm doing to my next dream.
I'm like, don't be paying attention to this one.
This is hard.
I have to use it.
Oh, what am I doing? I didn't have to use that.
I could have used it in a, whatever.
Whatever. That's me being a really, really dumb stupid person.
But you know what?
At least I can see it over there.
Let's see if it rooms right there.
What I need is I need damage up.
I know. I have a stealth.
I know. I know.
I know.
There you go.
So it's a music too loud right now.
I feel like it is.
Or am I just freaking out?
No reason.
Oh, come on.
Hit him.
Okay.
You know, I have headphones on, so it's kind of tough for me to decipher
how loud something is or not.
And open up that secret room, baby.
$3 or $3 pennies, not dogs.
That's not a total waste of a secret room.
How do you get the crates to me?
I'll probably set up some type of way.
Everybody doesn't have to give them though.
Because obviously I only need like 30 or 40 of them.
I want to give you stuff.
Should you get this game?
I'm going to 100% absolutely 100 million% say yes, yes, yes, a million times.
This is an incredibly fun and incredibly different game.
It's just like a like 17 and up.
Like if this is this game is not designed for like younger people to play.
Only because of the incredibly like blasphemous and ridiculous imagery that is associated with it.
But if you don't care about that then this game is one of the most fun addictive.
Probably one of the best games I've ever played that's under $10.
This game is only five bucks.
This game is five dollars on steam.
Like yikes, that's insane.
This was actually supposed to be ported to the 3DS.
But Nintendo said that's not happening.
I don't want to comment cause these things.
Do I even have enough money for anything?
I don't think so.
It's not even worth opening this door.
Not even worth opening the door.
I don't even have enough money to get anything in there.
Die!
Come on, hit him.
I got the triple shot. Why am I missing so much?
Yeah and Nintendo said because of religious and blasphemous and just...
The game is just really very very dark.
So it is only on steam.
It's the only place you can get it.
I don't think it's on Xbox Live.
Oh look a sun card.
Might as well like waste it.
I'll come back to the judgement.
Oh, what this boss is but?
Give an eye!
I'm like tempted to just use the sun card and not have to even fight this guy.
But you know what?
I'm not going to do that.
We will do this the right way.
I'm trying to get rid of the baby first.
I don't think I can though.
Pretty sure you can.
And he more tears.
Not shooting fast enough.
Something from the future I unlocked.
Some now in the basement.
Speed up.
I would use the sun card.
But honestly it's just...
It's a...
Oh crap moment.
Like I'm going to die.
I'm going to die.
Use it.
I'm not sure you sell bank.
I will take whatever is in there.
Take that key.
Thank you very much.
How do you play this game?
It's just with the keyboard.
And you just go from room to room.
Clearing out all the monsters just like Legends of Zelda or Star tropics.
Or other games that are around the same design philosophy.
Once you kill every single thing in the room,
I see the top left of the map.
You can see what rooms are open that you can go to.
Fight the boss.
You kill the boss.
You go on to the next level.
And if you die, it's over.
You cannot continue.
There is no lives.
There is no continuing.
You just die.
And if you start all over again.
This is going to be a room where I might have to be...
I just take this nice and slow.
I might only use the song card.
I think I've heard of these guys.
There we go.
Yeah, they're your big fat red bastard.
Oh!
The question is, how am I going to do it?
I'm going to do it.
Get the coin and the bomb back.
Oh!
Mmm.
I'll take that.
Yeah.
Money, money.
Lots of money.
Now if I see an item room, I will open the door.
Because it will be actually worth it.
Pills.
Cain is the best with pills.
Take them.
Oh!
Goddammit.
If I had only known that.
I had only known that.
Blast damage increased.
Oh, I hate this item.
It freaks me out.
Look at my guy.
That looks really screwed up.
Ha ha ha.
Should I go into the mob room?
I'll do it.
Why not?
Oh, more pills.
Who knows what they are.
I'm going to use them yet.
Man, I'm shooting way too slow.
This is like messing with me.
Need faster speed.
Firing speed.
Die.
Bad.
These guys make a really weird noise.
Oh, if I could just kill them faster.
Oh, die.
Oh, come on.
They don't shoot faster though.
There we go.
Oh, come on.
You freaking bastards.
Oh, my God.
There we go.
Let's see what this is.
Oh, no.
Well, that was dumb.
So I've got one more place and I have the secret room.
Probably right here.
Maybe either right here or down.
Now it's got to be down here.
Secret room.
Thank you very much.
Eggs.
I will take these eggs.
Oh, all right.
Easy as pie.
These guys are nothing.
The hanged man.
This one's kind of not really neat that right now.
But I will blow up this machine for sure.
And I'm going to do it with the common cause.
I don't even know if I can pretend to know.
The Emperor.
What does the Emperor do?
I forget what MLC stealth.
What do I do?
What does this one do?
I forget.
And now he's down.
Takes you to the boss.
Okay, I'm absolutely not going to do that.
I will pick this back up with the Sun card.
Hmm.
Don't even.
I'm not going to try and get it.
Sticking with the Sun card.
Oh, my.
I'm using it.
That was just, I that would have bad news written all over.
Okay.
10 bombs.
You know, I'm doing it.
I'm absolutely doing it.
And I get the key too.
And I get the heart.
I'll get it all.
I'll buy your whole damn store up.
Take the hanged man.
Actually, what?
No, I don't want the Emperor card.
Well, you know, I will take the Emperor card.
You know why?
Cause there's nowhere other rooms to go.
And let's go!
Woohoo!
Versus a fistudah!
You don't blow up.
I'm using, I'm going to use these bombs on them.
Actually, no, that's not a good idea.
I'm going to be in a lot of trouble because I'm shooting way too slow.
This is way too slow, Vishal.
God.
At least I did that.
Okay.
Now I'll get out of my way.
I just saw what you said.
Blizzard.
I just don't want to die, so I'll address it in a second.
And out of my face.
Okay.
I don't have Gotham City in Posterous, but I own Sirius Sam III.
I do not have Gotham City in Posterous.
I keep hearing it's fun though.
Okay, for now it's my name.
XXX, Latha1, XXX.
I even came close.
Oh come on, get out of my face.
At least I got faster tears.
This is way better.
My keyboard's getting stuck.
But I've heard nothing but good things about Gotham City in Posterous.
So I heard when it launched they had a lot of problems.
And I think it still has connection problems, directly if I'm wrong, but I remember people talking about that being like I can't even play the game.
Open, Sesame.
All right, let me read the chat.
Somebody had said something.
Will you be doing playthrough board lengths too?
I will probably.
I mean that game's not coming up for a very long time though.
I think September, right?
So I'm not sure exactly who I'll play with.
I have no idea.
But yes, I'm assuming I will play.
Where's the DLC for this game?
Talking about new releases, why don't we get the wrath of the lamb?
Whatever it's called, the DLC.
Oh my god, you know what?
Eat bomb.
Oh!
I used to come a Kazian and it killed me.
I hit the space bar and it...
Oh my god.
Dude, I accidentally hit the space bar and it killed me.
I can't believe I had the stupid item.
I cannot believe it.
I am so mad right now.
I could put my fist through the screen.
Like what?
My finger happened to slip over the space bar and touch it.
I can't believe it.
Oh!
I went like this.
Oh, sorry, hit space.
Oh god, damn.
That was a good run, too.
I was doing fine.
Alright, it's time for quap.
I come on.
I am so upset right now.
Freaking internet connection.
It's time for quap.
That's just...
I can't believe it.
I am sitting there doing...
I am running through Viningov Isaac without a problem.
And I hit the space bar because I have the Dan Kamikaze.
Well, we are just going to kill you.
I don't even pick that item up.
What a worthless item.
Well, you know, whatever.
It was bound to happen.
It was absolutely bound to happen.
That dat rage.
Let's do a new window.
Oh god.
Oh, so long a second.
Whoopsadaisy.
Add screen region.
Man, here it is.
Quap, quap, quap, quap.
Quap.
Oh, I am still mad about that.
I am still upset about that.
Alright, we are going to have another quaps on.
Let's see if I can get a quaps on.
The only way I play this game is if I can do a quaps on.
See if we go ready.
Plank clock.
Quap is the only game we play.
When we play every day to date.
We got a quap, quap, quap, quap, quap, quap.
We got a crown to quap with a slop and a block.
It sucks.
Alright, we will do another one.
Okay, it is going to start.
It is going to start like this.
Quap is the only game you play.
When you want to play every single day to snug.
You got a snug.
The only time you play you got to say quap is the only game you play.
When you snug stretched out.
And I can't even move.
I can't even move today.
But ness the way we say today.
We pray we got a new disguise.
My mind is like all over the place right now.
Like looking at this guy's legs, it is freaking me out.
Alright, I got to get past 15 meters.
Dead, dead, dead, dead, dead, dead, dead, dead, dead, dead, dead, sluck, sluck, sluck, sluck, sluck.
Alright, I got past 10.
I got to get past 15.
Oh yeah, baby.
What do you know about that?
Oh my god.
I just was doing it.
I was doing it guys.
I was just doing it.
Now we're doing it.
Oh I got it.
I figured it out.
Quap.
I figured it out how to play quap.
Alright, last try.
Last try.
Come on, I got to get back into that.
I had it.
I was running.
I was legitimately sprinting.
So bitch.
I strange love.
Strange love 23.
Come on, you slug bastard.
Alright, if I get by 10, I'm good.
Nope.
Okay, whatever.
Oh, that's going to be it guys.
That's going to be the end of the stream.
Nobody dreamed.
Dream of a dream.
Dream of a dream stream.
We got to go.
Go.
That's the end of the stream.
Thank you for coming to the stream.
I hope you enjoyed the time with me on the stream.
Now we got to slug one more time to say goodbye.
Thank you.
Everybody.
See you later guys.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Yeah, that's it.
Alright, ladies and girmes.
I'll see you guys later.
Thanks for coming out.
All over 200 of you guys still here.
You guys are amazing.
Thank you so much.
I'll catch you guys later guys.
Peace and oh, I forgot to mention.
Grandpa is going to be...
It's going to be on Machinima Respawn in like 20 minutes.
So if you want to see the new Grandpa trailer,
it's pretty ridiculous.
It's going to be there in like 25 minutes.
So Machinima Respawn 20 minutes.
And yeah, thanks so much guys.
I'll see you all later.
And take care.
Everybody.