Hi!
Hello, everyone. German 985 here.
Hello, everyone. German 985.
Oh, well, you can't lie to him like that.
What's up, guys?
Did anyone believe it?
No one's even here to hear it, so.
Yeah, there are like 15-20 people already here.
Oh, you're on Twitch, mother.
I am on the Twitch-itch.
Anyways, happy Saturday.
Happy Sunday if you're from a different country.
And let me show this out to people's.
Actually, I got to write, uh, app.
And they'll see.
Oh, come on.
Well, how come I can't bring up Brett, as I can app mentioned?
Maybe he blew up his Twitter.
MLC stealth.
Like, I'm not even doing you either.
What's going on here, Twitter?
Twitter, what is going on?
Why are you being like this?
I'm going to tweet, too.
You could just retweet what I tweet.
You can all tweet.
You can pick your dog.
You can tweet, I tweet, but you can't.
We all tweet for germistry.
And there we go.
With at MLs.
Okay, why that was weird.
I don't know why it didn't work before.
I wonder who that is.
And tweet.
No, no, no, tweet.
Come to it yet.
Because I need to, uh, write it.
I already tweeted.
Oh, no, it is.
Oh, no, no, no, I was talking to myself, not to you.
Like, as I was telling myself, because I was going to hit the Twitter button.
And I didn't even put like the link.
So I was like, no, no.
It has been Twittered.
And yes, it has.
And there's Twitter.
Now go to YouTube.
And post that.
And then get out of there, because it's not necessary.
And set it stream.
Which means you're going to find, okay.
Good evening.
I'm going to play some team fortress too.
And then if you guys don't know, they just put out a huge, huge CS go update.
So that should be interesting to check out for sure.
It's probably one of the big, they've added like five maps.
I would love to express my enthusiasm for that.
But the last.
I cannot.
You don't have it.
I don't have it.
No.
I don't know.
Yeah.
I think they're going to release this coming soon.
I think it's coming soon.
Otherwise did the update today was pretty huge.
So you know valve, though, it's going to be months, probably.
Yeah, yeah, true.
Very true.
Good evening, everyone.
All of you that are saying good evening.
So I want to show you.
You go tomorrow and go to tidings.
So let's get rolling.
A mLC stealth is here.
But he's currently he's currently in the bathroom.
And that's all we're going to say about that.
So let's find a server that is an empty.
Do we need to wait for him before we join a server so that he can play?
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, there you go. There he is.
Perfect timing, sir. Thank you. I was waiting for the right moment to enter.
And I once seemed pretty good.
No, I was watching clips from the on-de-genera show.
What are you doing that? She's funny.
Sorry, I'm late. You're supposed to be in the stream.
Now let's get into the server. Let's try to find a 32-way-way-go.
CPU Badlands. I don't know. I want to do CPU Badlands.
This is 28. That's 2-4. It's trading.
Oh, here we go. This is 2 out of 24.
All right, you guys ready? Uh, not quite yet.
Oh, you better hurry up. I'm, I'm launching it.
It's already on that screen. It's already on the screen.
I've already got Xbox connected. My console.
Ready to go. Wait a couple seconds.
Oh, by the way, if you guys may.
Everyone knows who Stealth is, but some people may not know who you are.
Alex, go ahead and give an introduction.
Hey guys, my name is Alex, and I make YouTube videos.
And my channel name is Gamers Descent, which you may know me by instead of a Talix.
That is where I hail from.
Yeah, you come from the the monitoring top of Gamers Descent.
What time is it right now? It is 15 after 6 if people that were just saying that.
All right, I'm ready.
What are we going to say to Alex before I cut you off?
I don't. Woo.
I don't know. I guess to further introduce myself, I'm a machinima realm director.
So I'm on, I'm on the other side of the chasm between the two machinima mountains.
I come in peace.
Here we go. People have already started joining. Let's do it.
68.177.101.44.27016.
You better go.
Oh, that confused me.
It has 16.
I've pressed 6 first.
Well, you better get in there.
Those teen numbers always confuse me.
Hey, I think so it still says, oh, I'm playing.
I didn't even update the dashboard either.
I think the good thing is still correct.
I'll get the change right now.
Put TF2 Moa hunting.
TF2 Moa hunting.
All you're going to do is get 25 kills in a row.
That's very difficult to do in this game.
That is not an easy thing to do in team fortress to get more than,
more than I'd say, more than 15 kills in a row.
10 kills in a row is even like a pretty big field strength.
The only one who could do it is a engineer.
Yeah, I'll have you to have you can get a lot of engineer.
If nobody is like smart and going,
Demoman or over medic.
I went on zero red team.
How's the game audio? Let's take a look.
How's the game audio guys?
Good.
Check again.
I cannot tell.
Are you going to tell them what's your name is?
People will probably figure it out by now.
Dick Simmons, the dump champion.
Oh, where's this scout going?
It's pretty nice player gun, dude.
Oh, I thought it was you.
Oh, watch it.
Oh, forgot fire kills me.
It's going up pretty well here.
All right, what do I have for a melee right now?
Actually, I got the postal pommel there.
All right, let's try and get some postal pommel there kills.
Yeah, you know, you're not spying.
I need a medic.
Oh, yeah, we did it.
Game over.
Oh, we did it.
Good job.
So we can do it again.
Very cool.
Oh, we changed.
I wanted to play on upwards.
Oh, I love upward.
I know.
I love it too.
Upward is one of my favorites.
Upward.
Oh, what are we going to do?
My most kills is only 25 as a sniper.
I would have only gotten one moeab.
I have no idea.
Oh, Thunder Mountain.
Good.
I love Thunder Mountain.
I like the first two stages.
Thunder Mountain.
Germa, can I be has in a hug?
If you ask him for a hug,
get ready.
Internet hug.
There we are.
He, he, he,
be has him in your hug.
Here we go.
He has been in.
Here comes the internet hug.
You just received the internet hug.
Look, worth 15 dollars.
You've got hugs.
That's actually pretty good.
You've got mail.
Oh, I have a new item.
Oh, I got a new item.
I'm giving away my backpack.
I finally got some new stuff.
Why am I even running?
Waiting for players.
What are we going?
You guys, no one's got to give me stuff.
I mean, items are one thing.
I have a, a nice plan.
As you probably saw in my latest video,
if you haven't,
I'm going to do a crate unboxing video.
Whatever I get in those crates.
If I get an unusual or something,
it's going to be given away.
So,
any unusual I get in the boxes,
it's going to be given away.
And if I get strangers, they're mine.
I'm keeping them.
Now we got, we got a full server.
I will prop the 24.
Yeah, there's this five spectators.
Be sure some people are kind of stuck in the spectator right now.
But the unboxing video will probably be
next week out as soon.
I do.
Take seven, the dump champion.
Yeah, that's me.
Dick Simmons, the dump champion.
Wait, did you put end quotes on that?
I think this is the parrots parentheses.
It's all I know.
It should be on this stream.
I don't think so.
I've been wrong before though.
All right, I close my door there.
Should be as not on this stream.
Not in the chat anyway.
No, I'm not that I can see.
High five.
Frank.
Can I just kill somebody already?
We got to wait.
Instead of time, man.
I want to blow them underneath the fence.
Well, I ever played Dona War II.
Oh, man, I was a huge Dona War one fan.
I don't really like what they did with Dona War II.
I'm not going to lie.
Wasn't a big Dona War II person.
Oh my God.
All right, forgot another shotgun.
Still pretty good.
Oh, thanks.
Covered in the G.A.
Roddy.
I'm going to puke as I get.
Derradi makes me puke.
Oh my God.
Derradi get out of here.
Conqueror.
Contrary.
I can't believe how many no points I got right there.
Oh no, no.
Damn it.
I thought I had more rockets loaded.
SHIT.
What does that spell shoot?
Gosh darn it.
Oh, good.
That's what that spells.
Oh, boom.
Who am I streaming with?
MLC stealth and italics.
Two grows.
We play games.
Sometimes we are special.
Sometimes we play video games.
Oh, occasionally.
Sometimes we laugh.
Sometimes we cry.
Sometimes we share valuable moments together.
The nec is better.
Oh, he's going to get away.
I refuse to let him get away.
He's going to get behind everybody.
He's going to get behind us.
Oh, I think he already is.
Oh, he's gone.
What?
Nine health and I'm jumping off of high surfaces.
Oh, how I survived.
Give me that health.
Can you donate an unusual um?
I thought you were about to say can you dig it, Sucker?
I would rather you hang onto that.
I don't need anything.
You know, you don't have to get me stuff.
Booker tea.
Best surely an unusual because an unusual is worth a lot.
And I don't want to take stuff like that from people so.
Oh, did I make it?
Oh, my god.
That was a good shot.
That guy caught me right when I was coming down.
Oh, oh.
I got to take off the conqueror.
Conqueror is oh, man.
Not feeling the conqueror.
Not right now.
Oh, damn.
That was in the face.
Oh.
What's it?
I'm taking this off.
I'm going to put on.
What am I going to put on?
I'm going to put on the shotgun.
The strange shotgun I still have to give these away.
I have given my third.
I've given 33% of the back back away so far.
Two more people I have to get in contact with.
And then after that, it is start all over again.
All right.
I'm going medic.
Yeah, we could use, we only got one.
Oh, actually, you are the one.
You just went.
Actually, there's two I think.
Areas, medicing.
Oh, okay.
Okay, okay.
I see.
So, which one is a German?
I swear, it's not Dick Simmons, the dump champion.
That is a spy.
Oh, no.
If I see, oh, bye.
Is it, is it, oh, bye, charge?
What classes are you guys playing as right now?
I'm soldier.
Oh, no.
Oh, so little hell.
I am the same time.
What do I have?
Video settings on here.
I'll show you.
I'm going to do that.
Video, 1280 by 720, because I'm running in a window right now.
I'm going to be able to stream it.
But I play on high, high, high, simple, medium,
disabled color correction, and then all these other things.
I don't play with anti-alasing on.
I feel like the amount of resources it takes
to the amount of gain you get is not really that noticeable, at least in my opinion.
Is it at least for a game like this?
Oh, my.
Thank you for putting me out of fire, Tyro.
For me, I always play with B-Sync God.
Oh, my God.
Damn.
Always.
I'm changing.
I'm changing to engineer.
Do I play any commonly hated games?
Oh, backstab.
Turn around.
Spy.
Do you guys play any commonly hated games?
Is outside our door?
Any commonly hated cadence?
I call it duty.
What would fall under that?
That's fine.
Number one right there.
Yes, stealth.
Answer it.
Yes.
Stealth does play commonly hated games.
Call it duty.
But like actually hated like literally bad games, I don't know.
Yeah, I don't.
I don't think I play any really hated games.
Oh, there's the sniper again.
We still got to level one up.
Oh, I think I got about a score.
Oh, come on.
Is this guy hacking?
I see a spy on their team running around in his taunts.
And he looks like a wax figure just moving around.
Skating around.
It's probably a glitch or something.
Yeah, I saw that earlier too.
I think it is just a glitch.
But even when he was disguised, it was just walking around.
Not moving.
Like arms in the air.
Oh, I got a change this.
I don't got a change that one.
I do.
You got to change it.
No, I got to hurry the hell up.
Oh, boy.
Do you engineer?
I was a second behind.
I threw my games off, thrown off now.
What is this like an RTS?
I've got to catch up.
My actions permitted is only a hundred.
Let's go.
What you gonna do?
What's the best scattergun for the scout?
They're all good.
Depends on how you play stylons.
Mid-range, too long-range, use the shortstop.
Close-range, meat shots, force nature, and everything else kind of in between.
The regular scatterguns are probably the best.
At least that's kind of how I see it.
I like that one the best.
No, I gotta go over here.
What am I doing?
Oh god, I've already spurred this up.
And I salvage this is the real question.
That's the real question.
Can I salvage this?
What am I doing?
I don't know where I want to put it.
I don't know what I want to do.
I'm so torn right now.
Oh, because this guy's right here now.
I'm putting it right here.
The limb of the limb of the...
I was that was so torn.
My brain put it on here.
I know what I was just doing right here.
Oh, lord.
Oh, this is going down in two seconds.
I have absolutely...
Oh, lag.
Oh yeah, I got that too.
Super lag.
Is that the real emulsie stealth?
I hope so.
Yep.
Oh, I'm getting a lot of lag.
Thank you, Engineer, for helping me build this.
Appreciate it.
And let's reload.
Is that the real emulsie stealth?
Oh yeah.
All right, I got some catching up to doing points.
This is kind of getting embarrassing.
Oh my gosh.
Here comes...
Oh, there comes the dispenser.
Oh my god.
Oh, he's up top.
Oh.
That just ruined my life.
There's my leg in.
Unmoving.
Yeah, I got him.
Or maybe you dead ring too, Nusk.
We're going this.
I like this better.
Because I don't feel as bad when I lose all my stuff.
Oh, spy.
Doing his thing.
I think that...
Oh, my word.
He is doing his thing, isn't he?
Get away, Romery.
He's not dead.
Oh, he is not dead.
I didn't get the...
I'm going to duel with him right now.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, so I didn't get the...
I don't know, everyone.
Finally, on the cart.
Shit.
Oh, my god.
You're all right, doc.
Oh, run away.
I want it up here.
They're about to get to the point.
They almost say...
Oh, crap thing.
Oh, no, no, no, where's he?
He's...
Oh, no.
Give me the help.
Oh, my god, run away.
Oh, this guy's still going to get me.
Oh, no.
Oh, I can't believe I'm still alive.
Oh, they got it.
No, I was dead.
I was toast right here.
I was toast.
Oh, I love butter toast.
What's name tag?
I think the chat...
The chat freeze for anybody else.
I think the chat froze for me.
Somebody has found name tag.
What's that mean?
I don't think the chat froze.
No, I was looking at it and I was like, wait, no, nothing.
Oh, they're going to...
They got a heavy medic right here.
Get rid of that medic.
Oh, my god.
When all of us fails, just duck and cover.
Well, I'll just fry.
I didn't know you found that stuff though.
Didn't know you found the name tags.
I thought you had a biome.
Ah, you can find it.
No, I think.
This one just found it.
Frazier, you can find it.
There's spies surfing around in the base.
There's two spies, I think sitting outside our doors.
Oh, god, he's over here.
No, wait, what?
That's not even mine.
That's not my century.
I'm really losing it here, guys.
My brain can't even handle what I'm doing.
Oh, get out of my way.
No, no, no, no.
Oh, I just barely saved that.
So many people.
So much death.
Trying to get this dispenser up.
Oh, all those primes.
I know you're not dead.
You could just.
Wow, oh, okay, I'm going out there.
I'm going out there.
Someone's going to get toasted out there.
Oh, it's probably going to be me.
Is that you, Dick?
Was that you?
It's just who walked right next to me?
Was that the spy?
Is that you, Richard?
Yeah, that's me.
Oh, hello.
What are you doing, Richard?
Yeah.
Oh, get the medic.
Oh, yeah, I went from like last place, like fourth place in one line.
Oh, my God.
What's ringing out?
Oh, that's a.
I bet this is fun.
I am.
Wow.
Hi.
What happened?
Hold on, hold on.
That's going to be cool.
Sorry, let's talk to my man.
I'm going to get back to that.
That's a spy.
Oh, well, shoot.
God.
Oh, God.
There we go.
This is what I'm talking about.
Ow.
What the fuck?
I'm with a scoreboard, boys.
I have faith in you, Jerma.
I wonder if I will play, you think, uh,
I read it.
I wonder if you're going to nice to.
What the hell was that?
Just get a nice gun in place when at the end of that hallway right there.
Yeah, I'm trying to, I can turn it.
Did I keep destroying it?
I got some people that know I get doing.
Uh, I've probably will play zombie fortress at some point.
Probably not tonight though.
What?
Zombie fortress.
I'm just going into punches.
I don't even care.
We might knock it out with one punch.
You're getting knocked out from the, uh,
oh, come on, feel the pain.
Feel it.
I would have killed them too.
Oh, fuck, let's try.
Let's get one shot.
Uh, let's set the next level to where we're going.
We're changing server after this anyway, so.
Oh,
all right.
Well, that answers that question.
We're changing server.
Just a people want to know,
German, what is zombie fortress?
I, uh, I don't know.
I think it's like kind of like every, oh my god.
Everybody plays as, oh, I think everyone has melee,
except for a small group of people.
Somebody explain it.
Oh, so it's like infection on Halo.
Hey, you're not me.
Whatever that game mode is called.
I think I know what you're talking about.
Yeah, it's, it's like, it's kind of like a zombie mode,
where everyone runs around with melee,
except for the small group of people that don't have,
did they're like the not zombies.
If I'm wrong, somebody please correct me in the chat,
because I know it's something like that though.
That's probably right.
Somebody said it's like Halo infection.
Watch out for spies.
Oh, they got taken out everything.
I got to be a little bit sneakier with these centers.
And that's going to blow up again.
And that's going to die.
I said, all right.
I go, I'm going to go.
I'm going to S sounds.
Who you playing as heavy?
I am playing as heavy.
See, Scout is what I rage quit as.
Five, I like to run around.
I start a scout and then I'm like, oh, okay, I suck.
Moving on to the heavy where I can actually kill people.
I like this setup.
I'll stick with this.
Whoa, I heard it backstabbed.
I'm standing in the corner.
Oh, God.
Oh, I don't think he's dead.
Maybe he is.
I don't know.
Man, we don't have any engineers do we?
Oh, my.
Wait, what just happened to me?
What just even happened?
I got headshot from across the map.
Oh, my God.
Oh, no, I just struck this.
We're about to lose.
Yeah, there's two spies on the point.
Oh, the car.
We lost.
What are you guys going to get like a set of spies?
How many spies are on that damn team?
All right, new new server.
Not GG.
New S-E-V-R-V-V-R-V.
Let's go to...
Hmm, actually, hold on.
I'm going to...
The screen's going to go black for one second.
Because I'm going to change...
Let me change something real quick.
While you do that, I'll be RB for about 10 seconds.
I'm going to see what my guys want.
Well, because for some reason, when I was doing
X-Fly in the game mode, it was lagging my game a lot.
I don't know why.
Sometimes I guess it does that.
I'm going to get a little bit of a bit of a lag.
I'm going to get a little bit of a lag.
Yeah, are you using like the...
What?
Screen area or the other one?
I was doing the game source.
When the game...
That was like lagging my game sort of.
All right, try a screen area.
I just did not change it over.
Explore it.
You're supposed to be like the release.
All right, let's go to...
Go to the top.
To me some things too.
You're going to the top.
Oh no, go to high tower.
High tower zero out of...
This is a good one.
Hopefully stealth gets back soon.
Otherwise he's going to be in trouble.
To delay for him when we were doing the test streaming.
I was using game source and it was working fine.
So it just seems like on again, off again.
Let's hit her miss now.
Very hit her miss now.
All right, that's all I got.
Still, still I got.
That's it.
That's your only...
That's my only delay.
All right.
Stealth.
You better hurry up.
Oh, eight.
It's so jama how things going over here today.
Here we go.
I'm pasting it.
Already got video and a stream.
Just ballin.
Like a YouTuber does.
Ballin.
Straight ballin.
All right, stealth.
Really, that's all I got.
Now, now we're never meant.
All right, 68.
Dot 232.
Dot 177.
Dot 105.
Colin 270.
15.
Sorry, stealth.
You weren't here.
But you missed out.
That's the IP.
That does be a wondering.
All right.
I hear somebody like here.
You're not gonna pick up.
Oh, he's it.
He's no, he's not making it.
There's no way he makes it.
All right, hey, there's no way you make it.
I was gonna say I have some bad news.
Bears.
Dinner is ready with my parents.
I always probably go.
Dinner is.
Sir,
put on like,
throw me out of the sun.
All right, well, yeah,
see you later, dude.
Thanks for coming.
Do you have no problem?
Oh, still, I'm gonna miss you, buddy.
Make sure you signify to this frame.
Is that gonna miss you?
Oh, by screen.
Two.
Thanks for, uh, having me.
And I'll see you guys later.
All right, miss you guys.
Oh, I'm the host of the call.
I'll just meet myself.
Oh, are you really?
Yeah, just mute your, uh,
all right?
Yeah, now, now who should have hosted?
Burbey.
Yeah, I know.
Well, the good thing I missed that,
so I can do it again and miss it again.
I will play until you decide that you want to play a CS go.
Then I will bow out as well.
Yeah, thanks for sticking around it.
Tell my wife, I said hello.
Hello, wife.
What?
On the stream?
Was that a stream comment?
Yeah, I guess.
Why, Stealth, why?
Stealth, how could you be so inconsiderate?
Wow.
Oh, there's a lot of spice.
Now, I just want to flying 100 feet in the air.
That's off to the spryme.
He doesn't mess around.
I'm running away.
I'm running into spawn.
You can't get me a spawn.
Sorry.
Text message.
Do you ever have a problem where like you hit Am or something
to change your loadout and then it opens like the options menu?
It does that sometimes, yeah.
Just curious.
That is an issue and now I'm going to die right here.
That is an issue, so I should get a tissue.
You know what?
I'm going to go straight up.
It's my fault.
No.
Yes.
I'm trying, Piro, but I'm not having a great luck right now.
Oh my god.
What is going on with the avatars?
What the hell is going on?
Why is everybody like a pony?
Wait, what?
Hold down tab for a second here.
Yeah.
Is every single avatar a pony for you?
No.
Oh my god.
I can see mine in yours.
Why?
What?
Yeah, that's all I can see.
Well, that's a...
I have no idea.
Everyone else in the street can see yours though.
I guess that's good.
Man, no one has pushed our cart past the like spawn area here.
I cannot even hit this person.
There we go.
We were getting absolutely dominated.
They're already going up the track.
Where's this pyro?
Oh my god, I'm doing so awful.
Oh my goodness.
No, medic stay alive.
Stay alive.
Medic.
All right, let's get on this cart.
Let's do this.
All right, for some reason no one ever wants to go heavy.
I guess we can get back stabbed all the time.
Does that cart really all the way over there?
Oh my god.
Come on, come at me.
Do you have the cart all the way at that last point?
Are you kidding me?
Holy crap.
Yeah, that was kind of what I was thinking.
How the hell did they get that there?
How the hell did they get there?
Oh, I'm hearing my stream.
Oh, I have to turn this off.
Whoops.
Yeah, that's...
Wow.
Blue team.
Bravo.
My god.
Look at this insanity going on here.
What is...
Wow.
There was a spy idling in a corner and we were sitting there
like pummeling him for about 10 seconds.
I think I'm gonna must have two scouts on the cart.
Get them.
Oh, come on.
That's it.
We lost.
That is game over right there.
I can't.
I can't get them.
Oh, no.
It's not game over.
Oh, what do I do?
What do I do?
Heavy.
Let's push the car people.
You know what I've got?
Get on that, got.
All right, I am as paranoid as you could possibly be right now.
And you know what?
I was literally...
I was turning around to check first by behind me and he got me.
Like, my brain was telling my mouse to do that
and like I got back to that.
That's why I went pyro.
I'm just like spraying everywhere.
I'm just watching you do that.
All right.
Paranoid.
What's up, guys?
You know, I'm just gonna be...
And again, with the spy, even though I'm a pyro,
I've come back to have again.
Oh my God, people are just everywhere.
I love their message.
Oh, they're gonna get it.
They're gonna get it.
All right.
Turn away when you play.
That's right now.
You're playing as a...
Heavy.
Oh, where were we?
Six shot.
Whoever that was.
That got that scout off.
German.
Do you love me?
Now that I can't dance.
That's a song, right?
Yeah?
I would sing it in the shower.
Sure.
Let's do it.
I'm not gonna do the uncrediting tonight.
I'm gonna be doing...
That's gonna be in a live calm, just a straight-up video.
Probably next week.
You...
Get out of here.
You're not dead.
I know you're not dead.
I'm jumping away.
I'm getting it.
Yeah, get away from me.
I need help.
Oh, do I get help?
Or do I spot-check everybody in my team?
Whatever works.
I see you up here, Spy.
You little sniper.
You crazy little sniper.
Yep.
Nice try on your stair step, but it didn't work.
Did it?
No, that was not Spy.
That got...
Oh, God!
Where's the other guy?
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God!
Where is the other guy?
No more heavy.
I'm gonna go...
Heavy.
I'm staying heavy.
Up there all on the-
They're all on the carto-
Uh, this is me, Robo.
Oh, my God.
Is that Pyro?
I just went to a side Pyro on them.
I got at least one, I think.
I gotta eat this so I can run fast.
Oh, they're going.
They're almost there.
They're gonna get it.
So that means I can run away, because I just took this-
There's three people on it?
Oh, they're definitely gonna get it.
Yeah, see how fast I'm running?
You won't get the satisfaction of killing me.
Actually, he kind of did.
He kind of did get the satisfaction of killing me.
Too late.
I am bit-
No, I have to-
Oh, do I go medic?
I-
I'm gonna wreck sniper.
I'm still too paranoid, man.
I'm just like-
I'm spraying inside the spawn area.
That's how paranoid I am.
Now that's paranoid for you.
I know, they all blew up.
You are R-S-5.
Are you not?
Apparently I am dueling.
Damn.
Oh, what-
I-
I don't even know what just happened.
I was like checking around too.
I'm going medic.
It's the best thing to do right now.
Oh, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow.
Spy?
I'm just gonna go kill bot medic.
And I can make sure everyone stays alive.
I'm gonna have my back turn the entire time.
Do it, man.
The entire time.
We have like-
Oh, we have two pirates on the team right now.
We have like three earlier.
People were just so paranoid.
Oh, you get-
Get caught up here.
Oh, god.
And there's another spy.
God, run away.
Help me, somebody help me.
Stay safe.
Stay close to the blue red.
I can't live it and hit him.
Oh, he's gonna kill me.
Oh, my god, I'm a lucky son of a bitch.
I'm-
I gotta run away.
I'm- I am on.
What do you say, honey?
What do you say?
Oh, shit.
Oh, no.
I didn't want to do that.
Oh, god, no.
I just like trade over somebody.
Dude, no one is pushing our cart, including myself.
Oh, I'm gonna love a god.
It's still like right there.
He's still right there.
Right there, it's fun, man.
Actually, to be quite honest with you,
that was the most success I've had all game.
It's with that medic.
And I- and I healed like two people.
Medic.
Alright, I'll get another medic.
Stop.
Ah.
Ah, still a side medic.
Oh, this guy is toast.
Oh, one more guy behind me.
Oh, no, no, no.
Oh, you, huh?
How many spies are on their team?
Just the count.
It's gotta be at least three.
It's gotta be.
If it's not, then I'm wrong.
I need to, you know what?
Take up the crit screen.
Quick fix.
No trades.
I don't take the trades right now.
That was a terrible scar.
So that was supposed to be a Scottish accent,
guys. How terrible was that?
That's a spy.
I am certain of this.
No, I guess I'm wrong.
Oh, barely got me.
And I'm like getting people killed
because I'm checking this.
Did I just heal this by?
No, I didn't.
No way.
Dude, we've got four pyros on our team now.
The people they are listening, they're like,
enough of this nonsense.
We have like getting shot from.
I don't even know where they're coming from.
It's almost like they're coming out of our spawn.
I'm going pyro on easy mode right here.
I've got like the back burner,
so I don't even have to think.
Just like spray.
I'm trying to use the, uh, the quick fix.
You know, I'm going to heal you.
We're just going to run like the dickens.
Uh-oh.
Run away.
Look at all the, what?
Those are all spies.
At least, oh my god, this is the worst thing ever.
Oh my god, chaos.
Run.
Oh my god, dude.
They keep running into like the same heavy.
I'm put, I got a, I'm playing spy.
We are trapped in this spawn area right now.
Where are you coming out from?
Left, right or center?
I keep going out because I'm a medic, so I'm trying to guard the middle.
God, somebody just killed me so I can just get a back stab and feel good about myself.
Look at this, look at this K-O.
You got to be S, I can't even say it.
I'm so upset.
All right, let's make, let's make some statues.
Oh, oh, my, I'm on like your team.
Oh, great.
Now he knows I'm a spy.
Oh, geez.
Oh, my, I'm, I'm, I can't get out of spawn either, man.
I'm just using the enforcer to kill people.
I can't.
As soon as I said there were four pyros, everyone switched back on our team.
Oh, get a little, there's, oh, man, I got blasted right there.
All right, after this, we're going to another server.
Because we need to scramble these teams.
They've got a century gun right next to our cart.
Really?
That's not cool.
Hey, you know what's the note I'll say?
Oh, what do you have?
What you got?
No.
And they're already winning again.
Oh, God, no, no, please, no.
All these ponies.
You know what, when all else fails, you just go.
Pretty sure there's at least two people idling.
Well, at least when all else fails, you go straight up, Demonite.
And if that don't work, I just speaking of the Monite.
Morgan.
And that's what I just went.
All right, like right before you said that.
Oh, my God.
I saw that.
I just charged out of spawn and I flew like 5,000 people.
Come on, Lazz.
Get him.
It's all up to you.
And he did it.
He's a champion.
All right, this is going to be a spire right here.
Get out of town.
I got one of the spites.
Oh, no, no, no, server change.
It's time to change servers.
Let's go to, I want to go two weeks.
A server we can win on.
Well, I'm just kidding.
I want to go to my server.
I want to go to a bold rush.
Sounds good.
Are you ready?
Yes.
So, the what's going on here?
72.9.
Dot 146.
Dot 118.
Call on 27015.
Go.
You almost lost me on the colon, but I think I got it.
Colon 27015.
27015.
What's the password?
That's a pretty easy password.
So, deal with it.
Yeah, I mean, my YouTube password was 1, 2, 3 for a long time.
I'm just kidding.
It told me I had to change it.
Oh, I got dropped due to the server.
What?
We went in there first.
How is that possible?
Okay.
Sorry, those are new.
How is that making sense?
We were on our way in before I.
In the game.
Well, I apologize to those of you that just got into that server, but we have to change.
So, 98.158.
Dot 87.226.
Colon 27040.
All right, now I'm going to wait a second before I give the sound.
Well, if they're probably listening.
Yeah, but it's like a 10 second.
A little.
Yeah, but still.
There's somebody out there with this ridiculous internet speeds.
Yeah, and I can just, I can just come right in.
Pipeline payload.
Yes, strange.
Angel, I think this is a talix playing.
You are correct.
Hey, guys, hey, strange love.
How's it going?
So, this is the server.
Wait, did that?
What? Wait, hold on a second.
Did that already fill up?
We already fold.
I didn't.
Oh, somebody else put it in.
Okay, thank you to whoever put that in.
Thank you.
I appreciate it.
I thought you didn't join.
That's what I thought at first.
Oh, God.
This is like a jellyfish server.
Like the screen is motor like a jellyfish for me right now.
Look at how laggy everybody is.
Look at this.
I feel like it's like.
Oh, my God.
Look at this claymation server.
Look at that.
Let me see.
Well, uh,
oh, look at the pings.
My goodness gracious.
Everyone except for me and you is like,
a hundred plus.
It really looks like a stop motion animation.
I feel now.
I'm like,
I feel like I'm playing at 20 frames per second.
But I'm not.
Oh, I'm sorry, guys.
Look, we got to change again because this is just bad.
All right.
This is not this is not against the people who are here.
This is one of the people who didn't get in.
Yeah, it's right.
It tells you you can look at the stream and see what I see right now.
It is like, it is pretty much like I'm watching a cartoon on drugs.
All right.
Well, yeah, it looks like nobody could even get into this one.
There was only seven on eight.
I apologize.
I sorry.
New server.
Take three.
Yeah, third time's a charm.
Third time.
How one?
Ah, two.
Ah, three crunch.
So why do I get my third time?
I'm probably going to get a 32 person server.
I'm going to hope I can.
But wait, wait till I get that server.
We'll be okay.
I want to server all the cool kids.
Half one.
All right.
Here we go.
66.55.154.
Don't two, three, four.
Call in 27015.
And we paste this in.
And a second once we get in.
I do apologize that we have to do this twice.
And that was the third time.
Hopefully this one is going to be the good one.
They pasted it in already.
You did really?
I told you it was like literally two seconds after you said it.
I saw it pop up in the chat.
You guys are fast.
Lightning fast, even.
You might say.
You can say that.
Oh.
I am going demo night.
Gamer night.
Actually found.
Oh, sorry.
What?
I said demo.
And I was just re-language.
I actually found a salt and ceremonial the other day.
Oh.
I was very happy about that.
Very cool.
So now I can have a legit demo night if I wanted to give up my grenade launcher.
It's a tough call for the for the booties.
Yeah.
booties.
And then we got Stimidae here.
With his wicked sick hat.
So I have to do this right now because somebody keeps sending me a very inappropriate
messenger.
And hopefully that stops that from happening.
I don't think it will, but I at least tried.
Oh.
Okay.
All right.
We got a full servanon.
Good to go.
Let's go.
Come back now.
Just in time.
Everyone is off the real way.
Like everyone.
Oh, so over at the same time.
Oh my god.
You just totally predicted where I was going to shoot.
Shotgun soldier.
Oh my god.
Did you see that?
Yeah.
I've loved him a night.
Yeah, I have only so far given one third.
I'm still waiting on two people.
So eventually I will be giving 100 percent.
But I have to wait for the other two people to get back to me.
Oh.
That hurts.
Oh, dear.
I made quite a mess.
Someone on the team was announcing how many spies they have.
They have four, apparently.
I want a good traitor.
He is.
How ironic is that?
So he's a double spy.
Yeah.
So he's telling us about spies.
So he's spying on the spies for his own spies.
As someone in the comments will undoubtedly say,
spy section.
Yep.
That is absolutely what it is.
Not far from this.
Maybe he's why.
Why?
Hmm, or suspicious.
Oh.
Maybe he's a triple spy.
He said, I served no one.
DTA, don't trust anyone.
Like, I like your attitude.
And that's his fine.
He's his dire.
He's going to get ugly.
And he's going to try and stare stabbing.
I already know this.
I've been around the block a few times.
You know what?
You, I know.
I'm going to stand right here.
You're going to have to go that way.
Oh god.
Oh no.
Oh.
Let's see where.
On the old until I get the gets flubbered pyro going down here.
Oh my god.
Well, you just die of pyro.
What am I doing?
Oh, they're almost there, man.
They're right at the edge with seven minutes and 40 seconds to go.
We can do this.
Oh, come on.
I would have had it.
I was being sarcastic, by the way.
I had no faith.
I don't even know if that's how you spell it,
but that's what I'm doing.
I love how the highest score,
scoring player on our team is four points and was like a four way tie for four.
Me included.
Yeah, yeah, four, four, four, four, four, three.
Boom.
Auto scrambling the teams.
Well, that's one way to do it.
Whoa.
All right.
So this is a goodbye.
Wait.
Oh, you changed your name to new.
Yeah, I did.
Did you guess who I am?
Well, I'm not hard.
Yes, because I can see your icon.
Henderson in corporate.
We sell carpets and we do floor finishing.
Where do you come up with your name?
So you just look at something and say, okay, I'm going to take that.
Kind of.
It's just whatever is in my brain at that particular second is what it is.
Oh, I tried to high five you.
So this is going to be the last round of TF2 and then I'm going to move on to CS.
Go for a little bit.
I got to make a count then.
Oh, then you have it, right?
I don't have CS go.
That's what I was saying.
I'm going to have to bow out when you switch games.
Let's go.
I mean, we've been playing for about an hour or something.
Still, still has it, but he.
Yeah, he's, I mean, if you need to the eat, I mean,
he's eating macaroni and cheese and like dog food, whatever he eats.
Dude, don't you make me hungry, man?
macaroni cheese and dog food.
Come on.
Oh, that's delicacy.
Watch out, Uber.
Right up the door.
Oh my god, that guy just killed every single person in here.
So stealth must be watching the stream.
Why is he responding?
I don't know.
Scrains love just said he's here.
He's in here.
Oh.
Oh my god.
He's eating a lot to nit at the tape at this parents.
Imagine he just has like his laptop out.
I should have done the buff banner.
I really should have.
I gotta get killed at the medic.
Oh, man.
I can't talk about.
Oh, that would have been cool if I had that go off.
Just get the telephone in the telecaribou.
You should be on the winning team now, maybe.
Don't hit my medic, you bastards.
I can't believe they haven't turned around.
How?
I just did two crits and I'm hitting my own teammate.
What the hell is going on?
Dude, I just planted it like six hits into this guy.
Holy crap.
That was ridiculous.
I've never seen that happen before.
Both hammering on the same guy.
Oh, guys.
Are we got a crit screen now?
We got a crit screen now.
Oh, man.
Oh, there's four demo man on demo men.
I think no wonder.
I just like saved that demo man's life.
But not really.
All right, push it.
Push it.
Oh, push it.
No.
This is a really bad idea.
I just ran around to spawn.
Maybe not.
Come on.
Oh, come on.
That is a sad face indeed.
Couldn't have had an explosion kill.
Couldn't have what a shut up.
What it didn't have.
That's a weird idea.
I'm trying my hand.
Oh, you guys are about to win.
You got like three pyros back here.
Just camping our spawn hard core.
Really?
Oh, man.
Never run.
Yeah.
Cool.
Let's do some crazy rocket jumps.
Here we come.
Rocket jump.
I think I got like one kill.
Dude, I've been doing I've been doing jump maps.
See we go.
I did some jump.
I know what I'm doing.
All right.
Somebody in the street said,
Jerma plays, play tribes of Synth.
That's what they said.
I'm not making that up.
Um, I see.
I see.
I see people say that.
But CSGO just had a big,
huge crazy update.
I want to check that out.
Five.
But to answer your questions in the comments,
tribes of Synth is free to play.
So it is.
And it's now totally open.
It's not in beta anymore.
It is out now.
Yeah, it's out.
It's been released.
It is fun.
So that's, uh, I'm going to move on from TF2 now.
Played upon an hour of TF2.
So before I go, I have to do something good.
I have to do something just stupid.
And just TF2.
Here we go.
Let's go, uh, place five.
And I'm going to just,
this is this is the goal here, guys.
The goal is to try
and blend in with the other team.
So it's going to be hard to people are watching the stream.
But this could be interesting.
I want to try doing this at least once.
Why is there a floating scout stuff here?
Oh no, I'm just the high five.
So the, the goal here is to try and blend in.
Let's see how well I do.
Let's see how well I do here.
All right, we're going to stop them.
Come on, get them.
Come on.
Oh my god, they're coming.
The car is upside down.
What the hell is going on with that car?
It is a thing.
Come on, we must get them.
All right.
Oh no, here they come.
They're coming out of the right door now.
Blue team.
That's, no.
I'm going to, oh, you figure me out.
That guy, no, he didn't see me.
Okay, I just got to build my stuff right here.
Just got to build some stuff.
I'm trying to build my, uh,
my teleporter, my century, and it's all good stuff.
Let me just, uh, build that up.
Thank you for the overhealed by the way.
Oh, I'm a fake.
Oh god.
It's got, uh, I got you.
Oh, my god.
Oh, I'm going to get back to my post.
These bastards, they ruined everything.
No, please don't take it.
Oh my god, I got, I got to get back to my century.
We're going to, I got to build my century.
Oh, that is, that's me right there.
Okay, cool.
Uh, sniper.
And there we go.
I'm going to snipe.
All right, let me get back to my sniping post.
All right, here we go.
Just sniping.
Now the enemy team is coming out here.
Watch out guys.
Be careful.
Now, let me snipe with you.
Oh god.
Who's the real one?
We're standing right next to each other.
Oh, you got me.
Shit.
Oh, you ruined my fun.
That's what I get angry and die.
Oh, all right, that's, uh, that's going to be actually,
I'll run the round out.
Why not?
It's disguised as an enemy sniper.
That's the best way to do it.
And then just sit in the corner and be like, oh, I'm sniping.
Oh, I'm going to get the three hits.
Uh, crit with the gun slinger.
Almost got it.
Uh, it's really satisfying.
Oh, damn it.
Oh, he didn't get me.
Uh-huh.
Oh, come on.
Come on.
No.
Okay, good, good, good.
All right, let me get my sniping skills.
I found an ambassador.
I still haven't had a sniper.
I'm going to get a sniper.
I still haven't been fortunate.
Really difficult.
Oh, come on.
I'm just trying to snipe.
All right, if you guys don't sub spam and chat
a most or block in some people.
No, they got it.
They found me out again.
Oh, we get the wrath of the mod coming down.
Uh-huh.
All right, this is my last life.
Then I'm moving on to uh-
counter-
Stephenson.
Great opportunity.
Backstab.
I'm going to tell you how-
yeah, I'm taking the teleporter as a spy.
At level two, I'm a real bad bastard.
I'm a real bastard.
Look at this.
Level two teleporter.
And I'm taking it as a spy.
What a jerk.
I wonder if I can uh-
just kill people up from up here.
Oh, for the love of God.
I just can't get the melee.
Oh.
Well, that's the last one.
That's the worst engineer ever.
How come I can't spray my spray?
That's not cool.
Yeah, I don't have a spray.
I need to- I need a cool one.
I am going to change to saw CS go.
After I swing it this guy over and over again.
Oh, oh.
So always one more life.
Yeah, this is really the last life.
I'm not- this is not a joke.
No more- no jokes.
This is the last one.
Yeah.
I have to backstab at least one person.
And that's not the guy apparently.
And that's not the guy either.
It's going to be not that guy.
It's what's- what's- what's-
Now I can't backstab anybody.
Oh, my no's will pretend.
Oh, let me do that pretender I am.
Come on, get that knife out.
Oh, my God.
Well,
that's the end for me.
Oh, thanks for playing guys.
Tf2.
I'm going to move on to some-
Yep, it's a go-go.
You're full-on.
It's a fun losing every round.
I'm the only comment denominator here,
so I take full responsibility for that.
I've been on every losing team so far.
My bad guys, my bad.
Well, at least now,
at least you got to play on the crazy teams that were getting beat.
Oh, my goodness.
That was-
You were reaching for that one.
That really was.
Actually, I was doing two things at once and my brain was kind of like,
wait, where am I?
Oh, yeah, I'm streaming, I forgot.
So I'll probably play like maybe three, two or three rounds of CSGO.
Just to check out the new update, because I wanted to check it out.
So, screen is going to go black in a second here.
And yeah, thank you for coming.
If you just came for the TF2,
if you're sticking around with the CSGO,
then it's going to happen in like four seconds.
Well, not really, but you get the idea.
Screen is going to go black in second.
Screen is totally not black, bro.
Oh, no, there it goes.
No, it's black.
No, it's not.
No, it's-
Oh, no, that's wrong, because I did screen region.
I forgot.
I pulled up the screen region.
But now it should be all screwed up.
Probably hear the sound now.
Get it into window mode.
Jeez, okay.
Anyway, guys, it's been fun.
Thanks for owning me.
Time and time again.
How I get my kicks.
I'm just kidding.
It was a lot of fun.
And enjoy CSGO.
I will catch you guys later.
Thanks for coming, man.
Always a pleasure.
Let's get the screen region
that.
And, huh.
Okay.
Let's play a couple rounds.
Let's see what they did.
Huge updates.
Let's find out exactly what they did
getting this update.
Have I ever- I've- I've watched South Park.
I used to love South Park back in the day.
It was one of my favorite shows.
That's right.
They did add a server, but I gotta check that out.
If I can even get in here.
Still searching, huh.
Let's try this again.
Find the game.
Oh, look at that.
There we go.
Retreating data.
Yeah, I'm probably only going to play
maybe two or three rounds.
Maybe 10, 20 minutes or so.
I just want to check out the new update in the honest.
Okay, so this is the new map.
No, maybe not.
This is not one of the new maps.
Is it?
I think I've already seen it.
I've already seen it.
No, maybe not.
Maybe it is a different map.
We'll find out, won't we?
Oh, I'm trying to pick up a headshot.
Damn.
So this is one of the new maps, safehouse.
There are already some other one like this, isn't there?
This game is not free to play.
It is in beta right now.
It's in closed beta.
I gotta stay alive next time.
The more screwing around.
And the terror is one.
Will they be punched in pie?
You know what?
I can't, we can't buy.
Why can't we not buy items?
I can't buy items.
I thought that's what it said you could do.
I'm gonna go around this way.
See if I can pull something off here.
No, I don't want to climb up there.
That's a bad idea.
No, I just saw somebody.
There we go.
Oh, I'm dead.
Nope.
Oh, God.
Behind me.
He's behind me.
He's down.
Bomb's down here.
What you got?
It's only one of them left.
No, that's a teammate.
There he is.
Henderson incorporated, but most eliminations.
I forgot my name was Henderson incorporated.
You click any clack.
Now this game will do that.
You'll get a big clickety clack.
I'm waiting for somebody to pop there.
I have any grades.
No, nobody, nobody.
Oh, my God.
I'm getting stuck.
Getting stuck.
This is right here.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
We live a,
you guys hanging out of a window.
What a creep.
I think I was legit like floating out of the window.
I want to do a different gun.
I don't like this gun.
Auto is upstairs right now.
He is, uh, I think he's created in the kitchen, to be honest.
Because he's, uh, he's a wild dog.
Somebody kill somebody.
Who's auto?
Auto is my, uh, my little doxan chihuahua
double-man-pinter breed thing.
He's a real cutie.
He is a real cutie.
I don't play League of Legends.
It's too much for my brain to handle.
I feel the same way about League as I do about Starcraft.
And that is, this already damn it.
Oh, now I got to sit here forever.
I feel the same way about League as I do Starcraft.
The Starcraft is,
it's everyone's just really, really good.
And to be able to play that game, you have to also be really, really good.
Yeah, I probably won't be playing that game anytime soon.
Well, this is, I don't want to just sit here.
I'm going to play a gun game after next round.
Because gun game is more action.
And I can actually pretty good at gun game.
See, this game, well, I'm not that good at, like the general CS go.
I'm not that good at it.
You know, we're going to go play gun game right now.
It's a tomato game.
Find a game.
Arms race.
You don't matter which one, that's going to play it.
It's not gun game.
It sure is.
Gun game.
Oh, I mean, arms race is the technical term for it.
I love this map.
It's so interesting.
You heard it like a, oh, I love the girl is man.
Favorite bands.
But far.
From behind.
Ah.
What's your right here?
Finally, moving on, moving on to the world.
Now where is he?
Oh, there's too many of them.
Damn it.
Yeah, keep in mind I'm playing this in a window, like half the size of my computer screen.
So it can be kind of difficult to play this game.
How many bolts does it take?
No, I don't want to do that.
Ow.
Wait, I got.
Oh, damn.
Yeah, I wish my computer was good enough to play games in full screen and stream them.
But it is, it is almost impossible to do that.
And I'm, I'm getting destroyed.
My god.
Their whole team is like 18 and 14 and.
I'm going this way, I'm going this way.
Get out of town.
Damn it.
Give me that head shot.
God damn.
Yeah, it's not my internet.
It's my computer just probably would not be able to handle it.
And I guess internet too.
To stream at like 1080 or 720, it takes a lot of bandwidth.
Oh.
No, what was I doing?
This, this potentially is the worst time, like the worst game I've ever had in this entire game ever.
Like ever.
It's making me look embarrassed.
No, I don't care.
I'm just playing for fun.
I just want to check out the new stuff.
My favorite guerrillas song is probably Stylo.
I love Stylo.
Where is he?
I don't even know when that guy even was.
Oh.
Ow.
Brrr.
Okay, let's get a string of people together here.
Let's get a string of people together.
Now it's already got it.
Oh.
Oh, 715.
Flip that score around and you got a great score.
All right, this time it's going to be different.
This time it will be different.
You need to pray to the Bruins.
All powerful Bruins, gods.
Please shine upon me your strength.
I see I got this.
My sensitivity might be wrong.
No, it's not.
That's an excuse.
That is just an excuse.
There we go.
Let's keep the ball rolling here.
We got it.
Mercy.
Up top.
Oh boy.
Now get away.
Get away.
Oh, damn.
Wow.
Where did he come from?
Where did that dude come from?
Going for the headshots.
Not getting them.
There we go.
PP90M1.
I think that's what I just had.
This is the shoot guns.
Oh, now I can't go that way.
I'm going to wrap around this way.
Oh, how does he not die?
Look at his health.
What did I even hit him with?
Like a sock?
I don't understand.
That guy had like 80% help.
And I hit him with like a wet sock apparently.
Geez, my god.
That's insta-death every single time.
No, that guy was invincible.
How was that guy just invincible?
Somebody explained that to me.
And that's not you.
There we go.
Get out of town.
No longer die.
Invincible.
Unpredictable.
Somebody up top.
See buddy, where they spawn?
What the hell are you guys?
I just puke in my mouth.
Pue, pu, pu.
No.
How come I'm going to go across the map?
They just spawned over here.
Get my face in your face.
Get out of here.
Oh, come on.
This guy's 29 right now.
My god.
What?
Man.
I'm gonna have to get out of here.
That's too many of them.
I at least want to be number one on the team.
Ow.
Stop puking.
That took a while.
Ow.
I at least want to go positive.
That's all I care about.
It's going positive.
Oh god, I'm being freaking out right now.
This guy's gonna get a knife level in two seconds.
To me, I scoped.
Ah.
Oh, it hurts to die in this game.
Where is everybody?
That did not kill that guy.
Oh, my god.
Spawning right next to me.
Spawns are wacky in this game.
People just appear next to you.
What's that?
Light machine guns.
Now, come on.
No, somebody lost.