Friends make sure we get you in here.
We like the game.
The rest of you guys should be in here.
I'm at starting.
We started.
It's already started.
Alright, so we got, we got about seven people.
Everything I can still join.
Yeah, people, you can still join.
So if you go to GTA free mode and you find our game, that's where we all are.
Alright, what am I going to do?
First of all, get out of that cock.
Give me that cock.
Alright, nice, nice.
Oh, jeep!
I didn't know there was going to be that like, oh my god.
Alright, everyone is like killing each other.
I was expecting like a-
Oh my god!
K-offs!
Alright, get- somebody get the car with me.
Alliance.
Alright, I absolutely do not want to be enough.
Oh, good Bob, get in.
Oh my god, it's total chaos.
Alright, everybody in, everybody in.
Alright, let's go.
Oh my gosh.
I don't even know who this guy shoot that, but-
Oh, this French guy left.
Alright, so what is it?
Everybody versus MLC stuff?
Does that just happen right now?
Oh my god.
Hey, you guys are my assassins.
You got to take out MLC stuff.
Where do you do it?
You just glitched out of the cock.
Oh my god, everyone's like glitches.
Alright, hissing jam.
We're gonna do a wrap around here.
Oh no.
Alright, oh, cops, cops.
Take about.
Alright, where is everybody?
Oh, this car's stalled.
He's not stalled, it just doesn't have tires.
All right, let's do something.
All right, you guys want to actually do something?
We should actually do something.
All right, let's do something.
A shibby wants to chat.
He's something me one of those two.
Uh oh.
We're streaming.
You can't all tap.
We can't all tap.
Oh no.
We can enter his group chat.
And then tell him we're streaming.
Hold on, let me do that.
Yeah, you just do that.
Tell him we're streaming.
Hello, shibby.
It's me and Jerma be streaming.
All right, who's behind me right now?
Who's in this car?
You guys are both.
All right, come here.
Let me get in this car.
Let me get in this baby.
I love this no door.
Let me just get in like a like it's a milk truck.
Who did he?
I love how burger boys just did an ambulance.
Or what is that?
An ambulance or a fire truck?
I don't really remember.
All right, let's take, let's go get a helicopter.
Let's go grab a helicopter.
Oh my god.
What did you do?
I'm just gonna sit here.
I don't have to go anywhere.
I could just go, oh my god.
Oh no, he's shooting at me.
Oh, that shit kills you.
No, I'm like sitting on top of a roof with my car.
Oh, that's not happening to me.
Officer, I can't believe what's happening here.
I'll be a good guy.
Hey, officer, can we have for a second?
Can I like look at your gun?
Can I just, can I...
I just saw you with my...
Oh, you're gonna bring a gun to a point.
Oh, come on.
You're gonna bring a gun.
All right, burger boy, where are you?
I want to get in your car.
Who's the pink?
Who's the pink blip?
Oh, let's just do it, all right.
He's being chased by police.
Let me get in your...
In your whip.
No!
You wanna shoot out?
That's what you got.
I'm taking your car, too.
I'm taking this thing to a dealer and I'm selling it.
Oh god, there he is.
Oh god, go, go, go, go, go, go.
All right.
I want everybody to...
MLC's to say it, it's to say it.
So everybody come to me on the map.
Where are you destroyed right now?
Everybody come to me on the map.
My car doesn't have any doors on it.
Look at my car.
Nobody killed each other.
Everybody come to, to, to win me an MLC stealth out right now.
The brown blip and the, what color am I?
I'm orange, I think?
This cop wants me dead.
I'm gonna let him kill me.
So if you guys come to the blip, I want to, I want to try something.
Let's see if we can make something weird happen right now.
Will you just kill me already?
Is that cop shooting at me?
Oh he is.
What?
Did he just kill me?
Did you just back into me or did that cop shoot me in the face?
He shot you in the face.
All right, you know what?
It's my list.
Screw this.
Oh no, it's my statue.
What's it look like?
I like a bow.
What the?
All right, follow me.
We're gonna, we're gonna, we're gonna get a helicopter.
Punch me in the face?
I did, but I was accidental.
I didn't meet him.
All right, let's go, we're gonna get a helicopter.
Hold on.
We can all these like people is fun.
Look at this wall going on right here.
Where is Bergeboy in all this?
Let's go get a helicopter.
Oh my.
These cops are doing a horrible job at regulating the laws.
Oh god, we got a spawn.
We got a spawner.
Don't kill us.
Yep.
Oh yeah, all right, he's not gonna kill us.
All right, come with us.
I get so afraid whenever I see a person in front of us.
Please don't shoot us.
Put your parachute on, everyone.
Yeah, make sure you get your parachute on.
I love all this.
There is something going on, like a hundred feet away from us.
People are just slaughtering each other.
And I feel like it has something to do with Bergeboy.
We need a car.
Wait, we're all just running with people.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, hey, got, oh, get in this thing.
It's only has two seats, I think.
That's all right though.
Oh my gosh, what's happening?
What's happening?
Crazy lady.
This guy's out of his mind.
I'm out of here.
That guy's out of his mind.
That guy hissing is like just killing people left and right.
I'm running away.
Oh, an hour's in.
Or not seen.
I just started like putting out everybody that was in a driver's seat
in a car that was next to us.
I'm going to get a helicopter.
This is, oh my god, this thing handles like-
Where are you driving?
I...
I have it on my GPS.
I'm really drunk.
I just bought my GPS.
From Walgreens.
I have coughs on me?
No, I don't.
I guess I do.
All right.
Look at this.
Look at these people just killing each other.
I'm going to get a helicopter and then it's going to be game over.
Get them going way too fast.
This always ends very badly.
Anytime I go this fast, it's never ends well.
Ever.
You never like finding like a nice safe jump to go off of.
Oh, here we go.
Add a control.
Here we add a control.
Why don't I do that?
There was no reason to do that.
I'm okay.
The coughs are still behind me.
Did I feel like I was just on a bike?
All right.
I'm going to add this guy so we can get him.
Jacob Watson.
Absolutely.
Come on in, man.
Come on in the game.
Oh, my god.
No.
Get away from me.
Oh.
Oh, Jacob's in, is he?
I believe.
Wait, what is singing right now?
What is singing?
Wait, what is that?
How come the people talking?
Oh, my gosh.
All right, let's go.
Go.
Oh, but I'll throw a bug.
I'll throw a bug.
Get in.
Quick.
All right.
We're going to get a helicopter.
Is it off this cliff right here?
Oh, you.
Okay.
All right.
Go.
I'll be the navigator.
Go straight.
Don't straight until you can't go straight anymore.
Burger boy, I love how you were in a ambulance.
Just like driving a hundred miles per hour.
One of our tires is blown and it's going to end very poorly.
All right, don't like driving into a cliff.
Oh, there we go.
Why did you get out?
It's so far away.
All right, so still.
We already had the, at the count of three.
I know where we're going.
We're going to, well, you know what we're going.
You take this like the, what just happened?
I love how I'm in the back.
I'm your chauffeur.
All right, just, I'm getting out.
I'm getting out.
I don't trust you.
No, no, get in.
I'm sorry, you just going to drive off the edge.
I don't know.
All right, okay.
Go.
Do you proceed to highlight the roof?
I don't even have like my headphones plugged in.
You guys are probably like, oh, what?
What?
Oh, my god.
It's hissing, Jim.
Get him.
What an intense shootout this is.
Oh, I got fire on when I was a kid.
There's rats from the Gary Shiwka, Jellars and hoods.
So, it's反y.
You guys, scared of me.
I probably like vaccines.
It's all heroes.
The sustenance shootout is safe.
A lot of hard-hit abuse events took so long to accomplish
the issue without assault.
If the judge is cruel,
their brain and their soldiers'呃,
grenades are coming on.
Oh, I'd really like to have the game because they don't kill
you.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
about it every night and day
I swear my way is in front of my way
I buried back in the soul
I see you running through the open door
Oh God, did I crash?
Oh no I crashed!
No I didn't, no I didn't, I'm good I'm here
I thought I crashed, but I'm good
Oh I gotta get my headphones out
Alright, we're good to go
We're good to go
So everyone's in the airport
Now it's pretty much just a race to who gets the helicopters
I'm sorry, I'm sorry
Nope
Dodge, jump and dodge
Oh give me this P90
Oh man, it is a bad sad day for anybody
Cup and Closet to be
Alright, I'm safe
I need to get, you know what? I gotta get a car
I gotta get a cup
Hey, how you doing?
Please don't kill me, okay, he ran by me good
Hey, this guy's idea of fun is getting inside the helicopter
and shooting all the other helicopters so nobody else can get in
Oh he's a piece of crap
Alright, Operation Takeout the guy in the helicopter
Operation Takeout helicopter flyer
Find rocket launcher and dispose of
I got in the helicopter, I was gonna
Alright, I'm gonna get over there, I'm on my way
I'm in route
Break that window
Oh this brings back memories and I smashed my face on that guy
He's not even moving, what is that guy doing?
Wait, where am I going?
The helicopter's right there, they're right there, okay
It's a good tactic man, that's alright
Alright, who thinks I'm gonna make it underneath this plane?
I do
Give me a helicopter
Please don't die, I'm so addicted to oh my god
Oh my god, oh my god
Oh my god
I need to crouch, how do I crouch?
Oh my god, what a psycho
What a psycho
What are you doing?
My helicopter, what is happening to you?
Why can't it stay flying?
Are you having a helicopter or are you driving?
Hey dude, stop crouching run
All these helicopters are destroyed
Oh dear god, this is bad
This is so bad, I'm gonna die the second I get into this
Oh, run away
I'm not even gonna go in that dude, I'm gonna die
The second I get into this
Oh my god
It's my chance, it's my chance, get in
Get in, get in, go, go you slug
Oh yeah, it's time for a helicopter wars
Oh my god, no, no, no
Get up, oh that was, I just really had a hot attack
The helicopter sucks, it being a helicopter
I'm alright
Yeah, what's going on, I feel like I'm driving a, alright let me name it down to the ground
Any unsuspecting people I can smash into?
Alright, this cop's down there, forage, unleash the fury
Not killing anybody, you know what, I'm going kamikaze
Oh my god, whoever this pink dot is
Did you pick the bad day to be a pink dot?
You picked a bad day to be a pink, oh I'm gonna throw up dude, really
I'm really kinda puke
Did like the controls change or is this lag
Oh wow
How did I work flying?
Well, that's how we get out of a helicopter and walk off the front and
Hey, come pick me up
Where I, oh my god, I think Papa got a brand new bag here
No!
I'm such a bad shot
I was like landing, oh you were trying to pick me up
Oh I'm sorry, I thought you were like you shooting missiles at me, I was scared
Because you shot a rocket at me
I'm conserving the rest of this stuff
Let's get out of here, we're like being shot at to death
I'm gonna be so angry
I got my gun and I'm just spawning and pulling out pistols and just shooting each other
This is so like un-fucking-hide
I'm gonna kill this guy
Get him, get him, oh I could have sworn
Do I blame Tom Brady or anybody for a Westwalker?
No, I mean the preachers didn't really have that
It was a pretty much string of luck that they got into the playoffs to begin with
So, good to see him get that far, but yeah go Celtics
That's all I got to say
Alright, where's Berger Boy? Berger Boy is the number one target for me right now
I think he is, no, you're brown, you're brown
He's green
They're orange
Alright, so stream Berger Boy is target number one
Look at how mad he is
I want the whole street
We can make him rage quit
You guys suck
For some reason I want to save Kordo Bomb
Get in, get in Berger Boy
We're making it out of here alive
Get in Kordo Bomb
Get in Berger Boy, I don't want to escape
I actually, you know Berger Boy
Oh no, oh no, oh I got the P&I D-Man
How was he, I just unloaded
70 bullets into that guy
What a champion
So are we still having a war against Berger Boy?
I'm trying to get an helicopter
I'll save you, I mean you guys
Oh, excuse my...
Oh my god
Stay with it
What was that?
What on earth was that?
That was ridiculous, was that a rocket?
Holy crap
Oh
No, I want to live
I want to live, get me all like the
Get me all like the Italian Scooter
Sick driving his Berger Boy
Oh here we go, get me on this bike
Berger Boy, you want to get in some helicopters?
Go on, Bob
Oh no, this dream is counting my deaths
I'm up to 11
Where'd you go?
Where are you?
Try it Berger Boy
Hey, get on this bike
I'm, that's a place I don't want to be at
Let me get in with you Berger
Hey wait, I want to drive like the fun too
I'm just going to drive like the fun
There's another helicopter
You can't, you can't get in
I'm trying to hit my head on the blades
Okay, let me just get in this helicopter
Like hit my face on the blades
Just go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, without me
We got, we got a ball
Oh my god
I'm getting out of this
What the fuck
Berger Boy, it's gonna blow up
That's gonna blow up
What are you doing still driving?
He jumped out
RPG, watch out
That was so perfect
Oh my god, thank god
This is being recorded
Because if I didn't get that on tape
I would have been so bad at myself
I wonder how destroyed he's just got
He's like trying so hard to stay alive
He just dies
You can see like the intensity in his like jump out of
Pull on Berger Boy
Oh my face
Hey, let me get him that car with you Berger Boy
Hey Jacob, will we get on the back of that scooter?
Oh you bastard
I was trying to get on the back
Everybody that got to see that
That was one of the funniest things I've seen
Alright, let's go
Oh wait, alright, get in, get in
Get in the car
Get in the car quick
Alright, who's all the cops on you?
Okay
Let's go back to the airfield
Oh man
That guy just got rolled by a cop
Where was the sandwich that did
Oh
Let's move
Alright, I'm going to get in the car
I'm going to get in the car
Oh, let's move
Alright, I'm getting you, let's get in this helicopter
Oh, look at that perfect pull up
I know, I've got a feeling this guy might be my turn to a traitor
I don't know, I'm scared
Oh my god, did you just run into the helicopter?
Alright, get it, get, oh you flipped it
You flipped it
Let me like flip it back, can I get back in?
I'm going the other way
Go away, go away
He's cops are on it
Get, no, I'm going to die from the police
Ah
Damn it
Damn it, damn it, damn it
I'll be coppers
I was trying to, can you like get it and flip it over that week?
So funny
Alright, I'm coming
I want to get in the helicopter and I want to just peacefully
Just fly down
And watch some TV, read a book when I'm parachuting down
That's all I want, that's all I care about
I just want to parachute out of the helicopter
That's all I want to do
Let me aim out this window, get out of town
Oh my god, that guy's a shotgun
You pull the front of the guy with the shotgun
Oh, that's more
Okay, I'll just
Pure okay, alright get us to the airfield quick
We got bogies on us
What's going on?
He's pulling me out of the car
He is pulling me out of the car right now
Oh
Appreciate it, alright get it, hurry up, hurry up, hurry up
Oh my god, they're unloading on us
Jeez
I love how this is just a race
It's all this is just who can get the helicopter
What is that cop doing?
Freak
He's a bad guy
Oh man, look at this chaos
We got a fight going on over here boys
You got an RPG doesn't he?
Yeah
Alright, I'm getting out of there now
Oh wait, burger boy you're dead?
I'm like sitting in the car with you, who gives you?
Alright, we
We're at the airfield waiting for a spawn
Come on, come on, spawn a copter
They're on the air, aren't they?
Oh man
I never really liked shooting
Nobody just wants to run cars into each other
Where's these helicopters?
I'm taking cover behind, I know someone's gonna come and just smash into us
Oh yeah, take the cover
I'm stuck on the door right now
Oh man, oh man, oh man, oh man
Oh no, no, no
Alright, at least I, that would have died from that explosion
If I didn't die from that explosion
I would have died from that explosion
Alright, at least I, that would have died from that explosion
If I didn't die from that explosion
I would have died from the
You know what, I'm going this way
Oh, there's police helicopters
I got a plan, you know, I have a plan
And it's gonna work
Oh, it is absolutely gonna work
Maybe it won't, probably not
Run, run, run, run, run, run, I'll take the cop, huh?
I'll take the cop, huh
For those of you asking in the stream, this is episodes from Liberty City
It's the expansion of GTA IV
We're playing the Ballad of Gay Tony
And if you want to join, did you just see that helicopter crash?
That was, who is in this helicopter?
Is it a real question?
So if you want to join my name on here
is Jerma with 4 A's
And just join the game I'm in
Once you've done a final question
You should be able to
I'll see PD
Oh my goodness
That is a missile coming at us
I'm getting out
Of course I have three stars, fantastic
Alright, let's set up shop here
I'm gonna add Zeus
Where are you Zeus?
Oh, not the back
Oh my god
I haven't...
I'm in the middle of like inviting somebody to the game
And I just hear a crash and you're next to me
And it bites a game
Alright
Okay
What am I doing?
I'm just like creeping
Now I'm waiting for a helicopter
I'm waiting for a helicopter
God, there's no way I'm gonna get it
Oh my god
Alright, I'm getting in
Look at all these people
Everywhere, I'm gonna do Plan B
Look at the mini map
Look at how many police are here
Oh, I just barely...
I just barely almost got in there
Alright, new plan, I'm doing Plan B
I am absolutely...
Well, plan B
Plan B
Is to go get the helicopter
That looks...oh, here comes the SWAT team
Good thing they're not coming after me
How tall
Somebody's already doing Plan B
What did he say it was?
To go base jump
And go float over here
Who is this?
Is nobody even in here?
I'm taking this
Give me that, give it to me
Get out of there
Oh man, that was bad, I'm sorry Mr. Amulet's driver
You just try to help people
I'm such a bad person, I'm sorry
Wooo
Alright, turn that off
Let's get an annoying
Alright, let's see
I need to go right here
Why am I flipped over?
I just ran to you
You're on fire! Oh my god, you're on fire
You're on fire, you're on fire
No! Get away from that cop
Give me this one
No!
Give me this, give me this, give me this, don't drive away
Did I get him?
No, I didn't
Come here
Let's see his lagging
I got him away
Alright, let's see if the plan goes
Let's see if the plan goes
Oh, alright, come here
I wasn't gonna run into it, I promise
Right, I'm in the back seat
Alright, driving Miss Daisy, driving Miss Stealth
Alright, hopefully this building is tall enough
So we can like base jump off of it
And fly into the action
That's a right hand
Oh, please
Please exit the vehicle and watch your hands and feet
Thank you for riding in German
The worst car driver in the world
Thank you so much
No, don't shoot me
Oh, you're gonna blow it up, I see
No, I'm shooting all the times
Who would have dealt like this will be on YouTube
It will
The whole thing will be on YouTube
Probably tomorrow
Alright, we're gonna get a new car
We need a new car
Oh, somebody's already doing the parachute
Where are the cars?
I found a motorcycle
Oh, geez
Is this the guy?
Why is he, oh, get this guy
Shoot him, shoot this guy
Shoot him
Kill him
Kill him, kill him
Alright, I got a cop
Where am I going?
Alright, I'm right there, I'm right here
Oh, he's the guy that was shooting us
Let's back into him
Oh, I will run you over as many times as I have to
Oh, there's many times as I have to
Oh, geez
Alright, let's get that out of here
I'm going to do that base job
It's gonna happen
Try the corner
Here we go
Oh, this is a really small building
Is there a taxi I can call?
Actually, that's not that small
I don't think we have taxes on multi-point
Oh, dude
Hurry, hurry, hurry
Alright, so how high up am I?
Actually, it is pretty damn high
Alright, where's the action going on?
Open here
So I got to jump off this side
And let's go
Open, open
Alright, let's see if I can like
float into the madness
That guy's a helicopter
Floating on the helicopter, boy
That will be pretty easy
Ah, look at how relaxing this is
Just floating around
Relaxing with my friends
Oh, hey, stealth
I made it
That was fun
Let's go do that again
Except, let's try it
I want to get on this
I want to get on the bike
I'm trying to
I can't just float
What?
He's right next to me
Oh, my god
He was still in the riding position
He jumped up and he was like
Oh, nothing's going on here
I'm just like still riding the bike
What the hell is that
Oh, I love how many glitches are in this game
Oh, jeez
Oh, my god, I can't control it
Oh, it wants to play baseball
We got enough people to play baseball
We got like, yeah, there's enough people in here
Alright, I'm going to be the pitcher
I'll be the batter
Let's play grenade baseball
Do we have any grenades?
I'm the batter
Alright, ready?
So I'm going to throw the ball
Alright, he did it
Oh, look at the wall
It went so far, looking so far
Around first pass, go to second
Oh, no, I got to throw about
Oh, I didn't get him
Oh, no, the ball got thrown in
Oh, he's still safe
Here you are, you got a triple
You got a triple
Alright, go to the good man on third
Oh, okay, go wait, no, no, no, no
I need to leave the car
Oh, but it's a ghost man
Yeah, then you have to get in the car
And drive to home plate
So you get over there
So you get over
Oh, someone in the stream just right
The crowd goes wild
Alright, so here we go, ready?
Yeah, I pitched it
Alright, now go run to first place
Oh, missed
Oh, god, there's another guy here
We're playing baseball, dude
Oh, it's Zeus
Oh, yeah, we'll play in baseball
Do you want to play baseball?
My running got home, I got a single
Zeus, you're up
Alright, baseball is over
I win because you didn't get home
What's my, what do I win?
I just shot you in the toe
Alright, run home
Do you have a real home?
What, what, what, I like, he's got a bad news bears joke
Alright, hey
Oh, it's getting the tanker
Please tell me those explode
Please tell me those, please tell me
No, no, no, don't shoot it, don't shoot it
Is it connected?
No, it's not connected
I don't think we can tonight, so this is an GTA sananjury
They definitely explode, though, for sure
Oh, let's see if I can connect them
No, you can't connect them
This is going to be a massive, you're going to die
You're going to die in like two seconds
The fighters are gone
Oh my god, look at
Look at this burger boy to save the day
He did, wow, what a prof, let me get in
He just flipped
Alright, burger boy, go as high as you can
Dude, he just flipped that car
That's like a five million pound car
He just flipped it over
I still have my parachute, right? I hope so
I love how you just came out of nowhere burger boy, that was like amazing
I can't believe that thing flipped my tanker
That's why I left so hot
Oh, burger boy, you're going to waste all your ramble
Alright, ready? Here we go
I am going to jump out of the, I'm going to parachute
I'm going to parachute and see how long I can parachute for
So keep going up
Shoot, oh shoot all the pre-fall down there
Wow, we are up really high
I think this is as high as we can go
Thanks burger boy, woohoo
Oh yeah
Thanks burger boy, I'm going to watch and see where burger boy goes
So I'll tell you a story while I'm parachute
It's like story time
So one time, let's see how long it takes before I can finish this story
One time I was in Halloween
I was having a good time as an inch turtles
And the story is really going nowhere
I just want to try and talk and see how long it takes for me to land
Let's see
Oh, more talking
I love on this beat
I feel the same way
Where we were just talking, in a different language
Let's see
Woo
Who is even talking
I just heard a language I am not familiar with
Wow
Who thinks I've placed your bets?
Am I going to die right now?
Am I going to die right now when I land?
We'll find out
It can't be somebody who is now chasing me
And I have a feeling they are going to take me out
Oh, it's burger boy
He's like patrolling the sky
He's like keeping his sight
He's patrolling the airwaves
There's a helicopter pat right here
Why did I not come here to begin with?
Is anybody like a secret helicopter pat?
Does anybody know about this?
There's no helicopter here
Hey, look at that
Two minutes
That took two minutes, oh my god, what a long time
Epic landing
Let's just jump over here
And okay
I thought I was going to die
Was it scary?
You're at the airport
I know, I'm fine
I'm fine
I'm flying the big one
I feel like the big one has a little more control
Who's that?
Is that burger boy?
It is
Hold on, don't take off yet
I'll never get in the mood
I just hit him with the blades
I'm sorry burger boy
I'm sorry
I'm so sorry
I had to
I don't think he died
He's still alive
I said he killed him
Oh, I killed him
I'm going
Wait, Zeus
Dude, can you imagine if you landed from that high up?
If you landed like flat on your stomach
Dude, you were inside, but just explode
Oh, god, that would be so horrible
You would not want to be at that crime scene, cleaning that up
What?
What the hell was that?
That guy just
Okay, I'll thank the car, fine
Oh, that guy's got an automatic gun, goodbye
Turn this way
All right, I'm going to play in cinematic mode for the remainder of the game
Look at this, oh, it's a trailer
I wonder how long I can survive
Oh, my god
Hope everyone in the stream just saw that
He can't, I like to hate you
Dude, on my screen
You just, how am I still?
How am I still?
Oh, I can't play this game for more than an hour, man
And my head starts to hurt from laughing at like the nonsense
Michael Bay present
What?
What is that?
What is this?
What is going on?
Why am I like a teddy bear like hippopotamus?
Why?
Why are we like a parade float?
Get in, get in, get in, get in, get in
Get in here
We gotta get another person in this car
Zeus is right above us
Zeus, get in this car
Take the other seat in here
Somebody please get in there
So we're gonna have like a siding can for a parade float
Dude, who's trying to land right now?
All right, let's just try
Let's just try
Look at what I'm trying
All right, before I get into uncontrollable after
When I turn, watch the heads go back into the car stall
All right
We don't have any of those
Paulie the hippopotamus
Let's play hungry hungry hungry
Let's play hungry hungry hippos, ready?
Just hit control
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait
So I'm gonna stay right here, you stay at opposite me
And then just keep hitting control over and over again
Hungry hungry hippos, ready?
They're hungry hungry hippos
Oh fuck
Hey Zeus is right here
Oh Zeus is a normal human
Why is he normal?
You must have died
Oh well, all right, get in this new car, get in this like, camera
Oh my god, just pulled up
Oh, how does that happen?
Are you guys in?
Look at our heads
All right, watch the heads when I turn
This is the funniest damn thing ever
I gotta get some speed
I gotta get some speed, old dog
Did it watch the heads
Here we go, ready?
All right, come on, look get out of this mode, I don't want this mode
I want like the head mode
I don't want to go too fast
Oh, the spirit
Look at her
Oh
How can I keep switching out?
I want to see like the heads tilt
This is the dumbest thing ever
How did this happen
I don't know, but it must be an advent in here
Look at the heads, like
We're looking like a Barney
I feel like, all right, look at what this looks like right now
This looks like America's like most wanted video tapes
And it's like what kind of criminals are we
You know what I mean?
Look at the criminals, driving away
And they're crazy costumes
Like they're trying to hide their identities
What way, what wouldn't you press the automatic?
It's a V until you get there
All right, here's the real kicker
Oh god, I'm out of control
All right, this is gonna be, I'm gonna laugh uncontrollably at this
All right, Zeus get in
America's most wanted, like the hungry, the hungry, hungry hippo
They robbed a liquor store
I'm gonna have like a couple of like view of us
Oh no, what was that?
Did he just kill us all?
Yeah, oh no, I don't have my hungry, hungry, hungry hippo head
Oh no
That was awesome
Oh my goodness gracious
Give us back hungry, hungry hippos
This is so funny
All right, so this
Oh, you should not shoot at the tires
That's our only vehicle
Oh, I think that's a good note to end on, to be honest
That seriously, that was...
It's not a pretzel for how that happened
There was probably an admin in here or something
I have no idea, but that was absolutely hysterical
Hippo Burgers
All right, let me get on that bike
All right, wait, wait, wait
Here's how we're gonna end it
There's how we're gonna end it guys, ready?
Everybody, everybody get into where we're standing right now
We're gonna have a giant boxing match
And the last man standing wins
So don't not yet, no, take the knife, put the knife away
Put the knife away
So everyone get to where we're standing and no knives
Only boxing
So if we all, if we, ready?
This is how it's gonna end, make sure we get everybody here
So this is how we're gonna end it
Wait, not yet, not yet
Burgers, watch me in the face
All right, wait, Burgermy stop it, Burgermy
I don't think he's even like watching this stream
All right, ready?
So three, two, one, boxing fight, go!
No
Burgermy, you just disappeared
I'm not over here punching people
Oh, I'm going down, I'm going down
No, I wanna run, I wanna get on top of the car
Like jumping punch
I'm gonna jump in the car
I'm gonna jump in the car, like jumping punch
People are like running away
Oh, he's gonna say hello on health
I love how nobody's even grunting or talking
So it's just like silence, ready?
Like
I'm just like, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude
Dude, gang up on Burger Boy, don't let him win
Don't let Burger Boy win
Gang up
Burger Boy's dead
Oh, I'm dead
Oh, did MLC stealth just win?
No, did this guy win
Oh, and you all win a
Hissing gem 2788
Congratulations, you won the punching round
And you know the win?
A knife to the face
Oh, now they're bringing out guns
Oh, my god
Oh, man
That was awesome
Oh
That was amazing
So if you missed it, if you missed some of the, we've been playing for about just about an hour now
Oh, if you missed, if you just got here or something, this is all gonna be on YouTube tomorrow
So
There were some hysterical things that happened in this
Like if you just joined us, you're gonna want to watch, you're gonna want to watch it tomorrow
Okay
Alright, it's time for some QWOP
That was an else driver
So what was my final death count?
Oh, god
Wait, does it say?
No, they've been counting in the stream
Alright, thanks a lot for playing, guys, if you played, I'll probably do this again
This was actually pretty damn fun, so thanks for coming, if you joined into the game and at the session
So now we're gonna play some QWOP
And yeah, thanks so much, guys
Oh
That was a shot in the face
Alright, let me pull up
How do I get out of here, leave game
Alright, it's gonna be a black screen until I get co-op loaded
QWOP, co-op, co-op, co-op, co-op
Hey, yo, yo
I love Liberty City
Co-op is a, it's like, it's a flash game
It's a flash game
Where you have to use QW and then OP to run and it is incredibly difficult
So screens, actually screens probably not gonna go black, it's probably gonna be just my background
Yep, just my desktop background
Alright, let me
Pull up some co-op
Let me make sure the stream thing is there
Oh man, that was funny
That was so damn funny
QWOP, co-op, co-op, co-op
Co-op
Ding-ding-ding-ding-ding-ding-ding-ding-ding-ding
I'm gonna make it so it scenario the co-op screen, because that's more fun that way black screen
Scree-gene-gene-gene-gene-gene-gene-gene-gene-gene-gene-gene-gene-gene-gene-gene-gene-gene-gene-gene-gene-gene-gene-gene-gene-gene-gene-gene-gene-gene-gene-gene-gene-gene-gene-gene-gene-gene-gene-gene-gene-gene-gene-gene-gene-gene-gene-gene-gene-gene-gene-gene-gene-gene-gene-gene-gene-gene-gene-gene-gene-gene-gene-gene-gene-gene-gene-gene-gene-gene-gene-gene-gene-gene-g
gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg gg g g g g g g g g g g g g g g g g g g g g g g g g g g g g g g g g g
gg g g g g g g g g g g g g g
If you want to check out my YouTube channel tomorrow it'll be there the whole thing go go go
I'm actually starting to kind of understand how this works. Oh
My god, how did I still wow okay? I'm good and
Diablo I'm gonna be this is for those of you guys that are still here
Diablo 3 I'm gonna be doing a lot of live streaming of that game
Lot of Diablo 3 streams are gonna happen so be on the lookout for those
All right, I gotta get the 30 come on 30 meters
Use your slug powers from the slug god of slugington
You know what I want I want to go to
Like a track in real life and see like just hopefully I'd see one guy just doing this
Hey, what are you doing man? I've jumped training for the fireworks like oh good. I probably get there
Keep trying man like just like slugging like
Go go go go go 30 meters. I'm gonna make it. I'm gonna make it oh
Speaking of grandpa then grandpa season one premiered tonight. I'm gonna make it sweet about it
But it's all machinem respawn go check it out. It's all machinem respawn right now season two episode one the montage
Go check it out. I got a 10 out of 10. Oh
30 meters. I did it. I did my goal now. I can well now. I'm gonna try and actually run
All right, come on put the blip what about no don't go backwards. Hey
So yeah, that's gonna be it guys. Thanks for coming. Thanks for sticking around for watching DTA
That was awesome if you and again if you just came and you were like oh no, it just ended
It's gonna be there tomorrow on my YouTube channel
So yeah, I will catch you guys all soon one last try
Come on
Last try come on. I'm gonna I'm gonna actually make it. No come on. No stay with it. Stay one more one more
No one more after that
I got I got in a groove last time. I don't know how I got in that groove. I'm like tiptoeing now. There we go
I
Had it I had it one more
You got to pull you know it's the the left leg has to come down
Oh, that's it. I can't do it
But yeah, thanks everybody so much for coming. Thank you so so so so so much and I will catch you guys
Next time I'm actually stay tuned tonight to my channel because there's gonna be a
It's gonna be Minecraft a new Minecraft video going up tonight because I got a lot of requests for more that's a
Wush game theme the theme what am I talking about?
Wush why can't I not say this I'm like having like a like a seizure a
Wush theme park those that's gonna go up tonight, so
Thank you so much for watching guys. I'll see you guys all next time and of course take care everybody
See you
You