720 p4 the win
Starting in 15 minutes exactly
And let's do it
All right ladies and germs
We'll go offline now
And let us go and do a server
It's trying to see how many people are in my server right now
My server is currently full
But um
It's okay
We can fill up an empty one just because that's what I typically do anyways
So let's fill up an empty server just because I feel like
A lot of you guys would rather be able to see where we're playing and you guys in the stream would like to play so here is the IP
If you can see it on the screen I'm also gonna put it in here
It's gonna be oh god a lot of typos in that statement
And
There you go posting it right now
Fundament
German needs a catch phrase like shibis chocolate sauce
How long am I gonna be streaming Diablo 3?
At least a couple hours at least at least that
Oh, and is the stream running okay? It's it's there's a 360 and a 720 option
Are are both of them looking okay or is it is you know how does it look? Are we good?
Hopefully we're good because this is the first time I've ever streamed in 720 and I think the test went
The test went okay. I don't I don't know if it's perfect, but it should be better than before
Let's worry stupid
And while I think about it let me uh
Turn up my fans here
How's that even possible
The oblo 3 looks oh no the oblo 3 is fun man
I got a lot of problems I have with it, but they are overshadowed by the fact that the game is really good
So I can't really complain
I have a major major problem with it though and it's something I can't get over and I
I'll probably talk about it in
The video I do when I review the game
What I actually reviewed the game I will talk about it
Where where is everybody
How can nobody say where is everybody
Somebody want to post the ip again in the chat
Oh make sure if you haven't already done it select um update automatically
For your stream thing on the chat window
Yeah, yeah
Because it's gonna be one V1 there's a lot of spots in this server
Now you know I'll do this for those of you so you guys can see because maybe the the chat is lagging or something
This is the server
63 dot 146 dot 183 23 270 15 you take a look at it right now write it down maybe
Okay, that's what we're gonna be for a little while
And hopefully you guys got it by now so I'm gonna close it and here we go
The only problem with the apple 3 is the constant required that's another thing that's kind of
shaky in my opinion as well
What's up zc s how you doing bro
The combat is incredible though it is one of the most satisfying combat games
At least action RPG combat games ever played
Playing a barbarian if you didn't see the video
Man, it was going on is this is this uh
Will we be getting like a crash or something? I know one's really joining
What is going on with this
server
People should be able to join
Yeah, I'll go online that makes no sense
All right, you can join off me you can you can join off me
You can and in fact we'll join off me
Uh, yeah, I gotta I gotta go over to twitch and say it's not gonna be there
The only reason why it's not on twitch is because
I I wanted 720 and I don't have a partnership with twitch
I never planned on really getting a partnership because I of course have a machinima contract with live streaming so
I'll need to utilize it a little bit
Can somebody do me a favor one of the mods I have in my typical twitch stream can somebody go over there
Then just tell them that the stream is over here
Because my window is currently closed
Now
Yeah, I'll uh
Somebody should replace go over there
Streaming on day youtube's
It's okay, I'm gonna be streaming for a long time so people uh
People will figure it out sooner or later I guess right
I'm gonna strip or T up
Uh, I'll probably stream it for maybe half an hour maybe 20 minutes
Couple rounds I want to get a couple of good rounds those and that's that's the most important thing
Now let me let me let me get this thing rolling now. Let's let's not let's not try hard as a scout
Just get this roll and here we go
I
Know I mean the devil three is to is taking over the streams by a large martian
Right here
Well when I say taking over I don't mean like it's not like taking over but
I got a bob bob area again
Oh
Oh god speaking of jag I'm getting lag what rhymes with jag
Oh, you see that I threw the milk and it didn't even come out of my hand
Oh, let's go candy cake
Yeah, twitch tv has it has a better chat system
But this is 720 and no I just wanted my diablo 3 videos to be 720 for the most part least
Oh
Oh, where you going where you going
Now we're doing it now we're doing it
Oh, that was like a goomba stomp with the scout of gun you guys see that
ah
Derma killer of steam is back
Yeah, it's not uh everyone's peng's look okay. It's I think it's the server we're on
That's it's definitely too many people at the same time
Maybe we gotta stop it
Damn
I can see the youtube comments I have a little pop-up window that comes up where I can see whatever you guys are saying
I
Say something in this video that could become a real viral saying um
I want I want burger boy to go viral I want like burger boys just entire presence to be viral but I don't know if that'll ever happen
Yes, this will all be uploaded to youtube probably tomorrow afternoon
Oh god
lag
All right, I'm gonna appear offline now
I think it's just too many people are trying to join at the same time
But yes burger boy 2012
Actually, no, let me refresh it. It's burger boy 2012 emperor of earth. That's the hashtag
I
I'm since if we can get a
Of good string of non lag here
God they're gonna push it with dead
No, this is not good
That's a dead ringer for sure
You
We all care up there you are spy
We don't have a medic do we might have to go medic
Derma say what do you want me to say alpha? I'm I missed it. I was alpha something something something
God that's a laggy shot. I shot him five seconds later. We got hit
Oh god
God
Oh my word
Watching germa and eaten brownies
Brownies are good man. I love brownies
So if burger boy was president of the united states of america
What do you think his first legislature would be
Spile there. I just saw him. I know as it sold directly that guy just floated
So reserve shooter is becoming my default. I love this thing
Oh no
Oh no no no no no no
Oh God it's bad he's gonna kill me
Oh god give it the health
Oh good good spy good spy good backstab
Oh good medic good medic oh he'll be help me
Oh I'm gonna die to what he thinks going on at the same time
Do some market gardening. I'm so bad with the market gardener. I'm terrible
Me market gardenering is like I'd rather watch paint dry. I'm terrible. I'm like so bad
Stand on the freaking point you moron stand on it
Oh did I get I didn't get the kill today
Oh shooter that me again damn
Listen
Where's grandpa grandpa you momento get him
your island
Can you justير
This is the biggest
them
They're heading that would be the
to
Random crits out my body
Kaver classes engineer I
Haven't been playing a whole lot of engineer though
I've not been playing really any engineer. I don't know why either
And we're gonna lose the game very no one's people gonna walk right by me watch this
People gonna walk right by me
Oh
My god
That killed me
Oh, so by the way those of you that were at the stream a couple weeks ago
During the whole debacle where people can see through the backpack the game show event
I wanted to clarify this that
Optimus Prime
was
What he could see the backpack and he wanted to make sure that it didn't get stolen because he's obviously a mod on the stream
So Optimus Prime is it's not a thief he oh god. I'm lagging
He is not a he is not a thief. He did that in the merits of his own heart to try and protect the unusual hat
So I oh my god. I can't even walk either what else going on
Maybe if we make if we all crouched the lag will go away
Yeah, that if you're wondering that that and I am working on a new solution
To figure out how to do another stream like that and have it work
I mean it worked it was okay after after the first like 15 or 20 minutes, but
There were a lot of issues and I will figure them out
And I'm gonna get overcharged throughout the gate and I'm gonna I'm gonna mess up and up here
I'm gonna be like sir Derpington when you when you hit this on me if you're gonna hit it on me
Actually, no, don't do it yet sit right here sit right here. We're gonna hide
We're gonna hide right here. We're gonna eat cookies and pancakes until they come out
No, no hold it hold it hold it okay go
Oh dear god oh how is he not dead
How many oobies did we just have out the gate you kidding me
That was like
Holy crap that was a lot of people
Soup can
God
So I'm after this round. I'm probably gonna move on to my own server
Because it's just it's just like chaos. I think too many people are trying to connect at the same time
I
Every time I hit let me tell agree in the comments if you agree with this
So every time I hear the ambassador shot that like boom boom. I always think it's not on our team
Oh my god
Got like broken legs. Oh, this is gonna be bad bad news for everybody on the cut
Oh good backstab good backstab
Come here you oh god hide
He's still alive right here
Oh dead ring and bastard
Well that was okay
Don't don't let him get away
He's gonna get away oh
God it's like lagging all over the place
All right
Run run away
All right now they think we're running away
Oh
No
Hey it was a good run it's a good run
It was a good run
You
Ambassador or backstabs you whenever I hear the backstabs sound that I always go
I freak out and I turn around looking around all over the place
Any spies over there oh
Oh, god spam everywhere
Oh
What just happened did I kill that guy what oh
Optimus prime backstab them okay
Oh, you need one more shot you're dead
Now get out of my face oh
Thank you for healing me
That's a spy that's definitely a spy
Oh I'm trying to reflect it
Get this health over here bro. There you go buddy
Oh, they know we're in here. This is not good. That's a spy. No it's not
Oh lord
Oh no
We'll be charged
Oh just die
No, just die
All I cared about was killing that guy and I didn't even get him
Oh damn
Oh, I guess they got the pyro
At least they got the pyro
Let's go sniper
You'll never get me
Spock out
Spa sap and mountain spans it
Favorite weapon in team fortress to probably uh-oh
Let us take a moment to mourn the loss of this sniper
He was a good man and all he wanted to do was just sniped and kill and may
I was actually hoping I was gonna get backstabbed that was like the whole point there. I was hoping I was gonna get backstab
Fio
I just heard it. Where is he
Ah, I thought he was gonna run into that
Oh god, they're everywhere
Oh get away from me! Crush him! Crush him!
Strategy that I never really talk about is the freak out melee
It actually works more times than you'd think. Oh god
Ow
Hello
Oh, and that came from Optimus Prime. What the hell was that?
Optimus Prime just like morphed into a woman for a minute there
Yeah
Did you you son of you bastard. Oh, I thought that was actually a spy. That was funny. You ducked from my arrow
Ah kill him kill him
Kosa
I lost
I lose
He's been a woman the whole time
Where am I? I'm actually not doing too terribly
For as laggy as this is being
Doctor
Don't worry. Oh my god. Oh god
It is so scary when I just bump in this pie and then I bump into a second one
Give me a headshot
I refuse to put this thing away until I get a headshot
Come on now. Oh
Damn
All right, you want you want the Boston Baster on there? I don't even think I have it
No, I don't even have the Boston Baster
I don't even have the Boston Baster
No, you stood oh my word
What wait a second wait a second wait a second I just shot by him and killed the spy that was behind him
All right, there we go. That's the re let me get it. Let me get a quad
No, no, no, no damn
Just freaked out right there
Freak out smash freak out smash it always works it always works
I told you
As long as you just freak out if you freak the hell out and stop swinging to somebody you probably will kill it
Oh, that's a crit screw
Chaos it's gonna be it's gonna work when all else fails
When all else fails chaos smash
Oh
No
No, no, you mean
What's up potato fryer how you doing my man
You can't beat the chaos smash
All right one more one more little life here with this huntsman and wait is somebody on the cart now
Going up top I'm going up top
Yeah
Just shoot down this hallway man. I'll kill somebody. I'm bumping into a spy too. I don't have Gerardi
Here he is
Oh god
What how many spots did they have on their tube
All right, I think I'm gonna try see here's like the big joke
See listen to this ready so my server is full right now, right?
And I can't I can't even get into it
I have reserved slots set up for myself, but apparently it doesn't work. I guess not
So I'm gonna try and do this again to see if it works
And let's see what happens
Yeah, see servers full I have a reserved slot. I'm probably doing it wrong who knows
But I'm changing servers we're gonna go somewhere else I would go in my server, but there's no way I'm gonna get it
I
Can't even get it to my own server I'd be
No, this is this this is like I'm knocking on the door to my own house
And there's like a potty going on in my house
That's pretty much the equivalent of this there is like a crazy potty going on in my house right now
They're like break and vases they're like somebody's like puking in the bathroom
And I'm outside just staring at the house. That's pretty much what's going on
I can't get it
Wait connect you rip what is that?
Oh, oh your IP. Yeah, I just tried it. I don't know I haven't set up it doesn't work
I'll try it one more time ready connect
Is the IP server is full and I have reserved slot
I don't want to be a jerk. That's my own fault. I'm not having it set up right
Party at Germans, but he's not invited I'm not invited to my own party
Oh, I want to check something
I gotta drop that down
I do play on shibby server. I mean, now that I have my server I kind of I try to stay on that as much as I can
Is that who's who's isn't who's on here is anybody's like anybody on there that I know
Nope, I'm all right new server
So what's gonna happen now is because my house is full of people at a party
We're gonna go to somebody else's house that doesn't is not having a party right now
So let's go
See no not dark to D
After after this I'm probably gonna play some the apple three
So
So here's the IP if somebody wants to paste that into the chat
It's right there because if I do it it's it's gonna get swarmed
So I'll post that into the chat if you by the way turn on automatic updates for the chat
Because that that'll help it with the the reload time but that is the IP if somebody want to link that I would be appreciated
I would be appreciative not appreciated what
I
Bet you burger boy the dump machine is there oh
Yeah, forgot. I'll go. Let me get grandpa hold on
Hey, your grandpa get down here
Yeah, you want to talk to you
It's that who wants to talk to me
Who wants to talk to me let me sit here sit down. I'm sitting. I told you I'm already sitting
Okay
All right, it's question and answer time with grandpa. So what do you want to ask me
In the comment section literally asking good question or I'm gonna punch you in the face and you're gonna bleed
Let's place a red team
We're here come on. I'm not invited to the party. Where's there a party
Who didn't fight me to party. I'm the best time to pass out of a bitch here
I'm gonna play engineer for a second here put this down put it right here against the wall
Because you never know that could be a spy that's gonna come on its corner here
I tried get the spawn so I'm gonna put that at the spawn door to make sure no spies get it. Let's see how it's going on with his lag
Oh
ah
What the hell is going on here
This is a laggy as piece of crap server I ever played out about your life
Oh
How old you might somebody want to hold I am I am
You'll never know
You're never gonna find out all damn
Let me get to century help me get to century level three while the lags will have server lags out
What how's your actually work. Oh, he's right there get him
You want me to high five you you look at the high five for me
Well my birthday is June 15th
1918 so if you could figure that out for yourself to go ahead
What is this game why don't you even happily where do I go I
Don't even know where to go in this game. I just know you build a century and protect the spawn from those backed spies and
Updusty too
What the hell is on this guy's hands?
What is that you look like a friggin Nordic goddess up and get away from me you break it way out
All right
Well this everybody lags too much. So I'll pull this over here
And he's gonna right here is a good spot for the century
century going up over here boys. It's a good spot for it and
Then the dispenser is gonna go like over here
Like
Suspense you're gonna go right there and then the century shoot people
And I'm lagging out way too bad as he's a worst ever ever
Do I get all the bitches yes absolutely yes
You might think because I'm old I don't have any uh
I don't have any libido left but should be totally wrong but you put that statement
So if I killed two people that I leave and I've already killed one so let's get another kill come on
What did you get out of here you're making me show up on the radar is this is like bottom warfare right tomorrow
You shoot tomorrow you show up on the radar right
Where is the radar
Where are you two two and go fight the battle
You guys need to fight a wall where you're doing hit them say it out here
Somebody challenge you to it do
What is that
I
What's that do
I got a second kill that means I can leave and put this entry down here for a suicide century
There we go
This is the best part of the game right here
This is where you get all the kills
Ha ha ha come at me come at me look at this entry to work
You're up
If you seek a ing spy not allowed to swear on his streams Jeremy tell me I you're getting troubles. I can't do that
Grandpa have you ever gone to the bathroom two times a day before yes
I actually go to the what's going on what's going on that's it for god
Yeah look how for that bastard by he's a Frenchman all Frenchmen's are bastards we all know that
They're all sneaky and they steal your stuff and they
Have love your women and
What what the hell does happen
What does happen to me
Oh, I'm out of here. I'm getting
The previous game again Jeremy I give sucks
All right
Go you need to go take a nap anyways you've been up a little too long
Keep it up a little too long grandpa
Somebody keeps repairing that century by the way
Oh, I got I didn't even know I was in a duel
I think you're a spy but I could I was right I was right
I was right all along and I cannot land a shot to save my life right now
There you go
Are you a spy?
No, but I'll have five year anyways
Yeah
Whoa, huh, huh, how did you even get me?
I'm stupidly like choking on my own throat
Oh
So is the stream is the is the is the lag in the game like I'm bearable to watch in the streamers
It okay like how does it look in the actual stream window?
Oh my god
Chaos remember remember what I taught you guys chaos
Okay
Chaos
I'm just gonna go wrench. I'm just gonna wrench people in the face. That's all I'm gonna do
There's a guy right here. I'm not gonna get that scout ever
Oh
Waiting I'm waiting to some of the jump over here so I can just laugh
I'm gonna freak somebody out ready. Let's do this
I want some of the walk out and land on this oh my god
Oh
It's coward killing time
I do I am a dark dark rink didn't I really am
Whatever I do these live streams I just buy my my brain shuts off and I like have to I'm look as I'm looking at the chat talking and I'm doing like like where you have
I feel like I like just bought the game bring back those memories
Let's get the century up at least a little bit
I'm not even like protecting it. I'm just like running away from it every time it goes up
There we go is it dude. I really do think if you guys if you're watching us on YouTube right now
Did I get more melee kills than I think you serious?
I'm getting I don't think I've killed anybody with anything else besides melee this entire time
Maybe I killed like four people with the Huntsman. I did I kill anybody with anything else besides melee
Maddie
Why am I not streaming on twitch because
I can't do 720 on twitch and we're lagging again, so I'm I'm gonna disconnect from the server
So I'm gonna go on a random server
So that nobody can see the IP because I think what the problem is happening right now is we keep on crashing servers out
Because too many people are getting the IP so let's just go to
I'm gonna take it off screen
I'm gonna take it off of this screen
My boy, what's going on here
Let's see let's find a map I like
And I'm gonna go play some gravel pit
No, we won't just we will no we won't just we will
What is that hat with the Eiffel Tower we all highly intrigued and I look that can't find the store
Oh, yeah, the uh
That is the radio tower hat from crits cast
You don't know crits cast. It's a team fortress to podcast. They do every week
And every week they give out player of the week
And I guess it's like a thing they do where they find like somebody that's doing a lot of
Cool stuff or they're doing well or they're something with competitive
I'm not really exactly sure
But I do know they give it out pretty much every week I think to somebody else
And I happen to get player of the week which is that's awesome
And thank you to the crits cast guys if you're watching this or if you're seeing that's at some point
Thank you for that. I much appreciated. That's awesome. Thank you so much
But that's where that had came from. It's from the crits cast guys
All right, let's go to
Gold rush this one whatever it is
Yeah, I want I want to get at least one good non laggy team fortress two game
And it seems like every time where it's I don't know recently. I don't know what's been going on
Every time it was me the streams from a long time ago from
I've been doing streams for the last four or five months
I've never seen this problem before and I used to give out IPs like crazy
We would always just flood a server on it would not that stuff would never happen
So I'm wondering I'm wondering if something else is going on
Who knows but I'm gonna try and play a little bit of one more session here with the
Demoman
I am appearing offline
So I don't want to kill this person's server
Thank you doctor
Got my strange lock-in-load
Oh, I thought he's gonna back up into that
Whoa, just barely just barely
No, I didn't get him almost got him
Oh my god, I just barely dodged that crit rocket
There's a century right there. Oh
And goodbye century
Oh, I'm gonna be in trouble need that medic. There's still stuff over there
Whatever that medic oh god
I hate when that happens
Bumps right into him shot him right the face instantly blow up myself. I do that far too often by the way
I do that more often than not
All right, let's go. I want to kill I want to kill like at least 10 people in a row
Doctor
No, I saved him. Oh my god more spies
Oh, that's crit someone's gonna walk over that
Someone's gonna walk over that I don't feel bad for them. Oh, this is not good. I forgot I had this equipped
It's fine that's by it's the only oh great
I
Want somebody walk over here. Somebody touch that car there he is
Oh
All right, that was gonna blow somebody up. Let's see. Let's see if I can't ambush somebody
Come on you coming. Oh, okay. Okay, we got a medic. We got a medic. We got a medic
Coming out this way buddy. Where you going?
What the I think I'm running through a spy
All right, all right, all right, stop the prey just like you would in the jungle
oh
Random crit random crit give me a random crit
Yes, yes, oh, I can't believe it
Oh, let's be a real jerk
Oh, I'm being a real bad person right now I'm out here
Oh
Get that spy. I keep pulling the stupid thing out
I'm gonna be playing Diablo 3 in like 15 minutes or so
Here we go same guy same guy round two
Round two come on
Oh round two
Round two I got him
Oh, now I'm on top
That pyro has to be very very upset with me
You gotta imagine that that pyro is probably not happy right now
Well
I would be quite upset as well
Oh
I'm hitting into the stupid thing
One heavy down
Come on somebody get on that cut
Nice in health and he's in health man
Help me please help me thank you
Oh
Come on, I got it
Spencer down
Come on walk out that front oh oh come on walk right into a crit rocket crap
Damn it
God dang
That pyro is your friend oh my god
We're going demo night
Seven and three what I say one of 10 kills where I'll get it all right now here's one
No, that's not spy
They get locked in the spawn man that's not feel bad for these guys
Hey
Spy I just ran into you don't know where you are, but it's okay
Oh there he is
Pre number one
Yikes
Oh how did they know how did they know
Did you win that duel Justin I don't even remember
You probably did
Maddie Maddie Maddie
Oh all you have now is that crits cast at
Uh no I have other hats I just I just recently got it so I've been put oh you this is it by the way if you want to see it
vintage lo fi long wave
I just have it on all my uh classes right now just for fun because I just got it recently and it can be equipped on anybody so
Oh
I just totally did not time that right
Totally didn't time that right
Broom
How bluff fatty what's up man
I played Diablo 3 with star shibi mlsc stealth and burger boy
All right, let's stop the chain here. Let's stop the chain here
This guy's gonna kill me. I have no health at all
Come on stay alive until I get charged
Yes
All right, let's do it
Let's go for this
So I'm gonna like walk up here
Suicide for the win all right one more kill and I'm gonna uh I'm gonna probably move on to Diablo 3
So
Let's all ask if if he's a brony
um
I
I don't think so no
That's somebody that really likes watching that that show right that my little pony show
I've never watched one episode and never seen one episode
I don't really watch any tv the only tv I really watch is I mean I watch a lot of youtube if you count that
I
Can't believe I missed thank god L scorch or just sniped in because that was awful
Oh
Ah
I'm sorry did you just say suicide for the win uh fake in-game suicide for the win we'll put it that way
Oh
One
I got the kill though that's what I wanted
Never seen one of my three is welcome thanks for coming man
Oh super trick
All right, uh let me see other as is anybody even online
To place them Diablo 3 not even in skype
Oh
Let's see if anyone's online
Burger boys online
Uh no side of bread with shibi
Shibi is online and star is online too
All right, we can make something happen here
Oh another game yeah
So I have to get Diablo 3 in a window
So if you came over the TF2, thank you for coming glad uh glad you stopped by
And yeah, thank you if you want to stick around for Diablo 3 I'm gonna be streaming Diablo 3 for
Probably quite a long time and when I say quite a long time, I mean at least an hour or two
So yeah, let me get that roll in here
First of me write a heart
Do
Screen is going to go black for a minute or so here
Whoa, screenception straight screen is gonna go black
But I'm still here not worry
I have not left
I'm still kicking
So what can I talk about while I do this oh
Diablo 3 because I'm gonna play Diablo 3 right now
To
Loading up Diablo 3
So what I can talk about while this is kind of a black screen right now is yes, I'm still a barbarian
I'm having fun with this new build and I'll try and talk about it
What I'm doing is I gotta I gotta show it on the screen before I uh
Before I need that good stuff happens so hold on a second guys
It's probably gonna be a whole lot of nonsense in the background
Do
Windowed
I can not make a different dough
Well, that's weird why can I change it to
Hmm
What's the deal here we go
All right windowed there's the window believe that's correct
It's about 720
There we go
Okay, come on back coming back
And
How we back
No, that's not quite what I wanted
Not quite hold on guys. Sorry about this
Not quite what I was looking for
It's okay
All right
I'm gonna do this
Okay, now I gotta do this
Hello
Oh
Inception inception
Inception
Hold on I'm trying to try one more thing here
It's got this black bars on the side I don't want that
I don't want that at all
To to to to now let's try this again
Okay, I got it this time I got it this time
Add screen region
And
And there we go
Hello
And let's do it
Okay, we're back
I'm actually gonna turn some of these down
For the purposes of
For the purposes of streaming
And here we go watch it be like service it down
That's suck
So now what I want to show you guys my this is my barbarian
I'm gonna be like cool
Oh
Perkyboy's in a game right now
I'll go play with burger boy is it act one oh so I gotta say this is gonna have um actually this is not gonna have any spoilers
Let's go join him
He's gonna be like he's gonna be so confused
He's gonna be like what are you doing in here
I
Just said sup burger. I'm streaming
Oh, where is he right now, so this is what I want to show you my build
This is the build I'm working on right now for the barbarian
So I have right now see this this this thing right here for Zirka rage
You inflict an additional 25% damage while at maximum fury
So what I'm trying to do is I'm trying to use as many moves as I can
That are not
Consumers of fury because obviously these ones are not they these as a barbarian if you don't know
You have moves that build fury and you have moves that
Use it they remove it so what I'm trying to do is I'm trying to do this kind of build where
I'm always at maximum fury at least for the most part so they get 25% damage from that
Just by having the fury as high as it can go and then this
Enter a rage which increases damage done by 15% and critical hit chance by 3% for 30 seconds
So it's a buff right and of course I have this rune where it um
It makes it so it increases that damage bonus to 30%
So if you can do the math what I'm trying to do is have this be it 30% and have this be full all the time
So it's at 25% so you're talking
55% more damage if I have full fury and that trying to stay there as much as I can
So let's uh let's go find bergoboy
Bergoboy I'm just gonna turn up uh
I'll just join off him. I'm not sure where he is right now. I think he's in the older ruins
Why barbarians someone's asking oh
God lag why barbarian because barbarian I don't know just I remember the barbarian from Diablo 2
Damn he turns into the sound down a little bit
The barbarian in Diablo 2 is just a classic and I'm a huge fan of the classic Diablo
So of course I'm gonna try and pick it and play
This is on nightmare by the way and we have already completed this game at least once
And it's probably gonna lag for the first few seconds or minutes or so of the uh game
Only because it does that for some reason. I don't know why Diablo 3 is very very buggy right now
All right, what's what's what's what question you want right now
Done this uh, I'm gonna show you what I'm talking about though. So I have frenzy right frenzy speeds up the more I hit
people
Like speeds up my attack speed
So what I'm trying to do is just be like an absolute psycho and swing like a hundred miles per hour
See if I can't show it I'm talking about here
So see the more I hit people the faster I'm gonna swing and those yellow letters those are crits
Yeah, but let me get burger boy in the sky call
Burger boy gunna I'm gonna I'm gonna call you
Where are you burger
Actually burger boy you can you can you call me
Just uh call me burger boy because uh, I'm a bit of the use too much of my bandwidth
Oh, he just started act one nightmare. So for those of you who's watching this is this is the very beginning of act one
And it's on nightmare difficulty
You just started burger boy
You
What where are you burger?
And that's where I am I'm trying to remember what quest he's even on
Oh burger boy has to come in here because he has the quest the quest person
So you want to see my stuff before we get going here before burger boy gives me a ring of ding ding
You
Burger look at that face by the way look at like burger boys face
Someone's asking what is Diablo 3 about oh, it's kind of a difficult thing to explain
But pretty much it's an action RPG where you run around and you kill
Literally hundreds and hundreds of monsters in at the same time and hold on burger boys actually calling
What's up burger
Oh, oh, and I got changed something you know you guys can hear am I gonna make it so he's coming through the right line
Line one
There we go
Burger boy close your windows oh
Yeah, sorry
Burger boy like lives are like on a highway
All right, uh, let's let's do this thing man
Bring a layer oh, she's actually ready
You want me to grab my 42 you want to continue
Oh, no, it's all right. That's a matter. We've got to catch up a little bit anyways because shibby and um
And all them they're all and Bretton they're all a little higher
It's a beautiful face somebody said about your face
Oh sweet
But someone who's asking what this game's about pretty much a loot it's about picking up stuff
It's about
collecting gear and I'll show you my character. This is my life character stuff
It's about collecting gems and rares and uniques and there's literally thousands and thousands and thousands of different items in the game
And right now we're in the middle of a the actmon quest where we're supposed to be killing
I think we're supposed to be finding somebody actually so let's uh whooping butt
So
So burgaboo I'm a barbarian burgaboo is a monk oh god freeze
Yeah, killing stuff. That's pretty much what it is killing stuff
Killing bosses trying to get better gear trying to have
For you TF2 guys, I'll explain it like this
So you have
unusual hats and team fortress, right?
So unusual hats
Pretty much think of any any every time like we kill a boss in this game or in time you kill like a major of enemy or like a very rare enemy
It's like opening a crate
It's like opening a team fortress crate and there's items that are really really incredibly are called legendary
And the chance of getting one of those is like probably one to two percent per
Major enemy you kill
So it's a very big like treasure box game where you want to get like as many cool pieces of gear you want to get all the awesome stuff
That's the best way to describe this game. It's all about making your character better
And I'm level 30. Oh, I'm 42
I should probably not even be here with you. I'm probably not gonna get that much experience
Okay
It's just very addicting the whole everything about it is a dig thing
There's an auction house you can sell stuff you can
There's a whole trading atmosphere to it. It's very very interesting
But I've been waiting for this game for over 10 years just about 10 years 2019 99
Yeah, exactly shacks exactly it is unboxing a boss
And even just regular enemies to it if you notice when I kill some of these guys, like they'll just drop stuff
The randomly will drop stuff on the ground
And there's a big storyline to it. There's a there's a whole lot of cool stuff to read about just interesting
Excuse me
Oh the puke spell puke spell
Give you guys this buff
That's still recharging
But if you are a fan of action RPGs
This is pretty much the series that started it all
Diablo one
I'm not I'm not gonna give up my battle tag for the main purposes of it's it's very easy just to to join off anybody's game
So I'm gonna keep that probably private for now
Because as you know if if if anybody joins your game
You the game just gets harder. I'm gonna get a water hold on
I started to get froggy
But if anybody joins your game the game just gets harder everything look everything just gets harder
Oh, this is where it gets nuts
Going to super second mode
See I can turn into this like giant barbarian
Smash
Get smashed
And I drop
You get bonus experience you get bonus experience for killing a certain amount of enemies in a row
It's very very addicting and everything about this game is addicting
I'm gonna go this way just split up so we can fight it easier I guess
I
Bang
I got 144 kill straight earlier it was insane oh my god
144 yeah the monks nasty oh I got turned you up a little bit
There you go people probably having trouble hearing you now they can hear you probably
Can you guys hear burger boy? Okay, or is should I lower them drop them?
Oh here we go. This is what I'm talking about. This is a rub. This is like a room for enemies. I want to fight bang
I'm at the uh
Point where we need to be just uh, I'll TP off you anything. Yeah
Yeah, I hope you don't mind this will all be uh this will all be uploaded to youtube
Tomorrow probably afternoon
Yeah, you can just take it out this except up you
So I'll just skip everything because I don't want to you know the story people might not want to see it. Yep
And skip
Get a minions
I'm tacking cane
It's tacking cane this is on nightmare right? Yep. Yep. I think it is yeah, it is
Got a big boy right there. What's he gonna drop legendary? Oh
He just keeps dropping like vintage items skip skip skip skip
Oh, I gotta go with the secret how much does the game is 60 bucks
It is 60 dollars. It's a brand new triple A release. So
Kind of expensive, but for the amount of time that we've been playing this for
Yeah, skip it for the amount of time we've been playing this for like I'll just show you I think I can show you
Uh heroes
I guess I can't but I've been playing this game on this character for probably 25 30 hours already
I'm almost a little bit 43 too. This is good stuff
I get the next quest
Yeah, burger burger boy is uh, he just changed classes. He's a witch doctor now
He was on his monk but now he's playing as the witch doctor
The cell some of this stuff
And as you can see he's like 37.7 dps and the thing I have on is 75.6
And you can look at the stats too and you kind of go you you stat crazy and you get all nuts
It's a lot of fun
I don't need any of this stuff really though
And I want money so I'm just gonna sell it
I want that money
Oh, no, it is not monthly it is not monthly
You just buy it once and you have it forever. You don't have to ever pay anything ever again
Yeah, that's the best part about this game. It was monthly man
I hate that monthly stuff. No, I wouldn't do it if it was monthly
I maybe for like a month or so maybe I don't know it would be tough because the game is really fun
I
Can't talk about fast
But it can get really crazy when you get a group of four people because the maximum amount of people you can have in a
In a lobbyist for
You get four people in this game and it gets pretty ridiculous
Maybe do we kill them to kill this lady or no. Yeah, we got to kill this lady. Uh
Yeah
Get her
Super Saiyan mode. Oh, she went down. I'll throw up all over
Nothing good
The major point of the quest is to
Make the story keep going progress the story gets some more gold. Get some more loot
But the real the real treasure chest is the bosses
The major there's like
15 major bosses in this game. Maybe a little bit more
That's like the real joy of this game is killing a boss and like crossing your fingers that you're gonna get a legendary
Or like a good rare or something
You
Somebody wrote
Doesn't burka boy only buy games when they attend our 10 dollars 10 dollars when they're 10 dollars. Wow. That's just a lot about this game
Yeah, that is true
Watch out we got some dudes over here
Oh
Bang
Oh, we got a lot of people over here. Oh god. Good
He just smash him smash him
I love that move so much cleave is so much fun
We just swipe at everybody and just crush him
Yeah, bosses are treasure boxes when you when you kill a boss
Don't do a ton of stuff just jumps out of the end of the screen and you see
What you want to pick up what you don't want to pick up what you want to trade the people what you want to sell
We'll be at one of those bosses fairly soon probably in the next like 25 minutes or so
The skeleton king
I
Was making sure this way
Burka boy
Get out of town
Pick up all the money is important
You
Way by now you found a way point nice
Oh, it's your way
Oh, just trying to see when people were online last
Always check the oh
Oh my god, I was just lost my mind
I thought my brain just collapsed right there. I thought that was a uh a set item or something. We just a book
You want to go down one of those doors and I'll go down another since we're a little uh, yeah on level here. Yeah
Sounds like a plan
Get that speed
Sure ma are you grandpa um that mystery will never be solved
I can either confirm no deny that statement
Go down here. Yeah, I'll check this one if you need help just call it out
Yeah, I'll be good. I got my minions. That's right. You are
You are a witch doctor. I do forget that sometimes
Uh
Technically deobble three is not an MMO, but I guess you could classify it as one
With the trading and the items and the multiplayer and the
But it is at at the heart of very it's a single player game for the most part
Oh treasure bandit. Oh man. I wish you were down here right now. Is that all right? I'll try and kill him
Oh, die you little bastard
Yes, nice. I gotta check that out
So what I just read there guys is there was it was a little dude and he carries around
Like a knapsack
Now burger burger boy immediately like came to where the treasure goblin was
And if you kill that guy he drops a lot of stuff as you can see look at the ground. It's covered with things
Pick it all up. See these these are rare
Oh
This is this is like the uncraditing thing I was talking about guys this not a legendary, but it's still rare. Let's see what it like
Hmm
The thing I have is better
Six vitality free health per second
Um, I can sell that though
I can sell it
This stuff
Yeah, I think they'll be DLC
I've got an event down here. They already they already confirmed that there was gonna be at least one expansion
Oh boy, there's a couple lords lords and ladies
Yeah, these guys got nothing we're we're a little bit high level for this
But I mean it's good just to clean through everything
Okay, well if you wanted to bring your what star I mean your munk in here when we get to the boss
You code just like speed level them
Hmm, good idea
I'm pretty sure that that that's how it works
Yeah, we'll try
What do you mean when you get to the skeleton cake? Yeah, yeah
What do you think oh like you don't have to complete the quest before
Oh, I don't I don't think so I could be wrong, but I don't think so
Of a 43 what I get
How a new ruin
I checked that
These guys these little bastards are running around like crazy
I'm a melee class I can't keep up oh
Oh
Oh damn kill this guy
Speed hack speed hack
I don't even need to use my my cooldown
Anything no
So somebody said if you hold oh that is good to know good to know thanks for whoever said that let me see what your name was
You
Dagless thank you for that
Uh, this guy just said if you hold down control while you hover over an item you can see the stats on it
Oh wow, that's awesome. I didn't even realize that
What an idiot bolts of us are oh man you can rash all the plates
So identify these babies oh
Oh shibby's gonna want these
74 intelligence 82 vitality I'll hold on to those for the shibster
All right, so it wasn't in here
Yeah, it wasn't that one might be the one you were at
I checked this one
What's my favorite type of cheese?
Swiss cheese
Oh
Or if you want we can try and do um
If you want to go to like act two and try and uh like farm the boss maybe
Yeah, let's do it if you want to do that after we um I want to go through a more little dungeon first
Yeah, cuz I don't even have to complete this area did this one. Yeah, yep, yep
I
Said the cool part about this game guys is you can literally
Just keep opening crates you just keep like killing the same boss over and over again to try and get cool stuff
Yeah, we'll do that. Let's do that. I'll make the game all right
Is that a new perk
Ah TF2 was before this if you missed it it's gonna be uploaded tomorrow to youtube
Okay, change quest
Act two
We'll do yeah the lord of lies but dial
Act two you know me when you're ready
Uh
With that what we just playing right there was the kind of the beginning of act one because burger boy was on it with another character
And I was just coming to help mount but now that we're on our like he's on his actual character and I'm on my main character too
We're gonna do the the boss back to again just because he's he's he's very major boss cool to farm
Maybe get some good stuff
No
Getting good items does not cost two dollars and fifty cents
Cost nothing
Unless of course there's the real money auction house is coming out at some point we don't know when in the next few days
Okay, yeah, this is what I'm talking about this is gonna give it difficult. Oh, yeah
So all boy being prepared
With that cleave
Let's get this sped up frenzy mode. I love frenzy
Stop them
Oh, I'm taking some hits now that I'm talking about I want to take that pain take that suffering
Oh, don't stand on the poison
Yeah
Nice
Do I think the real money auction house is a good idea?
Tough to say
I'm gonna go activate this uh tough to say because
It's one of those things where
Diablo is supposed to be all about finding blue and oh you found this you found that
But with the auction house it kind of makes it oh
Let me just go buy whatever I want from the auction house. I don't have to find anything
And to me that's I don't know that kind of takes away from the game a little bit
But most people probably aren't gonna really use it that often
I'm not sure but yeah, that's that's my opinion
I think that a real money auction house makes it so you can just buy whatever you want
And have the best gear in the game and you really maybe didn't even play you didn't even like try and get it
I'm an old school Diablo guy. I was all about farming the same boss over and over and over again
So you got that one item you wanted
But it's cool as it's it's something new something interesting that they add
Awesome rich kids kind of like get way better given you it's gonna piss you off isn't it?
No, I don't I mean I don't care
Just me personally I probably won't use the real money auction house at least right off the bat
Oh god, I'll stand on that
Get over here
I'll stand in that lighting it'll be your demise
Besides the barbarian uh the wizard I have a level like 17 wizard I haven't really been playing with lately, but
Probably the wizard
I gotta run away from that
See the problem with this build oh boy. We got oh boy oh boy oh boy
We got a couple of uh elite creatures over here
Oh they're all doing that lightning thing. I can't even stand near them
Oh god
I gotta try and single them out
I keep doing that mirror thing too. That's annoying
That out of here all right. I'm going super saying oh
You got nothing on me
Super saying mode
Maybe drops sick where'd you get
Oh
Not that was just a uh destructive
If you buy too much stuff wanted to defeat the purpose of Diablo
Yeah, that's my opinion and that's a like a lot of people share the same opinion
But there's also a lot of people that say and it's very warranted
They say I don't have time to grind the same boss over and over and over and over again
Oh by the way, we're about to want you're about to see a boss a major boss
So if you don't want to see it then you don't want to see it. So I recommend
clicking away from the screen for a second because yeah, we're about to see a major act boss
Oh, skip in the scene anyways, right? We're skipping it, but still it doesn't really matter
Spoiler alert
But
This guy is probably going to be incredibly difficult with just me and you this is act two
What was your question, Brondon? Sorry, I'll answer ask it again. I apologize
I'm trying to pay attention to five different things at once here. So sorry
You
Gotta get rid of his snake ads
Yeah, we we we're definitely gonna wipe the snow way we're gonna do this maybe we will
This guy's quite difficult
Actually we we can we can show this yeah, I know wait now. We don't this matter
Okay
Get him
Sick of minion
I only have one potion dude. This is gonna be really bad
This is gonna be really really bad
Man getting annihilated already
We are gonna get so owned it's not even funny
All right, it's almost like half life. Yeah
How are you forgetting the most important thing?
I
Crush him
And saving my super saying but when we really need it because we're really gonna need it
He's just about to give up. Yeah, kill that ad we don't want this guy here
This guy gone
Oh
Come on
Am I am I going to dream hack?
Oh, it's probably not it's across the world and I don't really have the funds I guess to travel across the world
Okay, this is where it gets nuts. Oh god. Oh god. I'm just I am literally scared
We're gonna wipe right in the first two seconds. We're gonna wipe in the first two seconds probably
Oh god
Yeah, I
Have like half health with dead. Yeah, me too
All right, let's go super second. Give me that health. Yes
Oh, come on. We get a burn up as quick as we can
He's crushing me right now. He's gonna do the poison thing
He's gonna do the poison thing
When he does it make him run for it trying to stand in it
There it is don't stand in it. Oh, no. Oh, that was so close
I got the walk you know
That was so close he does this for so long on nightmare
All right, come on here we go
Come on come on come on come on come on
Look at that help
Is the health right in front of you don't get it yet? Oh, oh
Did it? I didn't hold shift. There's another health there will be okay. I get I'm gonna grab it. I need it
Watch out
Crack get that health globe. All right
All right, here he goes here he goes run run around don't don't don't stand in it
Oh
So dead
Oh, no, can I revive you can I revive you come on come on come on
Oh, this is bad this is bad
Oh, no, it's over unless I get that health
You know what I have to do it. I have to do it right now now right now
Come on come on you son of a bitch. Yes. Yes. All right run run run
We got it we got to do some damage to him and he's not dropping any globes
There's one there's one all right good smoke a smoke a watch out watch out. What's up man?
Oh, I'm stuck in the corner over here. I just died again. No
Oh my god, no don't die. Oh
Oh, I'm so dead it is over super say it about
Go go smash him smash him smash him
No
Oh, it's over with dead. Oh, it's gonna hit me and I'm gonna die
I need to get a glow bad of him. It's over regardless
Ah
Oh, that was disappointing
Yeah, he was a little too hard little too hard. I'm just gotta go repair. Oh
We know we need we need we need we need um
We need to get potions. I didn't have any potions. I had like one potion going back to Tom
Damn, that was we got him down to half
Oh
Now let me read some of the comments sorry. I was paying attention to that craziness
When you die you don't lose your character. No, you don't that's hardcore mode only
If we just lost our characters right there, I would have peed my pants and then like pude my pants immediately after peeing
I wouldn't never play this game again
I have a little potion person's down here and tell
And yeah, I absolutely will do a ring this absolutely
I
Can't wait for them to come out to be honest. It's gonna be awesome. I need to go. Where's the potion person?
I think they're liking like another little area aren't they? Oh
They're all over here. I'm thinking of act three
Yeah, we I gotta think of a good arena team because
There's gonna be a lot of options
Bye bye bye bye. Super health potions
Okay
Yeah, this game is awesome for solo the reason why me and him are having trouble right now is because this is nightmare
This is on a higher difficulty mode and
When there's more than one person in a game
It makes the game like twice as hard
So when three people learn the game. It's three times as hard when four people learn the game
It is it max difficulty
All right, you are you ready to drive again
Yeah, see if we wait if we wipe again then we're gonna have to go back and uh
We should be all right this time. I we didn't have potion you did you get you got potions right I got four
I'll be good all right. You sure? I don't know about that four potions and seem like very much
I better put on the heroic ones too
And let's go
There we go again, we're doing it again
Yeah, let's do it
Night man
You know what I'm gonna put on I gotta put on a different passive
Where is it? I forgot to
Better offensive move
When we have a second here, I'm gonna put on the health globe one because we get more health gloves
Because we need them bad bad bad
I'm gonna hide behind your minion. All right, let's do it. What am I gonna replace it with?
This where is it? I'm gonna flesh take it. Thank you very much
So this is gonna do guys that I just put on a passive ability that makes it so much more
Health globe drop and they heal for much more
The health gloves a little like little health bubbles you see on the ground
Oh
This is absolutely worth getting
Troy thorn what's up man
I don't I'm not sure I'm gonna make be able to make it the pack's prime
The only reasons because I just I just it's just a lot of money. I don't have the money to fly out there and
I think the tickets are even sold out now to be honest
So I'm probably not gonna make it the pack's prime
We'll see though. I'm not totally ruling it out of the question
All right, doing much better this time much more controlled
This is I've done twice last time. Can't blame you for that
Are you gonna watch that poison?
My guys like
To like
Back is too awed like run
I was a pax East. I was at pax East. All right, here we go
Wow, we destroyed him that time. Yeah, well
He this is the bottom that matters
And here we go
Thank you Geron Gerino whatever you name us. Thank you so much
All right, this is where we go super saying
Cue all over all right, let leave the health gloves alone. Let them stay let them stay stick around for a little bit
You know, I mean till we need them
I'm gonna grab this one now. This one right next to me good. This health clothing was something absolutely should have had on from the beginning
That's what you're saying. It's all you'll fall pretty much is all my fault. Okay
Ha
Watch it. There we go. Oh no, not again
Anything but this try and stay away from each other. We're gonna like bump into each other
All right, let's do it start it up
Starts fashion
I've loved everywhere now. We're good
Or are we maybe spoke a little too soon. I had to take a potion
Yeah
Think as many as you need you have a tank
Oh, don't you spray that at me. I dare you
No, Lord, I'm running this way
He's gonna do that thing again very very soon. Oh here it comes. Yeah, it's definitely coming like right now
Oh, yeah, to do that right before you did this there it is
Oh, no, don't get clucked in the corner. Don't get clucked in the corner
Oh my god
Oh, no, I got hit by one
All right, we're good we're good. We're good
Even those dogs are like upset about this
All right, we got it. We got it. We got it
We're so pissed about so funny
Dude, this is getting so intense even like the dogs are getting intense
Oh
No, he's gonna do one more time it's gonna happen probably like right now
I'm gonna have superman get super saying mode one more time. Come on. Oh, no. There. I got you. I give you watch it. There it is
Oh, this is the last one
That's it. We got only deal with this last one and we'll kill him
Oh
Yes, all right, Burnham going super saying it's gonna get
Burnham burn him kill him oh legendary come on legendary legendary legendary legendary
Come on
Oh
Kidney
What's that garbage
Oh man
All that for blues we just I just got blues too
Rage quit rage quit
Oh, well, that was pretty difficult not gonna lie
Oh
Where is auto auto auto
All right, they can now let's
I don't want to move on to stealth. Yeah, where are they where should be stealth star worth everybody. It's gonna full-player action
Dylan
Continue on to act three. I would absolutely say that
That
Actually was not auto that was that was burger boys two dogs. Yeah, it's too big crazy dogs. They're like 180 pounds each
They both like like they stand six feet tall
I got I got a check on the stuff I just got
Well, that was a bad crate
Yeah, it was that was like that was like a crate eight no strangers. No, nothing
Oh
The only crates I have opened you know we the real problem here is we got to get magic find
I don't have like any you don't have any we need like a hundred percent extra magic fine
Okay, he's gonna save those for shibi
Hmm those those these they're actually not that great
I'm selling a could I sell them in the auction house probably not stats on these are really just dumb
I'm selling them sockets are good, but not not really too concerned about it
This is not that bad, but I got better
This is not that good
This is not that good and this is not that good all right
Actually, I think I had auctions that I'm going wonder if they sold
I'm gonna check on my auctions for a second. Okay, so I'm gonna show you guys the auction house
I'm doing the same. Okay, so this is the auction house
So what you do here is
You go to equipment jams crafting recipes pages and you can search for stuff
So let's say right now on level 43. So let's say I want something in 40 the 40 to 45 range right
And I want
One-handed weapons and now doesn't matter what one hand I want it to be rare though. I want it to be rare quality
So right now I just at search these are people that are selling things on the auction house
In though that particular
Category that I just mentioned so right now if you take a look at this this guy is absolutely not gonna sell this this thing
He's selling this for eight million gold, which is a Vade
I don't know if you're like you never gonna sell that
But see you you can you what you can do is you can play the auction house right you can play the field
So you go back to like the the bids and the buyouts to some of the cheaper stuff
There's a lot of pages as you can see
And burger boy is gonna like like puke on his microphone
Oh, sorry, see this is the least expensive one in here for the level 40 to 45 range
$115,000 so if I bought this right now for a high of a hundred and uh 18,000
If I bought this right now for 115 it I mean it really wouldn't be that
That good
Because obviously you you can find stuff you can make stuff. Oh you could buy this and then resell it and try and get more money for it
But for now, let's go to my completed auctions
See I put this up for 160,000 gold
This should have sold though. This is 14,000. That's like jump change
I had to see as you can see your past auctions. This is like the money that I've uh that I've made
A money that I've made money that things that I purchased
Say I can get really really addicting
You can get really addicting
So yeah and then eventually see currency
The real currency auction house will be available at a later date
529 so in a couple weeks you're going to be able to use real money to buy things
People are going to be able to put like oh here's my attack weapon thing. It's uh five dollars
Real money and it's going to be totally legal totally encouraged. It's going to be ridiculous