Okay, that's done on Twitter.
Oh, God, people are dying. They need my help.
I got you. Don't worry. I got you.
There's a spy up there, but I can't do anything about it.
But I can kill this sniper.
Nevermind.
All right. I got to write this on steam.
I need to go on steam.
Community. I decided first.
Groups.
Oh, I grew up of 5,000 members.
Wow. Awesome, guys. Thanks.
5,000 steam group members. That's unbelievable.
Party.
And it's happening. Let's say in 15 minutes.
Sounds good.
And I think it's gonna pop up.
Oh, we got hit.
All right. Now I can stop playing. I'm in my server right now, guys, if you're wondering.
It's 8 o'clock at night. Are you in Australia or something? Must be pretty across the world.
I'm in my server right now.
I have to play soldier.
Oh. I think we're gonna have a special guest.
Yeah, we're gonna have, I think we might have a special guest in a second here, dudes.
No, I gotta do something real quick.
Real quick and a quick.
Let me get back to this page.
So one more test for the new guys that just showed up.
Boy, was this in your sub box?
I feel like it's not.
If it is, I'm totally wrong if it isn't.
And I screwed something up.
But I think we might have a special guest referee.
Hold on, just a minute, guys.
Hold on, just a minute.
Thanks for the 8, Doc.
Bring this over here.
And special guest.
Are we gonna have a special guest?
Oh, ladies and gentlemen, special guest is.
I'll let him introduce himself when he gets in here.
What's up, man?
Hold on, hold on.
No one can hear anything you're saying because I have to change this.
I built you up, too.
I was like, oh, here he is, the special guest.
And then nobody can hear you.
Now they can.
Hello.
It's star, ladies and gentlemen.
Oh, my God, is it the real one?
I think it might be the fake one.
He usually is.
I literally just woke up.
Got out of bed.
He's streaming.
Yeah, yeah, I just decided to do it.
I didn't do it last night, so I tell him what's up.
I have to do it every week.
That is a good goal.
It's on your YouTube channel?
Yeah, I don't see it.
Maybe I'm just dumb.
It should be in feeds.
Oh, yeah, they like tuck it away there.
Yeah, it's not like in subscription boxes and the feed.
I'm like student people on my own team, like doing.
Can you get in here?
I will do that.
I just...
Is it possible?
Yeah, one second.
I was just like removing HUD elements and I'll fix that up.
And come in.
Somebody said, star, I just want to let you know.
You are the shit, brosif.
Oh, shit.
I did not know that about myself.
Well, you are.
Nice, nice, uh, Pyro.
Good job.
Good job, Pyro.
PyRizzle?
No.
Oh, my God, run.
There's nothing I could do there.
And now the plan is to jump.
Oh, the rocket.
You're going to use the rocket and immediately get back stabbed again.
Okay.
The control point is being corrected.
Mm.
Surfer is full.
Who the thunk?
Yeah, my reserve slot.
I'm going to have somebody in the sir.
Oh, God, this might be bad.
I might have to kick a couple people.
I'm going to ask if anyone's, because I'm not going to kick anyone to the list of willing.
Uh.
See if I can get maybe one or two people.
Because I need two slots.
I'm bad fat.
Boom.
All right.
Let's see.
Are you, uh, are you like auto joining?
Spamming joint game.
All right.
I'm going to get that set up.
My, uh.
There's a lot of things you need to get set up.
I know there is.
There is a lot of stuff I need to get set up.
Like removing gold rush.
But what?
Really?
You don't like gold rush?
It's alright sometimes.
I don't know.
It seems like it's come up a lot.
Every time I look at your answer, it's like, hey, let's play gold rush.
Oh, I love gold rush.
Gold rush is like my favorite map.
Okay, I didn't say anything.
I'm sorry.
No, I, I, I got a lot of things that have to happen with this server.
All right.
He's still, is it still full?
Yeah.
I'm ready.
Is it ready?
I'm about to do something right now.
It's a drastic time.
Scope of drastic measures.
Are you leaving your server?
No.
I'm going to restart it.
I don't know if that's the fairest way to do it.
I guess this is the, this is the really only way, the fair way.
No one's leaving.
Yeah, you're all getting out.
It's closed.
Uh-uh.
This is my server, but we're trying to get star in the game.
And my reserve slot isn't really set up correctly, so it doesn't work.
So I need to restart the server.
Just to make it so everyone can, you know, get in if they need to.
Server is going to restart right now after I do this.
Let me do this.
I'm all getting to here.
That's all right.
How's your morning doing?
You see, you just woke up.
Yep.
Say that a bed.
That's the best kind of, that's the best kind of out of bed.
Yeah, just.
Uh-uh.
Oh, at least I went to the bathroom first.
It wasn't like, hey, computer.
Yeah, at least you did you, uh, did you do number one, number two, number three, or all of them?
Number one, it smelled like pork.
What?
Extra info.
You could have said all the above.
Oh, no, I had to give the extra info.
Like, brag that I ate a whole bunch of pulled pork yesterday and it's probably the greatest food ever made.
I love pulled pork.
Pull pork is incredible.
All right, so here we go.
Server is going to restart.
So, dots, bam!
Err!
It's like I'm playing Diablo 3.
It's like a Harley B if neither of us is that on.
Look at this.
The stream is like, look at, look at how stupid this is right now.
It's like, can we get into my own server?
Oh my god, I think I got into my own server.
Yes.
Oh, or a harvest event.
Did you get in?
Yes.
It is a good day to be harvest event.
It is a good day.
Well, that's one way to do it.
So now we can start the stream.
So thank you for your patience, dudes.
I appreciate it.
It only took like 75 hours to start the stream.
Only all the hours.
All the things.
You're joking.
All right.
I have to restart TF2.
Oh, do you really?
Oh, we cursed it.
Yeah, I do.
Because you boarded something bright.
My graphics card immediately crashed.
All right.
Well, you will get in here if you restart as quick as you can.
Do a quick speedrun.
Join TF2.
There still looks like 7 on 7 right now.
And if not, then I'm going to have to kick somebody.
Someone who's playing spy.
That's how you'll choose.
It's full.
Oh, no, no, I got it.
Oh, yes.
Yes.
Where'd he go?
I need to get like a custom hard, like a real custom hard.
Because right now this thing is like blocking my view.
This capture holds the control points to win the game.
It's like, I didn't know that.
I told you again.
Oh, I just, I thought that was a trade.
Sorry.
You were trying to do it again.
I'm sorry.
I thought that was a trade.
Oh, run.
No, no.
That control point was being captured.
I was just assuming the item server was perpetually down.
Yeah, it should be up.
I got my items.
Yeah, I do.
So hello, everybody.
Welcome to this early Sunday stream.
We've got special guest star here.
I am going to bottom-frag every time.
I probably will too.
All I want to is jump.
Like jump it all I can do.
Jump this way, that way.
Oh, God.
Why is it doing this?
Okay, it didn't crash.
It didn't crash.
It's all good.
Good.
Good, good, good, good.
All right, I'm getting shot at from somewhere.
Oh, I'm too crazy.
He punched me.
He actually punched me.
See, I changed my setup a little bit.
See, I'm playing obviously in a window.
And I moved the window to the right part of my screen.
So I'm just like, look, I got to get used to this.
Because I have the chat on the left and I have the window.
I know, I need two monitors.
So bad.
I can't believe I waited as long as I did the end.
Just for streaming.
That's enough reason.
I just need a...
I need a better computer.
It's the problem is my computer is just...
It's good.
It's good computer, but it's just not good enough
to do two things at the same time.
I'm gonna go scout.
We'll go scout.
What's somebody's asking the IP?
It's just in my server.
When I got smashed right there, that's not good.
It's in many centuries.
I shouldn't even mention it.
But nothing?
What am I complaining about?
Nobody heard it.
No one heard it.
Oh, get him.
I can't believe I got up and he got away.
Also another problem.
Harvest event is really dark.
So it's a guard to see anyways.
This map is...
I should play it more often.
Because I play way too much harvest, but this is like...
It's totally different.
Yeah, it's like a whole new world.
Playing crit scout.
Yeah.
I can't even go over there.
You'll be in the rocket jumps.
Rocket job.
Oh, no, I ran into the damn ghost.
I hate this ghost.
Why is this mapping my rotation?
I don't know why.
I missed.
Actually, it's good every now and then.
Yeah.
Kind of like...
I really hate Iaduct for the fact that it has pumpkins laying everywhere.
You kill by a pumpkin, you feel like an idiot.
But Iaduct looks amazing.
Compared to the other buy-aducts.
Yeah, Iaduct is fun.
I just got killed by a pumpkin.
Crit scout.
Oh, come on.
He wasn't even there before.
That's Malaki.
Malaki.
I'm going to the straight.
Somebody's behind me, but I want to kill the soldiers.
Anyways.
No, this guy's got me.
This guy's got me.
Oh, this guy's got me.
Oh, no, I got him.
I'm not going in there.
Pumpkin.
I shouldn't have shot him from that far away.
Too bad.
Actually, I'm not doing too bad right now.
Well, I'm doing terrible because I haven't marked a garden to anyone yet.
Okay, it's off of that montage, remember.
Totally.
I got the most amazing one yesterday.
Quite literally the most amazing marking gardener has probably ever happened.
Ever.
What'd you do?
It's...
I don't know.
I haven't described it, but it was four rocket jumps.
I was surfing up a ramp.
So I was technically on the ground except for the ramp.
So I was technically on the ground except it doesn't count you as on the ground.
You know, is it the same type of thing when you...
You know when you air blast somebody that's on an incline and they don't go anywhere,
but technically they're still in the air.
Yeah, it's like if anything is slanted and you rocket jump past enough,
you'll slide up it and sort of launches you off.
It was the middle of sliding up something and I hit somebody.
Yeah, when I use the reserve shooter,
I'll air blast somebody that's on an incline.
They don't go anywhere, but they still get the mini-crets on them.
It's weird.
Is the server full?
I believe it is.
I have to imagine so.
This is your first stream ever.
And welcome.
Thanks for coming, man.
Oh, okay, Oss.
Absolute, okay, Oss.
I need health. I'm not going after that.
Demo, man, with that health.
What a bad idea. Why am I drinking this right here?
That was a terrible idea.
Pump good.
Yeah, grip.
How?
That is star.
Your ears are not deceiving you.
I think I just racked jumped off a pumpkin and it was...
It was glorious.
Is that like possible?
Can you actually do it?
Either that or a rocket hit me as I jumped.
I don't know.
Wow.
Oh, I was pulling out.
That was just one of those moments when my whole body just shaked.
Shaked.
Because I like this pulling out my melee and he shot me.
Nearly 11 p.m.
Ooniq bandit. Where are you from, man?
That's a long...
That's a huge difference.
Yeah, pumpkin.
Yes, this is being recorded and will be uploaded in a few hours whenever I finish.
14 days, you gotta wait for it.
It's two weeks for processing.
Actually, you know, the 720 streams on YouTube, they do take quite a long time process.
Really?
Melbourne, Australia.
That is across the whole world.
Well, thanks for coming to.
It's a long ways away.
Go in.
Immaculate crits.
Haha.
Yeah.
I can't go over there.
That's certain death. Get out of here.
Oh, it's a ghost.
Now I am so dead.
Nice shot, dude.
Nice shot.
Do I have any scout tips?
Start. Do you have any scout tips?
Shoot things, I guess.
Shoot things and run.
Yeah.
I will tell you, those scout from me at least used to be one of my worst classes.
I was awful.
I was just playing.
It's just the more you play with it, the better you're going to get.
I know.
I had like a die a lot.
I had pretty much, it was my least play class behind Pyro.
Now it's one of my most play classes.
Oh, God.
Do you need to die a lot to start realizing you're going to die a lot of scout?
No, I think we got a robot star here.
I'm sorry.
No, not anymore.
I am getting random blanks, so maybe everyone's in a while.
I'll be a robot.
That's okay.
We forgive you.
We all still love you.
I think that's spy.
No, yeah, it is.
Oh, yeah, it is.
It's smelling you getting off the elevate.
There's no elevator on this.
You was here last night, too, wasn't you?
Come on.
What's F from Fuldre?
I don't know.
Oh, come on.
I'm sorry.
Oh, home alone too.
I'm the one that's not cool and you're quoting home alone.
Never mind.
Did you I spoke to it? Oh, I love that movie
Babe Bob shot babe. Oh
So I went to Dunkin Donuts
Don't do it. Oh, you can oh, it's so good
You got Dunkin Donuts in New Jersey. I think I saw what the place is
Yeah, I actually a one train ride home from Boston. There's Dunkin Donuts. There's like three Dunkin Donuts in South Station
Yeah, so I bought a dozen chocolate frosted donuts for myself
The person getting them for you just the entire time they're picking out donuts giving me this awkward look
What could you possibly be using these for?
That's a lot for one person
I need two slots you need two reserves lots
Please reply what server is it it's my server
My server
German East Coast
No, put it down. I hate when that happens when I you go too far
You like just miss with the mini-century
That's too far man
You miss with the mini-century. I don't know some some reason it happens though
Oh god, this is the ghost again, you know what I'm just gonna talk because oh when you talk you
Just like dance it. Oh wait, that's because I have that I thought I had the um
Thought I had the
Gunslinger out but I didn't
Where is he I heard his buy
Not was a dumb thing
Someone said donuts are amazing especially crispy crispy creams. You've had a crispy cream donut
I think so now maybe oh, yeah, so good
Crispy cream donuts are incredible. I don't know don't have names
Well, it's like it's like a company. It's like kind of like a Dunkin Donuts
Except it's crispy creams
Pretty much a crispy cream donut is just a glaze donut and it literally melts inside of you mouth
It is just on it's unreal
You can't there's only like a few of them around the Northeast though unfortunate thing
You've ever had um ice cream
Ice cream what what's ice cream is that like something to do with like milk?
What am I doing why am I doing this
Am I ever gonna put a ping limit on my server to be honest?
Probably 20
Probably not the only reason why I say that is because I haven't had one in the last like two or three weeks since the server's been online
And hasn't really been any problems so probably not and if there ever was one it would probably be something very very high something like
Ridiculously high like 480 or something
That's pretty low. That's
I wish I had 480 thing
Oh
This heavy oh my god, I ran out of books. Oh no
Oh, why did I did what I do that
Mr. Foreman Gary the foreman Gary
Okay, it's like this is guy's name
Okay, he he told me I to say his name
And I just did it because I felt like
Don't worry about this thing built up baby. Let's do it baby
There was a ghost I'll name him Gary. Oh, what I didn't get it off in time. Oh, I'm so mad at myself
Let's go for a punch ready
I
Will go punch only engineer right now. It's gonna work because every time I stream I'm telling you dude every time I stream
I'm just going for melee only it for some reason it works. I don't know why I don't know
I wish I did the answer
But for instance like oh my god this guy just screwed me no
Oh, that was a nice attempt with the ng fest only crit sqree
It's super effective that's her Pokemon I
Hate this door glitch on our list. I want to leave a stuck somewhere
Punch in the center I'm gonna punch the crap out of it
All right, so I'm gonna ask you this first before I
For I answered but do you like the Vikings?
Vikings huh
Like
Like real Vikings are we talking about fictional Vikings right now?
I don't know that was the question. No, I actually meant to hit Jay. I hate our Jan K. I right next to you
Well, I mean the door was okay
Yeah, I was okay. I
I enjoy bike
But if you if you're having stream issues try to refresh the stream
You're gonna say if you're having stream issues then Vikings aren't that good
Yeah, especially if you're on 720 then a good refresh the stream will probably help you out probably
Vikings are even worse
How does it look by the way for anyone watching?
How because this is only the second time I've ever streamed in 720. Is it will be good?
We sound good. We look good. We smell good and your internet's fine with that
Apparently it wasn't last night. That's for sure
I
Not try to stream 720 all the time
My internet just seems that it doesn't enjoy yeah, rather layback
I if if all goes well then that's I mean last time I did 720 it seemed to work okay
But last night I was trying to set it up because I usually stream on Saturday nights and it was just like no
I could I could be only streaming 360 last night. I was like testing it by myself on listed
Well private whatever and it was not happening
If you haven't stream problems after bad for you son, I got 9 and 9 problems both are stream 8 1. No
Go be
I love your quote
Hey, look at what I tell you just punching. Oh, you're not getting away
That was a shotgun
No, was it not okay
Yeah, that was a I punched my fist and looked like a shotgun. Oh
My god, K off
There's like a line of soldiers waiting to market garden me
I'll go not wait you go
What classes star star
Spide spawn
Spide
What class is a what what what what class is star? He's a soldier. Sorry when that's by backstab me
I had like like an aneurysm or something that was weird
Don't do that. It's not good for you
Oh
Mini-century fight. Oh, we got too many centuries and we got a spa
I am almost there
No, anyone kills on my market garden
81 81 nice
Nice nice nice nice
Somebody asked am I gonna do another scary game face cam?
Yeah, dude that game was horrible
Horrible in the terms of I I completely I'm with you. I'm good with scary
Like just watching over. God, please. Why are you still going down?
We've agreed this is a bad idea
It's you know what it's because I started I'll give you guys I give you the back story about that video
So I started recording and I figured because I got a bunch of people asked me to do that
Somebody was like oh do amnesia do SCP do this or that so I just was like you know
I'm gonna do it. I feel like doing it and I got to a point where I was gonna turn it off
I was like you know what I'm not gonna make this video like I just do something else like I'm not gonna make this video
Because I sat down with it and notice how the video started when I was like kind of down a tooth like I want to
19 it sort of
Fades out. Yeah, like I I just I pretty much get oh god. I'm lagging why oh
No, that's a door, but that's the door glitcher than you were talking about before
What's I the video starts and I'm like already down two floors?
That's because I stopped recording and I just sitting there going I don't I can't do this
I really I really didn't think I could do it and then halfway through when I was actually recording
You can you can see like in my face during the video. Oh my god over time. This is a pretty ridiculous fight
I'll get back to that screw in a second
We lost no
Round ends as I'm in air
Mark it's not one that's all that matters
It's all matters
nothing else matters
But yeah, so I mean I I started to get to that point where I got that first spook the first like big jumping scare
For a second I was like you know what I'm about to hit I'm not I'm gonna escape F9 and I'm not doing it
But that's what I said like you know what I can't give up like I have I'm already like halfway done with like this thing and that is
We'll finish it
When that guy comes out that's oh I'm not gonna ruin it really if you ever do
It's it is it is terrifying
A
Rage quits the game for you too. That's why like at the end of the video
I look like somebody hit me in the face with a wrench after that
I watched more videos of the game because like I wanted to figure out like how it ended or it was more
Yeah, I freaked out cuz
Seriously like
What you saw at the end of that video was like a 100% genuine like my face
I thought I didn't even know what was going on I freaked out and then I was just like wait what happened?
Why am I did me I was genuinely the funnel
Live stream it
Oh
Become known as the stair simulator guy the stair simulator you're on it
Somebody was telling me to do containment breach and I looked up a couple things on it. Oh my god
That just looks it looks it looks ten times worse than SCP. Oh, it's seven the regular one
Oh nice shot. I'm gonna go
Bye
Like that one is like actually 3d like creatures and weird like stuff. We're not really 3d, but it's
I was scared playing Quake 4 so
This is the game you should not be scared playing
Quake 4
Yeah, there's this one room where there's like a giant beating heart and it's really dark
And it took me like 20 minutes to get through but all you have to do is walk up some stairs and like the missions over
I was like just crouch walking the whole time like nope nope
Doing this
Oh, we're gonna get up. I knew that was gonna happen. I knew that was gonna happen
But class what play the most probably engineer
You get actually they'll take a look you know, can I do it from here?
Stats here you go I've actually don't think I've ever shown this I didn't a Q and a one time but these are my team fortress two
Stats
And the reason why spy is so high is cuz back in like 2007
Like that's all I played
Got a spy. I was looking at my stats here today. Now it's disappointed with not much spy I play
Mm-hmm like 35 hours when did I do that when did I waste that much time? Yeah, I have 138 hours to do that
That's nothing though and also this is um I
Think my stats got reset at some point like very early on in the game. Oh, yeah, I reset mine a while. Yeah
God there was one day where I was playing with bots and no one was playing with bots as I go I have to do this
Just got spy spy on spy on spy
Whoa, whoa, no, I didn't want to hit end
All right team. What do you say we do this come on? Let's go baby
We're all here in this together. Yeah
Oh, I'll play spy
spy spy
But I want to be the cool kind of person to play spy I want to be the cool person to fly
Oh, come on. I was trying to did I actually get away with that like I did not I didn't
God I just keep getting people like right when they have no health
How you do it?
I knew I was gonna screw that up new I was gonna screw that up
That attitude
I did a dead space to video well technically, but I technically the grandpa has one on respawn
It's a hole in this straw and I can't drink the rest of my iced tea
They're supposed to be a hole in it. That's how straws work. No, I
Aren't you so glad I'm here?
I am I
It's it's hold on let me fix this stupid straw
There we go I did the I did the best thing I
Flip the straw upside down and put it back in
Genius, I know I am a genius already. I have no idea what we're going
I should have just changed the map to begin with but I was too busy like not paying attention
I hope it's gold rush hopefully it's gold rush stars favorite map
There's like nowhere to jump I love gold rush so much
Actually, I did see one person you can do a jump on a second point second map of gold rush from like start to finish
All the way through with one jump I'd probably just spend the entire round trying to do that
And if I did it our team would win just instantly. It's like getting a nuke
That's like getting a nuke
Somebody asked do I like yeah, I'm using the diamond back because I like it and plus it's strange too
So gotta use it at the strange
I think the diamond back has a bad rap
It's okay. I mean, it's not it's
Like 40 gunslinger and cheese it's yeah
Well, it's part of this way right so the the ambassador and the diamond back can't do the same damage right the
Ambassador shoots slower
The ambassador shoots 20% slower than the diamond back
But you get crits on the headshots. I mean you get crits on this if like you said if there are many centuries around they I would say they're both good
A lot of people really bash on the the diamond back
Well, the best part about the diamond back is the sound. Oh, yeah, so mean technically
It's it's like a better it's a
Default if you're not going for headshots. It's better than the ambassador if you can't get headshots. It's better than the ambassador for sure
The ambassador is still though. It's it's so good. It's so good
Oh, yeah playing that guitar are you
Why am I wearing that like Christmas item?
I got to put my ring on and somebody gave me
I like the Christmas heart thing on
You're just I don't know you're hardy I'm a cold like a thing
I totally forgot the frying pan
frying pan is
There's a mini century
You're gonna take that out
Do rank oh
screenshot post-or-read it
Screen shot screen. So I just screenshot. Why don't I need help am I doing?
Hide behind the cot
Blue open the push get over here get over here. Oh God
All right, here we go I
Want to kill you oh
Oh my god, that was so I'm sorry dude. That was like a face stab in a half don't ask me how that happened
Hmm
I want that medical I want to kill that medic I want that medic to heal me
Now yeah, I'm I'm disguised as you I know I know the deal. Oh, I tried to side stab and it never works because I'm too terrible with spot
What you spent all the hours no like a body block
It's gonna be awesome
Get fear three fear three three being scary. I don't think so hmm. I heard it's pretty I heard it's got it's moments my roommate in college played
He was like a big fan of fear one and two he like praised the game all the time. I just never had time to play it be honest
Align cast I gotta I gotta talk about that I
Will talk about that. I think I want to do it in a proper video though. Not like really in a live stream and wait. That's you
Yeah, I just I shoot you I'm sorry
But pretty much for the just about 400 people watching right now. I will I will give you a snake peek of what's going on?
I'm playing an internament
If those be the no incredible orb
He put together a team. It's an invite only
Tournament for this new game. That's not out yet. I don't even know if I can even say the name of the game. It's like it not even in pre alpha
but this this next weekend
We're gonna be playing a tournament
Me incredible orb and an emerald see stealth and whoever wins that tournament. It's gonna be all streamed total biscuits
Gonna be casting it. It's gonna be pretty ridiculous and
If you win you go to e3 and then if you win that you go to Paris so win we uh, I won't
So
Oh, give me that crit. Give me that crit oh
No, no, please, please. I want to get this crit. Please. Yes. Yes
But yeah, it's not it's not
It's kind of like a quake type game. It's kind of like a quake mod type game
But yeah, it is uh
It is a oh you're gonna get crit right here baby
You do it
But I'm gonna make I'll make a proper video explaining uh
Explaining what it actually is in like a vlog or something in the next couple days
But it's exciting. It's really exciting. I haven't been able to talk about it. So my lips had to be sealed for the last couple weeks
But yeah, maybe we'll get to go to e3
I need to do more secret things
It's like a really hey, I'm doing something I can't talk a bit
I need to do more secrets stuff
Please don't shoot me. Wow that was an amazing shot
Too bad it didn't kill me
Yeah, total biscuit. Uh, yeah, I forget their names. There's three like super super famous guys that are gonna be casting it on Twitch
I don't know their names. I'm a total biscuit. That's it
Well, it doesn't matter. I just did a good rock jump. That's all that matters
What what my my own fire?
What look at this? What's going on? I can't look at this. Why am I on fire right now?
What is that? I've been a boost I
I pulled up the dead ringer and I
Oh, that was I think I just had like a brain fought right there because I pulled the dead ring around when he lit me and
And it worked and then it instantly I why did I come out of it? Do you hear the noise? It was like oh I came out of the dead ringer
But I didn't I was still in it
It is not Renaissance heroes
It is or even online. I'm just gonna like ask him if I can like talk about it
Can I be like hey, can I chat people what I'm doing?
Where's it? It'll go
Yeah, we're very cool for us to
Now young gonna go off spy I'm I'm too stupid right now to go to planning out
Say hello to your Spanured viewers. Hello everybody in Spain. Hope you guys are in that Spanured land
The cool part is I want to go to you three. That's like the main thing is a man
I could really care less about like winning the whole thing. How is you?
I
Can care less about winning like the whole thing, but I do it would be awesome to go to E3
Because then I could make videos and stuff about going to E3 and
It would be so much fun
Wow, that was a wow I am sorry to every single person here that just got covered in that your body that was my fault
Oh
Well, I'm got got quick fixed what am I doing I gotta get up here? What are you doing? Oh?
Damn and oh
Oh
Oh, I
Hear the Christmas bells
Oh
Need ammo
I probably will do more morning streams well not really morning streams, but early afternoon streams on Sunday
Just because I know that Saturday night can a lot of people can't watch it and I am sorry about that
Oh
Every time I see somebody in the air I always think it's you and I get scared
Every time
Anytime you're in anyone's in the air I
Keep thinking it's you and it freaks me out
It's perfect
Spawn to spawn
Belly to belly the from for jump oh
Belly to belly you know what that's from back to back belly to belly. I think it's from where
Where in the world is Carmen Sandiego? I've really think it is the game show the old game show
Somebody please look that up somebody find that out for me right now
I that show is unwatchable. I wouldn't know
There is there is he's going for those garden kills
No
Three two
Hi, sir. Hey
Wait that wasn't you it wasn't no it's actually I know a looter you like where's the same hat as me
Those are my oh my god. I thought it was I thought it was you. I was like oh my god. Oh no, it was me. I already got you
Star stars sounds a bit robotic. He said he's a his internet's going up and down. So sorry
Not anymore though you sound fine now. Okay good
Have I killed one person this like entire time? How do I have 18 points?
What what did I do did I kill anybody? I guess so I don't even like remember killing anyone
I did a jump
My mommy was proud
Well, I my I got up my cat is like scratching
I probably have
One of if not the most annoying cats in the world
See he he knows my window when it's open he knows he can come over and annoy me by just going like
Until I gum let him in and if I don't let him in he will sit there
He probably wouldn't even eat or sleep until I let him in like through like the window
Yeah, he kiddin and it's like you know there's another way you can go right that you can't get in my window
He just knows I'll let him in
Always leave it open
This is what time is right now
That's the real question
I don't know
Probably another round or two on TF and I think I'm gonna transition to some Diablo free
Diablo some Diablo
Cuz I gotta get by which doctor up in
I think we're still the same 45 I did level up a bit
One a second
Are there
There's not random crits on right now is there nope
Was that it cuz like I got I was uber charts he wasn't Chris create
That was weird I got killed by a crit man. No, no, no, no, no, you know, it probably was like a fuck banner
That peepie probably was the peepie banner
Peep banner that I'm gonna get headshot
Oh my god, you both just like came in at the same time and I missed
Let's go you're
Let's go
What I'm with that thing what the Thomas love yeah, just how do you aim?
It's too hard. I love the Thomas love. It's my favorite
It's too hard
Gaming is hard
Yeah, star does make rocket jumping look so much fun. He also makes it look really easy too, and it is absolutely not
One of the best videos I've ever seen of team fortress two is that video where you jumped
to do
Where you jumped across like the whole thing a high tower and man tread in some pyro it was unbelievable
That wasn't even that good. Oh, it was the best. I don't even know
When I finally put all these hard gardener goes together
Well, when you finally put this box garden thing together I
It's probably gonna get like 700 million views. It's gonna be that good
The bomb is nearing a checkpoint
I hide oh
Man, hey you did
Somebody where I can't believe I'm watching a YouTube stream that's working
that
They're yeah YouTube streams are well, they're in beta. So there is always gonna be a lot of problems
But you know whatever it's all good
And who's the other guy that is star I'm a guy that is STAR
Thank you for spelling it
Haha
Some somebody write stars channel in the in the comments section just so the people that don't know will know
It's youtube comm slash niched
N.i.c.hts right yes, you're very good at spelling
Usually I'm pretty bad
Some I know you're gonna win this tournament because I'm guaranteeing it's a spelling bee. That's why I don't want to talk about it
Oh my god get at it
Just on your head. Oh, it's so scary. I
Like don't know like what to do. There's like spies this rocket gardening stars and
Third guy, that's like another star. That's doing it
Like heavy. I don't have any diagnoses that I could smoke
Oh, he's a pro like a pro chip pro tip as heavy on car if you being a car-heavy do it do the crouch dance
You gotta go like do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do?
You gotta like crouch.
Grouch.
You gotta be-
You're gonna win because I think I've convinced my team not to try it all off.
You see like the pyro walking out there.
We're taking it easy.
Haha.
Uh-uh.
Card heavy is fun.
Yeah, okay.
It is.
Card heavy is fun.
Oh, to jump is card heavy.
You gotta get the new rocket launcher for the heavy.
The best you could do is like, um, gloves of running urgently jumps.
Here we go, ready?
I'll show you how to rocket jump as a heavy.
See, look at how far I just went.
Oh no, I'm almost out of my large Dunkin' Donuts fresh brewed iced tea.
That's not a good thing.
Get another.
I mean, I have to drive to Dunkin' Donuts.
I wish I could get a Dunkin' Donuts in my house.
Get it?
Get a Dunkin' Donuts.
Just buy a franchise.
Just own it.
Just so you can live in it.
I would- I would.
If I find a house, I think I'm not even really a big coffee drinker.
I as I love iced tea.
And their iced tea is really, really, really good.
Oh dear god.
Hey, awesome.
Maybe I should shoot some things.
I think I'm gonna shoot some things.
Oh yeah?
Yeah.
I got a ghost reacon and they gave me hats.
Ghost reacon?
Yes.
So now the classes I'm allowed to play in this is to rocket jumping soldier or one of
the classes I got a hat.
Is that game any good?
It's not out yet.
It's out in like a week.
Oh, it's actually looking really good.
Yeah, I heard it's supposed to be pretty intense.
They're going in a different direction, aren't they?
It's kind of funny that a ghost reacon is, I love the first one.
And they have dumbed down the series a lot since then and usually that would like piss
me off to no end.
For some reason this time I'm glad ghost reacon is dumb.
Well, it's like the one game I'm happy about that it's dumb.
It wasn't the ghost recon series very, very strategic.
Like you had a very hard time planning groups and this one, I mean it has all of that,
but for the most part you know it's not going to happen.
Right, right.
It's kind of like TF2.
Hmm.
When I watch like trailer, I think I'm rising big years of war a little bit like that kind
of, it's like third person running around.
Yeah, it's got that third person vibe to it.
It's definitely, it has like all the wall hugging mechanics that you guys would have.
But I don't actually want this game since the first of it showing single player trailers
of it, but multiplayer looks pretty fun.
I love fun things.
Yeah, definitely.
I love fun stuff.
I throw to P.P.
Alright, we'll do...
I cannot get on that car.
What am I doing?
Why did I just pull that out?
I'm going to die.
Why, what do I have this on for?
Not this, it's a steal.
I need to put those on.
Remember, you keep running in a circle, I know.
I know.
That's what happens when I live stream.
I'm like, my two centers in my brain fight for dominance.
And I just like, lock out in circle, what happened?
Now we get a wrangled, essentially, that is Yikes.
I think that's a spy.
Oh, I missed my melee swing because I was in his body.
Where's this other guy?
Wait, sandwich, take it.
Yeah.
Come this way, come this way.
We're going to go up, we're going to go up top.
And...
Oh!
Get on the car!
Hey, oh.
And come on, somebody touch it!
I should have stayed behind it.
Yeah, but you didn't.
You know, I'm stupid.
One more round after this, and then we'll move on to some...
Dwia below three.
Okay.
Oh.
Take that.
And...
I showed you a grade A.
That's it, no time.
Oh, my...
I should have given this sandwich, my poor, medic friend.
Let's be close, I was...
No!
I warned you.
It was essentially a warning.
New reg.
I'm sufficient.
Kind of lethal.
It's getting there.
Oh, God's by.
A spa.
Yes, this will be on YouTube.
And...
When I finish the stream, it'll probably be up there after maybe an hour to a processing.
So...
We assume, what time is it right now?
It's 9.30am for me.
Probably streamed for another couple hours or so.
At least another hour.
And...
It should be up by maybe...
New-nish, maybe?
Yeah, so...
Does it upload things if they're really long?
That's what it says.
I talked to some people and they said that apparently that's not true.
That's not the case.
Yeah, I guess they just lie to you.
It's like, oh, you can't upload a automatic stream longer than two hours and then people
do it.
So I don't know.
I guess they would want to discourage everyone.
I don't know.
Yeah.
It's weird.
It's very weird.
Someone said, since when is Herb Lurga a warning?
Herb Lurga.
It is.
Yeah, yeah, I could be seen as a warning.
Well, what else do you think I'm going to do if I'm screaming at it?
Besides...
I'm either on the toilet or about to kill you.
Oh man, they have too many things going on in there.
Watch out for me.
Yeah, you take the sandwich.
You need it.
Dude, eat sandwich.
I'm going to go around.
It's all about...
They only have a mini-century, man.
We're getting pushed back by a mini-sense.
It's all about...
They only have a mini-century, man.
We're getting pushed back by a mini-century and like a bunch of devil men.
Oh god, I'm so dead.
Oh god.
Why do I not have these out?
Somebody ask?
All right, here we go.
Here we go.
There we go.
Come on.
Somebody help me.
I shot you with my gun.
It was a bomb gun.
A bomb gun, is that new?
Yeah.
I hope I get it.
Cool.
I'm...
I'm probably not going to switch servers, but some of you guys are asking only because
the stars in here and I wouldn't want it to be like, oh, we both can't get into the
same server.
And plus I'm on my server, so I like playing on my server because I like playing with
the dudes on my server because they're cool.
So one more, we say.
Let's go to...
No, no, no, no.
Let's go to good old gold rush.
No, please, no.
All right, finally, fine.
Well, then I'm trying to like figure out how to like do something fun.
Ah!
Nrrrr.
I slapped you.
I got you.
You need to rapid fire that.
Oh, you can do that?
Yeah, if you just keep mashing the button, you can get slapped so much it like pops you
up in the air.
Hold you there.
All right, let's go.
Oh, you're going to be mad, but I kind of want to play on Turbline.
You know what, as long as I don't know, I just want to gel, man.
Turbine.
I guess Turbine has stairs.
I just love Turbine.
I love a lot of things, don't I?
Should have played 2-4.
2-4.
But Turbine's like the good 2-4, doesn't it?
No, the 2-4 is the best 2-4.
Oh, I'll stick them all night.
Oh, it's my spray.
Ah, Derma.
Oh.
This hero now hates you.
Gary Monster.
Look what you did.
What I do.
What happened?
What I do?
You picked this map.
So there's a ceiling on this map.
There's nowhere that does not have a ceiling.
Yeah, but you could do like an off the wall kind of like move, can't you?
Yeah.
I don't know, I'll ask him.
Star, are you going to play Diablo 3 as well?
Yeah, sure.
T-Milion.
Okay.
Oh, I hear a dog.
I think that might be my dog.
My dog.
Oh, my God, a sentry.
A strategy to turbine hold mid-wind game.
Oh.
How are you still?
Oh, you get an overview.
Makes sense.
Oh, damn it.
I was trying to go for a top kill on that.
I'm going to walk into corner.
Why is this respawn so long?
I changed that.
It's respawned.
I'm respawned by time, right?
You can't.
It's too turbine.
You could change the respawn.
Easy can.
I don't know.
I have my respawned wave time at two.
Isn't that supposed to be God, crits?
I thought I was going to bite my ankles in a second.
He's probably going to run here.
Oh, come on.
I want my crits.
Let grandpa play Diablo.
I don't think he would get it.
I think he'd be too confused.
There's too many numbers to deal with in Diablo.
You don't just shoot people.
Well, that's why they made numbers off by default.
And you know advanced tool tips.
People like him.
What just happened?
All right, so I charged with the charging charge.
And right when I clicked right click, I got backstabbed.
And my body just like baseball slid across like the whole map.
I love getting backstabbed.
It's right as you're I could jump and your body just poof.
It's God.
Boom.
Okay.
Let me say.
Let me find some dude to run into here.
Here's a mini-century.
Mm-hmm.
Help me.
I'm real ice-wear.
That's a sticky.
That's me getting shot.
Hi, right here.
I know a secret.
What?
And then you just what?
I was going to work on my secret technique.
And 20 seconds.
Hold on a minute.
Oh, actually, I was about to type in the server password.
It's like, hold on.
Let me just type my arcon password right now in front of like 400 people.
Okay.
No big bad idea.
20, that's too long.
20 seconds.
It's supposed to be like nine.
Come on.
Oh, it was turbine.
Oh, I had a knockback.
Get over here.
It is morning.
It is nine.
Just about 10 a.m. here in the East Coast United States.
Oh, I've got it.
I thought it.
Oh, he only had like 2% health left.
10% 20, whatever.
It killed a guy.
This is why we can't have nice things.
Please, German.
Just please 1, 2, 4.
I think 2, 4 is, maybe I took it out of the rotation.
All right.
How about this?
Before I leave, I will switch the map to 2, 4.
How's that sound?
That does not sound good.
Yeah, this guy does.
Oh, my God.
That guy did not know that was coming.
Yeah, he was too busy hitting me.
Remember, if you crouch and just stand still when you're in a melee fight,
one-on-one, you're probably going to win.
Because people freak out too much.
They run around, they go, oh, it's this.
And hey, open that door.
Whoa.
I'm going to get the intelligence.
You know what, screw this.
Oh, never mind.
He already got it.
Good job, he's got it.
Good job, dude.
You typed 25 comments and haven't gotten a cheeseburger yet?
I think there's a YouTube bug.
You should have already gotten at least three cheeseburgers dispensed from your laptop.
Are you reading?
Well, just on the chat.
The stream.
How do you do that?
It's just, you make a...
I used to be all the time, sorry, I can't even speak.
To where stuff going on?
I'm sure I'm doing it.
You just do update comments automatically, and they'll come in as they come in.
I think there's still a minute or so behind, though, that's the thing with YouTube.
This isn't even pro-terbine.
There's no banana.
Pro-terbine?
Yeah.
And pro-terbine, there's a banana.
Is it really?
Well, they call it banana, but it's like a different path on the side.
It's shaped like a banana.
You should get a double cheeseburger.
You should come out of your...
out of your CD trade.
Every 25 comments that you make on the stream.
A double cheeseburger from your favorite restaurant comes out of your CD trade.
I don't have a CD trade.
That's probably why it's not working.
Yeah.
If you don't have a CD trade...
Oh, it's a zip drive, too.
You have to have a zip drive.
Oh god.
Daaaaaayyyy.
Why am I still equipped?
Why is it still out?
Why do I still have this out?
What am I doing?
I can't believe I got away with that.
Oh, right, come on.
I can't believe I got away with that, either.
I can't believe what you've always been doing.
Oh, that was a brigade.
Oh, I'm at the end of my drink.
You know what that means?
It's timed it.
This thing's like floating.
What the hell?
your cheeseburger had blue cheese sounds pretty dang good all right star you
ready I got a question for you oh god what is oh one more round we'll do one
more please all right fine we'll switch all right we'll go to start with star what
map do you want to play jump tricks do you want to play the jump map I don't
think I have it installed all right you need to be like in like the team fortress
database thank you
like frontier frontier yeah I love that a lot and here we go
you cheeseburger had a green bun that's definitely a big thing oh yeah I
forgot the thing I was gonna ask you probably was really really important
yeah one round of frontier and that'll end the team fortress the day and it
will bond the apple tree for a little while I was trying to think of good
stock payload maps that aren't upward and my mind just blanked and I said frontier
all right ready ready to let's go let's go blue go blue I'm gonna play
netic because I kind of feel like it I like this setup I'm gonna stick with it
except I don't want the crits query gotcha I want the default meady gun there we go you
gotta keep control of your TV you have snipers humping the door
spray mission begins in 500 seconds
that would be nice there's a sign out here that's a speed limit 15 speed limit 15
but but but but but but but but
pal five four three two
30 so have you guys been able to hear the in-game audio like the explosions and
stuff or is that been too low I'm always so afraid to turn that up because I
feel like it's gonna overpower everything I said I think I'm gonna get
crits which is perfect because then how could I possibly miss a market card
right I'm gonna give this to I don't know
go with the uh now he's are doing one go this way oh my god oh god oh god
well come here come here oh god work where where good where good you're good I'm not oh
no I was brought I was my hand my right click and you drop over my right click was
clicking on the Uber it was like and I got back step
you know that got oh no that's you I can't believe that no work
I don't even know if it was you because there was like three medics maybe two I can
count give me that over give me that over
all right I got I'm not gonna look now I better watch out doing it right away come on
heavy and team over I'm hiding everyone is safe now
come on give me another rubber oh god two spies that's not gonna work I'm in
my head right now spies spy spy help me no stay alive this guy oh my god you
were about to die oh I'd use it that was really early I was
to say I know you this guy oh yeah well look what we just did we just came
like we did a good job well I saw this guy only had like one percent health and if I
didn't use it he would have died and it was only me and a sniper behind him so when
with the next grandpa video be uploaded it was uploaded last night with Shinema
Riesman so on the feature video list go check it out I actually to be honest I'm
sorry I didn't even like I didn't even let anybody know that was there I'll do
that today happy this is over this is bad the tension what do I know I guess I do
have two kills no come here Mark let me hear you
oh backed up into a knife somebody wants me to say a dirty word hidden it's hidden
in like a regular sentence I know that I know that trick that's a dirty trick
if you chat is frozen trying to refresh the page
reexact re only what is it re-equipped re-exact the config
how you health I need you to help me please oh this thing is so good I love this
thing doesn't seem like much but the overdose doesn't seem like much but it is it
really helps in situations a lot of situations it's not that much it is no
you need it's the boot solider yeah but then you start to take damage like you you
don't get the full plus the one you just had to make sure you hit every needle but that's
too hard and you are gonna land right on my face now if you're gonna back up like a
punk not gonna like what you don't want to die see like I'm running fast
you're gonna back up all right I'm going for a team move right here we're gonna we
get a push up it's not gonna be a single man effort right now oh no oh did I just
totally block you from that I actually apologize if I could probably wouldn't
miss anyway I'm missing like every swing given you a first saw no I don't want to die
that's a spy that's a spy that's a spy definitely is no it's not
honest thing be careful
I thought that was I know not that anything but the little full camera anything but the
full camera come here scout come here don't run away
oh everybody needs health and there's nothing like watch don't die there's a guy behind you
oh push that up oh yeah get on this this mini century oh I'm dead goodbye
goodbye cruel world you got chicken out of the terrain that's that's not supposed to
happen there's only supposed to be cheeseburgers meet and cheese catch up onion
mustard relish why am I going this way I always do that on upward I always go the
wrong way upward support the little guy hashtag that's that's my
philosophy and apparently grandpa 30th century set up you guys have a lot of
stuff over there you don't even know yet because it's set up like four miles away
you need a time to prepare and put it in a really really lame century spot so
lame lame everything's lame I backed up into another life
backed up back it up
that's the way you are up top there and I'm gonna die man these spies are
really making me paranoid there's like 40 hundred of them I mean two
this one back here somewhere oh there is well I was gonna heal that guy too my
god I am not turning my back I'm gonna face this way the whole time see I know it
get out of that oh overdose you are my friend it's all in your mind yeah but even
if it is all my mind it still still makes me get that extra mile in your mind oh
by god I can't heal y'all trying all right let's push this thing
somebody get up there
there we go there we go there we go push little wagon
you're prepared for lame century are you mentally ready for this
is there like a bunch there sorry sorry it's by I got you I got you I'll make
sure you have a nice thick overheal by the time you get out here and by the time
I'm not afraid to leave which is right now there's a lot of people here oh
no no no heal me heal me please oh dammit I'm gun that was pretty nice run though I
I'm proud of that little run proud people say you should try to pan me I am missing every
single mark garden oh that was a glitch
that's why that's not why it looks like he's running slow I was weird
yeah I gotta get up move up move up no come here move that gear up always our
century young oh damn leave it is we got three medics too we should be pushing this
cart like crazy you need 14 heavies really have one and there was his
spine right there that pyro I'm waiting for him to come over here mine here he's
no head either where's his head where's this guy's head yeah I've been noticing that a lot
lately is that just on spies yeah if a spy disguises as a pyro and they're wearing a certain
hat it can't display the hat oh she's or something like that oh god I that got his
Uber at the same time as me we just both over the same guy at the same time
damn I'm going I'm going for it I'm going for some not so stuff right here what I'm
slaper because we had none now we have three I could say higher number that guy only needed one hit and I didn't get it
what movies what films my planet on seeing probably I still haven't seen the Avengers I have to see the
avengers have you seen that star yep is it was it good yes I know it's good because there's explosions
but I had like a two hour long conversation with someone about why it's terrible really
just nothing makes sense if you watch it you need to question everything that happens and say why
use this happening and you will realize you don't know nobody knows the avengers I don't really
watch a lot of movies to be honest dark night yeah that's definitely one I mean yeah you have to see
that though that this is pretty much it's pretty much a moral obligation for every human being to
watch the crystal and all of that man movies like at least you know you're ubering a spy yeah I know
I'm aware of that I realize that like about two or three seconds into that uber I just thought I'd let you know
yeah I realized it because I realized especially when you ran the other direction when I ubered
him when he turned left and like went backwards I was like wait I did fight that way what are you doing
you could just have uber phobia good do I read me books I do not don't really actually I take that back
I read some time I read like graphic novels does that count that does not count but there's
words in there let's look at ones uh dug to napel that makes good one
oh
dug to napel makes great great graphic novels the earth where mj guy oh I didn't know he did that
yeah they're pretty good at least like the art is very very interesting really awesome
I got you I got you ball and calling
you need help more than anybody I'll make sure to get you oh my god all right you know
know my medic knit his pyro time I'm gonna see my backpack here you go it's kind of all over the
place right now ever since I gave everything away I don't have anymore like cool hats
okay I should stop stop doing this and actually shoot bullets
oh I gotta take that teleporter am I doing
spies spies I don't know match for the pyro
oh
I gotta go step sometimes no no no no no no no no
oh come on what have you even gone from I have zero unusuals
ah bad player
yeah I don't know how would you guys are winning more well we only have one minute
that's pretty much the end right there do I still like the gorillas oh my god yes
girl is there the best band like ever we're not gonna win this this is too much too much good stuff
happening on it as a center we lost it's over it is over so in that in that case you know you
always got to do this you always got to go spy the skies as an enemy heavy or something well you
know I'm gonna play I'm gonna go scout just so I can run away I'm gonna I'm gonna take the coward
way out why am I taking the teleporter to go so this is where we transition what oh what
what can we maybe maybe I think yeah it's over it's over I have to move on to some Diablo 3
oh my god are we gonna find items or gold hopefully gold because I need more no we lost
yeah just please I hope I don't find any items just get me we lost it yeah
oh well thanks guys for playing if you got in thank you and time to transition to Diablo 3 if
you just came if you're wondering oh but it's over no it's this is all gonna be on YouTube later
on today so yeah thanks playing dudes let's go on to Diablo 3 this is where we go disconnect
we go it's quick yes oh do you sure I don't know how to have replays I don't want to lose
all right so now Diablo 3
super money and I combat I've it's I can't I can't get into it it's I don't know what it is
I'm not sure I have a couple of friends now that are really starting to enjoy it but I just can't
I don't know why they did just add a new game mode which is weird it's kind of like realism I guess
where everybody dies quicker really yeah I just I need to get into it at some point maybe I'm
not sure yet but is this even in the right spot like it is not quite hold on I'm gonna screen
I gotta go black for a second dudes you can even rocket jump in that game and I still don't
like it that much so I don't know what else there could be to encourage me to play um maybe hats
oh there are hats then yeah that's a good way to play screen region Diablo 3
is that and you know you can stream with DX story and it's better in screen region
really yeah whoa stream exception oh my god do you use DX story oh yeah yeah you do yeah I do I don't
stream with it though you should oh my good god every time I try to do a stupid window right now
it'll be magic all right I'm gonna try this one more time because this is being ridiculous
okay stream exception media that was just like I felt like I was looking through a tunnel right
there that might like I'm gonna like puke okay love of everything that is sacred can we get this
in the right spot yes you're story telling you but the X-Tory is expensive okay that's good enough
good enough good enough
all right nobody like steal my password
stolen hacked nobody steal my stuff because I have like a book I have like really good stuff
no I don't all right I'm on nightmare oh you like my like what you talk to name burglar
he's the burglar are you and I in a game I'm not in a game I'm on X3 nightmare no that's
I'm further than that well you have to come help me okay you have to okay sure everything's on
I'm sure you don't want to just kill asthma and 4,000 times that's right
now we're gonna make this game where you don't have to run the same bosses open over again
then we're gonna make asthma and give you all the experience every single cent of experience
I want in my bank account so for holon I gotta get over like the Diablo 3 lag for the first two
minutes and just like doing random moves I wonder I you know this gotta be a reason why that
happens it has to be because it's syncing you up with like the DRM or something like that it has
to be I don't know but you need to invite me that's right star invite to party invite to the party
yeah and now I'm gonna reject it be cool but please be like friend
nah turn burglar
the turn burglar that I was I made his name burglar because of like burgaboy
oh yeah little legs yeah you gotta get rid of the you gotta get rid of the initial lag of Diablo 3
oh who hooray all right I think we can do it
well it's the the reason why it lags is even when I'm not streaming when I'm just playing
just by myself the first like two or three minutes every time you play Diablo 3 for some reason
it just does this yeah do a new move and it's like wait what is this yeah you have to like let it
load Diablo 3 or anything it's sort it's sort of like Minecraft that's like the only way I can
really make an assumption to what it's kind of like you know Minecraft is like when you first
start playing it's like loading every single thing in the world see like no I have to load all this
stuff it'll leave it out in a minute I promise oh I did level a lot more of you I didn't even
yeah all in all I'm still like you know it's a good game um medium pizza medium a large cheese pizza yes
well pizza now let's go let's go with the lag
all right I want to get some rays some unique
thanks
all the people still people people are still seeing extreme exception no they're not in this
whereas that's just an old comment from somebody from a while back
I don't shoot arrows anymore I'm taking all the stuff on people still in there seeing
shouldn't be
well let me watch my own stream make sure nothing's happening
you should stream with the x story I gave the recommendation I mean I should
stream the stocks added teach you in two seconds every every time I stream when I did the
exploit game stream thing for some reason I don't know why it like it lags it lags really
really terribly oh no we're not getting streamception it looks okay what about 720
that looks okay too okay just making sure nothing was happening it's probably the youtube
comment system like all slow and dumb that's what it is so I'm playing which doctor
which doctor is very fun very good very cool
I am shooting bombs bombs
this is actually pretty cool build with demon hunter I found out that we just regenerate hatred
like ridiculous amounts of it you could use cluster arrow nonstop really that's true I was
amazing that's pretty cool pretty damn cool pretty snazzy pretty snazzy this guy's an elite in these
did he kill my little buddy oh he's back onward
I'm feeling maybe I shouldn't even be helping you my I don't know I've got it's 5300 damage it
feels wrong but I need the help get out of here huh already a rare really didn't think this
happened I thought it was just gonna be the sea of blue but I want one what do I think of the
spider-man reboot I think it's um not out yeah it's not out I mean I don't know I thought it was
gonna be like a Christopher Nolan type reboot but it's kind of everything's like I'll see GIE and stuff
I don't want to see it but I don't know man I'll probably see it just do some else leave
spider-man alone oh I'll probably watch it to be honest I was a big spider-man man I love the
first movie second one was good too oh boy hopefully uh this time they do anything with venom
even later on well please not like a total debag anything like that venom I have a cool face
and giant teeth but I pull my mask back to talk thanks yeah I didn't really like the way they
handled venom either it was kind of lack of luck I'm mad at you because you took my girlfriend or
something I don't remember what his deal was wasn't he also in the only in the movie for like
25 minutes the actual venom like symbiote monsters like that's less than that and the way he
beats him is like oh I gotta humiliate a guy like that why you gotta be like I thought you were a
good guy spider-man if you guys want to see my ruins I'll give you a little looksy looksy do
so this is poison I'm using poison dart and fire bats and I have it so it's just pretty much
pure damage so if you take a look poison dart I have it so it's then the the fire one so it just
doesn't more just straight up damage every time you hit somebody that is leveled up apparently oh I'm
sorry then fire bats I have the poison ones actually I got a new one I have ferrets hmm I'll stick with
the poison ones for now I think ferrets yeah I got the gargantuan the one that goes crazy when there's
more than a few people around yeah I got oh yeah yeah yeah so harvest because it is just
too good for not having intelligence is it giving you now 102 for every enemy affected so I get
I can get a fire like 550 and intelligence if I get five people oh it's that's a lot mask
confusion and then spirit walk mask confusion makes everyone hit themselves pretty much and spirit
walk is just amazing because it makes you pretty much unkillable you just go like this you go
and you run around very very awesome so do you have ferrets I don't I don't have ferrets
on let me turn on my uh ferrets make this a little my GPU fan a little higher like okay just to make sure
all right we're gonna go we're gonna find this is the spider lady isn't it um yeah she's down
away still now we we missed her we missed her all right if you were just here for the TF2 then take
it easy man thank you come
give me this gold my ferrets they pick up gold for me do they really the most yeah the most important
skill in the game it's pick up gold that is a really important skill because you have to like
go move over and run over and then crease gold fine just for being ferrets like I didn't know
ferrets did that but they're rolling in it rolling in those ferrets
so we went the wrong way it's Diablo 3 that's the name of the game in D3 going the wrong way it
almost feels sometimes like it generates the map as you go somewhere like go you went this way
looks generated so many little spider freaks oh god come on go get him got ganchoan
so though we were talking about the ganchoan the little buddy that I have for a pet
and we we can't have the conclusion that this is what he's doing so I'll try and do the voice
I don't know if we get it through the spite
so ready so this is look at how like cutie is so ready just like
fresh fresh that's the noise he's making when he runs
and he's got a diaper to be that you run I hit this guy I help you
I'm out at her I just feel like he's big dumb cute but I'm gonna die doesn't it lead right here
it's okay I'll hold you yikes
confusion all right let's get a rare so yeah I thought I had a really cool skill that
could rival your mask confusion because it knocks everything back for like 10 seconds really it
doesn't work on rares the really like all rares are immune to knockback that's kind of
vs yeah I was kind of gonna go like all knockback demon under there's Diablo 2
I probably still am it's just kind of like that rares are gonna be like this okay you might get one
back up a little bit
hey jamer can you make a shout out to edgel like in the stream just say your name
what's up edgel
I think it's around edgel edgel waffles yes
oh god yes please I actually don't like waffles I go waffles at least I know I know that's
blasphemy I know like Belgium waffles are better naturally I mean
I mean
I you know waffles are just two it's almost like too much it's too doughy ready for me
same thing with pancakes I'm not a big pancake person either wow
I did not need to know that about you I don't think anyone need to know that about you
like everyone is leaving the stream right now because I said that
yeah well what's the point of watching this if this guy doesn't even like pancakes I thought we
could like bond on some sort of human level but apparently not I thought we were gonna be friends
well why would I want to be friends with you now I need help do I have any potions that I'm not
using I gotta run back to town real quick you don't like pancakes unsubbed no I love pancakes come
back I was only joking you know I the only pancakes I like are are chocolate chip pancakes that's it
everything else I'm not a big fan of are you just like trying to run your name into the ground
but chocolate chip pancakes are really good what's wrong with that chocolate chip pancakes this
is a breakfast food we were talking about yeah you want to put chocolate chips in would you put
like chocolate chips and scrambled eggs and be like oh good idea yeah but scrimp eggs are like eggs
then they're not like pancakes are sweet you know all right let me let me give you a rebuttal
would you put cheese on your pancakes I'm sure that wouldn't be that bad I don't think so I don't
know about that what does cheese go badly with besides chocolate chips I'm like a glass of
chocolate milk feel like put easy cheese in it well besides anything chocolate
well when does chocolate go bad you you just made my point for me
I'm trying to say chocolate doesn't go with anything wait this is just eat chocolate
chocolate ice cream chocolate milkshake chocolate straw berries yeah all by
the point is I'm right I just said I just have to go back to town again because I forgot I've
went hit a buy potions and I didn't chocolate chip pancakes that's the best part about the
apple three is what is your time to consider the important parts of life that we weren't talking
about this one playing TF2 but now we're down to the root well now we have a little it's a little
more laid back we get some time to discuss things laid back it's a little more laid back I would
consider this more serious this is so serious it's Diablo here I am clicking on things and you're
in town clicking on things is the most serious thing I've ever done my life oh snake oh well
whatever I'm just gonna come meet you yeah this is act three nightmare if you guys are wondering
this is the character I don't have this character in hell he's only 46 he's little
and you are I had I need to come up and find you yeah I figured you'd spawn on me
well I don't assume that I'm that intelligent okay sorry I've never been to Comic Con I kind
I want to go it would be really fun oh there's an elite right there not cool yeah
that guy Comic Con is really interesting because it's isn't Comic Con not just like
comics it's like pretty much about everything isn't it kind of a little bit everything they have
a lot of movie stuff there too and I don't know I could have gone once but I didn't I might go to
one eventually this one on in New York right New York and in Chicago I probably go to the New York
one like you had the chance if I had like the money did that's the most important thing
go into all these events it cost money and that's just money that I don't have
oh my god Gancho I need more health I only have like 11000 or so I have 12000
somebody wants to know treasure if you're gonna oh god treasure goblin really get him get him
buy some blues no no no this is not good at all mask confusion get him they're oh god this is just
chaos he's dead oh he dropped a rare yay nightmare rare oh I'm about to die oh run away run away run away
run away totally there I'm gonna jail you and then mortar you so what I was gonna say is somebody
wants to know if you're gonna continue your let's play they want to know there because they want
to see the whole story they said oh of Diablo 3 yeah I was gonna upload one last night actually did
upload one apparently never finished rendering so it was like a fourth of a video that's the worst
thing see this video the one that right when this is the stream is done once it gets uploaded to
YouTube it is gonna take like two hours to process it's just like yeah yeah I wish there was a way
we did a full circle we did but that's we need to XP and we need to add them to oh I didn't even
identify the but oh this is one hander oh oh this is not a posterity on it though but this is
actually pretty good do you want to I have this thing that I found it's a blue so you know it's good
go over here do you want to look at this is this thing better than what you have I know I mean
you could maybe use that oh geez that's not better that thing is not better I will sell it
um I'm I'm gonna be losing like 2000 life I put this on but I'm gonna gain a ton of damage
damage always need damage that's 2000 health I'm gonna lose but you know what it's worth it to do
almost a thousand more damage it's up blue we'll do it yeah we'll do it and temporarily I'm just
gonna put a uh did this gem into it all right lost a bunch of health so I'm gonna be an absolute
whoops I have pants too maybe one pants pants I don't need pants what do I oh god these way better
than what I have again I'm gonna be losing health oh oh well bad I'm losing health who cares
put this in there for no just to have it in there for now all right what's that
you know what's all this what do you drop in I want to look
but imagine if this is what the elbow three was we just stand in place and items fall what's this
we know what's that what's this what's this this magic in the air what's this what's this
all right 20 germapoints do whoever figures out what that song is for up
that's the only remember what you can buy germapoints
I don't think anything to be on but you can still buy a salad you can buy a germap salad
but 15 germapoints don't sell it germapoints give it to me there's probably chocolate chips in the
germapoints I don't know if people want it you know I can't believe that you uh that you don't like
chocolate chip pancakes that's that's that's unbelievable I've never actually had them just because
the thought of that is absolutely rare disgusting disgusting chocolate chip oh it's an off-hand
hold on oh man oh man gosh she got oh I can't I don't have time to look at that but I think it's
better I'm a witch doctor I am a witch doctor star is a demon hunter we're two best friends in
Diablo three I hunt demons except sometimes they help me make sense makes sense
the bones I carry a bow and confusion mask confusion everyone's not fight each other
oh my god too much it's a good thing you don't have that health
good thing I could need it I could need it I could use it oh we got the lead watch out we got
it lead any he's got that pole move any slows you down that's just fantastic he did
he has all the things he dropped any yeah those of you that said nightmare before Christmas
you uh you are a winner you get my right I'm gonna I'm gonna put my hand up the screen right now
and it's a high five oh hey come here hey fuck fuck where you go what's that
wait where do you keep finding these I don't know floor how come I'm not finding these and
oh it's way better than what I have thank you that did not just find so many items I don't know what you do
uh no where there it is 231947 intellect it's way better but it's way yeah critical hit chance though
it's got 2.5% crit on it this does not have it but oh hey what's your amulet I'll inspect you I'll
inspect you I'm gonna put this on I'm gonna put a vitality gem in that because I I'm under 10k
health right now is awful just like this amulet tell me if you're like interested and you can
just have it anyway all right like seriously you have just replaced like six pieces of my gear
okay the critical hit damage this this I have a rare on 30 what do you think 30% more crit damage
or extra health and a little bit more damage how much are you critting with mask confusion um 10
million I think I'm gonna leave it on because I do pretty big crits with poison dart
it's the treasure google
hmm
what I recommend getting d3 compared to d2 hmm I probably not there is this really good game
called you know I think this is treasure goblin where's he why is all his money over here
why was that money right there where's this goblin that was the goblin like
go you know um d2 is one of my favorite games ever made so I'm very very biased when it comes
to comparing the obelotu and the obelotary but the obelotu I mean this game is awesome
man I'm playing it right now I've I've dumped a ton of time into it but if you were a huge fan of
the obelotu then it's if you saw I did a review on this game already it's on the channel but
it's it's kind of a left-down in the item department at least as of right now they're gonna
apparently they're gonna maybe potentially look at legendaries because where it stands right now
a legendary item can be potentially worse than a blue which is that's just just shouldn't be
happening but for the most part I mean if you've never played a Diablo game this is a perfect time
to get into it because this game is just it's a very streamlined it's very fond very addicting
I say yes go buy go buy it if you've never if you've never played Diablo before and you want to
then check it out for sure it's awesome
star oh god oh my god oh my god oh my god too many blue oh no oh my god my friend my my god
I can't you would he died now he almost it he grew stabilizers you did to have like when you go home
with your witch doctor on the wall you need to put notches on the wall for how high or gargantuan
girls well I want to look at something real quick give me one second okay oh hide and corner
with you how far behind is this dream like this three like I think this I think my 720 stream is
like seven years behind that happens oh let me let me take a look at this
because that's like so people are still like just answering that nightmare before Christmas and that
was like five minutes ago so I want to see I want to see just how far back it is
somebody said 15 seconds actually no the youtube comment system is probably just bugged like it
always is I probably said that before yeah oh why am I I'm watching an ad ad
adception right there ads on top of ads on top of ads they're advertising an ad go watch this ad
please go watch this ad on top of this ad on top of this ad go watch this ad
there are many to stop Dan from let me see let me see go watch this ad on top of this ad
you're go watch this ad my hatred is too low for this
yeah I guess if you are behind on 720 then oh my god what am I dead from
if you're behind on 720 then refer I died oh
so my fault no it's my fault if you're behind on 720 refresh the page because that'll
put that I'll get you back in check because some people are like five to ten minutes behind
why don't I have ad block on um because I mean at least for youtube I like to support
youtubers like at least people that run ads on their videos so like if I have a friend or
something that has ads I usually keep it on just because I like to be nice to them I don't know
pretty good guy plus can't ad block block other stuff it's that kind of not supposed to
I don't think so what's the not supposed to block I don't know like I remember like hearing that
some it's some places like it might think something is an ad when it's not
I don't think I see anything like that do you have ad block I do I turn it off sometimes though
usually when I watch streams or whatever yeah I assume that's what a lot of people do because I
mean I I guess it can get really annoying like if you're just browsing websites and it's like oh
take over your entire screen with an ad I hate those I would like to open like four pages to tell
you that this is an ad yeah the worst thing is gonna open it until you to watch the other page
oh that did I for a second I thought we just beat her but I was I was looking at the chat
she's done kill the daughters of pain
the story's in hot wait did she she really did died didn't she
oh no that's that's like her like introduce myself thing isn't it oh yeah this is the one
where she doesn't even fight you she just like shows up and is like hey and then you shoot her once
and she says no she just introduces herself hi I'm a spider yeah somebody said ad blockers
didn't mess up some for honestly for this part I was flying through when I was doing with this
character and I was thinking myself that you probably were supposed to beat her there and there
was probably supposed to be a different boss later and they just are like no yeah baby no I'm
old as a letter glitter run away really feels like that feels like that with a lot of stuff in this game
but there are other patch in it there's apparently a big patch they're working on for this game
and I don't they haven't said anything about it but let's let's wait and see what it is I hope it's
fifteen dollars please let it be fifteen dollars two dollars it was fifteen dollars I would literally
a dump of brick like a brick would I would I would have to run to the bathroom because a brick
would be coming out I just imagine you're taking a very long drive to nearby dump taking a brick out
of your car just flopping it somewhere that is how mad you are going that far out of your way
so close now children of the corn oh you destroyed the heart I'm so mad but I'll keep haunting you
with my body there implications anyone would want to bang as spider spider so said nothing
good job confusing those two bugs hey I did by part it's not like these things are given up they
like died before it even came out I did my part see I should have used it right now but it's not
cool down because I'm stupid oh yeah this would be a great time to use it because there's like a bunch
of blue people oh I see a yellow I see yellow I'm not going to pick it up now because I want to kill
stuff first then the server shut down oh that would be terrible did I'm already overburdened really
you were in a Justin town legs okay legs these are very good for someone else that is not me
oh I will hold on to them oh god I make a ton run so all about that money
all about the paper so all about that Diablo 3 money
once I get a million gold I'll be happy slowly getting I have five hours 71 thousand good
getting there take a look at some of this stuff um I got a lot of just crappy rare that I just need
to sell it's gonna take too long in the auction house mmm I'll save these for later maybe I will try
and sell them yeah I think my auction house actually like cleared and all of the items that were
in the completed section are gone mm-hmm all the items that I was selling are gone weird
that shouldn't do that yeah if I shouldn't but it
I just I got to stash a lot of this stuff I need after we kill Asma Dan I need like a million
minutes to like sit sort through all this stuff that I have
okay I hope people are ready for like the most exciting part of this stream
germa going through his items and figuring out what he's gonna sell I would
detain him
oh okay now I got run my backpack
I'm just gonna sell these I don't need them
I have whatever I hold on for now just because you destroyed the sin heart
potions are expensive in this game yes I can go
I
potions are very expensive that's why I got ferrets ferrets
my buddy's here
you know I'm gonna check out that other ruin for fire bats
you
you check it out
money money money get it get it get it get the money
all right let me see the fire that's not get it get it get it get it get it
rapidly summon bats that seek out nearby enemies for 280 percent weapon damage
as fire oh my god I'll try that right now don't even oh there's a lot of damage
I would recommend that to anyone who likes damage I'll stick with blowdart just because I love
blowdart let me check this out let's see oh it's okay cool it's a lot less
group not really a crowd boob anymore it's kind of a single target move now
I should go to whimsy shire I'm not at that stage I'm a noob I'm not ready for
deponies I'm not ready for it yet what is holdore hold hold hold hold
holdore what's that I guess I can just kind of stand back and do this does a lot of damage
blows through mana like crazy though I don't know if I like it I'll try it for a little while
uh I'm not picking up pages of jewel crafting only because I'm it's not something I point
on doing at least right now once I have a ton of money well then even then you would use
yeah I mean it's I'm in nightmare right now so the pages of jewel crafting
aren't gonna get me really anything why is my dude dead
run away go get him bats
uh the reason why I didn't stream yesterday is because that was having internet problems
some right I couldn't I couldn't get 720 to to go go through and even 360 was being really really
slow and choppy so something was going on with the internet I don't know why but doing an extra
long one tonight today this morning extra extra extra extra extra x3 read all about it
you can help me you feel like it I thought I felt like it
okay man if you're just joining us if you just you just kind of jumped in this is a stars here
oh these star they just do 47 there we go level it up
ooh move ruins what on it spirit walkeroon I'm gonna check that out yep this will be on the
channel later oh shall oh sure first sure
fine the time is it so almost 20 of 11 am oh yeah it tells you the time in Diablo
yeah remember we were talking about that it's like oh how much time we lost oh there it is
in my dex story it was covered but actually it's on the left now
the sin hot
get that way point
bats bats everywhere
give me that money give me that money
yo money good fusion see I used it to a good time that time didn't are you proud of it
I am there was it was a lot of reasons to do that
I might have to take off that passive skill what makes all my mana stuff cost more money
mean more mana oh makes all my mana cost more money
I mean no matter cost more mana for what it's yeah it's all of your damages increased by 20%
but every spell cost 30% more mana but that's so good that's it's so much more damage than I
wouldn't be doing squeaky chair wait wait
I'll probably be playing Diablo 3 I mean today you mean today
hmm it probably after we kill um aspa then once we get to the last part of this act
I might take a break but if you met long-term I'll be playing this game for probably very long time
I would say if it turns out after all the patches and all the bug fixes and
after the initial launch period then but all stays well and it's all good I'll be playing this game
for a very very very long time yeah okay you're here this game I'm exel
I really still need to play uh most Mxc mostly 3-mm elimination challenge yes did you actually
install a D2 I actually did not but I could that I'll take two seconds it's only like a one gig file to be
honest or did you download it I think I have to download it so it shouldn't take that long to
do when you download it and install it don't open it oh okay I think actually I think I still have
I think I downloaded it on this computer a long time ago I think it's just still sitting like
the installation file is just still sitting on the computer somewhere I'd like to ask you a
very serious question right now okay what is with the dudes in the background what is your theory
on why you can never see their feet um they're having a party and they're the pinata
these poor guys I mean as men would certainly have a much higher chance of winning this whole war
if you just like unchained yeah you oh watch out for the disco ball just like one of them
you unchained one of those guys he will take out an entire city yeah I don't know
maybe they they're not that good at fighting
so they're good at what do they do why are they here well I mean look look think of it this way
these guys are probably not that strong at this point they've been kind of chained up with like
stuff in their heads why I don't I don't think they'd be that tough anymore if you release them
they'd probably just fall over and go well even if they just fell over that'd be a pretty big fall
they can fall in the right spot maybe they can fall around and be like change my diaper
you don't want that in her I get through wherever you're so close now so close
oh yeah you destroyed the synhot I can't believe you oh dear you second important question
yeah why is there no elevator here yeah and you know what follow up important question how did
azmedan get down here like did he he didn't come down these stairs he's too big was he just like
born in the bottom and it just never goes anywhere he doesn't ever go out I guess like oh
I mean like here's my house my big azmedan house I'm like a 75 foot tall like 9 million
pollen monster let me walk down my spiral staircase when you can like astral project images of your
heads you can talk shit to people like when that's your thing I don't imagine going out yeah I
probably just sit there like call x girlfriend you have no hope put the put dive
eat it bats eat bats
more bats stand in the middle oh god oh god oh god yeah I need I need a more crowd move this
this is this big very single target it's not sure I'm gonna stick with it or I'm gonna have to change
boys and dark something else maybe he uses teleportation that is a good theory that is a good theory
maybe I mean he is the lord of uh uh sin beer I was saying beer did you say beer no I said beer
azmedan lord of beer oh yeah azmedan like he owns a micro brewery a lot of beer
how dare you oh god I'm dead I'm gonna die right now how dare you insult the lord of beer
yeah well oh in the fear of my delicious hops and yees time you know I thought he was fearing that's
why he was always uh lord of sin getting off on that he is a weird one he does live with a spider
lady that's hell bent on making us like love her but hate her at the same time why won't you bang me
this is his roommate by the way you know that says you that's what you got to live with I would go crazy
to his wife or something maybe he just got drunk one night and woke up down there is what someone said
she just won't leave like oh man where am I you have job showed shit face right now what is this
place I own it now oh this is mine oh this is mine
yeah I think he doesn't even know why these giant tall guys are here all right this definitely
gets comment of the stream uh damn it I want to take a dump well you guys talk louder so I can hear
you from the crap oh my god oh my goodness getter yeah I can't even stun that that move only works
on like actual enemies unfortunate all right kill him before the teleport kill him before the
teleport oh he's just lying down die die die die what's your like a normal and one shot or maybe we're
getting it oh wow well blow up at one of asthma dance like four hearts is he a cow or something
ah he must be a cow don't know cow oh my god I'm it get it no one has this cow cows have multiple
stomachs not multiple hearts oh is he like a cow he has like four hearts
dirt oh look oh come on it's starting to make sense what's what is it this is one of those big
guys chests it's ripped open and the heart is placed over here what what you see that's why would
they do such a thing and then the heart powers door sale I don't get how the hearts power is
well how come how come then look at this guy how come this guy isn't like has a sin heart maybe
he's not cool enough maybe you didn't like I guess they're I guess they're like harvesting them like
okay seriously seriously look at this there is no way as madden can fit down this staircase look
at this there's no way look at this look at look at look at the height I'm pointing at the screen
right now by the way I don't know why the height of this ceiling look at this oh I'm gonna go
in my door like he wouldn't even be able to get in here just jump down like he isn't used to
stay so just run fat and he rolls off the edge somebody asked how was this early morning um I
started this anymore well yeah yeah I started this straight I've been going for a couple hours at
least a few hours it was it was early morning when I started I am here so after this I'm probably
gonna close the stream out for a little while I might come back I'm not sure though probably not
because I want to get some food in my way I might go to the gym but get the way point where about
to kill asthma then this is on nightmare so it might be a little tough yeah okay he might be super
tough oh build it up the room can be very disappointed when he dies bats bats bats bats bats bats
use mask and fuse right I started oh let me use mask confusion ready I'll do it I'll use it I
started at 7.30 a.m. my time so it's been about three hours going on like three and a half maybe
I never I never know until I'm done and I look at the file that goes up to you too
but it would probably be about three and a half four hours the whole time I would assume
oh god
oh you live in Hong Kong so what is like nighttime or something for you well you wait no you're
behind I don't even know time zones how you work if you didn't get to see the TF2 or you didn't
get to see the beginning of the Diablo 3 stuff it's all gonna be up in probably a couple hours
the whole thing will be on YouTube mask confusion there's no there we go all right I got that
through charmed kill him you're on my team now okay oh I wasn't talking to you hey kill him now
I'm not that much would you all right it's got a rare come on give me a good roll give me a good roll
no I'll actually with a gem in there no I don't think so
oh do I look good in this do I do I just make me look fat
where's my body there he is you always dies and I never like realize it yeah
if you just made like a compilation of the noises I've made in this stream and just made a
video of it like it would be but you probably pretty funny like yeah what I make a whole lot of
noises someone said go star I love you I'm going I hear we are all right so this is it's after
this I'm gonna close out the stream and we will go from there and this will all be uploaded to you
tube if we if we don't wipe like five times which we will not star is pro there is there's a guy
that like lives in his like down here and that's if he can't move wiggles around jiggles is
oh there he comes oh get him gargantuan you know what I want to do this and that
bats he's going down very very easily what does that bomb move you're doing oh my god it looks
got one shot what bomb moves the way it kind of looks like that looks like the assassin skill
remember the first assassin skill you really got is oh yeah fire bombs yeah it's kind of like that
I can't even like I really only use it to build hatred I'm gonna die I'm dead oh you're dead I'm dead
stay alive star I'm okay I got ferrets use those ferrets to kill this
bats sloppy bastard they're trying to keep up with me and they're like spashing out so hard
there's no way you're gonna be able to come get me by the way I'm like in this pool of like
this darkness pool you're gonna die of even trying to revive me I got you trust me I can do it
I'm gonna do it just because you said I couldn't oh oh oh oh oh oh oh you did it I love you
oh
because he spawns ads I don't know he did god man that's what it's a it's a MMO term
give me a legendary give me a legendary no just but give me a blue got a blue sweet
oh we gotta see the uh the cutscene uh skip no I wanted to know what happened all right here's
what happened so we just killed a big fat guy and he died yeah and then she slams a rock into his soul
and then they all rock out
oh I've never been to Hong Kong it's very far away I've never I don't think I've never been
besides Canada I've never been out of the country you know I was in Pennsylvania ones one time
first of the first I've been is probably Wisconsin I'm gonna soda whichever is further
further so I've been is Seattle Seattle Washington
I just said you were in Canada well I I've been to Canada I don't live there
whatever well I met like out of the country that's like the only that's like the furthest
place out of the country I've never ever got anywhere else
oh
that's a lot of damage it's too hand-in-dough I don't want to do this event I don't want to
do spoiler or spoiler alert spoiler spoiler spoiler spoiler spoiler spoiler spoiler
except here we go spoiler I don't know how many times I have to say that spoiler
okay all right that's gonna be the end here guys
oh my god what goodbye
everyone I every time I try to end a youtube stream like I like always forget how to do it so let me
like figure this out yeah thank you all so much for watching sticking around and goodbye to star
say your buys thank you star for coming along and playing I hope you all hate um germa I mean
pancakes with chips and uh hey chocolate chip pancakes are good good
I'm hoping every comment is about that just telling you you're wrong you're wrong
I would make my day um event manager life control and there it is all right dudes take it easy
everybody and take care everybody peace soup
you
not yet I'm still figuring out this is getting awkward
I'll try to edit this