Alright.
Huh.
So I think it's going.
Hopefully there's no problems with the actual stream.
Is that would not be cool.
Twitch.
.tv.
I gotta change this.
It says I'm gonna be playing CSCOPH but that's not the case.
That's gotta be changed.
Okay.
Yeah, the chat is laggy.
I can't see any of these uh...
The chat is all screwed up.
That is not cool.
So let me uh...
I don't have a solution to that so...
Just gonna have to do it, play it by ear and if something happens,
something happens, you know.
Oh yeah, I tried to say how to spell principal right.
If you saw that in the uh...
Google chat.
How do you spell principal?
I don't know.
Alright, let's see if I can pop this out.
Pop out.
Alright.
This is muted.
Lower.
Just want the chat.
Hmm, that's not working for me.
That is not working for me.
Come on, Twitch get your act together.
I won't pop it out.
I'm refreshing the page.
If you have any chat problems, just try refreshing.
Maybe that'll help.
If not, then I'm not exactly sure what to do.
But it's okay.
We shall push the view.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
That's right there.
Okay, I'm just going to tell people what's happening on various social media networks.
It's going on Twitter.
And then of course, the Steam Group.
Steam.
Community.
Groups.
The Inhumane Strike UpWats.
Let's get on the mat.
Brody.
Twitch.tv.
Oh, by the way, I'm also sorry for starting this pretty late.
I was trying to get that video up and it was not working.
I don't know why, but it just wasn't.
Not in all caps.
Let me scream it.
Woohoo!
15 minutes.
And that's that.
And one more.
I've got to tell all the people on the YouTube's about it.
Channel.
Speed.
Streaming TF2 and Flash Games.
HTTP.com.
Flash.tv.
Flash.
All right.
Okay.
Good afternoon, morning evening, night time, whatever it happens to be in your quarters of the world.
Welcome to the stream.
Flash Gordon Games.
So, sooner or later here when I get my server up and running, we're not going to have to do this anymore.
It'll just be, hey, I'm in my server.
Everyone go there if you want to play.
Because now it's kind of like, where are we going to find a good map to play on?
How about the gold rush?
All right, gold rush it is.
Oh, no way, never mind.
Refresh.
It was like 15 people already in there.
How about players?
I should have been not full.
That's fine.
All right, come on.
Stop with the refresh.
Oh, come on.
I just refreshed again trying to hit stop refresh.
Valve, why do you do that?
Stop.
Okay.
How about, that's fine, a good one.
Ooh, that one is Thunder Mountain.
Caught bad lands.
Can't get the health bad lands.
Here is the IP.
Let's get started.
And boom, head's in there.
All hands on deck.
King of the Hill, Nukleus.
Should be a rocket time.
It's 405 in California, yeah?
Yeah, I'm sorry for starting late.
I said this before, but I'll say it again.
It's probably like seven in the morning.
Or like five in the morning for people that are used to seeing this at least at a reasonable time.
And I apologize for that.
I usually want to start it around 536.
730 is when we're actually starting.
I feel bad for you, European guys.
That's my fault and I do apologize.
What do I want to do now?
Let's go soldier.
Oh, make sure the audio is good.
How's the endgame audio?
Should it be lower higher?
How's the sound?
My bump it into.
You know, I'll stick with the directed.
The chat's still broken.
Yeah, I don't know.
If you can not see the chat, I apologize.
There's nothing I can do.
Oh, come on, you scout.
Why am I using the...
I have to touch you, by the way.
Come here!
Oh, which way are you going to go?
What was that?
Oh, it's a crit.
Yeah, the chat's not refreshing for me either.
So I guess just sit back and relax and if you're playing play, I guess.
543, I'm taking the directed off.
Get rid of this thing.
Why am I using the gun boats?
What on earth are these audio for right now?
I'll keep the half to touch you on.
I'm not very good with the directed.
It's hard.
It's very hard to use.
I'm going this way.
Now you know what?
Where'd he go?
We're going to jump around.
What's he going on here?
Super lag.
Oh no, get rid of that.
Scent's redown.
It's any health.
I'm not at all my shots in this shotgun.
I don't know how that happened.
Oh my god.
Oh, it's something that's changed.
That's why.
Sensitivity was all a little low.
I got to deal with it though.
So when are we going to get an update?
When's the team fortress update coming out?
How am I not hitting him?
I feel like I'm lagging like crazy.
I'm starting to go on a roll here.
Ding, ding.
Oh, here comes Bergerboy.
Who do that is?
That can't be Bergerboy right there, can it?
Bergerboy.
Hold that point.
Oh.
I wish I could see the chat.
I'm going to refresh it.
This is stupid.
I can't see the chat.
Maybe if I do this, I might be able to see the chat
or maybe just the actual chat is screwed up.
Maybe not.
Twitch, what the heck?
I'm streaming on Twitch because YouTube is usually broken.
And I guess not.
I guess not Twitch.
Ding, ding, ding.
Oh, I'm going to get headshot.
I know it.
Run away.
All right.
This guy is screwed.
Get rid of that medic.
Oh, I thought I killed him.
You see that in the kill?
I was like, oh, nope.
You killed the guy behind him.
Get away from me.
I think that was a dead runner.
I don't think he's dead.
Pretty sure he's still alive.
Might as well go get some health.
Right.
Boom, boom.
Fire!
Oh, no.
We're going to get on this.
Oh, jump around.
So get off your feet and jump around.
Jump, jump, jump, jump.
I don't know what the point of that was.
Oh, my God.
Oh, no.
I'm just like jumping around like a idiot.
I'm doing okay.
Still no chat.
This is what it looks like, by the way, for me.
Like the wheel of death.
So I can't answer your questions.
Oh, that's stupid.
I'm going to try refreshing it again.
It sort of looks like, unfortunately.
Oh, I'm going to get the chat back.
Did I?
Of course not.
That was a spy, my God.
That was a dead ranger.
See if I can evolve.
Oh, that was unlucky.
Look out, look out, look out.
Oh, that's going to kill me.
I need the equalizer.
I need to put the equalizer on.
We're going to lose.
I'm going to fire.
I'm going to help it.
Stay on it.
Stay on it, my brethren.
Get that spy and let's go.
Stay on it, come on.
Come on, come on, come on.
Yes.
Nice job.
Good job, guys.
Look at this guy.
He's like hiding behind like the stakeout area.
Good job.
Oh, now I got the chat.
Okay, I just got MGE's live streaming.
What's the last thing I saw?
Oh, I was going for a new shot.
I'm not hitting people with rockets right now.
I think every single one of my kills has been put the shotgun.
Except for that one.
Except for Burger Boy.
I'm not going over there.
I need health.
Come on, hit him.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
I can't believe I'm that stupid.
Oh, my God.
What is wrong with me?
Yeah, good game, that's good game.
Oh, my God.
I'm just standing there like scratching my butt.
What is going on?
What the hell is this?
What is it?
A prop hunt mod?
Wow.
That's pretty cool.
All right, we're going to go in.
Whatever this is, I'm using it.
All right, good.
Good.
Good, good, good.
Oh, come on, get hit, Mark.
Get hit, Mark.
How did I lose on it?
How did I lose it in people?
Oh, I find it.
Now I can read the chat, so I will, I will, oh, God.
So yes, I will talk about my steam workshop item.
Oh, no, Burger Boy.
Just punch him.
My steam workshop item is going well.
The modeller behind it, he, thank you often, is prime.
But the modeller behind it, he had to take a little break from modeling because I think he just had some school stuff he was trying to get out of the way and I had some family things he wanted to get done.
So it is still going.
Well, I got a pretzel in my mouth.
I'm sitting here eating pretzels that I can't even like, boy, yeah, so the, it probably in a couple weeks, I would assume will be more updates on that.
And I'm going to die.
It's going to take one shot.
I'm going to go down.
I just want to make it epic.
That is, that's a spy.
How come I didn't get any medal for this?
What is, what is, was that not really a spy?
I swear I bumped into him.
I swear to every single deity that exists.
I was bumping into that guy.
It's my pile.
Oh man, look at all these dudes in here.
Yeah, the pretzels are meeting there.
They're the small still looking, I'm running into, look at me.
I'm like, hey, I got one hand playing it.
Okay, okay, okay, I've got, let me wash this down.
First, before I was an idiot.
Oh, I got a kill.
They're the small still into pretzels, like the ones, the best ones.
I'm not a big fan of the really skinny ones.
If you guys know what I'm talking about, the tiny little skinny baby pretzels.
Yeah, not for me.
Now, let's actually start playing this game.
You know what?
I want this.
There we go.
Hey, you spy.
I bet you are.
Oh no, here comes Gergenwood.
The insensitive one.
I have demo games with Spy.
I can't, I gotta shoot somebody.
Come on, one good meetshot on someone.
Mmm.
Do you want some hats?
Derma?
No, I'm good.
I'm good to go.
Thank you for offering though.
Appreciate that.
I don't need any items or anything.
Oh boy, Pyro coming in.
Oh, come on.
Come on.
Oh no, I'm dead.
I didn't mean to taunt by the way.
I was just trying not to die.
Well, the chat is back.
Thank goodness.
Can I play some payload?
Of course.
I'm going to try and find a good Gold Drusher Bad Water map after this.
What's the look of what we looking like?
That's spy.
I don't know why.
I'll put it right here.
Give me those hit markers.
Oh.
Gosh darn it.
Am I a fan of Frank Sinatra?
Yeah.
Who couldn't be with a voice like that?
Locked be your lady tonight.
Locked if you ever killed Derma in Team Fortress.
Locked be your scout tonight.
I apologize for doing that.
That was not, uh, that was not cool.
As you go, oh my god.
I'm going to die again.
No, no.
Can I make it?
Take your batson.
Go, go, go, go, go.
Oh.
Come on.
I had my finger touching.
I was reaching for it too and everything.
Give me a break.
Oh well.
Alright.
It's time.
Are you?
Every time I get out of spawns, something bad happens.
I'm getting kills with a mini-century.
That's one good thing that comes out of all this.
That's what I was just saying.
You know, I'm going to move it.
I want it up here.
Oh my god.
You toast bastard.
How much was TF2, TF2, was 10 bucks?
I think it was originally 20, wasn't it?
1999 for a while.
And then it went to 9.
Did it ever go to 999?
I don't remember it being 999.
Maybe it's because I just never bought it.
That's a crit.
I'm dead.
I was trying to strafe and drop down not in the pit
and I ended up landing on the crit.
Well, you know what?
We're going to change this.
Oh, by the way, I'm going to say this here just because, you know,
it makes sense to say it here.
I still have to give away 33% of that backpack because it's been about five days
and the third person still has not responded.
So if I'm going to give them maybe another 48 hours
and if I still don't see anything,
we're going to talk about maybe another small giveaway potentially in the stream.
So I might not do it.
If I do it on Twitter, I do it on Twitter,
but I'm not decided at this point.
What I'm going to do.
I'll probably just re-pick.
Ow.
Oh, put me out.
Put me out.
I was behind you.
I have not played Gotham City in Vosters.
I heard it's fun though.
Are we going to win?
They're going to get it.
They are absolutely going to get this.
You're going up here.
Good.
I'm protecting this room.
This health is mine for the rest of this goddamn game.
What?
Oh my god.
What's going on?
What's happening?
Oh my god.
During the livestream.
Hold on.
That just took me totally off guard.
Thank you so much for that.
I hope I let me accept it.
Let me even see what just happened.
I got to duck away for one second.
I'll wait one.
What is happening right now?
Where is it?
You've received a gift.
Total war, Shogun 2.
Oh my god.
Oh this is from my wedding partner.
I have to show this.
I forgot to show this off.
This guy already has a suicidal engineer.
He sent me the ring.
Where is it?
Where's my diamond ring?
Special something for special someone.
Thank you so much.
I wanted to really mention that.
Yes, I will accept this.
It's not wedding, it's like Valentine's Day.
But yeah.
Special shout out to that guy.
That's really, really thoughtful.
I'm not going to accept your gift.
I don't even know how to do it.
Where is it?
I accept.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Add to my game library.
I will absolutely play this.
Thank you so much.
That's all I can say.
You're awesome.
Thank you.
Oh, I'm a little bit sure if I should grow enough now.
Yeah, that's awesome.
That's not a good way to go.
Yeah, I did see the new Gord Bord stuff.
The new Gord, how do you even say that?
I always say that wrong.
Gord Bord.
Oh my god, every time!
Every time I exit spawn.
Oh, I'm going to just plant, you know what?
No, you're killing this guy first.
Holy running away, that works as well.
Protect this room.
Let's at least get some area denial going here.
This guy's down here.
This guy knows a mirror.
Where is he?
Change it right here.
Oh, what?
That's a big century.
That is a big century.
My goodness.
No, I'm not a god.
All right, all right.
Time to go scout.
I'm going to use, oh no, that's right.
You know what?
For the sake of my backpack being gone,
we're going to go all default.
At least item wise.
I'm going to go to the bottom.
You are not real.
And you probably still alive.
I can't believe I just did that.
I can't believe it.
I can't believe that just happened.
I can't believe I just did that.
I got behind two people.
I want to just go,
and push myself in the face with like an iron.
Oh my god.
That is really depressing.
You know what I mean?
It's just like I got behind those two guys.
At one soldier.
And there was a crit.
And I missed.
There, that's a spy coming up.
I need help.
He's going to headshot me.
This always happens.
Why don't I just hit E?
God.
This is a spy.
Maybe not.
Let's bump.
No, it's a, it's Ari.
Hey, Ari.
Alright, let's go.
Let's go.
That's a bad place to go.
What?
What just happened?
The guy showed me through the staircase.
I am mad.
Alright, I'm putting the milk on.
I need my milk.
I need my calcium.
My calcium for the week.
If I were to have any unusual effect on a hat or any unusual,
I would want the, what is it?
The searing, towering, pillar of hats.
Because that is not worth like like $5 million or something.
It's like a lot of money.
On two soldiers.
I can't deal with that.
And a scout.
And I have milk.
I threw it.
Oh my goodness gracious.
How much, what, what, somebody tell me?
What is the most expensive team purchase hat?
Like in dollars, in US dollars.
Is it searing, towering pillar or sunlight towering pillar?
Is it like $2,000 or something crazy?
God.
What is the approximation of the value of that item?
Can't even go after him.
I have no help.
Oh boy, I'm in trouble.
Someone just has to like burp on me and I'm going to die.
Well, he's don't burp on me.
I don't want to die.
There we go.
I have to lay to LA anymore.
Oh.
What?
Oh, I would, I just maybe sad, which is happened.
I'm not even mad about that.
I'm just like upset.
I just want to cry.
Get a game.
Money out.
Sunbeams TC is about 40 buds.
It's how much is one bud?
How much is one bud US dollars?
Get in there.
Oh, come on, did I get him?
Yeah, I did.
Get rid of that many centuries.
I can't even go over there.
I can't even go anywhere.
I can't take you anywhere, Scalp.
Hi, spawn, bye spawn.
I can't go over there, God.
Oh, that's not the right taunt.
Wait, we failed.
Wait, I thought we were winning.
I thought we had the point.
Well, that's a...
So one bud is $35, so that's a lot of money.
That is a lot of money.
Let's go to our new server.
New server.
Thanks to you guys in this server right now.
We're going to trade.
Trade servers.
Let's try and get on a payload.
Payload race.
No, no payload race.
I do, but it can be 2k, Yodic.
Peel bad water in too many bots.
People won't be able to get in so easily.
Here we go, who do?
There we go.
Apps of freaking loot.
Who do?
It's going in the chat right now.
This is the IP.
There you are.
Ladies and gents.
The last giveaway winner...
I sent him a Twitter message.
And he still isn't replied.
I'll check right now.
That was a long time.
That was a while ago.
So, be on the lookout in the next week or the next three or four days.
I may be picking another person on Twitter for this 33% of his back-back.
I want your items.
I want all your items.
I'm probably going to play tower defense again.
That was fun.
Bluens tower defense.
Here's the IP again.
For those of you wondering.
That is the IP, right?
Let me make sure.
Yes, it is.
That is the IP.
Let's do sniper.
I don't think I've ever done the scope sniper on a stream before.
I'm not going to do that.
I need a hat.
One of these like potty hats and sunglasses.
Oh yeah, high five.
Shippvel.
Pro ping right here.
That's not that bad, Norben.
That's not too terrible.
I'd say if you got to like 160 or 150, you should start to count your blessings.
Oh my god, boo.
Yeah, boo.
Sorry, there's like no Skype call.
I was running very, very, very late, more than an hour late to the stream.
So I had to just go.
What is this guy doing?
That guy was like standing in the create a character position.
I'm a little too close.
You know what, this is a bad spot.
I'm going to get trouble.
Yeah, I know it.
That's a bad spot.
Late to his own stream as usual.
Yeah, I do frequently.
I'm always at least at least at 10, 5, 10, but it's late.
Hey, better late than never though, right?
Is that even an adage?
Oh my cat's in here now.
Going, ma-a-a.
Let's get a couple of headshots, huh?
There goes the engineer that's in like the create a character stance.
What?
Oh boy.
Where is he?
I didn't cover him.
My god, what a totally idiot I am.
Stop the bloody boom.
Ow!
Right in my face.
Am I going to play Left-for-Dead 2?
Probably not on this stream tonight, but I absolutely love that game.
Probably at some point, yeah?
Will you stop meowing?
You're ruining my stream cat meowing.
Bum dum dum dum dum dum dum dum dum dum dum dum dum dum dum dum dum dum dum dum dum dum dum dum dum dum dum dum dum dum dum dum dum dum dum dum dum dum.
Oh my god.
Hey, you look like you could do some pee on your back.
I'll roll it right into one of my teammates' backs.
Oh!
Ugh, I just peoped.
Cat.
I gotta switch I gotta go heavy there. They're gonna win
Gotta go heavy with the brass beast
And I'm just gonna stand in a corner and just hold down this damn button come on come on come on come on go a little get it
Don't let them get it
No, no I gotta get I gotta get right up on here
Bye oh my god, I'm gonna die
Just gonna eat the switch on the cart
Oh
Yeah heavy turtle and what you know about heavy turtles the two heavy turtles
Actually gonna work
Who needs center of guns and you got three super heavies are these two the same person. Oh, no, they got different hats
We got I think we're good all they're coming up there. Oh
Here to me help me
Teenage mutant ninja heavy alien turtles
So I don't ask this before but I couldn't see the chat is the audio fine is it can you hear me and is the stream too loud or
But we just write as Goldilocks would say
That's good that's good
Ha
You cannot defeat the heavy I
Just bumped into someone for sure
You can always tell you know you can you never know if it's lag or you actually up bumping into someone and that's I don't want to get by that again
Oh, I love of all that is sacred
Ditto zero zero zero how are you man?
Look I love this heavy look at this guy that is a true heavy right there
Standing on the cart with sunglasses a lucha to a mask and a Russian hat on
What a goofy goofy person I love
Oh my goodness
I have on the brass piece can't move must punch someone in face no not gonna happen
I heard I heard back step. Oh, I'm so scared right now
Oh
That is the worst part about the brass beast if you get ubered and there's people like a 50 a hundred feet away from you
It's all over
Is by the time you run up there. It's just like go everyone just turn around the corner and run away
I'm sorry
You know we could use
Mmm, I
Don't know what I want to do
Pyro sad old him going pyro
Bescarillo song is absolutely stylo either stylo or you know what this is gonna sound weird, but I actually like dare
You got
The
I don't know the lyrics of that song I
Do know the lyrics of the song, but they're very odd
Oh pyrone pyro fight that's you are not real that's not me. I didn't just look in a mirror that wasn't me
bumping into somebody
Watch your backs
Oh, he turned smoke me
I
Started listening to the guerrillas because it well they are a great band. I'm glad you are
You got to listen to them. Is there awesome?
My cat right now is just sitting under the about you fake
Literally just sitting underneath my legs just rubbing up against my legs over and over again
I just want to I just want to be like cat get out of here, but I can't because it's too cute
Find the way I'm gonna go around here
Die die how much help do you have?
You know
Oh, we found them we got a winner
We got a winner
Come here, come here, put you out
No, no stay alive
I need I'm gonna run to ammo
Oh
Shoot me show me show me
That would have been a crit
Get him
Oh my god
What what just what just happened somebody look at the look what just happened what just even happened right there guys I
What did I reflect?
I put I tried to put the heavy out that was on fire what even just happened
That was very very odd maybe I reflected a
I'm so confused
Well, we like put this heavy out of here like the crit noise and then kill somebody like what?
So that was you that I just killed I have no idea how it happened
This wears it whoa oh
Always sniper damn damn
Whoa hold on stop freaking out here
Gotcha
Back to cut out back to go oh my god, they're gonna win. Oh
Oh, so Berga so Berga boy you got to like are you raging yet?
Oh, you want you're on this no you're on the other team Berga boy. Why are you not like freaking out right now?
No, no, no
Gotta put people out
Oh, nice team over nice team over already. Oh here comes
Damn it damn it
Yeah, I'm upset I'm going medic
I thought for sure I was gonna time that but he had the direct hit yeah
You got killed by herp and dirt at the same time they both killed me
Where is grandpa did you see my latest vlog talking about that? Oh my god spies everywhere
And my latest vlog I talk about grandpa and what's oh my god there behind us
No, don't just I'm gonna sit down here no, I'm not
I was so concerned about getting the shot from behind from people on the cart that I
Oh, we won. There we go cool
I do want to play Grand Theft Auto on a stream. I really do
It's just the only problem with Grand Theft Auto is it's very
poorly optimized on the PC so it can be very difficult to do even record that game
So it's something I would have to look and do try to make it run at a little lower settings maybe because that game
Takes almost like 5,000 percent like CPU when you try and play it on like good settings
Now this will be the last round in this server. I'm gonna go somewhere else
Oh look at you you match don't you just look so beautiful?
All right, here we go ship back will bomb oh
Look my spray my spray scroll ah
Who wants this who's getting this I don't know yet. You're all good players. I don't always gonna get it
I guess the person that I do it to is the person that's gonna get it so be on the lookout
No trades not right now
Why is everybody think everybody's like
Well, I wasn't going like driving Miss Daisy and do it
Demo spam everywhere
What is happening
Am I excited for Borderlands 2?
Yeah, yeah, I guess a Borderlands one I was I had a good time with it
But I don't know you you have to really play that game with other people you can't really play that game alone if it's to
It's just not my type of game play by myself, but I would probably play with other people for sure and make videos absolutely
As there is a spy for sure like look at this crowd of people. There's gotta be a spy stuck somewhere in here
Oh
My god, where are you? I need to go you how to start come here come here come here. Oh
Hey, at least I did that right least I said I at least I've ever avenged you what oh
Are you ready? Oh
Corrects everywhere
Probably should have saved that but you know, oh my god
Oh
No, no
Get out of here
Oh backed up right into a knife right into a knife
I'm gonna spell out what I want to say but I'm not gonna say it s h i i i i i i i t and then as many
exclamation points you can put on the end of that sentence
That's how I feel right
I got you I got you
Put that away
Let me hear you
Final push oh wouldn't it be great to be on defense right now with a crit squeak as a demo man and kill every single person standing right here my goodness
I think we're gonna get it. Let's try and get these people stay in yield
That's one way all right nice job guys
Critt needles oh
Oh my god, they just respawn like oh my god
You want to talk about a way to burn out a hard drive? I'm not a graphics card. Oh my god. Oh, it's picking up that
Let me make sure I'm like not gonna explode here. I
Say this every time not good. I'm good. We're good to go
We're good
All right, change in servers one more time
This correct browse servers refresh
Favour classes engineer then probably Huntsman sniper
All right, I change it my mind changes on a daily basis. So it's hard to say what my favorite classes
Let's go to a we could always go to good old dog gravel pit gravel pit for sure
Play a couple more rounds on here. There's the IP
Yeah, IP
Oh, it's decals
Maybe it's gonna be cool looking maybe
Maybe
Well the reason why I don't accept trade requests during streams is because I like to keep the action
This is high as I can keep it like I'm sure people don't want to you know, I'm in a trade
Oh, what am I gonna get like let's do some trade? I guess a baby that could be entertaining to some people
But I like to keep the action flowing
I go blue this time and I'm gonna play
Spy
With my revolver my spy sickle I
Just got this I might as well use these things
Totally strange strange I don't have a strange sapper too bad
Too bad
Magic doctor magic
Doctor
Doctor, all right, that's enough of that wait a second. I
Thought I was waiting for set-up time apparently this is no okay
It's just happening
Oh, I'm looking at the chat right now. I'm not even looking at I'm not even looking at my screen
I just tried to give it
That's weird
Okay, so the chat just screwed up. Can anyone see what I just wrote by the way
Did can you guys see the I can you guys see the IP?
Because apparently it's
Twitch
What are you saying burger boy?
Oh burger boy
Lose captain I'm so confused right now
I think I'm playing mom. I don't know why I think I'm right. I'm looking at the chat
Oh my goodness pulled the hamburger. I don't have it
I do have it
Hey, I'm a scout don't shoot me. Oh, no
Oh God run
Oh, no
Please oh
So you guys hear my idea for a spy video I think I said it last driven oh my god. Oh
My god
That is
That is a
If you've never seen that spray before that is burger boy spray and he is a disgusting human being
God dang it. I'm in trouble
Hey, let's go this way then
Instant respawn my goodness
Think we're about to win all right. Let's like get like a new round start it. So I'm not so confused
I don't want to be confused
I don't want to fall asleep cuz that's two songs combined in one
I miss you, babe, and I don't want to miss a thing
My hands are in my face right now. I really thought I was gonna get that stale stab
I really thought it was gonna get it
And it didn't happen and I crouched in everything
I did I crouched I did crouched. Oh, you're gonna taunt are you ready to get it?
He's gonna get away
Just running right into people again
Oh my god
I'm gonna do this
It's gonna be like the tank
Yeah, he'll be
Spies not working right now. I'm not playing Spidey more
When I a lot of you guys know this I've said it before playing Spide on a live stream is like
Pulling teeth out of my brain
Like when I play Spide I need a hundred percent concentration and if I don't have that it's like I
Have essentially regressed to being like nine years old
Oh, that life calm
Oh my goodness
Did even have a okay that didn't hit anybody. Oh my god
Bottle attack of the bottle
Croba
Croba is my best friend on this team because his name is crowbar. I can say it
Oh
Where is he?
Locked load
You want to go bottle you want to go into bottle
He's gone he's gone. Don't worry. We got it. We got it. We could
Where is it? Is there something up there?
There's nothing up here except this one dude. Oh
Like a hit by
Rocky
Flying demo man here we go blank. Oh
Oh, yeah
You know, I'm gonna take this off. I want to put on the weed booties
And a front back we're gonna go sticky tech sticky tech
Sticky tech
Worst item in the game
Oop-hole cable
In my opinion I do not like that thing. I think it's just a dumb weapon. I don't know
I've never used it and I think it just is just a suicide weapon in my opinion
Wish there's not something terribly wrong with that, but I
Build your old before you look oh, I missed the high five. I'm sorry
All right, ready play shipets
How many people are gonna watch the stream right now and see what I'm doing and just not open this door
I bet every single person is not here right now except for this one dude who might die
No
Oh, I can just wait in one more second
Sticky tank
That's bye
They're all going hey
Get over here
Oh, he's not dead oh
For the love of good disc gracious
Oh my god get rid of this guy
Blowin us all around like hot pockets that analogy did not make very much sense not did it
I wonder what that looks like on his screen that must have been so funny he must have saw that cup what what oh
He's up there
My god dude, oh, that was so funny
Defend the point
Another lucky crit I'm sorry about that I'm back into another knife
Gosh darn it
With a capital D
Chat slow for anybody I can't see anything
Apps of positive are looting about friend towering pillar of hats two dudes with it except I'm not gonna have it for very long
Neurus still alive
Oh my god you are a spy
He's still alive how many how many did it take I?
Do play in windowed mode I have to just stream it
How much help do you have he must have a bunch of heads I
Don't trust you I don't trust you snake
Don't you back up into that I can't believe I didn't hit him I am so shocked and appalled
My god
There he is why I thought we got rid of him I thought somebody killed him
Nobody spies are on that team one two three four three
Yeah, I'm not doing too well either so don't worry
I'm on that guy's head I was just standing on his head
Oh
I'm scared I
Wish I if I was standing I would be so cool I
Of course I put the crit down right in front of my face
Is that guy still up here?
What he is oh
Yeah, he is found him
I
Know more devil man not doing how with them let's go back to pyro
Let's do reserve shooter
Come here, let me put you out and junior
Dude, I'm just the designated putter router people of person
Oh get back here
God let me reload
Good good good oh god crits Creek I don't know if you want to give it to me might be a total failure
Oh my god, how he's still up there
I'll get rid of him
Oh
No
Oh, he's still alive I need more bullets in the stamp thing ah
What's my opinion on the royal wedding
Um, it's cool. I guess people getting married
Hmm, and it's whales right friends. I think I could be totally wrong
Boo, don't be mad at me if I don't know that answer
Because of course you don't know boo boo man 61 is from whales
If you didn't know that's some a little bit of a it
Trying to think of the word trivia
Well, I'm sure everyone knows that anyways. Oh, geez. I got to the double jump
I
Go this way. Oh
Yeah, yeah, let me get stuck on the wall
What was that
This guy is lagging very badly. I'm sorry. I apologize to the lag dude. I'm sorry
Let's go this way
Yeah, it's true
Oh
I've new items less
I haven't died yet
I got a feeling
There's a lot of people trying to
What even killed him on the century mini-century
Wasn't just a century it was a gosh dang mini-century
Oh
Shoot me Jimmy
Oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh
No no no no no no no
Oh, come on kill everybody
Oh
At least I got two or three people
brass beast
Two and two on this guy I haven't seen this guy in a little while this guy last
The chat is not loading for me so what the hell
What
Well, that's one way to die
Yeah, the chat is not loading what the hell is going on here
You chat bastard
Wow
Cat stop yelling cat
Do I speak English
It depends if I'm playing a game and talking at that point probably not probably speaking some other language is nobody knows
I don't know how I didn't hit him the first one
Will you be quiet cat you're messing with my fun sway oh
Trying to catch him in the air
Where is that spy
Oh
Die
People everywhere
Oh right into walk right into it. Yeah
Favorite movie is probably
Now that is a tough question because then you have to talk about the dark night
Momento ghost busters I cannot pick a favorite movie no way even if I tried
Even if I really wanted to tell you
Get him in the air
This guy's getting unusual he means business oh
Let's go let's rock out
I don't even care anybody brought it to the lake and it ain't
Five club is also an amazing one ghost busters you never you never seen ghost busters before
If you've never seen ghost busters you all go go do it right now
Go go to Netflix dot. I mean it isn't even on Netflix. I don't know
Eight damage hitting me
There you go
You still live
Oh
Oh if I had a shot if I had a damn shot
There's our shoot somebody in the face good crit
How come that didn't anybody I didn't get a crit with that actually maybe I did protest and show up
Two minutes left
Hello spy
You happen to be in the base red spy in the base
Blue spy base actually
Blue spy the base
Make sure no no mission or rap scallions are coming up behind us
Oh
Damn it
What how did that do
Just barely killed him no stay away from my medic trying to keep my way from you oh
I'm gonna have to catch him off guard
He's alive for sure
Oh
My goodness
How is he not gonna die from that I was gonna say oh
Get up in the air again I'm sorry. I can't protect you now
Believe my spread alone
Where's he
He's up top watch yourself. I don't have any I don't have any air blast left retreat retreat
Crit to the face I
Think we're gonna get it guys
Let's see if any any craziness happens at the very end. Oh
Don't jump
Probably a good idea to oh my god
I got came out of nowhere
Might as well sit on the point and just do this
This air blast anyone that tries to jump up here nice game guys good game
Oh
Alright, so I think I'm gonna transition now to play some balloons tower defense
I'm gonna play until I die. Well, hopefully I do
I'm gonna go one more life. So if I want next time I die
My last life
This streaming TF2 for about an hour and 10 minutes just about an hour full 60 minutes
Yeah, balloons is fun man
You
Ten hour games by
Is balloon five how can I play that?
I've never had balloons for my iPhone I got to do that my god
All right, so if you want to keep playing team fortress the only way it's gonna happen is it is like nine medics on me
You know what let's do it. Let's do it everyone everyone on blue go medic. We'll see how long this lasts
If you are on blue just go medic
And just octo heavy me I want to how long I will stay alive
This is the last life
Here we go
My god, oh
This is immediately
Is it even like possible to die?
It's possible to die
It looks like it's backstabbed there's no way we're gonna die
This is her still left
Oh
No, don't kill my medics I need them oh
No, we lost quite a few oh
No, oh
Oh, I'm gonna I'm gonna like pass out man. I just like left too hot oh
Oh my face hurts
We really know there's no way this is gonna work
There's no way this is gonna work if this actually works no way no my my battalion
I'm gonna get backstab it's gonna end it the backstab is gonna end it all oh
Don't kill me
Is that this oh my god, they're all going spy they're all going spy
Everybody went spy
Well you did it and I think we won did we win do we just win the game right there? Oh
Come on, we got a win we got a win I'm going again
All right, this is it this is it is it possible is it possible I
Thought we're gonna do it in one life that would have been ridiculous now
It's been like a joke such a total nonsense careful for spies
There's a spy back here somewhere look at all those stickies
That's all right. I'm off to all right
Oh, that's it that's it I'm dead I
Said it was gonna be one life turning into two and
Third times a job baby. Let's do it one more time
And after this I'm gonna play one round of blueness
God
This is it this is the real that this is it this is the real yet by die right here. I am rage quitting
Okay, I was just keep my back turned
Oh, definitely somebody's hiding in this room
This is chaos this is absolute total chaos go come on. Come on. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go jump down all the medics
Jump down watch out of the spy medic. Oh my god. He's killing everyone. Oh
My god, he's killing oh my god, they were all spies
How many of those medics were actually spies is the real question all right, that's that's gonna be it oh
I didn't get it in free oh
Meow yourself cat
All right guys, oh my goodness my throat hurts
From just like cackling for the last ten minutes this time because I'm gonna get this a little bit of time
I want to really
Get a tactic down because I usually I end I end the stream with this and I'm probably gonna end the stream with this as well
But I want to get a
Tactic down a real tactic
So let's see
So the the actual tactic is you're supposed to do
It's somebody gave me a tactic before and they said you have to do
It's you have to raise your right leg and then raise your left leg, but you don't raise the calf like that like that
Like that all my god come on
This is the first time I've ever stepped more than two steps in this game
So the goal tonight guys
The goal tonight is 50 meters I'm gonna do it
I'm gonna get to 50 you don't believe me just watch
50 meters right now once I get to 50 I can end the stream
50 meters come on come on slug your way over there you bastard 50 meters. We're doing it. I'm doing it
I don't care if it takes me till eight in the morning. I'm doing 50 meters or at least 40. We'll say 40 at least 40 meters or I
have
Oh my god, I'm okay. We're good. We're good. Gotta get to at least 40
Here we go baby. Come on. We're doing the niche. We're doing the niche right
We're doing the niche slug
I imagine how bad that would hurt. Can you imagine how awful that would hurt?
I'm I seem to be stuck here. I'm stuck here. Oh my god
There we go. What you there? We go there? We go come on keep it stay with it stay with it now
Gotta get to 30 or 40. Oh
My god, this is the best I've ever done
All right, all right slow down slow down a little slow down a little we're gonna hit 30 oh
My god, oh
My god
Slug slug slug slug slug slug slug slug slug slug
Oh
Oh when I say 40 but I said 30 or 40
Let's try and get it again. Oh god damn it. I'm so mad right now. I
Can't believe it. I can't believe it. I am so so mad right now
I
Slug slug slug slug slug slug slug I'm gonna get to 40 with the slug
Just you see
So now that we got a little slug going here. Let's talk about a story
So one time there was a slug named Jerma and the slug was I can't even talk because I'm like balancing on a loadfoot
All right transition here
No
All right, 30 plus 10 is 40 I did it
I just got to get down I got to get down on like the ground I got to have this like I got to get
I had it down the first time and you know what I screwed it all up
30 plus 10 is 40 I did it
There we go. There we go
Nice workout I'm doing here, huh
Slug slug slug slug slug slug slug slug slug slug slug
All right, we're at 10 I've made it to a combined a combined 50 meters can I make it to 40 doing this?
I
Don't think it's gonna happen. I really don't think it's gonna happen. Oh
Don't lose it
All right 30 plus 10 plus 13 is more than 50 I did it I made it
Do
Apparently I can walk up sideways
There we go just gotta keep this rhythm. I'm gonna keep the rhythm boom
Dint dint dint dint dint
Slug slug we're gonna slug slug everybody's got a slug. We're gonna slug slug
Everyday you got a slug till it's totally end-to-may you got a slug
Dimp the music helps the music helps the music helps
Why don't I stop singing the music helped let's do it again
This is the last time here we go
Damn, I never seen such a slow
Damn in my entire life
When you slug you got a slug when you go you go you got to get on the track and be super slow you got it
The music the music
Never never don't slow
Never stop flogging till you get to the end of town
I think that was a a combined over a hundred meters
Well, there we go
That's
That's gonna be it I've drained all my energy with this qual
At least I got 30 meters I said 30 or 40 a month. I actually said 40 or 50
But I'm gonna change my words. I'm gonna be like a politician and say well, I actually said 30 or 40
But yeah, that that was fun. That was fun
So everybody thank you so much for coming. This is the end of the stream
I need to go drink some tea my throat is a little dry and itchy
But anyways guys, thank you so so much for coming all you guys that stuck around
Means a lot you guys rock
So yeah stay tuned. I'm gonna off this will all be uploaded to YouTube at least this part
I'll make sure to get the TF2 and the at least the quad part uploaded to YouTube so
Be on the lookout for that
I'll be yeah, probably tomorrow tomorrow in the afternoon. How to swim
But the chat I cannot the chat just died from me right at the end here
So I'm sorry if I can't see anything that you guys are saying but
Thank you so much guys and I'll catch you guys all later. So take care everybody
peace
you