Who cares?
You know what I mean?
Gipsy shit.
I was working on a video.
I wanted to take a quick little break.
Maybe stream for an hour or two.
Go back to it.
So what is going to play?
So this game is a little different.
You are the bad guy in this game.
You have to kill the not Super Mario as a gumball.
I have a certain amount of time.
Sometimes you just have to say who cares turn on the stream.
I just screwed it up.
I have to restart.
What is the quick restart?
Right bumper?
That is good enough.
It is a neat little game.
It gets much harder.
This is just the first little area.
It is cold.
It is really cold.
It is extremely cold.
What?
It is going to get really cold tonight too.
I think it is going to be like 10 degrees or something around here.
Later on.
Oh, he got it.
How do I get three stars here?
I feel like that is going to be hard to do.
Because I have to, if you are wondering what is going on on the bottom of the screen here,
I have to start an amount of time to get three stars.
How am I supposed to get him to die before the first star is taken away?
I am not going for perfect, but going for completion.
I am going to make him jump this way.
I can do that over here.
Yes, you are playing as the goombas.
You play as the bad guys in this game.
Fuck.
How am I supposed to get up there?
I can't jump right now.
Is there something I am missing?
That is one star.
Don't ask me.
Damn it.
This game makes me mess myself.
I just didn't even mean to do that, but I got two stars.
I got three stars.
I am going to kill the plumber.
Free to play.
Is it really?
I got it on steam.
One star is better than three stars.
I screwed it up already.
I can definitely get him here.
Oh, come on.
I know I can get him here.
I am positive.
I am 100% positive.
He is not jumping on my head either.
I am going to call shenanigans.
I am going to get this.
This does remind me of an old mini clip game.
Last time I was able to watch a stream, I was off sick from work.
I just know.
You are going to be quick in this game.
If he gets to that pole, it is over.
Damn it.
There we go.
Seems like it is a lot like super house of dead ninjas where the steam version has some extra levels.
I saw, hey, this is cool.
I have to be the stop guy.
See, that first little area was this.
Come on, walk through.
Gotcha.
You can't get away from the stop.
I am already beaten this one.
I have to be way faster than that.
No, there is no snow at here yet.
I am still snowless at the moment.
That wasn't right.
Still three stars.
Well, Inky, I hope you had a good new year as well in holiday.
I can turn to a hammer brother now.
Let's redo this one.
Very slow.
He is standing completely still.
I am just trying to get like the three stars.
I have to suck it up.
I have something cool for Christmas.
I have a safety razor for Christmas.
I have a cold fashion, your grandfather 1930s shave razor.
I think it is wonderful.
I am going to do this shoe at three.
Let's see, one, two, three.
And then he is a movie.
I just have to jump over these and throw that.
I am going to throw it again.
That will let him go over.
Right at the bush.
Swinny Todd.
There we go.
Red Ranger just subscribed to the channel.
Welcome.
I didn't realize that one was going there.
I just put that one in.
My first and only emote ever.
It is currently processing through Twitch right now.
It is fucking terrible.
I am not paying attention.
Big one little one.
I got him.
The moment of the coaster.
First beta explode.
I like this one.
Can I jump too?
Hey, whoa, whoa, he shoots.
What?
How am I supposed to get him?
I can go underneath it.
I am going to hold left.
Three stars, right?
Yeah.
I will tell you, I will be honest with you.
I don't know what my emotes are going to be.
I have no idea.
This emote is just such an awful, it is just the fucking moon.
You will see it a little bit.
The timer doesn't start to move.
I get it.
Look at this guy in the chat.
Ghostly hell.
You are correct.
Now I am controlling two people at the same time.
This is going to be odd for me.
I don't know if he can kill that one.
Can I jump out of this?
I don't think I can even jump out of this.
I knocked him up.
I just can't wait till you guys.
Whoever is subscribed to this channel.
When stars streaming, you can spam the fuck out of his chat with the German moon emote.
That is all I care about.
This is just like a big boo.
I get it.
What just killed him?
He just jumped me.
I thought he couldn't see me.
This is not sponsored.
Can I jump through here?
I think I can.
Can I close that off?
Kind of confused here.
This is definitely where I can get him to go through that hole.
Wait, wait, wait, hold on.
Let's think about this for a second.
When that's closed, he's looking over here.
Open it so I can go down.
No!
I'm just going to have to catch him over here when he comes down here.
Yeah.
How long till we get moon butt?
The moon butt.
Tremor, why didn't you show up at our wedding?
I don't know, man.
Make him collect all the green coins to disable his powers.
How the hell am I going to get him to do that?
He's going to kill me right here.
Will he just want, and he's going to walk into all of them except for...
He's showing me this is a new mechanic in the game.
He's going to get them all.
I didn't even have to do anything.
I think they're just teaching me this.
Huh?
Okay, okay. I still had to kill him.
I let him get all the coins that I didn't do anything about it.
See, oh, this is going to be...
Okay, I'm going to have to give him a second here, guys.
No.
You know, I think I can hide in here, right?
Just wait till he's done and just follow him down.
Kind of.
Maybe?
No, I don't think so.
Yeah, actually, that was right.
Because I'm going to appear right here and he's going to walk right into me.
Fuck the other coin!
There we go.
I don't even care if I got no...
Only two stars on this one.
He tried to jump me.
I just barely beat that one.
Took me a really long time to realize that you're the ghost of nothing running, dude.
Yeah, I guess so.
Okay, so I got to...
Shit.
You jump and get those coins.
Kind of just have to get out of the way.
Get that last one.
Oh, you...oh, come on!
That was so not fair.
Grab that one.
Almost died.
Who's this?
I don't even know what happened.
I'm the cannon.
Okay, I was the cannon.
I thought I was the guy in the painting.
For a second, I thought I was going to shoot laser beams out of my eyes.
Alrighty.
I can do better than that.
I'm making fun of a lava.
Nope.
I will now.
Whoa!
I shouldn't have shot the second.
That was a stupid idea.
I shouldn't have shot the second time.
Please, please.
That doesn't sound sense.
There we go.
Thought I was the flag.
Oh, it gets real confusing when you have to control two different things at the same time.
I'm going to try to just air-shot them.
I'll be able to.
Forget about the ghost.
We're just going to go with a direct shot in the air.
I'll get him.
Don't worry, guys.
Just pop some popcorn or something.
He'll come back and he'll be gone.
That was total dog shit.
I hit him right in the face.
Ghosts just go down there.
Ghosts.
Yeah.
No, come.
I have to shoot him in the air.
Oh, I just figured it out accidentally.
He's at it again.
The green coins will make...
Alright, so shoot him.
Get a knock him up to the...
Oh.
Fuck.
Thank God they put that safety net right there.
I would never have done that.
I'll just shoot fireballs.
I'll smash to the ground while in the air.
Can I...
I could probably make that jump, huh?
Nope.
I knock him up in the air when I do that.
I got it.
Easy.
Why don't you walk forward?
There's no reason for him to walk forward.
Ooh, he's invincible.
Okay, I got him.
Hold on, hold on. I need a second to think about this.
Oh boy, hold on a minute.
I can't land on that.
Shouldn't I be able to?
I guess I can move.
Shit.
Fucking all four of them.
All four of them?
Why did I say four of them?
There was like 10 of four of them.
I gotta make it over here.
Damn. Where are the coins?
He's invincible.
I gotta drop him.
I have to drop him.
Shit, I dropped myself.
Do I have to...
Yeah, I gotta go all the way across.
This one's actually gonna be pretty tough.
I just need to get all the way around my fat fucking sloppy body.
See ya.
Hey, that was the first world I believe.
What?
Don't cry, Princess.
We have taken care of your stalker flummer.
You don't have to transfer to another castle anymore.
We won.
Yay.
Onto the next world.
This is the sand level.
What is this?
You need 15 stars more.
I need more stars.
That's total stars, I guess.
Whatever, we're just gonna play the...
I can go back.
World, or...
He's heading for the princess to destroy him.
Look at that face, shit, my god.
We got the princess.
Stop him.
I think I'm a bumpers head, I think.
Oh, come on, that is what you have to do.
You have to get him caught there and then...
You plumber.
Yeah.
No.
This one's tricky.
You gotta get him caught.
But he has such a huge frame hitbox.
I got him to... oh, I got a sub-emote coming in.
It just has to get approved.
Huh?
Jump over him and then...
Oh, I got it, okay.
So he's gonna jump over this one.
And then I have to let him jump on this one up to hit that one.
Sort of.
Got to catch him right in the middle.
Not gonna fool me.
He's gonna get the coins.
Oh, wait just a second.
He jumps the first one.
I don't want him to win.
Interesting.
Huh.
Yep, you gotta get him to drop down that way.
So he has to jump.
The first one and the second one right about here.
Almost got it.
There.
One, two, three, four.
Get the last one.
Oh, you prick.
They're getting a little harder here.
Jump that one.
What did I do?
He has to jump this one.
Get that coin.
Now he has flight.
Well, that's not fair.
So I just gonna wait and just jump right in his face.
He just jumped over me.
No, I gotta get him up here.
There we go.
I didn't have any reactions either.
Just my luck.
He's gonna get them all and then he's gonna fall and I'm gonna die.
So now he's gonna be running.
He's out of the flying.
The ears.
And then I just gotta be there right when he lands right here.
Nice pin point.
Hacking accuracy you have right there, by the way.
Shoot one down.
And then right there.
Chronic waffle.
Thank you for subscribing.
Welcome to the coaster.
You know the joke that we did before.
Boomerang.
And jump and use the boomerang.
Let me just hide.
I'm gonna play that again.
Thanks for subbing though.
Appreciate it.
Can have two out at one time.
Okay.
Can I get him too?
The leaf freak out at that.
He's not going that far.
I think I'm missing something here.
Does he jump at all?
He doesn't have to.
Huh.
Oh the fuck is happening.
Oh.
Okay.
All right.
Get him right in his touchy.
Got ya.
Spams him until...
Okay.
I have to...
Just throw behind me in the dodge.
No, this is a sock.
I have thrown a sock as a weapon.
That's great.
What am I now?
What the hell is that?
Oh.
All right.
I turn into a shell.
And I do the Cooper Trooper shell thing.
No. Get up.
Get up.
Fuck.
I think I feel like I have the right idea here.
But not the right execution.
Because he needs to hit himself into me.
I didn't work.
He died.
He fell down the hole.
Oh, Drexter.
Thanks for subscribing.
I was reading chat and I won.
Literally reading that somebody subscribed
and I beat the level.
I have no idea what happened.
Thanks for something, dude.
Yes, there isn't an emote coming later today.
I promise.
He can just fly, though.
What the fuck is going on?
Do I have to just move this all the way down here?
Because he can...
Hold on.
I need a second to think about this.
He can fly.
Do I have to bring this up?
Oh, would you look at that?
Would you look at that?
Are you serious?
That's what I have to do.
Why is he hitting it?
What the fuck just happened?
I don't even know.
I don't know.
Somebody else subbed too.
Man.
Thanks for something, dude.
I'm going to mess up your name.
A prey.
A Peru.
Thanks for subscribing.
I love you.
I don't know what to say.
I don't know what the fuck to say.
Ah.
So that's another bright idea.
I just have to knock him into the first one.
Maybe wait until he gets on this one.
Yep.
And then he...
Shit.
I have to go backwards, so that's for sure.
The block on the left.
Oh my god, he's a moron.
Come on.
You ready?
Oh.
I feel like that was it.
I feel like that was probably it.
Kind of.
Yeah, it was.
I just have to bounce him to this one.
Come on.
Get it.
Maybe not.
There it is.
Now what do I do?
Is it one of these times he's going to be an idiot?
Or is this just done?
Is this over?
Yeah, this is over.
Here comes the first one.
All right, I'm going to sit right here.
Let's damn it.
Damn it.
There it is.
He didn't pick it.
He didn't pick up the second coin.
He's got a lot of things to do.
I'm going to sit right here.
Let's damn it.
Damn it.
There it is.
He didn't pick it.
He didn't pick up the second coin.
He's got a lot of things to do.
He's got both.
Oh, you disappointed me completely.
Actually, that is what I have to do.
Grab the first one.
Grab the second one.
I'll get it.
I don't even know.
Fuck.
Why did I just hit restart?
That was so dumb.
I just had it right there.
I just had it.
He has to jump over twice.
Oh, this is going to drive me crazy.
Why is he not touching that coin?
Get it.
Just jump.
Just do the jump.
Like you've been trained your whole life for.
I'm going to jump over twice.
Why is he not touching that coin?
My whole life for.
Not Mario.
This music.
I'm going to hear this music in my sleep.
I got him.
Three started.
First beat of throw up to three spikers.
Move sideways.
It would be deep.
Oh, you get to be the most his name.
Look at the key to.
Right.
And I'm right his head.
I got him right in the crown of his head.
Well, they can't die.
Really.
How can they walk in there?
They don't die.
Will he just walk?
Oh, I have to control him.
Right.
I forgot.
All right.
This is what we're going to do.
I put him here.
You fucker.
One here.
Okay.
Go for it, Mario.
I don't know what to do.
What do I do?
I don't know.
I think that's it.
I'm pretty sure that's it.
I'm just going to drop him onto him.
It's the only thing i'm going to,
I'm just going to drop him on him.
Just like playing magic on a different Minecraft.
I'm just going to try to do that another way.
Almost 1 a.m. here in South Korea.
That's late. We are on opposite sides of the world.
Have a good sleep.
That's way too long for me to understand what was going on.
No, you don't think I know what to do?
You guys think I'm some kind of dummy, huh?
Yeah, three stars.
Okay.
I thought I was going to get three stars, but turns out I'm only going to get one.
Got you.
And then when I'm just staying right here.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute. Right here.
And then right here.
Am I going to play more vermin tide?
I mean, really the reason why I'm streaming, I'm just taking a break from making my latest video.
I ran into a spot where I'm just way home.
Move out and in of the box.
Oh, I'm a little chump.
But my next video is just taking time to make.
It's just like it's like I'm taking a break.
I'm just like, I don't want to do it.
I'm just going to stream for like an hour or two and then maybe do something.
Maybe we're going a little more.
Oh, one is up and one is down.
Smart.
He didn't even have to do it.
He just jumped and threw his stuff.
This is a fireball one.
He killed it.
All right, well, I'll just wait till he comes down here then.
What do I care?
He's going to get the coins. Just shoot him.
That's why.
So right when he's right in the middle is when I'm going to pop up.
So right now.
What does he do?
So I have to wait till he gets down to the lower like the butt crack and the lower left
and then I'll be all right.
Walk into it.
I can turn and I can shoot guys.
I can turn and I can shoot.
Did not know.
Oh, that's kind of awkward.
Does this even hurt him?
I don't think I can hurt him yet.
How am I going to get him to jump here though?
Shit.
Oh, that was too busy pay.
Shoot the fucking right way you moron.
This is much more awkward than it looks. Trust me.
All right, just going to keep it right there.
Just look at the zero stars. I don't care.
So you can kill him.
Obviously I have to wait till he turns and boost him up.
What are you doing?
No.
You're going to scare him.
So this comes up.
Drop that. This comes up.
I'm not doing this one right at all.
I think I have to boost him up.
So he jumps up on this one.
So jump.
Or does he have to hit both?
Maybe he has to hit both.
Make them both come out.
Yeah, there we go.
And there it is.
One, two, three, four.
Gotcha.
My next plane how this works.
You play as the enemies and you have to kill the AI Mario.
Swim sideways with a deep head and swim up with A.
Now you're a fish.
Just get killed.
100 lives lost.
Cool.
Airborne archer.
Welcome to the jock shockers.
Enjoy your stay.
You are now a certified licensed shock joker.
Shit.
Maybe I should wait till he bumps into the wall.
I don't know what to do.
I'm going to send him sideways.
See you.
Bye bye.
Same deal, right?
That was three stars gone immediately.
I can just lock him over here, right?
I don't know.
I wonder how do you do that one with three stars?
Yeah, if you're a subscriber to this channel,
you obviously are certified shock jokking jock shocker.
I mean, why wouldn't you be?
I don't know.
This one I think is just patience.
He will jump.
He will, okay, he will not jump to go to the flag.
I can do this one a little more clearly.
Make him get all the ones on the bottom.
Make him jump and get this one.
Maybe not all of them, but at this point, you know,
who gives his shit?
Just try to get him to collect the coins.
I'm going to stay over here for this.
I do not want him to get.
He obviously has to get that one last.
I went down to one star.
Damn it.
So how I hope to let him kill him when he does this?
That's time, this right?
Fucking it.
Eat my ass.
That was uncalled for.
That was just completely uncalled for.
Sorry.
I know everyone asks about Germany and German rumble,
but do you actually have plans for another one?
I'm not asking.
I don't even need to read the rest of this.
I can give you an answer.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, a thousand times.
Yes.
You're just going to have to trust me on this one.
I want to see a new one just as bad as you do.
You can quote me on that.
And it will happen.
It's going to happen.
I'm glad you are as enthusiastic as I'm glad you're enthusiastic about it because it's
like one of my favorite things to do.
And this one will be absolutely no exception.
Zero stars.
Spring 2016 is when you can know that you'll see it.
I am looking forward to it.
More than probably any video I've probably ever made.
Or ever will make.
That's all I'm going to say.
Swim sideways with a deep head and swim up with a.
So just to be the octopus guy.
I did it again.
I just pixel perfect.
I did it like a fourth time in a row.
Just let him walk into you.
I did it again.
Thank God the pixels lined up.
Well, that's different.
That is a different pattern.
Right there.
Right in the V.
Just going to swim in the V.
We just like the mighty ducks.
That's the idea.
But I've got to get it.
Got it.
I got a couple of little ones now.
I think I get what they want me to do here.
I think it's collect all these little guys and just stick them out and have them walk into it.
That's what we're going to do.
And that's what we needed to do.
Oh, shit.
What am I doing?
He's invincible.
Will he just fall down and collect these?
No, I got him.
Ah, this sucks.
So he's going to shoot right when he lends.
Ah.
Just come on.
Just get it.
That's so trolled.
Really is.
I'm just...
Then he doesn't even do it.
No, don't look at that.
Goodness.
Fuck.
That's kind.
Just be easy.
That's should...
He shouldn't have even done it like that.
He should have landed in a shot.
That was not even something I would consider cool.
Why is he not jumping?
He's supposed to jump when he sees me.
He's supposed to jump over me.
Just like that.
He did it.
Now just don't do not die from the...
He's used months.
We're gonna get tickets for the next drama rumble.
Well, it's gonna be free and on YouTube.
I die.
This woman's dash fall would be.
Come here.
Get away.
I'm gonna get you.
I'll get you.
Gotta be fast, but...
Gotta fucking quick.
Gotta be quick.
Can I fit through here?
No.
Okay.
Ooh.
So that's dropping.
Okay.
So smash.
Smash.
Fuck.
Okay, slow it out.
Slow it out.
Yeah, bring him right where you'll want him.
Okay.
Slow, slow, slow.
It literally drops.
Did he seriously squeak by?
He squeaked through and now he stuck over here?
I don't even feel like that.
That's even...
Just restart it.
Not on my watch.
That's some aggressive clicking.
Yeah, it kind of is.
I get it.
I know what the woman to do.
They want me to go back and forth.
Shit.
I gotta fall all the way down here.
Not that far.
Right there.
All right.
Right in the middle.
I'm thinking right in the middle, right?
I was holding down the button, by the way.
He's not going to hit me from right in the middle.
Of course he will.
Of course he'll still hit me.
Of course he'll hit me there too.
I've about to do a little bit of, I've been raging.
One, two, three, four.
Smash.
Ah!
So you gotta do two spaces.
When he gets these coins, please do not.
Please come on.
I'm being a little whiner right now.
I'll get it.
And then one, two.
Now I just have to not die.
And then right when he grabs that coin.
Wipe it off.
Wipe off.
I give one star.
It's perfect.
All right.
What is he supposed to be grabbing?
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Go all the way up.
You can shoot up.
That's such a bullshit.
I had the right idea.
Gotta go all the way up to the top.
I do that again.
I swear to God, I'm gonna put this controller into the drywall.
It hurts.
Why is it bouncing?
There should not be an added fucking flop on this.
You should be fucking bouncing.
No, God.
Ugh.
Get out of the way.
Out of the way.
I don't care about three stars.
I just want to win.
Crush him.
Nice relaxing game.
Don't cry, Princess.
We have trapped your stalker plumber forever in the minus world.
We are now safe here on this island.
We won.
Is there a minute I can go back here?
No.
15 more stars.
Are there even 15 stars available to get here?
Five?
Yeah, I have to do three stars on every single level.
Fuck that.
I can't see you.
We are in the ice level now.
Why is he like a maniacal psycho?
He will pay with his blood.
So he is still winning.
I'm assuming there is going to be a lot of slip in his lead.
And it's a nice level.
What a dummy.
Okay, so we obviously have to just get him stuck.
Can't jump.
I'm not going to jump over it.
I'm not over that.
How is he not jumping on that?
I'm going to have to get it next time.
Oh, I freaked out again.
I hate controlling two characters.
I walked off the screen with this other guy.
I'm going to get him stuck in the game.
Numbers are plummeting.
And then I get to follow him.
I'm just running quick enough.
I still might be able to do it.
I'm going to get him stuck.
Why am I blue?
Interesting.
It hurts my head.
You have to hold right the whole time.
Right is left and left is right down there.
Oh, forget that.
I'm assuming he's going to go like that.
Oh, let him look as bark.
He's going to be easy on him.
Oh, I just hit the blast.
I have to last the whole time with it.
Is this the only safe spot here on the right?
Kind of.
I wish I could jump a little bit everywhere.
It sounds like me.
Where are you taking my blood off my back?
Young creepess Jump.
It's me.
Don't.
two seconds two one I got it hey sweet chili Charlie what's his name oh
sweat sweat pants man I don't know hey thanks to something welcome to the
welcome to the welcome to the shit stand nice to meet you
this is my can too hard for me to do
does the moon work does German moon work yet when is that gonna work
but I just just scare him to jump in right so like this no
how do I get him to jump there have to be in the bottom I guess it has to be
when they're facing this way I don't know
how do I get him to confuse again
I guess it doesn't work
oh I just I just did it how did I do that oh I get it I get it I get it I
figured it out I got it I got it I got it I got it I got it I got it I got it
gonna be like that no you dumb idiot stupid wrong wrong wrong
wrong wrong wrong idiot stupid dumb moron
I kind of was right why is it not working after time
part of me feels like this shit just should be working but it just ain't
the other half of me just wants to never play the game again but with this far
right what actually makes him jump I don't know I've no damn I will what what
actually makes this fucking asshole jump I don't know
is that really it guys get the secrets and fucking universe here now that
guy just might have figured out the secret to the fucking universe guys
just to see the fucking universe
check out this little secret fucking universe come on god damn it I'm not happy
why is there's not a professional streamer gamer it looks whatever you're
saying stealth what are you talking about
he just clipped through did land on me he clipped through this fucking asshole
this stupid plumber this dumb plumber guy thought he could just clip through
now I'll give you a clip it's the backwards right is left and left is right
it's gonna screw me up a thousand times
nice screw it up again so close so what are you doing wait till he gets down
here I forget everything okay I remember I forget I remember I forget I forget
right is left and left is right why did he jump there of all places why did he
jump there and that was so dumb he did it again telling me so one of the
developers is controlling the character right now causing me all kinds of hell
I just wish the clipping I wish he actually had to jump on me I got a feeling
this stream will end soon maybe that was it but he didn't do it he didn't go the
all the way I should get it right here I didn't do it again there it is
finally what is it if I got a little hat does it mean anything
am I getting my good slowdowns right there what the hell man this is a two-dimensional
game I should not be getting three-dimensional lag in a two-dimensional game
all right I'm just gonna have to wait for right he's eventually he has to jump he's
gonna have to jump eventually right
to do yeah well all right yeah we're gonna both I'll just bore him to death
it doesn't matter he's not going anywhere he's not gonna move
what am I supposed to do then go take a shower yeah everyone just got mad at me for
not for moving and I'm not moving and then nothing happened we're gonna move I have
a little an opportunity like I have a small window see how I'm like walking still I sure I can't
fly with this hat then they tell me about the snowballs when did they tell me about the snowballs
they never told me about the snowballs well just got to make it bounce correctly
I wish I knew about that before saved me a lot of bullshit
hit him right in his nuts
yeah going right kills you you just have to it you just got to get this like perfect
that was not perfect one two okay maybe right on the back end of it I'm gonna have to get it right
on the right side like right there if I can close I don't care about the time or anymore
I'm gonna win talk about lose my goddamn mind thank you thank you just spam spam snowballs who cares
that was actually gonna work kind of I feel like I'm playing one of those elaborate mini golf games
where you have to land it perfectly that's what I have to do here I have to use that kind of little
double jump that you get from throwing the snowball to get back there it is
gorgeous I got confused because I didn't know I didn't I thought I was still
controlling the little snow people really going I don't know zero stars that's just not
cool
there we go I gotta get him to jump to the left who is the water
so it's one two one two I'm not gonna lie guys I could sit here and like figure this out but I
kind of just want to do this until it works I could care less right now
and there we go using all Oculus Rift for pre-order January 6th I probably puke if I play Oculus Rift I
will throw up if I play anything on Oculus Rift I'm missing something I gotta get him to hit the spikes
or not just shoot him right in the stomach that works oh that was so close
that would be quicker than that shit he's hitting the other one accidentally I don't want him to
here we go all right we can toss his brain out I'm assuming I need to keep both of
their helmets yes okay see you later do I break stuff when I get angry no not really I kind of
just say a couple of swear words and then I'm done with it and go on with my day
actually does they regenerate don't want to die I'm not just get a money comes back on the other side
they am I crazy or did they regenerate last time I felt like they did
shit I hit the button accidentally I hit the stupid how am I gonna kill him by the way if I get him to
do this how am I gonna actually kill him I didn't really think about that
what if he lands on one does it will they stay dead or will they come back they stay dead I think
I just would be perfect when he lands like right when he lands I'm getting some weird slowdowns
here too by the way right when he jumps right here oh it's definitely like I'm in the lag it's
definitely lag spot all lag there we go
he
I had almost had the first try.
See ya.
That's three stats.
Kind of lucky.
That was like the same level without the whole.
Whoa.
This is gonna take a little bit of a.
Alright, let me just.
Let me do something here.
I can't go through it even when it's.
I thought I could go through it or something.
Now I'm gonna pee my pants.
Hopefully I can end this soon.
Shit, that's a way to go though.
Shit, fuck.
Alright, I think this might be the last level.
What's wrong with my guy?
What was the point of that level?
These guys don't really do anything.
Okay, they do not get hurt from the fire.
Can they get stepped on?
I want to see if they can get stepped on.
You know, I'm gonna assume these are like the bone characters in Mario where they come back to life and I'm gonna have to make somebody go down.
Let's see if that theory is true.
Yes it is.
I have to set these guys up in a spot where.
Oh, and especially needing to pee is it gonna be tough.
They have to stay on their respective levels, I think.
One.
Space like this for a reason.
Shit.
That may have just been my ticket to make him go up there.
Kind of, right?
I think.
Why does he go jump and get that first one?
So he has to make him go up and then.
I think now I have to bring him down.
Yeah.
No, stop doing the things I don't tell you to do.
We're gonna have a gap problem.
Okay, now technically I shouldn't need to care about that guy.
But now how does he get up there?
He blew it already.
It's the way that they're spaced.
I almost need another person.
Kind of confused on how you get him to jump over there.
Unless I have to, I kind of have to bring them down, right?
Yeah, I'm gonna be slow with this one.
Oh, you fucking.
I don't think you can do it like that.
Because he'll just hit it every time.
Long to fight that.
Give your subscriber welcome to the.
Whatever I'm calling people.
Thank you so much.
Thank you very much. Welcome. Welcome.
The way that they're spaced.
Almost leads me to believe.
Right now this might sound crazy.
This might sound crazy. I am crazy. It's wrong.
I don't think he can jump up here.
Can he even make that jump?
Hey, he gets up there.
But shit.
I think I got it. I think I got it.
I think I got it.
I'm pretty sure I got it.
I'm pretty sure I figured it out.
I think he gets that one.
He'll jump over here.
And then this needs this guy needs to be over here.
Because then he can he can jump this way up there.
Oh.
Wait, how do I kill him?
How do I kill him?
I don't know how I'm gonna kill him.
And I'm scared because I don't know.
Okay, I know how to do it.
I got a I think.
No, I don't.
How do I kill this guy?
No. What do I do?
Somebody please tell me before I die.
Oh, that's what you gotta do.
I don't even care about zero stars.
I gotta say I gotta be so slow with this.
New past zero.
I don't care.
Oh, right.
I was thinking I could clip him.
This music doesn't fit by the way.
This music is like the price is right.
This is the song they play when you guess correctly
the amount of money something is on the price is right.
Then Bob Barker calls you to the stage.
Does that kill me?
Yes, it does.
Wait a minute.
What, what, what can, why can those be exploded?
Cheeky.
Very clever.
Bob Barker is dead, German.
Well, who's the new guy?
Drew Carey, right?
That one was pretty easy.
I just gotta, I get it.
I thought I got it.
I don't know if it's explode.
You need to drop him.
See ya.
This is it.
Last level.
I'm gonna take the giant Furby and jump with the giant Furby.
And then bounce again and get him to get the coins.
Right?
This is the last boss.
So what makes him jump?
This.
So how does he get the coins?
I kinda have the right idea.
Can I blow him up?
I'm gonna blow him up.
Ah!
Explode him into the coins.
Will he actually, yeah, he doesn't seem to get hit by the explosive to go up.
We're gonna restart it.
Now why does that matter?
Having them go up that high.
There has to be a reason for that.
I gotta wait till he go.
You didn't touch the coins.
You worked so all over those coins.
Now I'm just getting sloppy.
I don't even know what I'm being sloppy on, be honest.
There we go.
Letting the gentleman beat the game.
Cause, sick ya.
That should be it, right?
Unless there's a super secret level.
This is a super secret level.
A secret.
Oh, man.
Too many things to have to think about at the same time.
Cause I can get, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Can I get hit by any of these?
No, so I was freaking out for no reason.
Just put him all the way over here.
Bring down a guy.
And now we just slowly inch our way over.
We just screw it all up.
That works too.
Just start it over.
Cause then I can get a good read on it.
Don't fall off.
I'm falling off.
Shit.
Shit, shit, shit, shit, shit.
How far can I go?
That's how far I can go.
I'm perfectly timing these to get hit by the fireballs.
Oh, man.
This one is not easy.
This sucks.
This sucks so bad.
Thankfully.
New best.
Another one.
That was easier than the last one.
Tony, more of these are there.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no.
I already know.
I'm just going to be able to do this.
I just have to focus on the guy in the lower right.
Eventually the bomb's going to drop.
And I can blow it up.
Come on.
You freeze.
Look it ready.
I'm tapping jump right now.
There's a point where you cannot move.
I can pee.
I got a pee.
I got a goma.
That's so annoying.
And there's a point where I have to bring him to the right too.
Damn it.
I'm not really sure a good place to be standing.
Just take it slow.
Only three more times.
No, I can get him right here.
I'm getting too close.
I think that might be it.
Yay.
This is it, Princess.
It's over.
Hey, it's over.
We have frozen your stalker plumber forever.
You are now safe here in this ice cat cell.
Period.
We want to be actually win.
I don't know.
Yay.
Developed by Techie Town.
Code and Design by Barry Silver Street.
Art and Design by Gumbo.
Oh no.
Is he Emanov?
Sound effects by Sac Strifer.
Music by Jim Kulabowski.
Hey, special thanks.
Dojo.com.
Bryce Fitzsimmons.
My wife and kids and this guy and boom zap and attainment to studios Jeremy.
Jeremy, that's me Jeremy.
Michael, why am I doing this?
It's fun.
That was a fun little game.
That was a fun little game, guys.
I want to see if there's something.
There's a secret.
There's definitely a secret.
There's always a secret.
Who's FGL?
I'm just waiting to the very end.
Just the secret that's always there.
Here we go.
The secret credits level.
Thank you for playing.
And by the way, I forgot to mention here's the secret.
Gonna pop up.
The end.
Question mark.
Okay.
Yeah.
What is the secret?
Fine.
There is something that I do want to see.
I got some notification.
No.
No notification.
What's this?
These are my trophies.
See?
A beat level 36.
I beat it.
I got a bunch of trophies.
Beat speed run mode and map three in under six minutes.
Kill the plumber 100 times.
Kill the plumber 9 times.
I'm going to assume this is 250.
Kill the plumber before the timer runs out on level 23.
These are like achievements.
That's cool.
It might be worth trying.
Okay.
I'm going to peak.
So those of you that need to peak, OP.
And then we're going to, I just to see what this even is.
I'm going to try to get three stars on a few more levels.
So I can potentially unlock that.
Whatever that held that is.
I don't know.
A couple minutes.
I'm going to do a few more.
Am I getting mad?
Get me a dog.
Ato.
He's sitting on that mat so much sitting on that mat.
He's sitting on the toilet.
Who is it like a 60 second piss?
You guys have never had one of those before?
You tell me no, you're lying.
Alright, this one.
One star, what did I do wrong here?
Yeah, I couldn't figure this one out.
I can't get up there.
Unless I'm missing something which I don't think I am.
How am I supposed to get up there?
How do you not get one star on this level?
Ato.
Bibi.
See, you don't even.
Oh, they don't move thing, right?
Yeah, okay.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's before I remembered you could even do that.
Okay, let's...
Let's just walk.
There we go.
So that is all of them completed on this as three stars.
I still need 12 more.
Alright.
Now, he does he move.
I wonder if he moves.
No, I guess he's got a...
Oh, he does move.
He does move.
Okay.
That's an odd timing.
One, two, three, four, five, six.
After six seconds.
How long does this take?
One, two, three.
Okay, so at three seconds, I need to throw it.
One, two, three, four, five.
No, at four seconds, one, two, three, four, five, six.
One, two, three, four, five, six.
What the fuck, one, two, three, four, five?
Thankfully, I'm not as dumb as I look.
I'm way dumber.
Okay, so that's what you gotta do.
Wait, and then throw it right in this space.
That's not cool.
So I'm gonna move after the second one.
Shit, that's hard.
That is hard.
Actually, that would be it.
One, two, three, four, five.
This one was atrocious-why.
See, move again.
I think he's going to do the same thing.
That, come on.
Now, that was what we like to call in this industry.
That's what we like to call a real stanker.
Wait too late.
I don't know anymore, do I need?
I'll pay more.
What was wrong with this one?
I was moving away too much.
Okay, so I thought I could get through that whole thing.
The very last second right when this one comes all the way over is when you have to start moving.
And there it is.
This one, 21.
It's extremely easy.
Not much more to go.
I need five more.
31, 32, 33, 34, 35, 36.
You just have to three-star every single level.
Shit, I don't know.
This is going to be tough.
Considering that I need to get this like perfect.
Oh, boy.
So it needs to be right.
Right?
No.
I didn't do it right.
I actually still might be able to get three if I can make it all the way down here.
Ah.
Oh, shit.
I don't know if I...
I just got to get over there.
I can't.