Hoping up. Please I'm gonna have to lower the volume on it too because it is pretty loud
Oh
Marty getting the chills and
Abracadabra can you see it? I hope so
Think you can well, I gotta get the chat up here. I cannot hit escape though
That's one the one big thing cannot hit escape
You move this
So I can see what you guys are saying
There is that
No, no the chat does kid frittany where oh, can I move this I can excellent
Here we are one more second guys
This
Here
Perfect perfect now I can see what everybody's saying
Tanplace lender
Oh
Boy oh boy
So the goal here tonight guys is I'm gonna try and
Um, I can get all the pages. I'm gonna try and beat this game. I'm gonna do it
Let's go
Doon doon doon doon doon doon doon doon. I'm gonna beat slender
Definitely not gonna beat slender because it is like
Impossible to beat is once you get like seven pages he just eats your soul
Here comes page one guys welcome to the sketch dream
Happy preliminary Halloween. Let's do oh wait, uh
Never hold on oh that just ruined my whole entrance hit E not quick
Here we go
I only have the headphone and one ear. I know you can call me whatever you want to call me
I thought I just arm. I thought I just saw
This I'm gonna try to upload this to YouTube. So if you are gonna miss some of this I'm gonna try to get the whole thing up there
If you're watching this on YouTube, hey, what's up? How you doing?
Did I just walk in like a circle? All right, let's see what
I'm not looking behind me everyone's like oh, oh behind you behind you. I ain't looking behind me
I need to I'm gonna go left
Oh
Whoa, I hear static where is he I hear static right now where the hell is he I hear static right now where is he
He's probably right there
Ah what what where is he I don't even know where he is all the hell is where is he oh
My god, where is he
I
He's probably like right if I if I ready
No, he's right there. He's right there. He's right there run to the tree run to the tree run to the tree run to the tree the tree of life
Hmm
Don't look for him. I you have but that's the thing you have to look for him
You have to like turn and look
At a row page two he's as long as an or he is
I'm gonna be fine. He's right behind me. Just right up my ass
I'll tell you a thing or two cylinder man
You want to mess with me?
I'll give you the one tube. Why am I taking my hands off I'm like oh
Let me make like a joke and die. That's a great idea, Jeremiah
Is there anything on here?
Can I like go in there and like go to the bathroom? I thought he was like right there. Come on kids, three go
He's still behind me. I know exactly where he is
I wish I could run
Damn I wish I could sprint
I can't spread no
I love reading the chat. It's so fun
I'm gonna I can't believe I said I was gonna beat this game
There's no way I'm gonna beat this game. You kidding me
Are you kidding me
Did I just walk in a giant circle? No, there's there's I can't see. Yep, that's the next part. I gotta go there
You needed something to fall asleep to Larry. I'm sorry. This is what you have to fall asleep to
It would be tough if I was you
Slender and SCP containment breach
See it's good to have you guys here in the chat because when I play this game alone if whatever I play like scary games alone
This there's no hole. I it's it's so terrifying. I can't
I'm much better like looking over and seeing all you guys in the chat makes it so much better
Because now I
Won't like crap my pants except I already did like in the first 30 seconds of this game started
I'm scared right now. My teeth are chattering
Oh
There was no indication that that was gonna happen
One down
Only three more games to play oh
Man that hurt my whole body
Wow
I thought I was supposed to play static whenever he gets like close to you
Geez
All right um we're gonna do this again
Hmm
We'll load it up again, but doing Slender again
Yes, of course I want to run it
And
I honestly like that
I did not I really did not think that he was there
I really did not think he was there
How's that look
Now I didn't want to do that I wanted to go to here
Okay, it looks fine
Not big surprise
All right, looks good let's go
Drag you over here
See the bad part about these uh these like SCP and Slender and stuff
If you try to hit escape or get like to a menu or something you just close the game
So you have to I have to be uh
I have to be a little weird with it try to keep it on the sign drag the chat over
Do I want to hug yeah I do especially after that
All right, what I get three pages four pages. Yeah, that was great great job Jeremy. You you did a great job there
Let's go
I
I gotta get ready for this one
Last time I was stupid and I turned around and looked at him and said hello
Page one all right, I got to I got to think of a plan of action here before I pick this up
Where's the page? What the hell?
Okay, there's the page one. I'm gonna go straight through here
No, wait, do I want to go there? Go straight down there. Let's see
We're gonna go straight down there
Here we go ready go
You can't run you can't hide you can't get away from the man
So I already here static
I think I already here's the no idea. Oh great. I think I decided to run into offense now. I'm gonna turn around
He's gonna be right there
Cool great
Hmm
I
Shouldn't ran. That was a dumb idea. I shouldn't have sprinted
Oh, you know what I wish there was a stamina bar somebody said the stamina is like it's hard to read
I wish there was a bar right there like right on the screen that said all you have like this percentage or this amount
I just walk into circle
Man, I hate this I hate this guy
Where's like the gun so I can turn around just just unload on his and touch that
Where's that water
I think this water in this game. Oh is that water or static? There's no water
I'm not looking behind me. I'm not I'm not making that same mistake
See last time I look behind me that was a massive mistake
What do you guys say? Let's see
Straight jump and you can jump in this game. I don't think you can jump
I thought that was him right there by the way like whatever the hell that is
Oh, we have some moss on the tree. That's painted just like slenderman's body
No, I'm not looking behind me don't ever look behind you
Worst idea
You know what's people to talk about the spy and slenderman think about it. He's in a suit
He has like no face. He's got like a mask on or whatever. I don't maybe maybe it doesn't have a mask on
Tall guy in a suit that gets behind you
Slenderman is a spy
What I hate being in here get oh
Hi fantastic
How you doing man good to meet you get me out of this hellhole of a bathroom
I don't even care. Screw that friggin paper. I don't even care
I'll lose the game. I don't even I don't even want to be in there if I get stuck in there with him
I'm dead over I'm dead. I'm so dead right now
I'm gonna back up right into him. It's gonna scare me. I'm not gonna get scared. I'm not gonna get scared this time
I'm gonna look him right in his eyes
Run
I'm gonna spit that out
I was if he jumped at me right there. I would have spit that all of my screen in the stream what I had to like and
Getting stuck on trees now. That's not cool
Probably right behind me and it's gonna make that noise
Move faster you
Piece of
Oh, there's so many things like it say right now. I don't even know what adjective to use
What's what somebody say jerma is lend him and but I don't know I don't even know what that said I'm too scared
There's another one right here
He's probably this asshole is probably gonna be standing right here
I wish I could just take my headphones out of the here this music
I'm gonna have to turn around
Yeah, I gotta turn around great
Oh, is that him oh no, no, it's not go
New way
I'm gonna
I can't look high surface. I can't look at the screen
Oh
He's he's like to the left to be he's like right there and I I need to go that way
Mmm
Oh, this is the worst especially because I can't run anymore
Oh
This is it for slender I can't take slender anymore. It's it's I can't take it anymore. He's when he's gonna
You know what this ready for this guys
I'm gonna run right out of
Wait, no no opening opening make sure you know, we're gonna just we're gonna check we're gonna do a quick check
Hey, where are you right behind me
Yep, he's right behind me
You know now I'm not so scared because I know the son of a bitch is right behind me
And he's a slow slug
Catch him up to me
Good luck catch it up to me. I got I got legs. I can run
He has legs too
What's that okay
He's definitely still right behind I'm gonna grab it. Oh my god
I
Can feel him behind
Is there a note there? I don't even care
I
Can't even turn to look and see if there's a note I think there is
What if I do this no, I just gonna keep moving
Oh
This is another note. I see it
Is that a note?
Okay, good
Grab the note grab the note
Hey, can't run. Yeah, I wish I had more stamina. Oh, is that him? I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know who knows. I don't know man
I
Hmm
Did I already get the one on the tree I don't remember I
Don't know if I got the one on the tree. I don't think I did
Go
I don't want to turn around to grab this got it hello
It's gonna do it. He's right here
It's he's right here. I do it. I do it. See I know it
I know it I could feel him I could feel him like right up my
He was he was grabbing onto my butt cheeks and squeezing him. That's like how much I felt him
Selenderman
I'll punch lend a man in his in his cylinder face
I'll knock his like teeth out
What
All right, I I I can't play Selenderman anymore. I can't play you anymore. I'm gonna move on to
You
If I can tame and breach
Actually containment breach is probably worse than stencelenda
You
Containment breach
All right, this game is loud as hell memory access violation
What the hell does that mean?
Hold on
What
Memory access violation I'll give you a violation
I'll like park my car at double parking after seven o'clock and I'll get a violation
I'll show you that was a bad joke. I apologize for that one
All right, let's look for playing the SCP-087-B is next up on the list
Next up on the list. Let's do it. Here we go
Oh wow, this is loud
This is loud
Gotta turn you down. Oh god. Oh my head
Wow, that's loud you are loud as hell wow
Sorry about that. That was bad that was loud
Why can't I
I'm like stuck in this god for saving thing
Wait, wait, oh wait, whoa
Hold on hold on a second that was weird
That was weird
You'll done
Yeah, I'm gonna turn it down the window was that loud for all you guys to that was like
For like somebody's shopping in the side of the head
Hmm, okay, I can turn it down from here. All right, let's do this again
I
In fact, oh no, I'm gonna I'm gonna turn this all the way down
Let's see
Can I open that up open up
All right
Oh
Can I I got no no why am I stuck again?
What in the name of God
Keeps it keeps on locking out my mouse and I can't change anything
Let's see if I can catch it quick
Yeah, I gotta I gotta hit the I gotta make direct show go through. I know it's a black screen. I'm sorry
Let's try this again
I gotta catch it right when it pops up so I need this open
And can you can make make make make oh I had it
Move over here so I can catch you quicker
Got it. No, now it's a zero. Damn it. I'll get it. I'll get it
There we go. Okay, bingo bingo
Please proceed with caution
All right here we go oh 8 7 b
B is for bowl
You know the rest
Going downstairs
So this is like a hallway
Simulator and stuff jumps out at you and scares you and it's horrible
Oh
We had three
I don't want to go down there screw that
Scoot grew that
Oh
8 7 b you are now entering
Whoa, hello, what the hell was that
It's been a long time since I played oh 8 7 b so I forget whatever I forget what happens
It's been a while
You
Can I can I just say that we live in the 21st century
How can you have a radio that sucks at that bad
I mean really seriously what like where did you get that radio dude your radio sucks big time
You might want to replace the batteries. Why is everything good and all we're looking
What's going on why
There's something right here
Yeah, why why everything's changing everything looks like weird now
Um, maybe I'm just going absolutely crazy
For more 7 oh, I don't know how much longer I can do scary games
Oh, hi
Thanks for closing in on me. I appreciate it
Come on something jump out of me. I'm ready. I'm ready to just just just throw up on my screen come on
I know what this means. I know what this means something's gonna happen right now something's gonna happen right now
I know it I've been here before we've been down this road before man. Yeah, I see you. I see it. I can see it
It's
What yeah, hi
What was that noise what is going on what is going on I am I'm ready to just jump and run
Oh
No
Floor number no, okay
Hey, whoa, hi
Damn man, come on. Hey, how are you? How's your house your kids and your wife and your and your son
How's that I heard he plays baseball now good to see him. Yeah, he's growing. He's big
Hmm, I need the chat tell pull on chat. What do you think?
What do I do
All right, okay, I have the support from the chat. I'm ready. I'm ready to play the game now
Oh, I don't even want to see it. I don't even want to see it. I know it's gonna something
So was it a bug what the hell was that I
I don't know if you could just see that right there, but I did a bubble just came out of my mouth a floating like soap bubble
Don't ask me how the hell that happened
God
I'm about to rage put this game because I I can't handle it because this game I know is horrible when it comes to things jumping at you
Hmm
What if I just put my head down oh
Man, this is worse than this is probably worse than slender
I'm about to escape I'm my hand is on escape right now about to just exit the game
So on my hand is on escape
The second I see something I don't like it's I'm hitting it
Then
Come on show me something scary so I can just insta quit the game
It's throwing all kinds of noises
Bye, see you later
Have fun have fun slender man whatever the who the hell you are
You
You see that damn thing
It was like right here on the screen that was hard that was horrible
Oh wow
So stupid oh
All right, give me a second get that one took a lot of out of me right there
Oh
I think I might have to change my pants let's see let's let's let's check
Nope, I'm fine
Oh
All right, I need a break I need like a five second break
I want to play a containment breach. I don't know why I can't get to the load hold on let me try loading this again
This is this is stupid it should load
Open yes, I want you to run. No, why I had I ran earlier hold on a second give me a second
Let me go
Options
Change this to
Launcher let's do launcher. Okay, I think I got I'm gonna get it. I got it. I'm gonna get it guys
Watch this magic right here
I
Watch this magic you're about to see right here
Now we're ready for the magic here comes the magic here it comes
And for my next trick I'm not gonna be able to do the magic trick because it's still to work
Wait, wait, wait a second. I could get this to hold on
Oh
All screen falls
Launcher enabled yeah, I mean like hello of course
Damn it
Yeah, I'm getting that memory access violation whatever the hell it is
Run it as administrator good call good call
Those of you that said that good call because that's probably what's gonna happen. It's what it's gonna work right now
No, I had I had this work in two I made sure it worked before I started the stream and it worked
Now it's being a real piece crap
All right run as administrator and
And that's the what I want that's what I want watch
I
Again
Want watch
Nope, it's not gonna launch oh
Good looks like I'm gonna have to drink a bunch of doctor pepper that I mean come on
What if I just like
Freakin puke
How many like how many like people do you think would want to see that if I was just like oh yeah, you know, I'm gonna say tricks of Dr.
Just like hurled all over the place
I would I wish I could see something like that I would laugh my absolute
Ass off if I got to see something like that
I do me me me me me
That's so funny
Well, it looks like we're playing contain uh
The 087 B again, which is my favorite game of all time
After this I'm gonna play some TF2 so I'll stick around you're not gonna want to miss this
I can't believe I'm well in this game up again. I did not want to play contain
087 B again. I wanted to play it once and that was it
I didn't want to have to do this damn game more than once
Here we go
It's gonna be like
So hey prepare your ears. I'm one of you guys right now turn your headphones down
Because I gotta catch this if I don't catch it immediately
Then it's gonna be an issue. So we'll give me a minute
Let me make sure the face game's nice and big and the corner there
Here we go
I gotta make sure the mixers here
Wait, wait, why does it say containment breach is in the background hold on a second hold on a second
One second here
I think the reason why it's screwing up is because
It's like thinks it's running in the background
Oh, whatever. I don't want to waste your guys time anymore. You guys have been patient. Let's do it
You guys have been patient. Let's do it
Here we go
Here we go. I'm just stalling as much as I can here we go. No
Super crate box. That's a great game
Hmm
Don't want to click this button. I don't want to play this game again
But you know what I'm gonna play it again because you have to man up sometimes and do it
So here we go
All right
Please proceed with caution please I'll give you
Oh
No, what's this oh smart that game's fun
What if I just like don't look at the screen once
What the see you later bye no
No, no, I don't think so. I don't think so I don't think so
See you
That's not happening
Did you see that it just was like it
All right fine fine fine. We'll do it again. We'll do it again
No
I don't want to in there
You
The if you missed what what just happened
Something just flashed on the screen like a face just flashed in my face
I looked like the Cheshire cat from house in Wonderland
What happens if I go down here
Oh
What
Third times the charm guys
I keep leaving
You gotta be kidding me. Oh, be sure you don't like fall out of the hole and die
Let's go is this is gonna be the real one
I'm not gonna do any dumb mistakes and I'm not gonna leave right off the bat
Yeah, I know
Pretty sure I pretty sure I know that that's where I am at this point. You don't have to keep telling me
Well, let me get like the dust off my screen because it's making me think that this stuff on there
You are now entering some gauntlet legends you are now entering the crypt of the spider kingdom or something whatever it was
Just keep talking and I won't be scared just keep talking just keep making noises with your mouth and you won't be
scared about things that are jumping out of you on the screen
You know what man
I am just so sick of you
Why do you have to keep doing that
What what what what is this what the hell is this why is it what's this
stare why
Where am I I don't have a flashlight I don't even know where I am
Do I go in there do I go over here I don't know I don't know
Do with one eye if I do it with one eye it's not that bad
I do it with one eye it it still is bad it's still just as bad with one eye forget that
Never mind what I just said it's still just as bad with one eye closed or about both eyes closed
But I get to where I'm going
Things are getting weird looking again things are getting like green and like oh pagan
Oh, this is it I'll get me out of here
I think he's on steps
Stop it
Why
This is what happened last time and then the thing jumped out of me
Oh
If you I got to think of a song a nice happy song hold on
Rain drops keep falling on my head
But that don't leave my lives a true video there red
But the server bed
The rain drops keep falling on my head
They keep falling
But you're blue deep inside of the heart is bad
I don't know the lyrics but it's helping lots it just helping lots when no it's not
No
Just keep
Oh man I hate it bummed down pretty far I didn't get down this far last time
I think it did I don't remember it's just a blur at this point
15 hi
It she knows it she knows it's a it's a it's a way for me to pretend like I haven't that she knows so I can like not look at the screen kind of brilliant maybe
Damn it man
I
Am I going down further
I'm not going down further than that
Containment breach
Like that that this game hurts my head wow
Oh
Beatbox the Halloween theme but like the t-tint. All right, I'll do that
I
As I go
Here we go all right
See if I can I can do this
Because it's Halloween makes sense right
Most of Halloween right now but it will be
Here we go
Oh
I can't even do it it's too hard I'll slow it down on
There we go that was better. I was a little bit better
I tried to do it like way too fast the first time like
It wasn't gonna work
All right