Do do do do do do do.
Do do do do.
Oh, I can hear myself.
Gotta change that.
I can hear myself.
It's going on, guys.
How is your Saturday going?
Or potentially Sunday if you're from a different country?
Oh, I got a.
I'll save that for a second here.
Hold on.
OK, OK.
This is a little smaller on the right.
Oh, yeah.
So I'm trying something a little different.
And I am trying a.
I bought X-plit.
So I have X-plit here and I'm trying a few things.
I'm doing the capture source.
I'm not doing the screen region.
So it's probably going to be a little different or at least on
your end, it'll look the same on my and it's going to be a little bit different.
All right.
Let me shot this out.
Twitter.
I already have a pre done.
Don't worry.
It's all pre done.
Is that.
And close that window.
I got to do the YouTube one.
Over the hack that is.
There it is.
Tried.
Just hand.
Post.
OK.
Close out that window.
And then I got this to do.
All right.
We're in business.
We are in business.
All right.
Let's get in here now.
So for those of you wondering.
I'm going to this is going to be uploaded to YouTube after this.
Probably what I'm going to start doing until YouTube gets its act together.
Because the last time I streamed on YouTube last couple times I streamed on YouTube, it wasn't pretty.
There's a lot of problems.
So maybe I'll try doing YouTube next week or something like that.
I'm not sure.
But this will be up on YouTube.
This whole thing.
All right.
Refresh again because I didn't check that.
Where from Massachusetts am I from?
I am from Boston.
I guess I'm not really from Boston.
I'm kind of from a suburb of Boston.
But I'm close enough where I can say I'm from Boston, I guess.
Let's get a zero out of.
Try 24.
Any zero out of 32.
There is a number of.
There is.
All right.
How about this one?
Here's the IP.
I know what Reading is.
I have family members in Reading.
That's pretty cool.
All right.
The IP is going in the chat right now.
Make sure I get in there first.
There you go.
What's going on guys?
Bad water basin.
Let's fill this server up.
Come on.
Let's go.
I don't got all day.
Oh my kid and I got plenty of time.
I get all the time in the world.
That's not really that true.
Zero out of zero.
Where is everybody?
I'm the only one who's in the world.
I'm the only person who's in the world.
Did I give the right server?
I think I did, didn't I?
I hope I did.
I hope I gave the right server.
Make sure I did.
This is the one, right?
Yeah.
Okay.
Just in case.
All right.
It looks like that was the right server.
Here's the hopes up.
I like you on fire.
Okay.
Okay, I like you.
I like you.
Nimbee you get a cool hat.
First time in my stream because you had six hours ahead.
It is late for you.
You are late dweller.
Oh, that guy's lagging.
I don't want to kill him.
That guy was like slow motion.
I'm going to kill him.
Got my lemonade over here on the left.
It has been really nice out.
I don't know what it's been like for you guys,
wherever you live.
But my goodness, it has been so beautiful out here lately.
It's been 75 degrees, 80 degrees, every single day.
And I've been going outside a lot.
I've been taking my new dog from walks.
Oh, that's a, that's why.
Oh, nice shot, dude.
Nice shooting text.
Funny spots.
All right, let me go out here.
Yo, boy.
Ooh, good dodging.
Jump into it.
Damn.
How long do you stream and go?
I just started.
I literally just started like five minutes ago.
Oh, boy, that's dead.
Oh, come on.
Pyro versus Pyro.
Oh, I didn't kill him.
Oh, I thought he was going to go to the, ah.
I'm going to die.
He kills that much health I have.
Oh, run away.
Dead.
Aqua fire, 102.
What's up, dude?
No demo, man.
I'll change this stuff.
Oh, by the way, if anybody has noticed,
I'm not sure if you've noticed.
Oh, God, that's great again.
But I changed my FOV.
I made it bigger.
I'll show you what I did.
I didn't make it too huge, but here's my FOV now.
I changed it to like, 30% more.
And I made my weapon view model like 30% more.
So if you've noticed that, I know a lot of people are saying,
please change that.
I did.
And it actually is a little bit better.
Easier to see things.
Got a healer now, all right.
Okay, he's got a fucking gun.
Oh, I didn't kill him.
He walks right over it too.
What did he come from?
What did he even come from?
Was he the medic?
Was he healing me?
Like, the medic behind me was healing me.
He just came out of legit nowhere.
Dear NG, I staff your sentries.
See you again soon.
Wall of Spy.
Spray over.
That's a nice spray.
That's how he gets in here.
He's the light still alive.
Don't let him get me.
He's got nowhere to go now.
How did he get that?
He's going to get me.
He's doing a side stab.
I'm not going to move.
There we go.
Dear NG, I staffed your sentry.
Oh, I'm moving that.
That's me.
We're going to get rolled right now.
Oh, my god.
I haven't done anything.
Oh, you're making me waste my stuff scout.
Oh, come on.
I don't know how to hit him.
That's what's going on out here.
He's not dead.
He is definitely still alive.
Let's go for a super spam shot here, dude.
Come on, walk over that.
Oh, my god.
Chaos.
What am I?
Let me get the medic at least.
I didn't kill that medic.
I would have been so upset with myself.
Oh, cancel.
Do I like Twitch or do I like YouTube better?
I mean, YouTube has a lot of problems right now.
There's a lot of glitches with YouTube.
There's a lot of bugs and stuff.
And it's in beta.
I can understand that.
But it's, um,
Twitch.
That's what I will just say at least.
The YouTube stream is better quality though, because I'm partnered on YouTube and I'm partnered through
Mishinema, so the YouTube stream will look better.
But, I don't know.
Hopefully they fix up some of their bugs.
I'm confident they will.
Oh, scout.
Whoa.
Let's really walk through there.
Medic!
Yeah, I'll go combat in Junex.
Absolute.
Look at all these people.
Like goodness.
Don't you stuff killed.
Oh, man.
Oh, come on, kill somebody.
Oh, my god.
Come on now.
Oh, I got the medic.
Good.
Oh, keep coming.
Oh, no.
Come on, give me the help.
What?
Oomer!
Escape.
Damn.
Thought I was gonna escape, but I didn't.
Boom.
Yeah, after this round, I'm gonna go combat, Angie.
Oh, there's a crit dude right there.
Oh, no, give me a way.
Where's the spy?
He's up top there.
He's going up this way.
Get off.
Why am I stuck in the staircase?
Is that another spy?
I love how it's just like everyone's running frantically around chasing this spy.
Oh, walk over that, please.
Somebody go to the left side.
Come on.
There you go.
I double-dogged there.
Anybody up there?
I'll leave that there.
That can be the defense.
Spam.
Oh, god.
Can we run the car?
Get away from me.
Yeah, come on.
Get on the car now.
Come step on that car.
You know you want to.
Ah, come on.
Get him.
Somebody get on that car.
I want to blow it up.
I need to get healed.
Wait, is there a spy up there?
It's spawn, isn't there?
I'm going to deal with that.
Hold on.
I'll just launch myself into nowhere.
What is going on?
Why?
Why are they bouncing?
Oh, well, because...
Where's this spy?
He's freaking me out.
Is that a sniper?
No.
Yikes.
The IP, I linked it a while ago.
I'm going to be changing servers after this anyways.
And get more people into the game.
There's a lot of people in this room.
Oh, this is definitely a lot of people still in here.
Oh, crits.
Oh, I didn't get anybody.
Oh, damn.
Oh, I'm going to move behind.
Soldier, hold on.
Oh!
That's a spy.
That's definitely a spy.
No way.
Maybe not.
No, it's not a spy.
Wow.
Oh, my god.
I was not ready for this, but I'm going to do it anyways.
Let's do it.
Come on, have a little bit of something over here.
I can blow people up.
Come on.
Oh, die you bastard.
Ha.
Derma is a wizard.
Official.
Ha.
Let's go.
Woohoo.
Oh, man.
Look at all those people.
How am I doing?
I'm not that bad.
Yeah, no, no 720 here.
I am not part of it on Twitch.
It's over.
I owe gaming.
Register today.
Oh, I killed myself.
Damn.
Ha.
I want to start live streaming soon.
Any advice on how to get started?
Oh, yeah.
Most important thing is your internet needs to be able to handle it.
That's, I'd say, the number one thing is go to speedtest.net
and run a speed test.
And I'd say if your upload speed is less than one, like 1.0,
one megabit per second up,
I'd say it might be difficult for you to stream in good quality.
But if you're higher than one,
or two megs up,
you should be fine to stream.
But I mean, you guys have been here before
when I've had problem streaming.
I mean, I have 10 up connection.
And, oh my god.
Oh my god, somebody run over that.
Here we go.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
That's what I wanted to run.
But you guys have been to streams before
where it's been unwatchable from lag
and in the past,
I've been here for a while.
Unwatchable from lag.
And I have a 10 up connection.
It's just weird.
The internet is a weird place.
And also, I'd also say you need a pretty good processor and video card
because essentially your computer's doing kind of like double work.
Oh.
No, I got crit rocket.
Oh, I got two cats, man. I love cats.
I love any animal.
The only animal that I could probably say I don't like
is, I don't know, maybe like,
oh, this is a hard question.
The only animal that I don't think I would like to,
oh my god, another Uber, this is ridiculous.
I like the Uber machine tonight.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, my god.
Oh, it's crazy.
Anyways, probably an animal big enough that will like,
literally kill me if I go near it.
So, probably something like that.
Oh, yeah, 4 up is fine.
You'll be fine with 4 up.
Here we go.
Oh, boy.
God, I feel like the other team is getting neglected.
Spread the Uber's around.
I don't need them all.
No, I'm just kidding.
We're going up top here.
Or I can just apparently not detonate the mine.
What's going on here?
So many people.
So many people to spam.
This is chaos.
Oh, this is absolute chaos.
Oh, my god.
This is ridiculous.
There are two player servers in sanity.
Yeah, this, oh my god.
This is a full group in here, man.
Yeah, right after this round ends, I'm going to hope that I'm hopping a new server.
Oh, fly.
Oh, that's a double.
That's a double.
It's going up here.
Hey, hey you.
Oh, you're real.
I was going high five.
Oh, you want high five?
Oh, sure, I'll high five.
And then just explode myself.
Wow, that was pretty unintelligent, dumpy.
But yeah, that's what I do.
All right, new server.
Server.
Wait.
Oh, you want to see my brain.
A lot of you guys already know this.
Sometimes I just don't think it happens quite often actually.
All right, let's see.
Let's see here.
Hmm, I would say let's play a randomizer server.
But for my streams, I like to get a lot of people into the games as many people as I possibly can that are watching.
So I don't want to just, you know, because most of the randomizer and arena mod tech servers, they're always full.
They always have 23 out of 24.
So I would be the only one that would be able to get in.
So I like to have people from the stream get priority and come and play and stuff like that.
Let's find another server.
This one was 32.
All right, oh my god, there's so many loading.
Looking for 32.
Hi, tower. We're going to bunch of bots.
And then...
Well, I ever do a workout video.
I've thrown it around.
I was going to do it a long time ago.
But it's just, I don't know if people would even watch it.
A very small group of people that would probably watch it.
But I don't know if like how it would be received.
I think a lot of people would be like, what the hell are you doing?
Why are you like a Whiston Waits?
24 or 20? Me to 32.
Okay.
No, here we go.
Good old fashion Dustball.
Here is the IP.
Oh, everyone's always asking about Enlighten.
The new Enlighten.
I'm working on it right now.
So there will be a new Enlighten in the next couple days.
Working on it right now.
Yeah, I'll probably do another one of those videos where I give advice.
And I'll probably do like maybe a one or two minute vlog type thing
or I show you some stuff.
But I'm not sure I would do like a 20 minute workout video.
Okay, then up, then down, then up, then left.
I think that would just be odd.
I mean, I think there would be very weird.
Let's go blue.
I was red last time.
Oh, boom.
Oh, what do I want to use?
Oh, the new PDA.
He might not.
And up, and down, and left, and egg.
And egg.
Let me say this.
Would you guys watch an egg workout video?
Like if it was the egg.
What do I want to even play with?
Oh, I'll stay with this.
I'll stick with this.
Why not?
Buh, buh, buh, buh, buh, buh, buh, buh, buh, buh.
This server is like...
Is this server like weird?
It's like, I'm like lagging.
Oh, I'm trying to...
I tried to have an iPhone.
Oh, wait, you can just hold your hand like that?
Oh, yeah.
I thought, baby.
I don't know if it's like the server enough.
Is everybody like all jumpy?
They are on my screen.
Does anybody else see that?
I don't want to...
We'll go for one or two rounds like this.
Oh, high five.
Here we go.
Shloping.
Yeah, I mean...
Oh, god.
Everyone's like jumping all over the place for me.
Oh!
Centred down.
Hey, hey, hey.
What do you think you're doing?
Oh, but I forgot I was going to answer that question.
The reason why I don't do auto reload is because...
Is somebody in here?
Like the ghost of the pyro just in that room with me.
Oh, no.
Oh, god.
What do I do?
All right, well, here we are.
I'll block you way out.
You can't get out.
You're a dead ringer.
I got you blocked in.
Hey.
That is a tip right there.
If you shoot a dead ringer and you know he's a dead ringer,
just stand in the middle of the hallway.
And he can't get by.
At least, at least sometimes.
I'm not going to get out of here.
At least sometimes.
Oh, just bads are going up up here.
I don't know why I decided to put her here.
It's a bad idea.
Oh, yeah.
Where is my mini-century?
Why is it still alive?
Oh, my God.
I'm getting distracted.
I get distracted.
I have ADD, man.
Wow, we already won.
My goodness.
FG Spidey, Betia, I can say your name.
I bet you a dollar, I can say your name.
32-man Dust Bowl is chaos.
I'm going to go Huntsman Schneipan.
If you want to throw me a duel, I'll absolutely do it.
Ah!
Oh, now I go, let me say, I go to Sion,
I think that's what you say.
Sion, I go, sir.
By the way, if you're watching this on YouTube,
I'm responding to people in the chat.
Don't just think I have weird disorder where I just say random words.
Like I said that last time, too.
Oh, come on.
This guy is going to get head shot right now.
Right now, here we go.
I don't think you understand.
Here it comes.
Oh, my God, he killed me.
Oh, no, a different guy did.
Eggs.
Look at this egg.
Man, this server is lagging for me.
I'll tell you right now, oh, look at this double spy collateral.
Oh, no, run away.
Oh, tack!
Oh, I can't even aim at people.
My screen is like, to take a jellyfish.
Oh, he got me.
He got me.
Oh, whoa.
Look at the server.
I don't think the server was designed that, but it's been a people in it.
You want to get covered in jirati?
Is that what you're saying?
Is that what you just said?
You want to get smashed in your face?
I got him.
Fan of Kid Icarus, I never played it.
Not even the original.
And I'm an old bastard and I didn't even play the original.
Oh, that would have been sick.
I heard somebody.
I love to kill somebody.
Finally.
I got my first kill ever.
Whoa.
Did you see where I shot?
If you're watching this on YouTube, please rewind that and look at where I shot.
I shot like five feet over that guy's head.
I still killed him.
No.
Oh, god.
Let's just, all right.
Let's do it.
Oh.
Oh, there's no way I was going to get out of there.
A good affordable graphics card.
That's a good one.
Hmm.
I'd say probably like the GTX 550 for the 560.
I think those are both under 200 bucks.
I think, under 100.
I think the 550 is, I don't know, the 550 Ti, I think it's called.
I don't even remember.
Go.
I missed him.
Oh, god.
I think Ag should be a weapon.
I don't know how well they work.
Oh, it's simsass.
You got the 550?
How much is the 550?
And follow up, is it a good graphics card?
There we go.
Did you hear it?
Oh, my god.
Hey, let's go on.
Just hiding over here.
Away from you.
No, no, please don't kill me, please.
Did you buy the 550 or did you buy the 550?
Or did it come with your computer?
Really?
I'm thinking.
I didn't get him.
Oh, crap.
Okay, yeah.
So the 550 is only like 130 bucks.
I'd say that's a good graphics card to be able to save a little bit of money.
Because the 580 is,
geez, what, like $500?
Something like that?
I know it's up there.
And they're already working on the 600, aren't they?
The 600 series?
Oh.
Is that?
Okay, you're real.
You're the real deal.
I got you.
Oh, cover them all.
No.
Get this one guy.
Come on.
The 680 is out now.
Oh, dear Lord.
What is that?
Like $900?
You can only imagine.
Woo!
I don't think we're going to win this.
Oh god, there's people over there too.
All right, I'm going this way.
Is anybody up here?
We almost just got it.
Oh, he's still alive.
He's still alive.
Hey, turn already behind you.
Oh my god.
I guess like, crushed that guy.
Geez.
Oh, forget that.
I'm going this way.
Oh my god.
Grrrr.
That's my favorite movie?
Hmm.
I don't know.
Probably Ghostbusters or Memento or The Dark Knight or one of the Muffet movies.
Or there's a lot of movies I've watched.
I'm not a big movie watcher though.
I'm not even a big TV watcher either.
Oh my god, I just missed his head.
Oh, this guy could be toast.
Oh my god.
Get away from me.
Oh, this guy doesn't even know I'm here.
Damn it.
Fireclub is also a good one, Ari.
Fireclub is a good one.
I'm over the first time I watched Fireclub.
I was so confused.
I think I was like 16.
I'm like 17.
When did that movie come up?
I didn't fight club releasing.
When did it come up with theaters?
Did somebody write the foot?
contenit.
Oh my god.
Hide.
I don't see if like Grandpuck and Beatbox?
I don't think you can.
I would assume Grandpuck could not beatbox.
1999, okay.
Oh.
So that means I was.
So 10 years ago was 2009.
So 10, 11, 12.
So that was 13 years ago.
I was.
Hmm.
So I'm 26.
16.
15, 14, 13.
I definitely didn't watch it when I was 13.
I don't think my parents would have let me do that.
Yeah, I mean once I watched it,
when I, I think the first time I watched it when I was like 15,
or 16, something like that.
And I was confused.
I was absolutely confused.
Office space is a good movie too.
The thing is I've seen a lot of movies,
but I don't watch a lot of movies.
If that makes any sense to anybody,
then oh my god.
That's accidentally got that guy.
Greetings from Chi-Label.
Greetings from East Coast USA, dude.
I'm going to go to the movies.
I'm going to go to his movies.
I don't have the money for anything to eat.
I'm going to go to the movies.
I'm going to go to my movies.
I'm going to go to chat with him.
Well, what's the name of the movie?
I don't know what to say.
Dude.
It's either very early or very late for you.
I'm not sure.
Actually, I think we're in the same time zone.
We're close, in the same time zone.
Oh my god.
blowing all the teammates up you get a gold star no it's not Jeremiah it's
just Jeremy oh there's a lot of people right there
oh much it much it
okay all right and Skulls not gonna work I'll go medic do I like Irish people I do I
am Irish I am Irish so look at this server all right
after a kind of change servers after I die next just because the server is very
lacking look at this guy looks like he's a part of like a claymation look at
this like claymation server we're on
oh no no no no no
oh this is why I like the quick fix because you can just do this and it like
makes sense oh my god that was the guy I have to see new server
yeah new server what's this oh yeah he defeated me
probably hop in one more server and try some tribes to send because that game is
really cool let's go zero out of 24 this time just to keep the lag factor
down a little can you the health sawmill no can you help nucleus that could be
good
yeah you know hi tower I'm torn guys I don't know where to go you are garbage
germ oh why what did I do oh bad water mountain lab a day in the life of
germa where I just eat like Cheetos and take a bath
and we're gonna go here we're gonna go to via that
cauth via that there's the IP
I put the IP right in chat should say a little camera next to my name
oh
let's go
let's go spy this is a very weird load up I don't
muster what I was trying to do here I got the strange dead ring them
the summer's full the server's full server what am I talking about
yeah if you if you can't get in or you're trying to get in I do apologize
I think I do have a strange damn oh depth thanks for putting that up well it's gonna
belong to somebody else pretty soon so might as well rack up as many kills on it as I can right
hey look I'm an engineer walking at you from the other side oh you got me damn how dare you kill
me like that
if I could go pro at any sport baseball I've always wanted to be a baseball player
I'm not exactly sure why but I just have used to play baseball when I was younger
into high school and I stopped in high school
oh my my death so that way now they're gonna all know that I just dead run dead wrongs
I didn't like a word all right oh let's let's protect this point I'm a pyro I do that
the best now it's just a scared chaos stab right there
nobody rare um other team is still trickling in
well look I'm just coming out of spawn in myself hey let's let's get out of spawn together what
different oh germa I'm cheating I'm watching you stream
is my name even germa right now yeah oh scrumbo dump
Harvey hamburger George Bumberson I go by a lot of different titles
I won't get out of my way oh you son of a b
well that's like five million deaths in a row is it's by time to change up enough
low fps oh what am I even using okay I'll rock with this I'll roll with this I'm cool with that
I thought that was a spy oh what just happened oh my brain there was a soldier right there I
just killed that medic I'm sorry dude I don't think I've ever had a embarrassing name
oh my preferred breakfast food oh you kidding me eggs I had to say
I'll be moving out here all right no more fooling around let's get some kills
let's kill some bastards get on this point boys girls oh where is he
you are fine yep you're invisible now
no that was a total not good idea oh what was what did I jump in the air
did I what just happened to me
I I don't even understand how that happened
maybe I did jump that's a buzz veered kill germa nice name
ha ha at least I got one kill tattoo around
boy boy boy boy boy boy how do you open console it's the till day key thing under escape
oh I got some I got some expert rocket jumping guys there we go expert rocket
jumper check me out I'll be on I don't even know what the name of the site is
so wait what why would I give up TF2 but I made this explicitly clear that I never was
TF2 is a huge part of my existence
oh no oh no where is auto that's a good question that's a slight brain he's gonna know he's not
what is that oh that was awful there we go
oh can I get like a string or two or three in a row here
and you all right at least I'm killing people now
oh my liberty launcher is now a new rank
yeah I understand that phenomenal but to be honest the items that I have in my backpack right
now I mean I know I can understand like oh he's giving away his whole backpack he's gonna quit
I understand that but I mean I have a lot of friends in team fortress and a lot of people
that oh god hold on oh god I'm totally ruined that much oh my god but I've got a lot of friends
in team fortress and I have a lot of people that have they support me with this channel
so any item that I ever want to use I can just get it back it might not be strange you might not
be genuine but that's I don't care I figured because like I said in the video I started with team
fortress too and I got all the support from you guys from team fortress a lot of you guys
are team fortress guys and that was a decent decent shot and that's why I West I felt like doing
it you know something I felt like doing and mine's made up there's no going back now so it's
gonna happen and let's see if I can know there's a mini sector
all right after uh after this round go to one more server and then I'm gonna hop and try to send
boing boing boing
no that was laggy oh I didn't want to do that
oh my god
what was it going on that guy
the guy was just skydiving right there
oh I'm dead I am so dead
did did did did did oh you lagged out yeah
oh
mission ends in 60 seconds
oh how did I not hit him many centuries go out of here oh that's just an hyper good to know
oh this is where we're getting trouble
oh that's what it's like this
he's still alive watch this spawn Optimus Prime is on the Lewis
no you're real where could he be
you gotta get on that point
okay
get on there we go everyone just stop on here right now
we go
ah missed
all right one minute 40 seconds we got this
hmm
hmm you gotta back up
damn every time I shoot a crit rocket it just goes right by
track oh
oh
oh no no no
no I just ruined this again
oh I'm sorry medic I'm an idiot
oh
yeah tribes is a free to play game right now I would suggest everyone to go get it
if you play team fortress you'll probably like tribes it's just another one of those kind of
fast paced you know projectile based crazy fun games FPS it's first version shooter
nice so what's that news sir
news sir have it
all right well good one more server here then I'm gonna hop into tribes for probably like a half an hour or so
so you're out of 32 okay let's go to we got this one is open and it's dust fall
huh we just do we already did dust fall
busy town that was busy town
this one's well we can do well
I'm actually knowing and I know that server might not be able
all right we'll go to this one CTF well and there you are everyone join it
empty randomizer um I mean I mean randomizer
sure is it really empty though so those servers are like are like legit empty right now
no okay next week we'll do randomizer
we'll do some randomizer next week
let's get out I'm gonna use the shortstop and the I'm gonna put on the whole set
why not right why not
oh
oh the rounds about even started I'm gonna get a kill
no I'm not too bad
oh
whoa oh I'm gonna sneeze I get a sneeze there's nothing I can do about it
oh I'm gonna sneeze here I got no no false alarm no
sorry there's no button I can press to mute me
are we getting spawn traps what's going on thank you
oh
get me in here
oh god they got to get crits
oh damn
it's the vizzi spider
went up the water spout down came the rain and wiped out that god damn spider
I just bought the newest five but I don't care
oh did it wake me oh man I did help
oh
oh you are not you are a real bowl
is he still what no he's not wait what
how is that unless I actually really just killed him I don't think I did though
go top there's the health that's what I wanted
oh god no
this is bounced off the door and give me the face
oh
come on away
get me my milk get me my milk oh
all right so I have a level thanks for coming man
well I ever do more dual commentary so hell yeah I just did one the the other
night on csgo with mlsc still
oh
oh just just jump over everybody try and get around all those guys get by this rain
get me out of here get me out of here get me out of here
come on just give me the stupid intelligence
do
d-a-m-m damn damn
oh what just oh I got a backstab gang it
special delivery all right
did did did did did did was this in low right germa sucks and TF2
all we got a troll we got a troll
all right move more round of this I'm gonna go pyro this time
hmm my highest not I don't put on it let's go yeah
all right last round we're gonna hop over to tribes
ascend
damn
nah all right I got to clear offline we can't have any spam coming at me
especially what it has bad bad things
oh shhh
do do do do do do do do do do
oh no no no no no somebody behind us still while there it's
no god I turned it so I can't get a trade
oh I don't think I even have the half of the jigsore said to be honest
nah I don't have I don't have the hat
you know I saw I thought I could get by and then I turned and skid crap out of myself
oh my god they have crits cheer to that me come on
all right don't get to put the trade again oh oh oh
I almost got hit by the trade again
no I'm gonna make it oh damn it
where's burger boy
how am I not letting him on fire
oh is that mean like we're gonna play tribes ascend with burger boy
special guest appearance from burger boy
oh
god damn it burger boy reveal yourself
he has burger boy burger boy's been in videos
oh I'm out of ammo oh god
oh my power jack would I get one kill with it
all right train me versus you what do you say buddy let's do this
I uh I lost
oh we got crits yes
I just want to crit fire somebody yeah feels good to crit fire
it feels good to crit fire all right we're going sniper no one out I'm going heavy
run run run run run run run run run run run run
get away oh come on right when I get a spawn
B-U-L-L-S-H-I-T with six exclamation points after that
wait why do I have to attach it equipped okay whatever
I'm so scared I I I killed this five for like five thousand feet away
all right where's this guy oh my god he's on the roof I thought it was to the right
all right take this stupid thing off give me the regular I'm gonna go
boom boom boom boom boom boom boom
I gotta like really watch my back now
playing heavy like the probably the worst idea I could have ever done
I'm gonna be on fire die die die die you know what you know I
oh thank you so much oh no here comes another dude
oh
how are you still alive what
I can't find the train again
of course I can hit by the train again that would absolutely happen
oh full of god
uh hey we're gonna be Chris I think I hope we get Chris right now oh my god of course
we get Chris that I died I'm dead
oh take a lot take this take that
oh
how are you still alive I knew it I knew it was a guy behind
oh my god 32 person servers are just like ridiculous they are like insane
insanity like you walk out the door it's just like
oh
where is this guy so scared of the spider's backs that mean it's definitely gonna happen like right now
oh get by the train again oh god oh we've won how do we win how am I in the number two right now
oh
all right well good good night if you leave it man thanks for coming
so now I'm gonna head on to tribes a sometime dudes and dudeettes
thanks for playing everybody all right
so I think I might uh invite a few people into the call that have tribes
see how that goes I gotta change this to Sam might tell do that in a minute
let me open up tribes the screen Michael Black for a second guys so I apologize
screen is going to go black
so bear with me for one second while I load up tribes ascent
oh I have ADHD crazy bad I have really bad ADHD
I'm sure my is dead I'm still here
to talk this it's all I see
I uh I already did a set up video Hannibal go to my 4000 subscriber video it's uh it should be there
don't go into the light now my children let me tell you something I am god
coming to you from the black screen let me tell you all you need to do to have a good fun
interesting life is to crash because that's what I think I just did oh no no I'm here okay
okay hold on I really thought it is hard crash right there that would have been bad
all right let me get uh into the game screen should come back in about
10 seconds guys settings audio yeah that's fine video window come on let's go window
windowed all right now I'm coming back
change the resolution
all right let me just add this game as a source into the exploit
should be good to go
game hello is that gonna fit is that work let's see I think that fits
pretty sure at least get that out of the way what's with the double screen that's weird
hmm
hold on a second guys I'm gonna change this this is a little glitchy I'm just gonna add the screen
region that should be better okay yeah there we go all right so that should be better
all right so I think we're gonna um get some people in here to talk while we play
those of you that have never played this game please my goodness please go please go download it
it is an unbelievable game and it's free what what are the reasons do you need
to move this it's not in the way
to the left to the left to the right to the right I need to be moved a little bit
all right looks like it's centered at least on my screen
all right so we're gonna get anybody in this call
maybe might happen to the audio
audio still here yeah it's here I can hear
all right um somebody call me on Skype so we can start a call uh
or stealth or burger boy whichever one of you guys wants to
wants to do this thing and then just join up me home so they might have already been
calling yeah they are what's up burger boy oh burger boy now burger boys call me get out of here
I'm inviting them this one is that his door huh I was first but about uh what about
where's the talix maybe the talix play it was offline he might be doing a band thing
oh hey what's up burger boy
make sure you guys turn it off do all right if uh if somebody else wants to join can you
guys monitor or self can you monitor just in case I'm like in the game
I'm just saying like I when I alt tab in a window it's just like
like explodes so like I can't like really alt tab anymore
I mean you could play the game just every like 10 seconds just check this
so if you want it's gonna be difficult to join the game off me right now because the way
this game works is you have to have like if I don't know how many friends you can have to be
honest I really don't know but I'm gonna go pathfinder
turn this up the stream is under control I'm just standing yeah
stream under control and I'm gonna turn this up turn this up because you can't hear
all right I think we can go go go go sound on the stream should be
hey burger boy the app drugs this one oh he's got it yeah
he's absolutely got it so this game if you don't know what this is if you're like what the
hell are you doing right now this game is pretty much think of team fortress meets quake
meets skiing meets ski free meets windows 95 meets windows 98
I'm not sure if that made any sense but this game is just look at this is chaos
pretty much think of this game as your you play as a soldier like a liberty launch of soldier
and that's pretty much what everyone is using then you ski around like a hundred miles per hour
it's all about momentum and we just really want the game yeah that's a good way to put it this
game is halo with speed hacks and cooler mechanics in my opinion the music is cool
I agree with one gem of soda now it's changed it's changed you're gonna do map
but it's it's not really halo it's like a it's it's cool in a little in my opinion just because
I never really played a lot so because you've never had an Xbox you've never could play on I
had an Xbox at a 360 one um two or three years ago was the last time I had one oh what's
going on why am I like stuck here I'm like stuck in this like lobby area there we go
so it was lagging right this frame was lagging you kidding me
you know let me know if it keeps happening guys try this again
because if it keeps happening I might restart it just change a couple settings
but yeah once you get like on a date this game is so satisfying I'm going bloody eagle by the way
you can get some real satisfying kills within this game especially because it's all about a long
range it's a long-range in people it's awesome oh did you quit and join a different game I did just
join off me yeah it like kicks me out I'm sure I did
oh it's so long too what because burger boy is like not a lot of play how do I not kill that guy
here we go this is a beta this is a beta oh it's another kill it's free though it's open open beta
oh it was in the air why didn't you probably reserve shoot or did that free crit
good you get three shots pretty much when the pathfinder was like the scout you move around really fast
and soldiers like the soldier I guess there's like nine classes in this game I'm pretty sure there is
this is just team death match and essentially what why do we split the out I keep joining again we keep
this winning I do not quit this one keep keep stay and stay in this one
general general but you see this up here this 2700 xp pretty much if you don't want to buy the game
the game doesn't cost any money but it's kind of like in team fortress where you
do this economy where you can buy items if you don't want to wait and unlock them it's kind of
like that so if you want to spend money you can but if you don't it takes a long time to get all the
items and all the classes and everything so it looks like it's an exaggerated long time yeah
like one of the hours of game time so like unlock a new class yeah and you start with three classes
when you just get the game free you can spend 10 20 bucks and you'll unlock everything pretty much
you know in term I'm gonna go blood eagle pathfinder again I'm gonna turn the graphics down a tiny bit
just because I think people were saying it was lagging or you went on the other thing oh where
are good boys oh I like switch teams in this game this is first of state yeah you're gonna escape
minute switch teams oh this guy's toast down here this guy's toast guys oh get up
to right shot finish this dude off
there it is I so as you can see I got a shotgun you pretty much only have two weapons I have grenades
too but I don't really use them I mean I know I should but and see the top the middle top 9792 this
is team deathmatch and essentially how this works is when you die one point it's taken off your
side of the team but if your team has the flag or if their team has the flag kills count as two
so we have the flag right now so anytime we kill somebody on their team it's gonna count as two
points taken down from their score oh I just got nailed
so it's lagging huh oh let me see if the hell is on on here wasn't doing this on team fortress wasn't
no it wasn't let's find out what the hell is going on it's too rough with landing string
should be shouldn't be I'm watching the boys still on the terrorist team yeah you still on CT oh yeah I
got the flag come get me okay oh you're you're on the enemy team huh come here okay
destroy oh come on let's go on be one baby oh hi god me damn got me
it looks okay on my end when I'm watching the stream right now it looks okay
okay maybe it was just like a little issue I don't know not sure
but yeah look at all those people in that oh I get I get placed sniper rifle
yeah but see when you go down look at the left and right of my screen see how I have that like power meter
that's how fast I'm going when I ski the entire time you're gonna be holding down space
essentially in this game is the flag all right time time to pull off something
oh get him with an air shot come on now
I didn't get that guy oh kill people kill go with people going for the flag you gotta get rid of
these people there we go all right pick up the flag pick up flag I got it I got it oh protect me
oh the italics isn't this game drag him in the call because yes there
drag a talent to me oh that was you oh well you know friends
on italics just blew me to hell and I blew him to hell
here we go look at all these people ready grenade grenade
grenades are locked in this game oh there's a flag give me the flag where am I no that was
that was a snipe flag right there I just totally snipe that flag um lose momentum you gotta go
go get it go get it go I tried to settle before it's I'm not very good at it
god I'm being chased by like a mob of people
oh well press Z and all the people stop following me what I promise yeah because I do
gonna drop the full hack still got it oh maybe not anymore protect me still oh they got me
well let me let me drag it to Alex and here all right he's coming
there it is one more lose maybe one more lose oh one more no it's private hey guys what is
going on what's up man what the talent's playing the flag man like I do
yeah we got some good flag control to be like burger boys like terrible at this game he could
like he could like really like do something right now I can't even figure out how to switch James
and then go to change um I don't want to be on this team anymore oh I think I think I think
I think the mlsc stealth is lied to yeah no that's absolutely true I just did it oh wait you first
pee that's what I'm gonna say okay good I can't there's not enough people on that team
oh this guy is so toast right now oh here we go oh come on get him with those shots
oh fine whatever I'll go with this thing
okay there's just a swarm of red upside down triangles around that flag oh stealth you got
the flag all right I sure do all right let's let's do a little bit of let's do a little bit of
teamwork here I'm close to here watch how I go yeah if we're still we're still playing already
definitely I get you in here oh that is burger boy oh burger boy
oh burger boy
that's what you uh I think the teams are even yeah oh no no yeah you're not you didn't not yet
I've been to the auto balance moves I guess yeah well this game's almost over we're almost
going to lose oh but I have a flag that's good yeah and they're gonna win all right so do not
die nobody died and we might win no it won't that's gonna be a long range
oh gonna get the right of this guy got it and I'll see you flying around the map right
I'm chasing you for so long oh yeah like soon burger boy from behind he's just like right behind me
oh oh watch out burger boy is gonna take us all on somebody took him out I don't know who got
an assist burger boy I can't even catch up the stealth and I'm on his team I know really right
stand rock it stands oh we lost all right try and get on this team up like a piffon
okay try and get on this team burger boy the insensitive one all right let's see if any of us
made any MVP statistics no we sure didn't yet you got a mLC still flag held top accolade whoa
you got like a top medal you didn't get a MVP actually you got two you got two medals
you got two medals fly held and fly killer top accolades this thing is my most
flag held medals is 41 and that's because I got the flag right when the game started and I skied
around for 10 minutes and what did it why am I killing anybody either why am I not logged into my own
stream right now I just typed something how's that possible
so it's oh playing team fortress too when I'm absolutely not
do you want my deleted what do you do on bloody eagle
uh yeah go go right when you count
is that burger boy just like click spamming
yeah trying to get in that
as your best chance oh no
um are we gonna get split up here I think we might get split up here
uh whatever I'll catch you guys oh I just made it oh burger boy
you could have just waited you made it I made
okay
enemy has a flag oh I gotta I gotta change this it's this thing I'm playing tribes
try this end there we go
broadcast updated successfully oh got the flag probably not for long
nah I'm gonna go I'm gonna go soldiers this time
I think that's uh the best idea wow there is no one on my team over here at all
trying to tell like they're all behind you oh man nice air shot oh burger boy made it that's
shit all right let's keep going all right I got to go buy an arcs and buster whatever that is
it's probably stupid oh you bastard where you doing
oh that was the sweet under the bridge flight right there oh you want to go a salt rifle on a salt rifle or something
oh yeah oh this guy needs one hidden he's dead
oh come on fine bump up there we go there we go
all right we who's got the we got the flag oh uh oh uh oh I'm gonna catch me now I ran into like
the border of like at the edge of the map over here do we get the flogger cylinder flag
here we do and yeah talix says two evil men chasing him hi let's let's get over there
got some ninjas flying around behind me trying to kill one dude chasing it oh talix's voice is
smooth it is somebody said that smooth like an erection
all right this is PG 13 stream outside I don't even know what that man
yeah I was about to ask oh air shot nope that guy just got me this thing doesn't go very far
forget that sometimes I'm just gonna do the talix on the map right now I'm doing a lapse right
behind you drawn lands where is he oh god not a jetpack
I'm trying to prove on the better scared well the classes have a lot of impact on that as well
what are you all right fine yeah if you like the fastest class what do you oh damn I am a
raider yeah I just tried to somebody behind you so I'll slow down a little bit into him that
should this list game is the person that just asked this game is free and it's in open beta you
can just play it you play it as much as you want whatever you want
and it's a game about skiing momentum and fun this ski simulation game yes
oh this guy smart what am I doing with this smart guy wait till he lands
oh I believe I've been carrying the flag this entire time I really can't
take care of that hand here wow
uh oh are we gonna get to see some real raw burga boy rage remember burga boy you can't say any
like wicked horrible swiss
oh I'm about to run into a wall oh I ran into a wall it's over I see you try
up to help you this was on me dead oh you want to go with this boom oh nice nice nice is a good run
very nice very nice burga boys in first place burga boy there you go oh yeah that's
I'm gonna get that flag right one of our guys got the flag come on gotta get better aim
come on land oh I got a way I'm on this thing what am I doing
oh I gotta get to an ammo supply
oh damn not doing so well right this second oh that's not not doing so hot right there
I just grenade it myself like as fast as you move in this game that is nearly impossible
yeah I know all right that's crazy I got that guy on the couple of shoes oh that bad doing some
speed now get this guy I'll thump this guy I'll tumble is better than thump is
tumble is better than thump is not high enough like the flag is dropped I had the flag on my back
you get it a towel yeah I blew that guy away from you guys nice all right protect the tauts
all right I could just like sit down here alone by myself like it did it
oh I just got I just got air shot damn I'll lose in momentum there I just got mad air shot
I'm dead I don't know how I got to do my mind but what we are we're doing I believe there are some
grenades that can make you drop stuff like the flag that's lame actually that's pretty cool land on that
I gotta get more I gotta oh this guy's done that of town back off
oh just got killed by a blue fatty somebody just said juggernaut yeah that's a juggernaut probably
I might want to pull out the I might kill them one more shot come on this is the one this is the
one right here oh no he's not dead oh there we go I need to go to a resupply big time
oh ship has got a new video reserve shooter sick it needs to look at a challenge oh he's on
the other video oh yeah flag down baby
should they all right we're beating them by like we have like a 100% lead on them right
I think this guy off I try to get like hit markers on him but man I tell you right now this game
is a lot of fun I probably wouldn't have even started playing this game but it was not for
italics thank you sir thank you it was like you got to play this game you'd like I would have
I was like I'll give it a try whatever probably sucks now this game is very very good
I saw it before a long time ago like months ago when people were first started talking about it
and I was like yeah it looks okay but this game is very addicting very fun
somebody's behind me but I don't care to turn around and it's free yeah
as a huge class right there I actually don't buy games that were like 10 bucks
yeah burger boy doesn't buy video games until they are 10 dollars and we're talking like
Skyroom what's up but it's like Skyroom do you never gonna get that yeah you're gonna get Skyroom
like and when you're like 35 that's always that's the burger boy quote I'll be like oh hey dude
you know like de apple three it just came out 10 bucks yet like no it's not it's like 60
oh well fine it's all it's like 10 bucks
I'm gonna try and help you with this dude nice yep he was he was getting on you pretty good now
hey he's in 13 I thought yeah already let me know when um
I already showed nobody was here right what what did you just say
I've really just didn't even pay attention to where you said oh I need to get up here I'm dead
I'm so dead yeah absolutely oh chop for I can like about
there let's see if I can give a slider with the hair strike if you walk right into it oh no you almost
got him he was in the air he was in the air at least a look close from over here
oh
I'm trying to get him in the air
I'm not shooting far enough ahead of him no still not shooting far enough ahead of him
oh that could have been an air shot come on now mother may I
I need to wait I could have charged like stuff here oh god
oh
yeah black here we go
all right let's get already in here first one of the day there is
a burger boy that's called kill told you
did burger boy nice
I would not buy team fortress classic the only reason why I say that is because
it's just it's very and now it's just so difficult to play this grenade's fam is
it's it's unless it's like five dollars don't buy it we'll put it that way
okay
winner winner chicken dinner I think this is the first time I've ever gotten first place
in anything in drives oh really that isn't achievement in and of itself for me
not even first in the whole game this first in my team that's good enough all right quick
flood the bloody go bloody everybody click look it
yes go back to pass find out
oh there's a guy right here oh yeah shot no
it does oh it's like seem to defend on call it he never played seem to defend on call
hey watch it
I can't believe I didn't always gonna kill no Germany have to be the first kill my first
step I'm gonna be the I'm gonna be the first step if I don't get Lord chaos I'm the first damn
death wow that was the lucky skill I've ever had yeah I'll probably do videos for drives
eventually everyone I got I got to get familiar with it get to go to edit
but I'll probably do a few videos at least yeah
okay this game is really awesome boom the other boom the other one I'm going to absolute wrong
direction all right I'm gonna get some speed here picking up speed picking up speed
got him and it's all got me oh we got to get that flag you got it somebody on our team got it
and LC still was gonna die look at that chaos grenade into the chaos
oh I thought I got that guy my game is just updating it's doing some really weird stuff
hey when we when we installed it on burger boys computer is like all his fans turned on
this computer almost like close load just random there will be surprised
that is like awesome computer I have nice shot okay I got a really good shot but we've had issues
that borderline stuff before we've had issues burger boy borderlands so like all right how many times
have you heard bird and boy like swear and say horrible things in borderlands oh oh god
basically he did read back his keys for his special ability and every time we wanted to pick
up an item he decided to activate his special ability and playing his break he was just screaming
constantly for the entire three hours that we played at our first time oh burger boy come on
you can you can like do better than that
oh let's go shoddy
I don't have any momentum I'm like walking around the man
oh I still have you I'm gonna I'm gonna waste this grenade
let's get this guy double team
I missed
here we go another guy right there
two guys seven seventy and that's a direct shot
oh I got a phone lover oh you know wow that was a that was awesome
I mean a flag boy holy crap that was awesome yes I just tried to get a
resupply and a guy threw a grenade right into my feet when I went over there and got me
two shame I've rid of that was great
down
woo
ah so general what classes do you have unlocked so far just the sniper central
that's a nice thing about like yesterday we were talking about the like the ones that don't
detonate on the impacts yeah they bounce around I have the grenade launcher right now
and I've noticed that if you get a direct hit it's like the demo man you know we'll just explode
let's just pop oh really immediately wow and the nice thing about them also is that they
usually do a lot more damage and have a bigger radius than like the spin fusors yeah I've noticed
the explosion huge you just get a massive damage spike right there I'm going to the lava I keep
falling in lava like it is oh hey star wars I can't help
does anybody else feel like they're playing like star wars I like feeling like that yeah
I mean even the noises like the I feel like the green dream it sounds like star wars
oh thank you so what are you guys favorite losses with the games I like moving fast and having
zero well fast find them yeah I'd probably say the fast find too just give the shock the shock on
the cell that you break the trend break the trend I would say a raider or infiltrator see I don't
even I got to get those guys I'm never again with the infiltrator yet never been good with
stealthy classes in any game that's still fun yeah so you can you can cloak oh yeah you can
cloak and it's like instead of using your energy per your jetpack it'll use it for your
stealth oh okay that's a good trade off that's not like overpowering anything that's cool and there's
a few items in my perks making up perks but I know it's at least one or two items that can like
detect still people oh really I don't have any of those yet there's a lot of people here I'm so
dead yeah there's like ten people around me skate down here oh Tony Hawk presents tribes as
Sam do a kick flip all right I'm gonna do like a shaky 200 oh that's like 25 points
I gotta get some speed yeah I cannot catch up to the get flag carrier
now I try and cut them off I'm very worried about how did you know it was him how did you know
that hey car you're back I'm gonna like a stream I know germa's ringtone and I'm pretty sure
bring boys you know I'm always gonna have a stun on him right now what if the talc sense is
for them I didn't think he would I thought it was more of a burger more thing than I was
on them do you mean that do me that oh yeah I got flag I were losing yeah I got the flag just
protecting me oh I'm gonna lose speed right now I'm gonna be sitting duck in two seconds I'm
gonna be your your body shield oh my god there's a whole crew just following you did I kill that guy
oh finally geez oh yeah I got one up for you oh I'm dead I gotta kill though
good man I got another kill I know I'm gonna land right on top of everybody that's right there
oh no you mean that's like I ran right by it oh no oh that bastard got it
oh no oh we get the shotgun up oh damn yeah I didn't pull out early enough I should have
pulled it up way earlier oh it's Alex don't die I got him I got him man almost died I have 13
health my streak I'm not saying you're destroying 16 kills man I think I just blew that guy's
grenade up in mid air in front of him I think that's I think that's actually what just happened
where is the flag I don't know we don't have it there it's pretty much tied it's a pretty close game
right now I can't live this oh I just totally stole that from your burger boy
melee is so tough but so satisfying when you get it I only do like on a head cave people
are like snipers someone's last when you're an apple trader someone asks are they hats in this game
they do I wouldn't don't put a past them man this this game could have a lot of items in the coming
future all right you got the flag we're gonna lose we have absolutely
gonna lose try and cut this flag guy off yeah we're gonna lose oh it's done deal cut them off not
over yet guys no it's that guy's out of speed that guy's out of speed 7 to 24 I think it's over five
oh yeah absolutely I lose somebody called in the nuke oh wait no I had 10,000 credit but I called
in an inventory station instead mlsc has killed me 15 times in a row that's how he said
why I feel like a retarget I suppose going over the strike but I called him the end of
the choice it's all right there's nobody died give me that flag
oh all right I think uh whoops probably one more round maybe you guys want to play ctf or just
keep doing this um I don't see ctf can be very very long so I'll just do one more of this
you were you were here yet are you you you you you you you loaded at 45 seconds
he says 20 minutes ago well nowhere is I mean I got this game when beta first was announced for
this I signed up for this like this and firefall I signed up for like years ago yeah and
firefall is incredible I got the beta for that as well oh it's still jealous uh it's only two
times a week though you can only know gone in those two periods one for Europe and one for U.S but it
is it is insane it's looking like an incredible game if you get a chance to get it what what is five
four what is it it's another free to play game coming out and uh it was like the highlight
one of the highlights of e3 last year um it's um how can you describe it how can you describe
aesthetics what is it called firefall oh I think you said that someone said five four that's what
I that's what I just that's what I did just say oh well when you're gonna get five four three two one
it burns you and then fall as it falling oh sorry english accent fortunately come across great
well no I'm I'm just idiot so firefall is like okay oh firefoot we played that we played
that attack east last year yeah that's the one yeah five fourth three two one
it looks like borderlands with an immo and then open world and then awesome art style and it's
it beyond star is absolutely beautiful it's one of the one of those my stunning games I've seen in
beta like it looks good as it is yeah right that's cool oh this guy's gonna land on that no he's not
oh I get get blasted come on oh yeah oh why am I sure I'm here with being the flag guy
I'm going after this dude down here like I'm playing juggernaut I'm up the marker with juggernaut
I'm okay I'm gonna get better with him oh come on walk into that this guy is standing still
oh I just got that guy in the air with every name six did anyone else do that yeah I did I was
watching them come I was I was like 15 feet above the guy I just like look in front of him
and just like pop the grenade right on his back and he dropped the flag oh yeah change
in right behind you tell like so he's dead now somebody behind me now I think
is a okay guy you don't hope he's not okay more is he oh no he's okay oh boy come on land land
oh nice shot dude like a ballet of death right there germa you're on being chased I'm dead
another like a new about it you're right next to me why oh well where is he oh okay as you guys
my friends list like it's what you feel like names I know yeah I'm trying to get him to walk
into this grenade now he's going too fast how do you go I just launched him somewhere great where
the hell is he oh of course he's right next to me got like two people behind you germa yeah I'm
trying to go I'm trying to go for the suppressing oh I'm stuck I'm stuck I'm gonna die I'm so dead I'm
like on the ground nope nope you've got it you've got it oh my god oh you just saved my life right
there what's my graphics card I use a GTX 470 in video it's good I wouldn't really recommend if
you're gonna get a new graphics card don't get the 400 series because the 400 series at least the
470 and the 480 they heat up way too much they are not recommended they're very they're good cards
but they can get to be like 80 90 degrees Celsius and it's not really that good for your computer
York I did I did play Globo agenda I have something like 700 hours I think clocked in on that game
on global agenda yeah I've got I used to play both the insus used to play it like seriously
global global global agenda is different I think global offensive no no global agenda I was
before it was free like we we bought it and we played it and oh god like we put in hours into that
game and then it all kind of went downhill after a while when they went free and they built tribes
ascent instead they took all their money out of global agenda put it into tribes instead so yeah
yeah that's for and that's cool I what was global agenda was a like similar game third person
shooter yeah it was that first then you could also get into first person when you aim
down site and things like that it was it was a really good concept just it needed to be made by
a bigger company if that makes sense yeah it does like APB I guess APB could have been
out of some time or I don't know how to APB went into like the crap right didn't it because like
they granted a money or something oh yeah they they weren't so much dead yeah it was just like oh
free game we'll buy you just made it free for everybody just went downhill from then on in
yeah there is no health kit by the way there's no health kits in this game
oh
oh shit so
I think we're we're gonna win absolutely by the way I've had the flag of the entire game that guy
just been standing around hung with me with this oh give me a shot
that's that's a sniper
gorgeous man this guy this guy is get him here we go nice yeah buddy oh I got it
if I don't need it I just oh that was an air shot oh that was a pretty close air shot
the I don't know if I would really count that I get the more ammo and come back fight oh
blah I got a four core quad core four cores
oh that was interesting I guess what I just did
the spin fuser are you still carrying the flag MLC yeah this guy just walking right he's
like flew right by you like whatever I'm gonna come and chase you next I'm gonna come back to you
are you all right are you dead what's what are you doing still oh no I probably
want to work my problem oh you gotta do oh you got people on you now
how did they find a figure out how the game was played if I could not be such a slug I would come
over there all right they're not gonna be able to have a juggernaut why do you forstake me
oh here a juggernaut the one you can't keep up I'm pretty much like in molasses right now
always dead oh they're trying to slide me yeah they got a couple of snipers actually in the
else all right let's get some f in speed here well well live I look at that slug I missed them
I can't even like go chase it me either I'm like the heavy weapons guy
no that's a character in slow-tooler no that's right oh I finally died oh well am I actually
gonna like move more than like two miles for our now okay so what else picked up the flag oh great I'm
going in the opposite direction that everybody is all right as enough I'm changing the path finder
oh my find back time to commit suicide that didn't even kill me oh what's that it's a big bouncing
blue green ball oh
regular why is that you the fly no that's the clay oh so beautiful I'm going this way
mlg grandpa is on an offseason right now it'll be back in probably a couple weeks I'm assuming
I'm gonna go help protect the flag carrier
yeah
you whoo
hey if you hit one of those water guys who's when they're going off it'll actually give you like a
10 air really yeah it's gonna be seen on they like going off on the mountains
the best two maps are this one and the one we're gonna play next and the worst ones I love
how we just got done playing that's my opinion I left the castle on the best
oh what did you put what just hit me
that guy doesn't got a uh
oh
let's go on this way
guys on top
no
you have sweet sweet grenade bliss
you have 10,000 credits easier super duper okay
okay uh you just got that thing uh you have like yeah three four five
I'm just gonna shoot it randomly over here see if I end the game
I don't even help how big it's all over the world yeah I think I end it with my
straight over oh it starts huge yeah it's huge I got like four or five kills of them
hey 31 flag help medals
sick census 99 yes the Alex is on that server
oh all right though I think that's uh that's gonna be it to the stream
first place second place third place fifth place
cool that's pretty legit yeah almost
not correct yeah sorry I really you didn't get in but we're gonna quit anyway
sorry I didn't get it in time all right we do it for next time yeah no I'm getting for next time
but yeah um thanks everybody for coming appreciate it
and we're gonna play quap to end the stream by yourself
to end the stream by myself I am
so I'm not gonna go get some butter toast because I just woke up and it's like five
all right well for bandwidth purposes I'm gonna just end the call
no I'm gonna end the call because I'm the host all right well thanks for coming to the stream guys
all right I want to see you next time
take your bettas
oh all right let's play a little quap if you missed it I'm gonna upload this whole thing to
um to youtube by the way so the whole thing will be on youtube if you missed the beginning
quap make sure this is even lined up oh what's this big annoying ad over here oh my god
I'm refreshing this that's like gonna give me a seizure here we go
well let's do it all right I'm gonna really take my time with this
see if I can get the slug mode again yeah thank you if you guys are taking off thank you so much
for coming if you missed the beginning of the stream it's gonna be on youtube in the next probably
couple hours whenever youtube decides to process it who knows how long that's gonna take but yeah
let's end it on this one last one come on now I'm going backwards going backwards it's not what I
want to do if I get 10 meters I'll be happy that's all I care about oh yeah feel like I'm doing
a dance move like stick your left leg out for your left leg that that's gonna be oh my god
I can't I can't go forward I can't my right leg is always the leg that I can never use I don't
know why it always ends up like that and that's when we fall backwards oh for yeah thank you so
much guys I'm gonna end up with that I am tired but yeah I'll um I'll catch you guys later thanks
again for coming this will be on youtube again like I said so peace guys oh I'm getting some
acid reflux but yeah peace guys thank you so much for coming take care guys bye