Oh
Oh, yeah
Oh, yeah, test and out stuff test and out the stream test and out the stream
Test and out stuff test and out the stream test and out the stream
Oh
Test it
Oh, test it all right
Oh
Oh, yeah
Somebody got to stop that boom, let me let me get out of here
Let me just get out of I got a new item sick
Okay, we live I hope so
Pop this out
All right
Okay
Okay looks like we're live
Should be
Oh, we are there we are hey guys
Hop that out okay, here we go here we go
This all right
Okay
Hello
I gotta tell people I'm streaming
Gonna play some CS goal tonight along with some TF2
Oh happy same Patrick's day everybody I
Didn't even say that
Yeah
Yeah, this is a second live stream on YouTube
Hopefully it goes well. Hopefully nothing explodes
But yeah, happy same Patrick's day
Made a look at the eye or shine upon you
You gotta find a better server than that
I
Do live in Boston one two three I'm reading it
All right, let's get this going
All right, hold on I
Gotta tell my steam group what's going on
Because I'm trying to do the transition from Twitch to YouTube so we'll see how see how it goes
I get I got a lot of mixed responses a lot of people are like no go to Twitch and then people say no YouTube is much better
It's torn between two different places
But eventually I'm gonna be able to stream an HD on here so that should be pretty cool. Why can't I go to my steam group?
Oh, right. I'm not like even online
Whoops
Let's get to an event Saturday YouTube stream
Oh party
And
Woo
All right, let's get a server here
Has nobody in it
Zero out of 28 arena lumberyard game. I don't know if I want to go there
One two three
Let's get zero out of 30 there we go. There we go zero out of 32. That's what I'm looking for
Warm front Casbah
King of Hill, New Cleans. Let's go to New Cleans
All right guys, this is the server I'm playing on right now
And here it comes we'll let everybody go
Yo, my stream is broken
My stream isn't broken is it
I
Try and refresh it give it a good old refresh
All right join that I just put a IP into the chat that's where I'm gonna be playing
Oh
Using the vlog estimator
Shhh, I'm not gonna play with that play soldier
And ready even in here
All right, Weston if some of you guys could repost the IP I would be very grateful
You have a male what's going on chicken
So I have a new mouse we're gonna see how well this goes
And I don't hit that guy I got a razor death at her. Oh
Yeah, razor death at her. It's the blue one I'm gonna lights up blue
And if I'm gonna give never gonna give
So a lot of people can't load the stream. I wonder why
Everything should be the same as it was last time
Is it is more than one person having stream problems or is it just one or two people?
Error huh hold on a second
That's weird
The people that are having problems with what what country from
It might be because you're from a country that doesn't support or something
YouTube is still in kind of like a debate of streaming stages
Oh my god
I can't believe I well
How
Yeah, if you're I guess if you're having stream problems
Just close out your browser and then come back or clear out some of your cookies or something like that
I don't know I wish I knew what was going on because if everybody was having that problem
I would be like dog and I'd have to like fix it right away
Oh, that was so lucky
Oh, you're the spy
Yeah, let me just look at my own stream and see what happens
Gonna pull it up for a second here. Let's see what it looks like for me
Expedia, let's see
Why not just get a double at
I got a double add on my own stream
I'll offer a sacrifice to YouTube. I mean looks yeah, I'll show you guys we'll do streamception
It looks all right on my end. I don't know
I'm not sure guys. I apologize if it doesn't look like that on your screen
Oh my god, look at all these people high five baby
Oh, we're gonna get spawn trapped. Everyone's like just in here hanging out
Oh
Oh crit screen go now
Put a lot of pressure on me here
No, it's not a spy
Oh my god, it's alive. I'm so bad
Oh god
I just hit like a lag patch right there. That wasn't good
Oh, yeah, I'll show my loadouts good good call good call loot. Oh, well, I just missed your name good call Phoenix
So right now I'm using
The black box reserve shooter in the equalizer and I got this stuff on too
You
Got let's do it
Yeah
All right, so I'm getting a couple more messages saying the stream is all screwed up
You know we're gonna do this right we'll do this
I'm not sure if I can even restart it to be honest
It might like screw a bunch of stuff up
Yes
We'll go scout they got the mad milk the stock
stock
Oh crap no die
Well the only thing I could say is if people are still having problems and then
This should be uploaded to youtube within the next hour or two
You should be able to watch it on youtube
I
Don't make me I'll try every start because that looks like more people are having problems
Control point and they will get going
Yeah, I got it's a it's a razor death adder I like it. It's good. I'm not a big fan of big bulky mice, but this is uh
This fits comfortably
Where oh my god the railside the door that's just like scared the crap out of me
No, I'm going this way
Let's get out of here. Come on spy. Let's get the hell out of here
I'm lagging so bad
Look at all bad of lagging right now everyone's like a freaking slide show
Streamception
I
Did I did I kill that guy that I just confused myself
Oh
I can't believe I made it
Longer tech all day
Yeah, I actually know it if some of you guys will notice I have quick switch on now
I am not using the regular non-quicks which anymore because I can do stuff like this
See how I switch to that because I got a button on my thumb now
I can use the button on my thumb to switch to the um to the melee slot
Cool, huh? No more no more slow switch for germa those are the days of the past
Oh my god so many people up there
Chris Creek oh my god
Oh, I'm gonna go uh I'm going soldier
No, no, no, no, no
Somebody said go combat and gee I will I will go combat and gee
Oh my god, they got us like spawn trapped
We are spawn trapped
Anybody up here
Center down
How about how it's keeping a break I got one hit on that guy
Oh my god, I just realized something that I don't have the tunnel have the gunslinger on
I
All right, well whatever this works
Nice big century baby
Oh, no, oh no, oh no, I have no metal
Well, that's fine take it out. I don't care
What does even what does even happen to me right there what is going on
I did so much lag on this server
The girl I have is I want you know any dating advice do I have any dating advice um
The only dating advice I could give is
I don't know I'm not really the best at oh, I gotta I gotta take this off
I'm not really the best at dating advice to be honest
If I had any I would definitely give it to you
I
The only thing I can really say is don't pretend to be somebody and not because after a while people find out
That's pretty much the only advice I can really give
Oh stay a stab
Wait, wait, wait, where am I sent for even go just happened
What even just happened to me
Uh, no, I am not stoned. I am not
I don't do that drug free up in here
Dating advice it's a trap
You know we gotta get away from the spawn
You know in the other one my god rocket the face
Wait, how did I not
No, I'm gonna die and that's why
Oh yeah, I got like a dozen extra eggs here
I have two dozen eggs now I'm just kidding
No more eggs for me
Not unless I make a stupid bet with myself
Oh did I make it I made
All right, I made it made it out of the spawn door
Oh
Probably street for an hour or two
Oh my god, I just can't scrap at him
Uh, yes, I am playing in a window
I am in a window
Get him off the port
No point to any space
Eggs no, I'm not from New Jersey I'm from Boston. I'm from the bean town
And if you're just joining the stream happy St. Patrick's Day
If you happen to be of Irish descent I am of Irish descent so
I
Later on after this stream I'm going with my family we're gonna go get some corn beef and cabbage at a restaurant
Should be a good time
Did you see some aunts and uncles I haven't seen in a little while so should be cool
Whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa
How did I survive that wholly crap I need like health
I
Can't believe I survived that
Come on come on come on
Just at least give me like oh what am I doing my brain just like exploded right there
I'm trying to like why build something and just die with crit I idiot
I just burned it was by
At least I think I did oh
We really what what's doing this well over time you
I'll take that oh
Jump over the rocket I just rocket jumped with his rocket
Right now it is six p.m
Eastern time
Do I like streaming on twitch or youtube I think they both have their own little perks
I
For instance, I think more people can watch a twitch live stream because twitch is available in more areas
oh
Yeah twitch is available more in more places
I think that the reason why people are having problems with this stream is youtube streams are not available
All over the place in the world
I'm pretty sure that's the problem people are having
Is there no damage spread on the server?
How did I not hit him
Don't get yourself killed run away
Oh come on
Oh my god
No get that scout
Oh what
Which is I oh I thought I died from the flame thrower
Arbis corn beef I you know what I there is no arbis around here
I wish there was an arbis around here I'd go there every day
Those of you that have arbis near you is it any good I always see the commercials and I'm like god
I want one of those like roast big sandwiches
I
Spy spy sure why not
Mission be guidance in ten seconds
Oh, well, that's fine. That's fine with me. I'll just bump into you
I'll just bump into you
Look I am heavy. Oh my god. That's such a bloating
That is bull already
Slow-mo that back I backstabbed him
If we lose
How did it hold on you guys hear that it just said you fail victory. What was that?
You fail victory
You
No
Actually hit him
Hit me hit me hit me with that crit rocket
Oh god I'm I wait oh no get out of my way
Look I'm a heavy
Sick mini gun
Oh
Boink
Oh come on give me behind all these bastards
Oh
Like gloves of running urgently and I'm running wicked slow. Yeah, that's not like a trouble giveaway
Take you to
No, no no no more heavy disguise all this guys eat the sandwich no
Oh boy
Damn it
So Arby's really is terrible
My processor how many gigahertz is your processor it is 3.6 gigahertz I believe it's overclocked
It is an overclocked intel i7 950
I'm a real engineer don't worry
Oh, okay, I'll stab give me a k. I'll stab
Yeah, I do apologize if you're getting errors on here. There's not a whole lot
I can really do about it besides just like it's not stream
I
Want backup a little bit
Damn I got a GTX 470 in video
Evga edition I think that's also a clock too. That's overclocked as well
I got a lot of overclocked stuff
Oh
It's not gonna be good up here
Ah
We get away get away get away get away
Talking about like face stabs. I still have not gotten a stair step not once in the entire time
I've ever played team fortress to never gotten to oh my god. Hey stair step. Oh no I did no
I
This like 12 people in this hallway how did I get killed
Oh
If that scale fastened oh you're not gonna get away
I'm gonna get away
Let's go uh I'm gonna go sniper costume
Let's go sniper costume, baby. Oh
I'm just sniping just sniping home. We gotta like be careful here like let me in the spawn
Let me in like the spawn door
Is that a
Oh boy run away run away
Oh no that would have been my first stair step ever hey buddy
Damn it that would have been my first stair step ever
Oh
I will get one of those damn things
Damn I uh how did I not get that I'm just gonna I'm gonna get a stair step it's gonna happen
Oh shit
Today we're gonna go stair stabbing
Oh I'll go heavy we need to heavy
I'll go told me slob heavy I got on the
Tommy slob well still I got
Well crit rocket damn
Yeah after this rom we're gonna go to a new server so get to a new empty server
Yeah I have this is my heavy setup
Oh god five seconds left that we like losing a winning I don't even remember. Oh let's take a winning
Is it got a coming from
We did it
Hooray
I'll follow you to the depths of hell all right new server
The next server is going to be refresh
Oh stair stab with a heavy
Okay
Let's go to
Hmm
Oh
These are there 32 here we go stop refresh gold rush control point kings
Um looks like we're gonna go here
New server
For stream
Here you go
You
Putting it in the chat right now there it is
Everybody go there if you can make it
I have not played tribes this and Tony
I'm thinking about getting into it thinking about trying to get into the open beta
No, I just really haven't had time to be honest I've been doing a whole lot of um
TV watching lately
Plus I got that new dog and I'm kind of busy lately so
It's been it's been tough to get into new games at least the last week or so
Let's go red
Why don't I what how can I keep getting defaulted
To the pyro
I
Spray
Oh
I love that I want to do that too quick no too late
You know what I'm gonna play engineer I'm gonna play real engineer
I'm gonna be I'm gonna be a weird engineer weird bastard
No, but let's put it down. What's my thing?
I can see your comment
Help me build this pyro thanks dude
My opinion on the very controversial subject of bread
Well, obviously bread is an incredibly incredibly controversial subject
I think that the
Best kind of bread is weak bread
But then of course the white bread will get really irritated with that and the rye bread might rise up and take over the
Wheat country of d'Ostaadu so I'm you know, I like to stay pretty neutral
Bam
My brain just exploded right there. I'm like what am I doing? I thought I was on offense for a second
Where the hell is shibi?
Where is shibi 20 142? Oh, he's probably working right now. He's a he's a real working man now
Still we have six NG's oh my god. Oh
This is okay. Let's do it. I love you with this at least
It's at least I could do oh my god. Oh well it looks like we crashed the server
Oh, don't worry everybody. We have every entrance secure
All we need is one pointing down the stairs and you're talking about hystericalness
Oh my god, this server is laggy as hell
Oh my god, all right, I'm moving. I'm going down here
I'm going right here. They don't even know I'm here either
Oh
Skibi they revenge crits. That's all I'm caring about right now. I'll change classes after this
Oh, that's a spy
What what what what
Oh, it's because everyone like oh my god look at these pings
Look at these pings
Holy crap
Oh, well, it looks like we just like broke this guy's server
Hey, mr. wlf
Sorry, but we broke your server
Yeah, new server
New server
Oh god
All right, I'm just a shoot people with a pistol until I die again and then I'm changing
Oh, I'm gonna go on a tie-rate
Yeah, new server this place is this place is ridiculous about
All right
What is Caspa
Do another refresh
Yeah, somebody in the head like 900 ping oh my god
Forget that
There we go
We might have to go and do a 24 or 30. Yeah, let's see this one's 29
We'll go to capture the flag well why not most most spots
All right, this is where we're going
This new server
Here we are
Everyone head there, hopefully this place doesn't like crash
Yeah, if you're getting the stream error try closing out your browser and like clearing out like your like your browser history like you cash and all that and then try coming back in that seems to have been working for some people
Hark time
Yeah, I just wrote the IP
Oh, let me write this I don't think people can come on
Let's try it. I'm gonna write this in the chat just because some people um
There we go
That didn't go through
Oh
That's that oh god this this server is like no better
Yeah, I post I posted the IP earlier that's why
I like the black box better personally in my opinion. Oh my word
I just think the black box is just I don't know oh
That was a this oh
Man, I've never done somebody cock wheels in my life
She's
Give me that elf oh
I heard a fry mode
Mm-hmm, I'm a drill here. Oh damn mini century
He had a man's drop darin teller teams
Whoa, what was that I just heard a bunch of noise going on over there
You can't use your flames in here
Whoa nice dispenser
Yeah screw that train
Now I'm not gonna hit by the tree again. That would have been two in a row
That would have been two train travesties in a row
I want to kill that medic
Mm-hmm I'm not fire know
Get to that water gotta get in the water
Where'd he go where'd he go oh my god chaos
Oh, I'm so dead
Ha ha no I'm gonna drown
I'm making a run forward let's go let's go like all the way to the back of their base
Now they get a big century over here
Oh, not that I can't I can take it out oh no god why did I crouch
What was the what why did I crouch oh my god oh
What the hell
That was be you
You know the rest LL
Couldn't take anything out
What I like to see TF3 I would love to see a TF3
I don't think it'll ever happen though
I think they're kind of gonna stick with the community idea thing and let the community run with it and I'm gonna die
I
Play sniper I
Play sniper with the cozy camper
I got the coat let's see what it looks like. Yeah, it's here it is cozy camp
Other really slot reservations here. Oh, what am I doing?
What why am I running in there like that? Oh, I got the cozy camper doesn't even matter
I'm not gonna flinch
Ah
How am I missing this guy
Oh, how they just running by us all come here you bastard
What no items would I like to see in team fortress a
Run run no my friend
Oh come on come here
Oh come on that would have been sick
No get that
A weapon I like to see in team fortress is a
new
Engineer primary that's not a shotgun
I guess they kind of already did that with the Pomsim
But it's still technically a shotgun. I'd like to see a total replacement for the shotgun
Am
I'll protect that medic
Damn, I gotta put on I gotta put the uh
So is it true that this works the cozy camper works with the Huntsman?
Yeah, that this probably some bug in the youtube streaming right now to be honest because this should not be double ads playing
That's like that just should not be like happening
Oh
And are you like stuck in an infinite ad?
Infinite ad
Oh, watch it
Ow
So is it is the stream was it in your sub boxes guys just wondering
Oh, that was sick
Oh
Because maybe that's another part of the problem I've I've had a couple people say that it's not it wasn't in the subscription box
Or it should have been oh
Too many people attacking oh not and no I don't know to do
Oh, it is infinite ads are you serious?
Oh
My god
That's all that this this is just a bug in the youtube streaming definitely
In fit it ads
Give me a break just just
Reload the screen
I
Is reload the street
Yeah, if you're getting if you're getting infinite ads if you get like stuck in an infinite ad just reload the stream
youtube dot com the best website in the world
Oh
Oh, and anybody can buy the train
Damn it
Damn it I can't see him. He's the flames of blocking him
Oh
Yeah, if you if you're getting infinite ads definitely definitely just reload the stream or like just come back because that's
That's stupid
That should absolutely not be happening
Oh add that add then add
That's so the dumb
Oh
That medic is standing still
I didn't kill the medic
But I kill was weird
Oh
Oh god, oh god, no why why
Are we by any car
You
Yeah
Just kill can somebody in the stream right uh that if you're getting like an just reload the browser if you're getting an infinite ad like more like two or three of you say it because this the chat is uh
Quite fast
Because I wouldn't want someone to just sit there and like be like what is going on?
I
Got crits
Did that help
No, no, no, no, get out of the range
After this run I'm gonna hop into some CS go for a little bit should be interesting
Do
Yeah, all the all the things you're seeing are
YouTube streaming bugs apparently none of this happened last time those of you that were here last time
I i don't think I can restart the stream that's the problem
The thing with YouTube is once you start you have to either stop and like remake an event or you can't
I think it's it's weird like that. I've got a crit screen right now. Oh my god
I killed one person
Oh
Infinite ads. Oh my god. Well, I guess the one possibly good thing is this thing will be watchable on YouTube
Hopefully unless there's more bugs
Oh
Wonder why predict oh he's gonna fish kill me. No, he's gonna fish kill me. He's gonna fish kill me
He fish killed me
Oh
All right, we'll go with three more deaths and I'm gonna hop on CS go
I'll see if there's something I can do on my end
I don't think there is unless I turn off the stream and then like redo another live event
Which I mean it takes a little while to set these up on YouTube, so
uh
YouTube bugs for the win
Oh
Damn, but I only lowered that a little bit. Oh, where they get these crits
What what was it? No, that wasn't a medic
What was that
You're gonna be rolling that bacon buddy, huh? I don't think so maybe I'll get like banned like they're probably gonna be like oh
We saw that you loaded 25,000 ads to like you cheated
When in reality, it's just like a bug on this site
Yeah, CS go is the new counter strike. It's in beta
All right, this is my last life last life and I'm gonna hop on CS go. Where am I going?
Where's this guy going?
Oh another one. Oh no, that's in the comp one more life
YouTube premium only $30 a day
30 bucks a day
That's more money than my data plan for my phone is in a whole month
Oh, I got him to kill himself
First infinite ads second jerk wow
YouTube
Thank God for YouTube and then not buggy site at all
It works perfectly every single time you want to use it
How did I not hit him oh
All right CS go time
Okay, I'm gonna I'm gonna let's let me disconnect from here hold on a second. Let's figure this out
What the hell is going on I'm gonna I'm playing my own stream
We go
See what happens I'm watching okay, isn't it ad
Let's see what happens after this ad
All right, what do you got for me you're gonna give me like another ad what do you got
Oh look another ad you serious
Wow all right, uh, yeah, this is this is stupid
Oh my god you too, oh wait, it worked
Okay
Okay, I got two oh
Thank God for YouTube all right um
Can I like hold on let me go to my video manager for a second
Okay, I'm just gonna turn off all the ads now if I can even do that
I've been dashboard
No, the stream is in good health sure it is
Oh sure it is
I don't understand I see there's like nothing I like I'd I'd have to turn off the stream
This dumb
All right, well
You're stream is in good health apparently not
Yeah, if you still have in the ad problem or if you just barely getting back from it
I apologize that that is not what was supposed to be happening
Come on second, yeah see like the only thing I can do is just like stop broadcasting
Which will turn off everything and then I have to like reset up a new event
Oh, well, it should go right to YouTube this should be uploaded to YouTube without any
BS so I do apologize though
Let's uh go to
I'm gonna straight go
All right
Screen the screen's gonna go black
While I load up uh kind of straight go
Counter-strike global offensive
It's all on bear with me for a second ta
Remove ad
See yes go
Okay
Huh
So counter-strike go is
All the sudden 2000 people quit the stream I wouldn't blame a man that that's stupid that's annoying
If I was just sitting there wanting to watch a live stream and it was like oh here you go
Here's like 15 ads right next to each other in a row
I'd be pissed off too. That's stupid
How did I get a beta key from a really cool dude his name he's just wants to he wants to go buy anonymous
He uh if he's in the stream if you're in the stream anonymous then thank you so much. You are amazing
All right
I looks like we're on my map. We've been on holiday to buy stuff
Uh pistols let's go with the
That's a deal do I have enough money for that and I do
All right, let's do it
How much you see us go it's it's not out yet. I gotta turn my sensitivity is way too high on this
We'll change that
Oh god
Oh, I'm sensitivity
Keep order mouse mouse sensitivity come down
There we go
Audio
Audio down
Resume all right we lost
All right, that's much better
Doberad is baby. I need to start saving money. What am I doing?
Click click
De dust is dustier
Oh, I just sorry. It's like unloaded a clip on you. Whoa. They take a long time to reload
But
These things take a long time to reload
Bag
I actually like these
I'm gonna keep these
Let's get a uh how much money do I have?
I can't afford helmet and
I'm gonna stick with these. I'm good. I'm good with these
You
Long range pistol attack
It's up there
Oh
Oh god, what am I doing? What I what I just pick up I didn't want that
What was up with that
I didn't want to pick up that weapon that was BS
Is that the P90 or the ppm whatever it is
So let's watch this guy to see how good this guy is. Oh, you just got smashed
You just got smashed
I
Think this is coming out in a couple months. Maybe I don't know. There's no release date for it yet. It's in beta
It's a pp
Check the ppl
If I get one car for free, I would want the most expensive car you could ever make
I would want like a Lamborghini or like a Bentley
Give me like the absolute most expensive car you can buy and then like then I'll just resell it. Oh drops on
Damn, I got one guy. I got yeah, I got one guy
Take it
The best lord
If I like what's going on? Why is this guy just like sitting there?
Is this guy camping with a digel?
How you gonna copy isn't it of this is you have to go to give the take valve survey
They have like a csgo survey
All the famas and Kevin Longhom
I've been invited to join the group kill free gaming
So is this a burst this is a lot different than it is in colloduty I'm assuming
Where is this guy's down there oh no no no no no no run away
Ah
That guy's right there. Oh damn it got me
Boston's good
Boston is good
I like it
It's kind of cold out here now though
The survey is if you just type into google type in like
Connistrike go beta survey. I'm sure you can you know come up. It'll be on a valve website or connistrike website
I
Think you can do it through steam as well
I mean, maybe they aren't even doing it anymore. I'm not sure if anybody knows
Where's the
Is it the mp7 the the one from connistrike the original I like I think it might be forget
Oh
Yeah, they're not even close two totally different games. I'm gonna go this way I have more luck going this way before
Oh lord
Hmm I'm gonna get flashed. I'm gonna get flashed
Ah
Damn, how did I not get that guy come on that's ridiculous. That is redonculus. Oh, I'm gonna turn my uh I
Heat seeking missile thing up. Oh, or black screen per second
Resume game
The beta ends probably when the game comes out
I
Scout asks for a dispenser will you give him one?
Actually the questions were kind of weird
It was like let me ask you something
What's what does more damage in a round the m4a1 or the ak47 which one do you think is more powerful?
They ask you to ask you like actual real questions about itself
That's not how I got into it though. I got somebody gave me a beta key
I
Want to go let's go turn aside
Would I buy a Ferrari if I had the money like to just throw away I absolutely would
Oh, do a burrette is
Oh
Yeah, I need to buy a frag what am I doing?
Am I not buying anything
All that behind us to yikes
Gonna go around this way. I'm gonna I'm gonna surprise this bastard
Can I even go around this way? I don't think so. I would love to hear a joke
You
Where the hell is everybody there's only two guys left on the team. There's one
Oh, I just totally gave myself away
Oh my god, I'm out of the idiot I am
I'm so stupid
Firing around in the air with dual pistols equals MLG pro
Yeah, I want I want to buy I want to get a rifle man
Ah that guy I got just unloaded oh
You're taking the survey now. I'm good good
I love potatoes. They are unbelievable
All right, let me get a
What do I have a heavy Nova?
This thing is 5200 bucks. Oh my god
The
Gillil okay, I don't take out the Gillil
No, I want a grenade. I want a ball of top. We're doing a model top right now
How do I switch to it? Is it what is it three? Oh, it's four okay four
Gonna throw it down the hall
Let's throw this down here
Mall talk out
Oh
Whoops
Hey, I'm sorry. I just like totally ruined everything teammate. I apologize for that
I thought that was a guy right there next to him. Oh my god. Oh my god. No
Ah
Mr. Kami I'll say your name
You
Counter-terrorist win I lost all my money
Hmm
I want something with like a this thing's got the highest fire right huh
None of these are that accurate
This thing that's sniper oh the AWP's back
I'll go to Gillil I like to go Lil
I need some more money I gotta start killing people
Not like running around like a nitty-ditty
All right, this is where the action is oh my
Duh, oh I knew it. Why did that go around so carelessly
If I had a frag grenade or if I had a Molotov that would have been game over
Super Taco well. I'm glad to be your hero
If there's anything I can do to protect this country and this world I won't do it
This guy is this guy's so dead
Ah
He had the right idea right there
Leprechauns oh come on pull it off oh oh
Oh damn
Look at that he ended up be pulled it off
I bet you I will see that comment the awesome that you I will all right I want to go
I don't want the shotgun
Let's go to fire seven
KELVLAAR
And I want high explosive grenade
All right
I'm not messing around anymore here
Read the word an Arabic what what where are you talking about
All right, this is this is the magic magic area
Boom get blown
Damn I'll bring it in
Damn
Reflectors like cat baby I'll take you I'll take your uh PM290 whatever it is
Ah
Every time I start talking like I'm like I just get annihilated
All right, I'm definitely buying that again because that's like I did good with that
And I want
Okay, that's a flashbang you you can buy more than one grenade I think I don't know why I'm only buying one or two
Be prepared
What's that from
15 German points what's that from be prepared
Get flashed
I just flashed myself
Oh, I'm an imbecile
I'll take you down to where you at buddy
Damn it, damn it, damn it, damn it, damn it, damn it, damn it, damn it
Ah
MLG block
I like this gun I need to get I need to start to stop being a turd and like do well
And grenades
I'm gonna go with another mallet of anaheim explosive grenade
I'm gonna have two different grenades we'll go with the mallet first
It's all right line king line king you all get it
Molotov baby, what are you saying? Let's light it up
Light it up, baby. What just happened? Oh my god, no
Oh god, this guy's so mad. I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry. I just killed all my teammates. Oh my god
Oh
Damn it
Damn it, damn it damn it
This guy is so mad. I have my voice turned off
But that guy is definitely screaming at me. I can guarantee you that
I
Is this a scope it is
Ooh, I think I might like this thing
All right, this time I'm not gonna flashbang myself
We get it we get anybody
Oh for the love of god
Damn
Beep, beep, beep
Dermal, why was there fruit punch on the floor? I don't know
People think to stop eating so much fruit punch
Well that guy just totally this guy kill Roy just killed the entire team
He legit just killed every single person
I gotta start using the SMGs. I am absolutely not one of those guys that can sit back and like do well by aiming
I just need to go like this
Oh
This guy's so oh he's a bot. Okay never mind. He's a bot
And he's all bots
How can my team has the bots
All right, let's go spray and pray baby
Oh
My god, how much does it take to kill the guy
What just happened
Where was that guy
What name of god I can I really
That's pretty cool
All right, I'm just I'm going with this straight up. I want money
So I got money
What the shotgun
I'm gonna use the shotgun
Just because I feel like it
I did play CSource I played 1.6
I wasn't really that good at it though. My brother was really good
My older brother was really good account of strike
Me not so much
I
Let me get somebody that just play okay um
I was drugged for a head shot
Damn it
That guy's good it's not fair that guys like too good at this game
I was using the shotgun
I
Got kill Roy. I want to get on his team
I'm for a nine right now how wow I'm long I'm doing the best on this team no way
I want to what's the most expensive one
MP7 and
Grenades I explosive grenade and I want them all tough
Can you put a silencer on stuff too isn't that possible
No, right this time I'm not going to like the entire team on fire promise
I have played some mMOs I played world of warcraft for so long
Oh, how am I I can't believe I didn't kill like I
That can head shot at me like how did I not land one shot on him
That is ridiculous in my opinion ridiculous
Unless he's like aim-bottom no, he's definitely not
He's just really good
I'm four and ten
Oh, if you die one more time you need to even egg
I had the most I had the most success to be totally honest with the fires but the five seven
I
Have lar forget about the stupid grenades one more of let's go
I've this I've only killed people with this weapon
All right, let's get some area denial down there
I didn't want this I didn't want this
I didn't I didn't want that
Dude this guy killed Roy seriously is just like destroying everybody
Kill Roy
Look at my look at my team and look at their team look at how I'm looking at how many pros are on their team
Look at how many like scrubs are on my team including me
If you got the ultimate scrub which is me
And then like two of those guys are like eight and two KDR
All right, I'll definitely I'll definitely do that next time seeing I'll take control of one of these bought baskets
Oh god
Hey white screen
I
Joe watch out getting my weight
I'm so dead
Going this way
How we won cool I shot like five people
An awesome pro 360 controller user
I
Already got the clock no the far seven sorry
Let's do it oh max out the pistol ammo
Okay, let's go
There's gonna be somebody right here and I'm gonna get friggin head shoted
Yeah
Yeah right here
That kill Roy god damn it head shot
Right quit
I'm going on different lobby
Go somewhere else
Watch me get put right into the same game
Oh, let's go right into the same game with with freaking killjoy the guy with 40 kills and like three deaths
Oh
Yeah, I'm gonna get my first mower happened this game
Why am I not making commentaries about CS I just got it I just got it
I got CS go probably three four days ago
All right good good this is a new lobby new map too
Very cool
New map there's no this is Italy right this is CS Italy
Hi Mexican koala how are you good to see you
Need backup I'm going this way
You
There we go
Let's clear this place out gentlemen
Well, that's how you win
That's how you win
All right, I got one that that's that's one that's 24 away from a mo app
Yeah
Yeah, I don't know when the TF2 update's gonna come out to be honest. I'm not sure
They've already started rolling out some changes. So probably in the near future. I'd say in the next
Probably in the next couple weeks you probably see some more stuff in TF2 hopefully at least
Gonna be a bunch of people around this corner
Oh right there this guy oh
Only my reactions were better and I didn't think that was a teammate
I use a razor death-atter that's the mouse I use
Oh take control of the bot. Oh, hey, what's up hostages
Oh
No, they got the hostages. What do we do?
Those poor hostages
Oh, apparently my my stream is just starting that makes perfect sense
Oh get away from me
I got one
Oh my god, look at all this fruit punch something happened here
He's right there
Oh
Wayne
We lost oh
That's right. I got like my kills with them when I took control of bots. Whoops
Oh, we're gonna do some sniping
We're gonna do some straight-up legit sniping
Oh, yeah, this is gonna be sick
Hell yeah
Why did the chicken cross the road to go meet his family for supper?
Oh
Bastard how am I not hitting you?
Oh quick scope
What what I was gonna say you gotta be got it I missed that
That was gonna be like oh I just die I go walk up five feet away from you
Actually this guy over here
Where's he oh
Get get dominated
Anybody else there's two more guys
Oh
No, no, no, no, no
Shoot
Come on come around the corner
How's he going that scares me where'd he go
Where is that dude
Where the hell is he oh
It's what what the hell what's going what
What he was just sitting there
You bought
All right, we'll do
Another two or three rounds
I wanna buy
Let's go with the pp and I didn't buy the Kevlar on my thinking Kevlar best
Oh look at that fire rate
You
Yeah, well to get a mo app I gotta I gotta kill more than like one person in a row
Joe
That's ridiculous
I can't believe I didn't kill him and that's ridiculous
I got a GTX 470 from a video that's the video card I got
There's a legal
Kevlar and helmet and a high explosive
Oh, yeah, all right, this probably would be the last round before the I in the stream because I want to go back and look and see what was going on
See what kind of errors were happening
This will be on YouTube if you if you just came if you just missed the beginning it's going
Oh
Give me the whole line of people
Oh my god, I don't kill in the whole line. I just killed like four people right there
Not look at that ammo conservation
I was just aiming down there aiming in your heads and I just killed everybody
But yeah, this is gonna be uploaded to YouTube
So if you missed it or if you couldn't watch it or something like that
This will be in your sub box as an watchable just straight through a video
At least I hope it will
Have I used this gun yet? I don't know
Gonna go up here. I'm gonna go up the log cabin. I don't never mind. No, I'm not. It's too much work to do
I
This guy stopped talking
Listen to me. He's like got another flare positive situation. Got it. Yep, Roger
Oh my I
Don't even know how that I don't even know how that happened. I don't even know how that happened
I want to watch that again
Because I had a kevlar. Yeah
I don't understand
I don't get it. I'll take control of you buddy
All right, all right, hostages
Let's talk business. What do you know about the operation?
Too late you didn't ask fast enough answer fast enough. What about you?
You like seeing your friend get shot like that? What do you know about the organization X?
Oh, I don't know. I just I'm so scared. Please just let me get that's not the right answer
Oh, they rescued them. It's all right. I
How does that even?
Oh
Don't ask me how that happened. I don't understand. I don't understand.
Oh, this is the dog. I didn't even see this. I used to love the dog
The
Og AUG the oggy
Come on show yourself
Nothing here
Get out of my way get out of here
What am I doing? What are you doing? You're a bot
You listen to me
I can't kill him
Oh, look it. It's I'm gonna be the only one left
It's going on red vids
I was gonna shoot the chicken. I was gonna shoot the chicken
Hey, yeah, I what what how come these are all just bots? I just went to quick match. It's not like I said please play me with bot only
I went to I just wanted to quick match. I don't understand
I you know, I kind of want to just die ready. Oh, this is gonna be funny
I
Did any of these and any of those guys have grenades? I hope they do
Oh, I just went so high. All right, let's see uh
I want this guy where are the hostages where are the hostages
Oh my god the entire team is right there
Oh
Come on. Oh damn it. All right guys
That's enough for me. See watch look ready exit to main menu. I went to uh
Played as much to quick match did I did I do a quick match or create a game? I think I just did a quick match
I don't know but yeah
Oh, thanks everybody for coming
If you are if you missed it or if you were having problems with the stream earlier
This should all be uploaded to youtube so you can watch the whole stream if you want from the beginning to end
Thank you guys for watching and I by do apologize. I'm sorry for the
The shenanigans that happened early. I don't even know what was happening like everyone was getting like 50 ads in a row
And that's not how I that's not how we set up so
I apologize if you were having problems
But yeah, thank you guys so much. I'll talk to you guys soon
And take care everybody
Next stream is going to be next saturday probably or you know, I might do one during the week
I'm not sure yet. I'm I don't know. I'm not sure
I assume that I will probably do one if not this coming saturday at six then
probably
Like Thursday and Wednesday something like that if I end up doing a midweek one
But I will I will check you guys soon
Thank you everybody goodbye
See you
I'm just how do I turn it off
I don't even know how to turn off my youtube stream hold on
Um, I can't stop streaming
I mean it's going to youtube.com
What if it was just locked forever like oh sorry you you you just stuck on youtube for the rest of your life
Okay
What is going on? Why can't I I can open up a new tab
Here we go okay
Here we go there it is
All right, yep. Thank you guys see you soon take care everybody