Okay, I apologize about that. That was weird. So what's going on guys? Hopefully you have
an fantastic saturday or if it's Sunday where you are too. I gotta shout this out. I
gotta say hey everybody come hang out. Hey everybody. Streaming on twitch.tv.com
we'll go and see us go. The best game mode is in CS go right now. Gun game. The real
gun game. The fun one. The one where it's instant response. You run around like crazy.
Steam community body. 15 minutes. Yeah.
Okay, dokey. Almost forgot Twitter. Let's get a server going so people can play while I finish this up.
How about a couple of king of the hill badlands? All right. You guys ready to be happy?
Oh, one second. Nope. Not even on the thing for it. Hold on. Let me press play.
Well, I have to like give the IP to burger boy because he got really mad at me last time. I didn't give it to him.
So here we go. Ready? Nope. Oh, you're gonna get you're not gonna make it. I'm gonna
both face it. People probably reading it right now going in. Wait, did you already
paste it? No. I'm like wasted. It's just sitting on the screen right now. People will be able to
get it. There's already people in there. Oh, sorry. That was tweaking.
All right. Ready? I'll be in five seconds. What were you doing? Were you like all like toilet?
I was getting off. I'm about to hit this button. I'm about to hit the button. 63.146.
Call in 27025. You better hurry up. All right. I wasn't even ready.
What were you doing? But join the I'm joining off of you. Oh, you better hurry up, John.
Oh, steamy day.
We're good. I'm in here. I gotta like I don't even put it on. Yeah, I told you to like go because I could like remember the number.
I can remember that 12 digit number. No, HL2 dot EXE troll. What's gonna happen there? It's not real. It is real. It's always real.
Now when it's loading the game. Have I seen the hung I've not seen the hunger games? Is it any good?
And if the answer is yes, I will probably see it. It's about as good as the TV show community.
It's good as it gets. That was a good movie with Jack Nicholson. Oh, there's Berkaboy the insensitive one.
The insensitive one. Berkaboy the insensitive one.
There he is. Because we all know that he's a real insensitive bastard. You've seen it five times.
Oh, it's gonna be bad. You didn't think different happened that fifth time? Ouch. Different, I think.
Oh, there's a big Twitter. Where's my like hold on? I gotta like say it to my Twitter followers.
No, hold on. Just tick.
Oh, yeah. I just take it. Oh, it's those of you wondering. I'll bring up my back back so you can look at it.
Oh, Berkaboy. The insensitive one.
There's this page one. So you can go over page one while I do Twitter and then I'll do page two in a second.
I go backstabbed. Don't get backstabbed.
Alrighty. All right, we go to page two. Page two. That's the page two.
Even though you can't see. Oh, wait, show up. Oh, yeah. Sorry. Sorry.
So look at back to page one so you can see the colors. This whole thing's been given away.
So hopefully you're one of the winners.
Oh, no, page two. I got a lot of strangers. A lot of strangers.
Page three. That you hit your head. Yeah.
Page four.
I love how Berkaboy is using the vlogger now.
Hey, you're going to have to deal with it now, aren't you? No, I do know. He's on my arty.
I'm like, medic in hand.
One more page after this.
Does the needed one stick you to the wall?
I don't think it does. It ain't only the.
My character was like standing up. I tried to kill him. And then page six.
This is probably like the best page with all my actual hats that I like love.
And all the strangers are of course over here. You get the idea.
Let's do it. Let's do a high five and let's get this wrong.
Yeah, items that I cannot give away. I'm not. I won't be able to give away.
So I can't give away the cheaters lament. I can't give away.
I think there's a couple other things you can't give either.
There's like two or three items. I know for sure I can't not give.
Alvegim Julu. Let's turn it back.
Just a tick. Just a tick.
Where's my gerotti? I don't have the gerotti.
Oh, schmack. Oh dear, not again.
Oh, watch it, watch it, watch it, watch it.
On this corner here. Many century. Get out of here.
Oh, how did I not get him? Get him.
You as buy you kind of act in like one.
Look, MLC stealth just killed stealth.
It's fun. When do I think I'll hit 25,000?
Probably a couple weeks maybe. Maybe a week. I don't know.
It's going to happen sooner rather than later. I probably will say that.
I don't know though.
I have no idea.
Follow me, Jack.
Oh, you ran into it.
I was pretty nice.
I don't say so myself.
I just got like fished. I got fish killed.
I'm streaming this to the Boo Man 61 and MLC stealth.
Boo and stealth. Hello. Hello.
Those are your wonder.
I was kicked by console. That's not cool.
You got kicks? No, no, no, no, someone's saying they were kicked.
What would you do? Nothing proper.
That's a bunch of B. It's changing level.
It felt like you were talking to your dog.
What did you do? What did you do, auto?
I'm not.
Nukuleus, huh? Nukuleus. Nukuleus.
Direct it. I'll try it.
I'm not.
Why am I using that?
It's CH.
It's like church.
Do you know how to pronounce things?
Sniper's I'm scared.
Oh, do you remember yesterday I was saying about how hard it is to headshot soldiers?
I'm scared, Gemma.
Boo, why are you no post-motto warfare 3?
That's what I said.
I might not be totally dumb, but I'm weighing it up in my head.
Some old recorded gameplay I just never used.
I might make a few more of those out of it.
This is a fire roll.
Direct hit.
Watch out for the crits.
Oh, people everywhere.
No, no soldier.
I'm going to go.
I'm going to go fire roll with this setup.
Because I like it.
Hold on.
Let's go.
No, I missed it.
I missed it.
No.
I'm going to turn the volume up a little bit.
Can you guys hear the in-game volume?
Okay, where's the 2 low?
Let me know.
Oh no, I hit.
We have to play.
I got to start playing.
Oh no, I missed.
Get him off the point.
Oh no, the only one on here.
I'm screwed.
We're going to get it.
I'll hit or joke.
Tell me a joke.
Give me all you got with the jokes.
I love jokes.
No, I missed time badly.
Oh, you son of a bitch.
You rad bastard.
Wait, it's probably tight.
It's probably tight.
Oh no, I just missed.
I can step my game up a little bit here.
I'm going to get a bit of a dead.
I don't know why I could have survived that.
I can't be fired right now.
That was a lucky edge.
I'm going demo.
What makes you a good demo man?
A lot of things.
If you are good with shooting your pills.
I can drink from a frying pan.
What makes me a good demo man?
Oh, he just lost.
Well, I will raise a demo.
I want to be your discottenant with you now.
What are you?
No.
We need more than one medic.
You have two medic, sir.
I had shot at one of them.
I just walked right off the map.
Hey, there's a big hole in the middle of this map.
I'm still.
Your mom is so fat.
Everyone at the movie did it.
I can't really have burgdebois coming for me.
Your mom is so fat at the movie did it.
She sat next to everyone.
Sick.
I got one for you.
She made me cookies and was a wicked nice woman.
It was awesome to be around it all times.
There you go.
Oh, damn.
All right, I got one too.
Why did the king and queen get a divorce?
No. Why?
Because they had a bad night.
Yeah, you suck.
All right, boo, you got to do one now.
I've got to do a joke.
That's not working.
You'll have to give me a few minutes, son.
Oh, come on.
You have to make it your own.
No, the press is on now.
I've got a deliver.
Hey, joke.
Oh, my god.
No, I don't want that.
No.
Get on the foot.
I can't.
I can't pick my head over there.
I'm just trying to log stuff in the air.
No, no, no.
So, boo, how about that joke?
I'm trying to stop looking over my enemy element.
Sniper was walking down and everyone hid.
Was he snoozing?
He was singing that song.
He smashed into it.
I just got the like event for Germans and humane cycle path.
Oh really? It's just started.
Yes, that was happens like much later than it should.
Yeah, I sometimes said it to do that.
Because when I usually when I'm when I first put the announcement out,
I'm just kind of sitting there doing like nothing and shouting things out.
So people probably just like, what the hell is he doing?
So 15 minutes in is pretty much when everything really gets going.
I guess your string get priority as well.
Till the for the game, which is fair enough.
Let's do one more round in here and then we're going to go to different place.
What do I play as?
That's the question.
I'll go scout I guess.
Schmack.
What king?
I literally just tried holding down shift to sprint.
Yeah, I've been doing that since I've been playing battle.
Oh, look at how did you ox.
Oh, did I save your life just barely anything?
Who just wait, okay, I'm so confused right now.
I just still have stealth dying in front of me by MLC stealth.
That's by behind me, but I don't care. I'm too fast for them.
Hey, who's the real one?
Oh my god, I can't hit the soldier.
I'm so scared.
So there we go.
Oh my god, thank you for saving my life.
Can I play sacks and hail?
I we tried doing that a while ago.
It didn't really work out so well though.
Because we did prop hunt.
Well, only because it's I was the only person that could get into the server and we were just
spending a whole lot of time just watching, spectating and it was just kind of boring.
So at least for a stream, it was kind of boring.
I'd want to do that for like a video, get a bunch of people in there and make some like fun video
and I'm going to die.
Get me out of here.
There are ways of any people there to be fighting right now.
Oh my god, they're all chasing me.
Oh, come on.
You see his body?
He's still alive.
That other stealth guy is being as like 360.
I have two health.
Except for the sea and for me, might as well just do this.
Oh my god, oh my god.
I got killed by a fish.
I was you.
Oh, I'm just trying to be sort of a bitch.
I was in the spawn door and he shot me right in the back.
Like I was like I was right like in the door and I got hit right in the back.
Yeah, I'm right on the red team.
It was a revolver too.
He's not dead.
We got a lot of scout.
I just heard him.
Was this soldier behind this bastard?
I feel like Plank of Pyro.
You've starting to like him more now.
I was never good at Pyro before.
Oh, I'm scared.
I'm going to go around the screen.
I've learned to really like Plank Pyro.
Plank Pyro is like a ton of fun for me.
And I never used to like him because I always wanted to use the flag.
And when I found another Pyro, it's impossible.
Go, go, go, go.
Yeah, the flag on pretty much reinvented Pyro for me.
Like it became so much fun.
What are my views on meet the Pyro?
I think it's going to be epic.
Judging by the last two we've gotten meet the medic and meet the spy,
they've been unbelievable.
So one can only hope it's got to be something just as good if not better than meet the spy and meet the medic.
What if it was like a 2D animation thing?
Yeah, that'd be interesting.
It'd be interesting, it'd be cool.
No, no, no, like it's sucks.
And what if meet the Pyro sucked?
I would be disappointed.
I shouldn't have shot him.
Why don't you do that?
At least you got my back anyways.
I'm getting destroyed.
As you meet the Pyro was like stick fingers.
And like the music was a midi file.
Like, oh god.
What if the Pyro was a stick figure?
Well, you just blew my mind right there.
What?
You just totally blew it.
Like he takes off his mask and it's literally just a stick figure.
It's like a broom, like a family guy.
Oh no!
They're probably not going to take his mask off.
I bet you hit the hill, take his mask off.
You're saying mask.
Why is saying, well, him or her.
The Pyro would probably take off the mask right when the ending happens.
Like, oh, here I go, like here it.
Duh, duh, duh, duh, duh, duh, duh, duh, it'll probably be something like that.
What if it would be Gabe Newell's troll face?
What if it was a game, it would be Gabe Newell's face?
It's just Gabe Newell's face?
Here's him.
Like he made the character like after himself.
I cannot hit the scout to save my life.
Yeah, then anybody can save my life.
He's a real, he's.
Oh.
I mean, all jokes aside, the Pyro is clearly going to be Zoe.
Clearly, let's take the scout and then if I'm going to go with the...
I'm going to show it stop.
Do I have a stranger?
I don't.
We'll go with the whole set.
How do you stop a Gabe Ben?
Easy, you press the Gabe Ben.
Gabe Ben, Gabe Ben.
In addition, I'll save you.
Oh god.
Help me.
Oh, boo with the pistol.
Nice.
Okay, if somebody can find an empty randomizer server,
we need an empty randomizer server.
Not a full one, not one that's like in a arena.
A real good, like instant respawn randomizer server with nobody in it.
Then we can hop into it.
No, I'm not dealing with that.
This guy, the Lodinorbs, has been destroying me all game.
So that is a quest for the Jerma group to find that randomizer server?
I think you got the community.
How many Jerma points do they get for completing that quest?
I just say 15 Jerma points.
I know that's you.
Nothing.
Small one, you got Optimus Prime with you.
No.
Oh, come on now.
He's going to headshot me.
I know he is.
He always does.
Can I like vote Optimus Prime like Best Spy in the world?
Like Best Spy in team Fortress?
Can I like safely say that right now?
I like really the guy.
He's in part of that with like electric Buggalo.
Bungalo get electric, XSB inage.
Oh my god, why am I not hitting anybody with this?
Let's get in here and then do it.
That was so lucky stuff.
I'm going to die.
Oh, boy.
This is a brass piece.
What are you doing?
I don't know.
Oh, did I get it?
I was so lucky.
I did not get it.
I'm sorry.
No, I'll get on that.
Get on it.
Somebody get on it.
Somebody just sneeze on it.
No, no.
I refuse to die.
I refuse.
Jump it.
Jump the pit quick.
All right.
So that is a, we got to randomize server right there.
It empty.
If that is the case.
It was so close.
Let's go find out.
I need to go to
the chief server.
Add a server.
Let's see if this one has like no people in it.
All right.
So here we go.
This is the server that we're going into right now.
You ready guys?
Yes.
207.
Dot 188.
Dot 214.
Dot 12.
Colin 28.
016.
Go, go, go, go, go.
Attempting 15.
Idiot.
Shut the air.
I assume.
So randomizes like heathies with spy knives.
Yeah, this is like this is like total nonsensical.
It's on nucleus too.
What?
Oh man.
There you go.
Drop to the slot reservation.
What?
Okay.
I need to slot reservation.
Well,
well, my first one was a medic with the Machina Girati
and disciplinary action.
I should have got in there first before I sent it.
No, damn it.
All right.
What was the second one?
I don't even make it up.
I gotta get in there first.
Let's see if this one was existing.
We're gonna have to change.
This is no way I'll get in there now.
Got a server.
Let's try it again.
This one.
Okay.
There we go.
All right.
So I'm gonna put a new IP into the chat.
So when you get a chance,
everybody go to this server and I'm gonna tell you guys ready.
205.
Dot 234.
Dot 152.85.
Call in 27015.
Head in there now.
Let me know when you're connecting.
And there we go.
That's the one we're playing on right now.
The other one filled up too quickly and has a lot of slot reservations.
All right.
There we go.
Thank you, Ari.
Or Zeus, whoever it is.
And it doesn't really matter whatever you pick.
What?
Okay. This is like the oddest thing ever.
I'm holding the...
Am I the heavy?
Or on the sniper?
What in God's name?
I'm holding the enforcer.
It's totally broken apart.
And I just...
I can't even actually have to see this.
I can't even explain it.
Oh, I got the Ficky Chipper.
I've never had it.
I wasn't having it.
Oh, nice.
The golden wrench.
Oh, my God.
Shhh.
The hand models are sometimes they're fine.
Sometimes they're just totally broken because I'm a soldier and I have medic gloves with my syringe gun.
Then I pull a weird looking winger and he has normal hands.
Dude, I'm holding this wrench like a gun.
And it's like...
I'm not even touching it.
It's like floating in my hands.
Who has the century?
This guy's spying with a degreaser.
I was floating around like a clown.
That is an oxymoron right there.
A spy with a flamethrower.
Oh, oh yeah, like the trial was found missing.
This guy's just standing there like, hello.
What the hell is this?
Is this the force of nature?
I can't even do it.
I can't even taught.
All right, the force of nature, the pistol,
and the Clydean War.
Crits?
God, I can't even play my penhurtz by looking at this.
This is a thing to gougly as thick.
Is that guy still standing there?
Oh, I gotta see.
What?
I'm so confused.
Oh, look at this.
It's like a sniper with a liberty launcher, the chocolate.
And the fan of war.
All right, liberty launcher sniper.
This could be interesting.
And I zoom in.
Every funny could go.
Hold on, this guy has a,
that guy just had the Natasha as a sniper.
And he was holding it like a sniper rifle shooting it.
Oh my gosh.
I'm using the overdose and if you like,
reload and shoot at the same time,
you can just keep shooting forever.
I was like, I'm like, I'm just gonna reload it.
All right.
Oh, wait, no, it doesn't actually shoot.
Look at this like pump action, like freak out gun on music.
What else do I have?
Oh, the pistol, that's boring.
And what?
What the hell is this?
Why am I like a monster?
There.
What?
I wish you could have just seen that.
I had huge like brown monster hands.
As it was the engineer.
Who are you playing?
What are you doing?
I'm a spy with the old pool cable.
I was like Sasquatch right there.
A POCO fist is that like a fake thing?
Say, wait, the soldier, soldier spy, turn on.
But when I say soldier spy, I mean like soldier
with a knife.
Soldier spy.
So they've added new crazy funny items, huh?
All right, engineer with the, oh, the credit cola and the, oh, this is gonna be good.
Oh, that's awesome.
I hope I can stay alive.
Cause this is a great setup.
Is the soldier with the credit cola?
Soldier with rocket launcher?
Oh my.
Rocket launcher credit cola.
Like are you are you shooting me?
Oh no, come on.
I didn't even get to use this.
Are you come on?
What?
I didn't even get to use that awesome setup I just had.
That pains me.
Is there by not a, does it not have like King of the Hill?
Cause this would be great for King of the Hill.
I don't think so.
All right, Ubersah.
Frontier justice and drive.
This is fantastic.
That has a Medigan.
That's a pyro.
I'm a medic Tommy Slav.
It looks so like out of place.
Oh, okay.
Did I kill him?
I got it.
So the apoco fists are the regular fists, but they give people when you crit them.
I don't think I was hurting anyone.
I was shooting them and it wasn't doing damage.
Numbers weren't popping up above their head.
God, this, this like makes me so happy.
Like this moment doesn't, doesn't it just make you like so happy?
Look at this.
This guy's like wearing, wearing the intelligence like Mary Poppins.
Like what the hell are you doing?
He's bouncing it on his head.
All right, syringe gun and the wrench again.
Can I build, you can't build buildings if you got, well, this is the blue saga.
I'm, I'm dying right now.
Are you serious?
No.
I'm literally dying right now because I'm have blue, it's gonna kill me.
I can't help.
So the blue saga was literally killing.
Oh, that was ball.
Okay, I need, I need you to tell me what I have.
All right, where are I?
I'm standing outside this boring door.
I just, I have no idea what this is.
All right, you have the direct hit, the crit's Creeg and...
Oh, the crit's Creeg.
Yeah, you have the crit's Creeg.
It should seem that this looks like for my point of view.
This is retarded.
I just saw like two seconds.
All right, I got the, this, I don't even have the secondary.
I can't, I don't have the secondary.
I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't.
It's probably the Razer back.
So Razer back, fists of steel.
Wait, what's fish cake?
It's like a reeskin of a chocolate.
God, this is so, why is this looks so perfect with the sniper?
Oh, come, we just got crits too.
I can't, we got crits.
I have a spy knife.
Read the top of the screen.
What's at the top of the screen?
Oh, oh, oh, God, I am so stupid.
Wow, wow, wow, you, wow, look at how stupid I am.
It says what you have right there.
All right, that was a, like, right when you spawn, it tells you where you have.
Oh, my God.
This is not, I'm using like a regular Hydro set right now.
I literally have the, like, a normal, I have to,
whatever.
What, what are I for a melee?
It's golden wrench.
I'm a dimmer man with the enforcer and the guns like broken apart and floating.
Oh, I got it, I got a golden wrench, somebody.
I don't even know, I'm trying to reflect Brock, because I don't even know what he has.
The golden wrench.
This, they turn to a gold statue, don't they?
Yeah, they do.
I've never seen that before.
Yeah, everyone's like, he's like, he's a different class and I'll stand again in the same spot.
Oh, this person's awesome.
What do they keep like capturing the flag so quickly?
That's like, kill.
Kritsana.
Oh, that's too funny.
God, I don't, I don't know, I don't think, I could play this mode.
A thousand times and I probably left just as hard every single time.
It's just how this medic is holding this enforcer like a, like a gang member like sideways.
I wanted, I wanted to see just how I picked that up. Look at this.
Like, oh, yeah, let me just, I've been in this giant axe in my hand.
It's like, 180 pounds.
Let me just hold it with one hand.
It's not even doing any sweet animation.
There's no sweet animation with that.
This is so hard.
My brain, like, cannot handle how this looks.
It actually looks like kind of normal to be honest.
I feel like that's the way like a shotgun would act in somebody's hands.
Like, that one, God.
I'm gonna have those kills with this enforcer.
Oh, let me just one second guys.
Let me spin up my like 200 pound axe in one hand.
Let me go.
I'm gonna look at how useful this is gonna be.
Come on, I gotta kill him with it.
Wait.
I can't run now.
Who keep, whoa, that was weird.
No swing animation.
You can't tell, I got it.
Burger boy, the insensitive one.
Burger boy, you can't call a medic man.
Nobody has it.
It could be like a heavy with the damn crits.
Pretty good.
A medic on.
Engineer with the Natasha, the winger, and the atomizer.
Can I double, can I triple jump?
I can double jump.
I can double jump as the engineer.
Well, the atomizer.
Yeah, I have the atomizer with the ng.
I can double jump and I can build building.
That's five.
I get the cool setup and I die instantly.
This happens every single time.
I turn the corner.
Oh, that was a spy.
So I was going invisible behind people in my force in nature.
It's visible.
That's crazy.
Turn a singer song.
That's somebody just, um, come on.
Winger, oh, let me, let me hold, let me just,
just stupid.
It's like a little, no words can describe that.
I can't even make a joke.
It's too stupid.
Oh, god, that's a dead, that's a dying battle right there.
I have to revolver.
My spy has three hands.
Because I'm holding killing gloves of boxing.
I pull out my dandering.
This setup is terrible.
Scout with a mini gun.
Everyone run through your life.
T-go challenges me to a duel.
Yeah, I wonder how mad Bergerboy is right now.
I bet you Bergerboy is screaming at his computer screen.
I healed for a hundred points as a sniper.
Extend.
This way, am I holding this backwards?
All right, look at how I'm holding this.
I could really hurt myself with this thing.
Suck this a bit.
Fish cake?
Oh, it still works.
All right, we'll be launching your fish cake, and the backwards X thing was your.
Mm-hmm, yeah, make sure don't drop it on your face.
I have two shotguns.
Scout are going to family business.
I have the syringe gun of the heavy.
I don't like this.
Watch this you didn't kill me!
What what that I am confused that was weird
I was doing the heavy mini gun noise
Charging charge can I charge out of the sniper?
I can't oh I can't charge dammit what?
I'm a spy and all I have is the tribal and ship I don't have any other item
Can you cloak?
Yeah
I wish I could charge in charge right there that would have been hilarious
I just spawned and for some reason I spawned with like 350 health
Overhealed yeah I think some of the people do so I think everyone does be honest
I'm spawning overhealed I have a rocket jumper
I guess no maybe not everybody
But like a razor back okay this is actually a pretty good setup
I know I can't charge
Oh this sucks nevermind
That's a little worse setup ever
I got a razor back though I can't be back
I had Gerati rocket jumper and equalizer
I can't charge this sucks
This is the worst thing
I'm a spy with a tribal and ship and that is literally it
If you should be a duel I'll deal you I'll do anybody why not?
Absolutely
Dead rig or heavy
Both of the next map let's go to
Bad water?
Bad water sounds fun
I have soldier with a big urner and the enforcer
I can't do the taunt, dammit the taunt doesn't work with this thing
What the hell?
I'm better off just using this
Oh what's the Scottish resistance? I have no idea how this works
Okay
Look at that's just pointing straight down into the ground that's so funny
Oh this thing's great with people jumping
I don't think I've ever seen the guy I'm doing one time
Oh my god that guy just got so many people in that Natasha
This will be the last round of the randomizer and then we'll go to one more random server
And oh my god I'm a medic with the Natasha and the crit screen
What I have for melee I didn't even read it
Oh the wrench
Oh you thought the medic was just going to be here and didn't ya?
Oh my god this is so OP
Now I just switch over
Get some heals around you guys scrubbing around a little bit
I'm a spy running around with heavy fists punching people
Oh I got you I got you King DDD
Oh come on give me those crits
Come on come on where is somebody?
God this is so insane
Medic with a god damn mini god now you serious
And I'm healing people with the crit screen this is ridiculous
And I can upgrade and repair buildings
Wait what's the big kill?
It's a risk in the revolver
So I have a revolver and I have a pistol
I don't even know what he has what does he have
Let's get the Scottish resistance
Is that what he did something?
Well what in the last like two seconds?
I had the thing called a jar of ants
I thought it was dry but when I threw it at people they would like taking damage
I never seen that before
That's weird
I just healed a thousand points of the pyro
I don't think it was even a pyro that was weird
So because I'm a spy I have a wrench
And I can either disguise
But I can't build anything
Alright shotgun, short circuit
What is going on?
I'm so confused, is this how he's holding the shotgun?
Hold on
So this is faster reserve
Oh I have a knife too
Okay I was holding the shotgun down like a mini gun
And it was like shaking
I couldn't even tell where I was shooting
Alright so after this we're going to go to a normal one
I'm getting the worst things ever
Yeah I got a great one last time, the medic
The medic set up
Alright so
Bonka, this is going to be great
Bonka-togged punch, does it do anything?
Am I invincible right?
Yeah I am
Sick
I'm getting all these pistols
What?
I-
Okay
What's the Buffalo steak sandwich do again?
Many crits and you take many crits but you can't use anything but melee
That was weird, the no swing animation throws me off
Because I'm just like standing there, am I even swinging at people?
Oh it's tied up now
Oh wait a minute, how does the Widowmaker even work?
How would the Widowmaker work?
Am I just a fitted ammo? Well how is this going to work?
I think I just haven't fitted ammo
Oh no I can't lose this, no shit
Oh I really think I just had a fitted ammo with that thing
We're getting my spawn draft now
The Front View Justice had 10 shots in it, that's confusing
Oh man
Oh yeah I still have metal, I just can't see it
That's still funny
Alright, we're gonna go one more of random normal server to play
And then we're gonna hop in a CS go
Let's do, let's find another good server
Shit out
Let's try and get a 32 person
Here we go
Oh let's go back to her mind
No no no
Can go to Dust Bowl
That's 30, that's got 32 right now
Yeah we're gonna do it
32 people can play in this zone
This would be the last Shabang
I gotta give it to Berga Boy first, hold on
Berga Boy will like flip out if I don't
And then ready, 96
8, 113
36, 27015
And join
And that's the server guys
Go to all Dust Bowl, go to all Fashion Dust Bowl
Oh it's not randomizer is it?
No this is just regular
Okay
Oh yes Dust Bowl my favorite
I like Dust Bowl, people don't like it but I like it
I like it after that brass beast game yesterday
So my buddy I'm from Providence, so cool dude
Good old Rhode Island
I got blue, why not?
Mission begins in 50 seconds
That's what I just said
Oh Bull King, yeah I will absolutely do jailbreak
Oh I have, while there's people here I need to mention this
There is going to be no stream next weekend
Because I'm gonna be a Paxies
And I bring your computer with you
Foring everything, that would not happen
I'm gonna be a little bit weak, I just want to be very clear
But the good part is I'm gonna get plenty of cool videos and packs
And it'll be plenty of cool stuff to see from that stuff
Do not worry
So what do you actually do at Pax because I know nothing about game conventions?
You just play new games
It's just a convention where
Pretty much every developer you can think of
And it's just a great place to hang out
There's a bunch of free play rooms
They have like 100 Xboxes, 100 like PS3s
Like 100 PCs all lined up
You just go in and play with people that are in the room
It's really interesting, it's definitely fun
It's most of the games can you go and check out
Or are you looking forward to checking out?
I don't know man, nothing really
I'm trying to think that there's anything I particularly would like to
Portal 2?
Yeah, do Portal 2 last year, I went last year
The line for Portal 2 was like an hour and a half long to play the demo
And like to see like the trailer and stuff
It was like this enclosed off boxed off room
And you couldn't get, you couldn't even see what was in there
It was like a closed off box
And the line went into the box
So it was pretty nuts
Do I live near the west end?
I do not
I do not live in the city
I am just outside of the city
Oh, a lot of peeps up here
Oh, we got a double avar right there
That's spy, watch yourself, that's me
That's not me, or is it?
Twilight Zone
I just got freaked out right there
Oh god
Oh
Spam out the door
Oh my god, is that, is that what I think it is?
Is that Berger Boy?
It is
That's not a spy
Do it
I am kind of doing this up then
Oh, appearance from MLC Dad
MLC Pop, Illnessy Pop
MLC Pop
Yeah, he is a better than Red Sox
How could you say such a thing
Oh, I just got destroyed right there
Damn
Oh no, this is spy
We got to get around, I am going around
They are taking over, huh? They are up on the top
Nice reflect
You know what? I am going to go medic
We need another one
We need another medic
Oh auto-com inbound
Yeah, what up?
In my next vlog
Auto will do like a gameplay commentary
Oh, let me get that
Oh no, you heard it here first
Auto was going to do a gameplay commentary
I don't want to do my next vlog
Oh god, that is not safe
Oh, you don't stop
No, stay alive, where is he?
Where is he?
He is trying to kill too many people in the way
Alright, what do you say man?
What do you do?
Chris, Chris, Chris
Yeah, that is my dog
People like who is auto
That is my dog
That is my good old dog
Gotcha
No, no
I am doing something
Oh, MLC mom
Do they have YouTube channels?
Yeah, they do
No, they are doing Minecraft, don't they?
Wow, you just saved my life
No, I didn't
Auto, auto the dog
He is out of the way
Auto, scout on the point
He is trying to find him
He is trying to find my dog
Auto
Did he just run in here?
Okay, my dog just ran in here
I heard the chinchy, I am looking at the screen
I am trying to clap and get him to come over
No, he is not even in here
I am going insane
Look at all these people that need healing
No, I was lucky
I don't know what he is doing
I am going to kill him
I know that need healing
No, I was lucky
I don't think he is dead
Oh, God
Yeah
All right, new course of action
I am just charging up my Uber
And they were going in
Do I know any Irish?
I do not know any Irish
How much do you know?
I know Irish people
But I do not know
Language
How to speak it
Who do you know any Irish?
I mean even though you are not
I just bite
I cannot even speak Welsh
Which is like my own city's language
Or a bad answer language
Does it really?
Welsh yeah
No, well, anyone speaks it in this country
That is crazy
I do not know they have an actual
English
Don't open that door
Burger boys out there
Oh, it would be bad
It would be bad if burger boy got in here
Oh, close that door
Do not let burger boy in here
He just moved
And open it now
Don't open it
I love how we just got this guy here
Like holding this like, all right
We do it here
Oh, turn around, oh, jeez
No, no
Oh my god, they came from behind
Actually, that is damn
I am going to fugue
I am going to spy
I am going to go
So I
The original sounds so cool
If I was going to play Highland
Or what would I play for a class
Probably Engineer
I am like most comfortable playing Engineer
I knew you were a freak
I could smell you
Can I feel it?
Oh, I was waiting for him to try and stare at him
And I got killed
Either Engineer
Or
Maybe Pyro
Just because Pyro
I could probably do what we needed to be done
Hey, I am Pyro
He is not dead
There is no way he is dead
No, come on
No, here comes the chase
D-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d die
D-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d die
Wrestlemania 28
I got people that are at Wrestlemania 28
Friends of mine that are there right now
Oh, and they're there
They haven't even done it
They are on scene out of the rock
I used to be big into wrestling man
I used to love it
Not so much anymore though
Oh my god. Hey, what's up everybody? I'm just gonna like stuff myself into your face. Oh no.
Yeah, you know, don't let that time and stone cold stun the entire McMahon family. Actually, I do. I'll link that and then the rock rock bottom. Oh my god. Somebody please.
Thank you. Thank you.
I'm just being an idiot right now. Oh, I can't play spines. It's not possible right now.
Playing heavy. I'm not gonna be happy. I'm gonna use.
Okay, we're being like 10 seconds.
BRBB.
Check dot, well, this one dot, well, this.
I'll do one Minecraft. I mean, we're trying to.
The latest Minecraft thing that me left her in a toxic. We're having a lot of server problems. It would be crashing all the time.
And I don't know. We might try and do something else at some point just because it was. Hey me.
Is that another spy? I think so. Come on. We can do this.
Oh, no, we can't.
Eat the sandwich. The only thing you can do.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Where's my dog?
Auto. Auto.
I'm gonna get him in here.
Auto, you're gonna do like a face cam video.
Auto face cam. Let's see if I can do it.
He's not gonna come in here. He's like, no way. I'm back.
They're all I help Mr. or mom on top of stuff or something.
Nice, nice.
I'm gonna take the brass beast off of this one.
What do I think? Oh, he's tummy. What's the worst game ever?
Hmm.
I don't know. What's the worst game ever played?
Borderlands. That's tough one. No, it's definitely not. Not Borderlands. Not for me.
Borderlands. I don't know what I have such a thing against Borderlands.
You made you bought it. Come on.
Oh, I'm not dead.
I just heard a spot. That's where the god I did. Yeah, I knew I did. I knew I did.
I heard him, but I got killed anyways. Wait, they have seven spies?
Oh my god.
Oh, there's another one.
Thanks.
Worst game. Recently the worst game I played.
I can't think of one.
I heard that mermaid.
About that dark side. This is something like that.
Dark side. We just always say.
What am I doing?
There's something about this. I don't know. A new game that came out, which is kind of like.
It was like an indie game.
I like Nova did a playthrough on it. I know it's all the I am alive.
Go. Get him off.
All right. This will be the last round. That was too quick.
Last run before we go to CS go.
Counter strike. Go, go, go.
And what's Ghost stand for? Oh, just go. Ghost.
Kind of strike like move. Go forward.
I have to appear offline.
Oh, my fan. Can you start?
Yeah, just when we get into CS go to the top of us.
That's totally cool.
That's totally fan.
How do I do this?
What am I doing?
Actually, I'll stay online. I'll do that after we win the switch.
All right. If we get rolled again, this is not good news.
Get your crits Creek on the pyro now for this.
Oh, yeah.
You'll be able to see that video soon on Who Man 61?
You actually will.
Come to you soon on the new Team Fortress 2 exclusive channel.
I just get it.
I wish. No.
Let's do it.
That's a spy.
Holy moly.
Oh, my god.
Why did I jump down?
Dustball is crazy.
It's like no respawns to like no respawn delay.
We're getting absolutely destroyed right now.
The control point just being captured.
That's why he's still alive.
All right.
Fall back.
Watch your back, Stu.
No, he got out of here.
He's gonna fly out.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
This way.
All right.
Keep the deep fats.
Keep up the deep fats.
Watch the spy gap.
If I could be any class in TF2, I definitely would be the spy.
You could just go invisible and not die in real life.
Yeah, you could just never die.
I go, hey, go ahead.
Shoot me in the face.
I'm like, you're like,
I'm just gonna candle or something.
I'm fortunate like that.
I go, yeah, you can go ahead and put like three bullets in my head.
And I'll just deadbringer.
Oh.
That jermis is spy.
That'd be really weird.
Think about that in real life.
The deadbringer, right?
Let's say, let's say you had a gun and I had the deadbringer and you shot me.
And I had the deadbringer and deadbringer up.
So it would drop like a dummy body of me, but I would still be alive.
Like up here, again, would it be the same body?
What if you disguised as Birgoboys and you went to Birgoboys house?
You were like, hey, Birgoboys.
Oh, I just talked to Birgoboys like parents.
Hey, what's going on, Mr. and Mrs. Birgoboys.
All right.
Block that spy.
He's gonna try and get in mind.
Grono.
Careful.
Ooh.
Turn on, girl.
I turned around to fight the first spy and I got back stabbed by another spy that
came behind me.
Oh, the theme is a spy.
It's spy in the base.
Red is spy in the base.
Pi in the base.
That's spy.
No, it's not.
Can't hear that spy.
That's a spy.
No, it's not.
I have so conscious right now, I'm like freaking out.
That's a critter on a way.
Oh, he's faster.
He's still alive.
We need some serious spray action going on over here.
Oh, gonna go up.
No!
Run, run, run, run.
Run away from that.
Drive the sandwich.
Where's my sandwich?
Somebody eat it.
I just bumped into it by...
I knew it.
Let's go this way.
Oh no.
Kilometric.
Oh my god.
My sandwich.
Fall back.
No!
There we go.
This is going to be a losing battle.
I got a pack stat.
At least we're holding them, right?
Man, is there a spy right here?
What's going on there?
That was like a freak out session.
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
Oh no.
Run, run, run.
Oh, the spyrope.
Oh no.
I should probably stop sniping.
There's two spies behind this right now.
He's going to be right here in two seconds.
Every time.
Oh no, run away.
Oh, barely.
Oh, I'm going to still run away.
Oh.
You know, I was actually talking about Team Fortress and Chat.
The classic version.
You know what?
Oh.
Come on, kill the whole team.
Oh my god, I have a crit screen.
Oh my goodness.
That spy still behind us.
This could be really bad.
I was thinking about doing a Team Fortress 1 video.
Team Fortress Classic video.
Showing like what it looks like then and what it looks like now.
Oh.
Oh, there's another heavy right there too.
Dude, it's still, you just did a.
Oh, get spread.
Oh my god, they got a spy cap us.
Somebody came back there.
The grenades in Team Fortress 1 was ridiculous.
You could never go back and play that and really seriously play it.
It's just ridiculous.
No, we know about the lose.
We're your bros of lose.
We are.
No, I forgot.
You can't do that anymore.
Shit.
Oh, you can't.
I just threw the sandwich down for myself.
I was like, oh, I got more ammo.
Turma, you can't do that anymore.
Team Fortress 2 with grenades would be.
Well, put it like this.
Imagine everybody on the team is a demo man and has their own loadouts.
We got to get up in that room.
Oh, this is the loadout.
Oh.
Yeah, this is this is this is where we're putting up a defense right now.
Oh, oh, my God.
This is you again.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, how is he not dead?
My God.
Oh, no.
Yeah, that's where we are.
That's where we are.
Good medic.
Good medic is good.
Oh, nice counter Dracula voice.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
Counter Dracula, they're heavy.
Oh, boy.
Oh, they're trying to build up over here.
Oh, it's bad news.
Bad news, bad news, bears.
I'm not sure.
Back up.
I don't want to get killed.
Oh, it's interesting.
I actually like audition.
What's your bad movie?
A drama.
What movie?
Bad news, bears.
What?
I was like a baseball player and they said, hey, anybody's football player, like things like
an actor, I come to this like open audition thing.
I do.
I try to do work.
Dude, I'm not.
I can imagine Billy Ballford because I was in drama in middle school so I was like, I'm
a good actor.
You could have been a star, dude.
Who's constant?
Back up, back up, back up.
Whoa.
Hey, look what console just said.
Who?
In the chatter, in the.
Somebody said, oh, so you got the livestream right now?
Well, thanks for choosing the QQ buffet.
Oh, really?
You were very welcome.
Oh, we're coming in.
We're coming in.
Watch it.
Right when they turn the cool.
Oh.
Oh, well.
Yeah.
Oh, I do.
Oh, no.
So this is like a legit stalemate right now.
I think because I want to get see us going.
So we might have to like 16 on 16.
Yeah, this is just a totally balanced game right now.
Even though we respond to ladies on Dust Bowl.
Yeah, I know.
You're just gonna.
Oh, he's gonna do it.
Oh, no.
Oh, I'm gonna go.
We got a ton of engineers, dude.
We can, no, we can't.
No, no, take you to what you're either.
Oh, I hear the fan.
See, your fan just turned on mine.
I've heard.
And I was probably.
Actually, that probably was mine.
You're right.
Oh, it's fine mine.
Oh, my look at this debris, my god.
Run.
Run away.
I'll be on the ground.
That's.
Run away.
I think afterburn you can tweak it.
Yeah.
You can.
I think afterburn you can tweak it.
Yeah.
I think afterburn you can tweak afterburn a little bit.
Make it a little more balanced.
Maybe you'd make it shorter duration but more damage.
So, like instead of like 10 seconds or whatever it is, make it like 4 or 5 seconds but have it do more damage.
A little bit more damage.
It's okay in this current form though.
I think I don't think it's that.
It's not that bad.
Oh, my god.
Oh, come on, give me over there.
Oh, you got it.
Hello.
Hello, Mr. Medic.
How are you?
Oh!
I like how he just stood there and while we put mines all over him.
Oh, backstep.
All right, I'm going to go.
I'm going to scout for the end here.
Man, that's just such a difficult game to win.
Oh, my god.
But I don't think I've seen you once.
No, I've been, I keep getting killed by Gemma.
Stop being so selfish.
I won't kill this girl.
I just, I mean, I got like, I was like, Octo-heavy, but this like whole thing.
There's like, two or three medic zombies.
Not anymore though.
I'm saying that's the scoot.
No.
Oh, he went out this way.
Oh, where is he?
Imagine a team of 16 spies all just cloaked, sneak on the point and at the same time all decloat and capture.
I'm just going to say, imagine that and like they just like pretend that they're the other team.
Yeah, super spyjack load.
Super spyjack.
Oh, no.
Oh, it's up to me so long to get in fact.
Oh, man.
Dude, look at the, there's all the metals.
That's ridiculous.
I feel, I want to like switch the blue.
I can't though.
Oh my, yeah, the domination like things.
Nice headshot.
Sick.
Come on, blue.
Oh, stealth.
Come on, blue man, 61.
Ready to charge, doctor.
Oh, they got a big center back there now.
Tables good turn right now.
You guys got a good Uber, good push coming.
Tables coming.
Not too sure about the Uber.
Is that Uber charge?
What are you sure about the push?
Competence is growing slightly.
I'm standing in the tunnel not taking damage.
What about the burger boy?
Did I hear burger boy?
I'm not saying.
I think there's nothing good about this team.
Oh, burger boy.
Burger boy.
There's nothing good.
Yes, stealth, I lost.
There's nothing good about this team.
Oh, that's so funny.
He's on fire.
I wish I could hear that.
But I have my voice chat turned off.
That would be funny to be able to watch that.
Burger boy.
There's nothing good.
All right, so burger boy, on a scale of 1 to 10, 10 being like you will rip down your house, burn your house down.
And one being like, I guess I'm like kind of mad.
How like pissed off are you right now?
I bet you it's at least a seven or eight.
Let's be quiet so we can hear his answer.
I can't hear it.
So it's going to be really late for me.
Actually, maybe he's not even listening to the stream.
No, maybe he forgot I was streaming.
Oh, they got that.
Where's that spy right there?
Oh, my gosh.
What do you say?
I'm breaking my fridge.
Is that what he thought?
Damn it.
I wish I could have my...
I need to turn it on.
Hold on.
Oh, my God.
All right.
You can tell him to do it again.
Burger boy, do it again.
Burger boy, rage again.
Is he going to do it?
Oh, he's not like actually mad.
I wish I caught that on video.
Oh, you're losing, burger boy.
It's over.
Oh, look, it's all over.
Let's see what he says.
Hold on.
Here it comes.
Oh, what are you saying about that, burger boy?
Why are you talking to him?
Oh, I want to...
He's your friend.
No, I want him to like flip up.
He's silent.
He's your friend.
Yeah, but I...
Did he?
No, he's still here.
No, he's not.
Yeah, he is.
All right.
I'm going to transition to CSGO.
Thanks for coming.
No, you're not allowed to come.
Oh.
Very good boy.
This is perfect.
There's nothing good about this.
Let me try and figure out how to do CSGO.
Could it be sort of difficult?
I'm going to do windowed mode.
It's going to take maybe a few seconds.
Give me a minute, guys.
Counter-strike, global effects.
All right.
Screen's going to go black for 20 to 30 seconds.
I'm still here.
Don't worry.
Oh, no, black screen.
Oh!
What do we do?
It's a black screen.
Oh, burger boy.
You're listening right now?
After we play this for like 20 to 30 minutes, we're going to McDonald's.
We're going to get double cheeseburgers.
I hope you know that.
Video settings.
We are going to be playing in windowed.
And 1280 by 721.
I think I'm going to go and play Call of Duty 4.
I'll probably jump out the chat, but I'll still listen to the stream.
Okay. That's cool.
All right. Thanks for coming, dude.
Can you talk about you, then?
Yeah, I know what you're saying at all times, stealth.
Bomber.
All right.
If you're back later on Happy Days.
Enjoy CSGO.
Thanks for coming, boo.
Thank you.
Bye, boo.
So we're going to play some CSGO.
We're going to play some gun game.
And if you have this, you're more than welcome to try and join in off of me.
Or if stealth is appearing online him.
It's going to be difficult to join in on these.
It's going to be kind of difficult to get everyone in the game because it's um.
Wait, Valve confirms that Meet the Pyro is already done and ready?
Holy crap.
That means we're going to get it soon.
Almost we don't.
Unless it doesn't happen. Yeah, at least we don't get it.
It's already released. Cutting someone like sneak like I would steal that if I like work for Valve and put it on the internet.
And then I get fired for a long time.
Yeah, you probably would get fired. That would not be good.
Oh, you can, you guys can hardly, they're quiet. Are they still quiet?
Who, they like me.
Apparently you guys are quiet. I don't know why.
I just try to turn you out.
That's odd.
So this is gun game. This is like legit like gun game.
Was it like that the whole time? Was it like that just for when I changed it over?
Was it like that during TF2 as well?
Oh, gun game.
Oh, so they were both low really really low for the team for us.
Oh, just at the end there.
That's weird.
The whole time?
No, someone they were saying at the end of team fortress two probably when I transitioned over.
Oh.
Yeah, so this is the gun game. This is my favorite thing about this game.
I love gun game.
I can't handle the game.
Thanks for the feedback guys. I appreciate it because I try to, it's hard to make it sometimes explode is weird and they just lower the volume of everybody.
I don't know why, but so thanks for thanks for being here to be able to tell me what's going on.
So if you don't know what this is every time you get a kill every single time you kill somebody you get you get a different gun.
And I think it's 26 or 27 kills.
I don't see stuff as the worst counter strike play ever.
Oh, I must have it too in general.
No, audience fine.
Oh no, I'm not personajes still going to be.
That's off of his prime. Optimus prime.
Oh, he's dead.
Oh, I'm going to get behind.
Oh, damn it.
This is still in beta.
So as you see, when I kill somebody else here, if I can show you.
Right when I kill somebody, the instant I do it, I'm going to switch a gun.
It's going to go to something else.
This is the like shot gun type thing.
I'd love to show them that example too, but I can't get a kill to switch my gun.
Hey, well, you're not really on the screen.
Why was just saying.
Yeah, where this is PC.
I don't know, this is not really even getting developed right now for consoles.
I think they're doing that later.
I think it's actually code developed for five.
I could be totally wrong.
I'm not sure on that.
Well, that's how you missed three times point blank.
Well, that was the auto shotgun.
Somebody's already reached knife level.
So once you go through all the guns, once you get like 27 kills, you use a knife.
And you have to knife somebody.
And if you knife them, the game's over and you win.
Well, whatever team had the person knife thing.
Thanks.
Come on, keep it going.
Oh, that's game.
Oh, somebody wants.
Where's MLC still?
Oh, at the bottom of the ligabord.
Yeah, this is definitely the best mode in Counter Strike.
No, in my opinion.
It used to be a mod, then they made it like an actual game mode.
It's so fun.
Hey, what's the enemy going?
Go CT.
What up, what a deliq?
Yeah, I mean, the stream's been going for like an hour and a half now.
So if some of you guys got to go, you got to go.
Thanks for coming.
Appreciate it.
Oh, I love this map.
I love this map.
This is the map shibi was like losing his mind on.
There's only two maps on this one.
Oh, that's right. There is only two maps.
What?
Damn it.
Oh, no bullets.
Wait, did there used to be a map?
Huh?
There is.
Where?
It's in the top left.
We talked about it.
Oh, because there's nothing up there for me.
Oh, well, you must have been glitching out.
Oh, there it is.
It just came out there, Dad.
Oh, I got a headshot from across the map.
Oh, I'm going to make a ton of hits and packs, man.
It's going to be me and Paxies.
They're going to be best friends when it comes to videos.
Damn it.
I'm in trouble.
No, run in the boards.
Burger boy has a YouTube channel.
His first video is going to be going up in like probably like 15 months.
Show yourself.
Damn it.
I got to get a good stream together.
Oh, come on.
Damn.
I hear these people in the chat saying like this game of sucks.
No way.
This game, this is the most fun game mode on CS.
Oh, what are teammates here, Sam?
Oh, really?
Dad, is Goomba Stomp that guy?
I don't think I did.
We had that conversation last night.
We were like, can you goomba Stomp?
What's going on here?
Because I said I like damage with teammate when I land on top of them.
Oh, my God.
I can't believe it.
How many bullets does it take?
Damn.
My favorite gun in CS go is probably the shotgun.
He just regular shotgun.
I love that thing.
Oh, come on.
This thing.
This is my favorite gun in CS right now.
I love this thing.
Unfortunately, when I get one killed, it's going away.
Oh, I see it's gone.
I see it's gone.
I don't know how you get kills in this.
No one dies when I shoot him.
Is the auto shotty?
Damn it.
P90 is awesome too.
Everything is pretty balanced in this game.
There's way too many of them over there.
No way I was going to do that.
I'm the worst counter shot.
I'm the worst counter shot player.
I literally don't think.
It's a worse one.
You know, it's tough playing this game in a window.
It is very hard to do this.
My hand looks so tiny.
It's like, yeah, I'm a little baby.
I can't believe I didn't kill him.
Do I like pretzels?
I love pretzels.
World gold, baby.
I'm doing absolutely terrible right now.
Terrible.
I wish I could full screen this.
Alright, exploit.
Make it so I can full screen my game.
First problem.
There's no hats.
Second problem.
No hats.
Third problem.
No lasers.
I'm a fourth problem.
Oh my gosh.
That killed me.
Sorry.
I got already on the light machine gun.
Yeah.
I was doing pretty well last night.
Oh, that game begins already over.
No!
Jeez.
I have a...
Yeah.
That's Alex, I know.
I'm just saying.
Are there any vases in there?
He's in the...
Yeah, where is he?
Why is he not a mod?
That doesn't make any sense.
We don't we don't trust him after I would have...
After what happened?
I'm gonna go T.
Go T. Go Tarris.
After he got into the cookie jar.
Oh, are you really?
Well, I'm a moron.
No, I'm not shooting my own teammates now.
Oh, I thought I was gonna get him.
I got to get in Tri-Hard mode now.
I want to get a good game.
Tri-Hard mode.
Activate.
3 and 2.
Let's go.
I want to be at least one to two.
Oh, I didn't kill him.
What?
Gotta get that gun game.
Gotta get that gun game up.
I didn't even see that guy.
I got like blended in with the background.
Let's go.
I'll keep it moving.
Keep it moving there.
Keep it moving.
Okay, I literally think I'm doing 99% damage to people
and then other people are just taking the last shot.
I'm just gonna get a good game.
I'm gonna get a good game.
Oh, LL Cool J in here.
I can speak up on him.
There we go.
That's what I'm talking about.
Now we're going.
Now we're going strong.
Sting.
Keep it moving.
Keep it moving here.
Oh!
Eggs.
I got to try hard like an egg.
Sure, man.
How do you have 14 freaking points?
I went into try hard, boy.
Didn't I tell you?
There we go.
I'm not messing around anymore.
No more messing around, dude.
Let's go this way.
Sniper rifle.
Let's get one.
Hey!
Shabu!
Where is it?
Ah!
18 and 8.
Come on.
Give me like 10 more kills in a row, baby.
I'll be careful with this light machine gun, dude.
Oh, that was...
That was him killing.
Ah!
Come on.
It's high when you get to the pistols, it gets difficult.
This is where it gets really difficult.
It gets difficult when you're using any gun in this.
Haha.
God.
Now let's see what I got.
Trying to pull off a headshot.
Not going to happen.
I just...
Oh, come on now.
Come on now.
Oh, come on now, baby.
Ah! I had it.
I had it.
Come on.
Let me win this round.
Ah, damn it.
Nope.
Crap.
Crap in my pants.
No, this is not good.
I got to find the way around.
Damn it.
Alright, I'm going to...
Someone over here.
Oh, I can't believe that it had been the face.
Losing it now, I'm losing it.
I had it.
I had it for a little bit.
No, ah, I'm going to lose it.
I got to lose it.
I was so far ahead.
Ah, I got to take off somebody.
No one this way, man.
Here we go.
Finally got out of that stupid pistol.
Now I got the duel, but red is good.
Oh, this guy.
I'm going to make this guy's day bad.
This egg over here.
Where would this egg go?
I just had a clean shot on that egg.
Oh, my God, I can't believe I didn't get it.
Do I?
That was a lucky spawn.
Did I get it?
Oh, the game.
Yeah.
I did it.
Oh, I can't believe it.
I can't believe I won the game.
That's the first time I've ever had a game so hard.
Alright, let's take them rage Quinn.
Yeah, that's the first time I've ever done that.
Wow.
That was a, I wish I was like, fire.
I wish I was like recording that.
Because it's probably not going to happen again.
Oh, you got a word of the coordinates.
Um, I own battlefield three.
So do not, you don't, please do not get battlefield three.
I appreciate the gesture though.
Like, thank you so much for even considering doing that.
But I have battlefield three.
Oh, Boo, did you see, I just wanted to see.
That was for you.
Yeah, but I'm not, I don't, it's going to be 360.
I guess I could use it.
I could use that.
Oh, you bastard.
Optimus Prime.
Hey, what do you know?
Optimus Prime has the knife in this game and he's wicked good with it.
Coincidence?
I don't think so.
Give me that head shot.
Oh, no.
Boo.
All right. I, I, I quit the game.
You left?
Optimus Prime is pissing me off.
Oh, I guess he's wicked good.
Yep.
Counter strike source.
Did I say source?
I met counter strike.
Go.
Stealth can't take it.
Oh, jump down.
I was doing all right in the beginning.
I was doing all right.
See if I can come back to life here.
What?
How does that make any sense?
How, I killed that guy.
Did I shoot him through the grate?
Now the hell did that happen?
Yeah, I'm not sure how much money it'll be.
I, I was assuming it won't be more than 50 bucks.
It probably won't be more than 40.
I bet you it's, I'm going to say 30 bucks.
That's my prediction.
Again, I could be totally wrong.
It really depends on what kind of strategy they want to go for.
Nope.
16.
Damn it.
Stop killing people.
I can't see what gun you have.
This is going to be tough sniper.
You have to like cool.
I have to like call a duty quick scope somebody.
Where'd he go? Where'd he go?
How did I not hit him?
Here we go.
LMG. Is that the real burger boy?
We better believe it.
You better believe it.
Oh, Greg.
Oh, that's a bot.
Bot Greg.
Come on, I'm at the pistol level.
Come on, this is a bot.
Come on, this is a damn...
Damn it.
22, somebody's already at the knife level.
It might end right now.
Nah, it's over.
It is over.
The TKO.
I believe he's the one that got it.
Good game.
Oh.
I think I'm going to hop out of CS.
I just wanted to play.
I'm probably going to use that gameplay.
I might actually use that one that I went ham on.
Ham.
I got a ham sandwich.
A ham hamburger.
Oh, you're still here?
Me.
I thought you were like ran away.
Well, I'm still...
I thought you were sad that you were like can't play CS.
I'm sad, I'm so bad, yeah.
That's going to wrap it up here, guys.
Thanks for coming, everybody.
And see you guys next time.
Oh, by the way, I need to make sure you guys all...
Oh, you're not even going to do quap.
Oh, you're right.
What am I thinking?
Am I out of my mind?
Quap.
I'm going to go black.
Oh, he's gone.
I thought you were legit rage, but...
I thought you were like, end sky call.
And get me out of here.
I really thought you did that.
I was like, oh, he's gone.
And he goes healing.
Nice.
Screen region.
Let's go for five lives on quap.
See if we can't do something cool.
Here we go.
Just keep good enough at the game so we can hear the music in the background.
That's never going to happen.
I will never get good enough at this game for that to not happen.
Quap looks like Grandpa trying to walk when he has no crutches.
I almost did a legit back foot.
That was sick.
Oh, good.
Thanks for reminding me, Woody Delek.
There is no stream next week and there will be no stream.
I'm going to be at Paxi's pretty much for the whole Friday Saturday Sunday.
So there will be no stream next weekend that I will try and do a makeup stream in the middle of the week sometime.
Probably...
I would say probably Thursday of that next week after that.
So no stream next week.
And I am just sitting here idling like a car.
Dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun.
I'm doing like the skip method.
The music just keeps coming in.
I'm so bad at this.
I can't even get the music to start playing.
Damn.
Alright, that's it.
I'm not going to get better than that.
So yeah, thanks everybody so much.
I will see you guys all soon.
And take care everybody.
Thanks for coming so much.
See you later.
Bye!
Oh, and we...
What's it all?
I'm like frozen.
I think I'm frozen with the stream on.
Oh, so, hello.
What's going on, everybody?
It's the Jarvis Frozen computer screen.
And...