You've seen me do it like a hundred times
You can't dodge them all
He's looking he's turning oh shit, he's turning he just growled at us
Oh
He just turned and growled
Okay, I need to get my bearings
Okay, we're good
Oh
Okay, I'm gonna beat him
Like you're laughing too hard
It's a good of course, I know the horse has a dodge I've played I've pressed it probably
Five thousand times in the course of the last two weeks
That
Was really funny I would like to continue to play the game that would be swell
Everyone you growled at us
I
Need to see it I have to see it I
Need to see it
This is it hold on we need to watch this I need to examine this because I I don't know what the fuck
I don't know what the fuck happened
Oh
What what is that so weird
What's wrong with this why do I sound like a is that what I sound like
Why do I sound like a fucking cave troll, oh
Yeah heaven
Doesn't sound much better
He's like he's turning oh shit, he's turning he just growled at us
Fucking god, dude
So he said Tim the tool man
You
Honestly man, what somebody asked you what somebody says? Hey, dude, you know, there's a dodge in the game. It's like, bro
Yes
The fundamental part of the whole game
Oh
All right