You've seen me do it, like a hundred times!
You can't dodge them all!
He's turning!
Oh shit, he's turning!
He just growled at us!
He just turned and growled Okay, I need to get my bearings Okay, we're good Okay, I'm gonna beat a fist
I can't laugh at too hard.
Of course I know.
The horse has to dodge.
I've pressed it probably 5,000 times in the course of the last two weeks.
I'm gonna die.
That was really funny.
I would like to continue to play the game.
That would be swell.
Everyone, you growled at us?
I need to see it.
I have to see it.
Is this it?
Hold on.
We need to watch this.
I need to examine this because I- I don't know what the fuck- I don't know what the fuck happened.
Holy fucking god, I look like a weirdo.
Oh my god, dude.
Why does it sound so weird?
What's wrong with this?
Is that what I sound like?
Why do I sound like a fucking cave troll?
It doesn't sound much better.
He's like, he's turning.
Oh shit, he's turning.
He just growled at us.
Oh my fucking god, dude.
Somebody said, Tim the tool man.
Honestly, man, if somebody asks you, if somebody says, hey dude, do you know there's a dodge in the game?
It's like, bro.
Yes.
They're a fundamental part of the whole game.
Oh.
Alright.